<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="tunarr" date="20250928173722 +0000"><channel id="C2.50.tunarr.com"><display-name>2 Movies</display-name><display-name>2</display-name><display-name>Movies</display-name><icon src="{{host}}/images/tunarr.png" width="250"/></channel><channel id="C32.101.tunarr.com"><display-name>32 Spongebob</display-name><display-name>32</display-name><display-name>Spongebob</display-name><icon src="{{host}}/images/tunarr.png" width="250"/></channel><channel id="C1.49.tunarr.com"><display-name>1 Shows</display-name><display-name>1</display-name><display-name>Shows</display-name><icon src="{{host}}/images/tunarr.png" width="250"/></channel><programme start="20250928164437 +0000" stop="20250928184842 +0000" channel="C2.50.tunarr.com"><title>xXx</title><previously-shown/><desc>Xander Cage is your standard adrenaline junkie with no fear and a lousy attitude. When the US Government &quot;recruits&quot; him to go on a mission, he&#39;s not exactly thrilled. His mission: to gather information on an organization that may just be planning the destruction of the world, led by the nihilistic Yorgi.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>PG-13</value></rating><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/4eb0b49e-7561-4d08-b316-9d838ce65f36/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928184842 +0000" stop="20250928210837 +0000" channel="C2.50.tunarr.com"><title>Warrior</title><previously-shown/><desc>The youngest son of an alcoholic former boxer returns home, where he&#39;s trained by his father for competition in a mixed martial arts tournament – a path that puts the fighter on a collision course with his estranged, older brother.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>PG-13</value></rating><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/1e79052f-3e33-45d3-9c6d-8f552ee621e3/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928210837 +0000" stop="20250928231020 +0000" channel="C2.50.tunarr.com"><title>Lord of War</title><previously-shown/><desc>Yuri Orlov is a globetrotting arms dealer and, through some of the deadliest war zones, he struggles to stay one step ahead of a relentless Interpol agent, his business rivals and even some of his customers who include many of the world&#39;s most notorious dictators. Finally, he must also face his own conscience.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>R</value></rating><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/8832b559-bd14-470f-92b3-a96744944cb3/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928231020 +0000" stop="20250929010847 +0000" channel="C2.50.tunarr.com"><title>Insomnia</title><previously-shown/><desc>Two Los Angeles homicide detectives are dispatched to a northern town where the sun doesn&#39;t set to investigate the methodical murder of a local teen.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>R</value></rating><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/9a4fbea9-982b-4eab-a2cf-059a516eb9b0/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929010847 +0000" stop="20250929045114 +0000" channel="C2.50.tunarr.com"><title>Ben-Hur</title><previously-shown/><desc>In 25 AD, Judah Ben-Hur, a Jew in ancient Judea, opposes the occupying Roman empire.  Falsely accused by a Roman childhood friend-turned-overlord of trying to kill the Roman governor, he is put into slavery and his mother and sister are taken away as prisoners.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>G</value></rating><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/d4912b27-f826-49aa-8a09-844a77bf4662/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929045114 +0000" stop="20250929065416 +0000" channel="C2.50.tunarr.com"><title>Ad Astra</title><previously-shown/><desc>The near future, a time when both hope and hardships drive humanity to look to the stars and beyond. While a mysterious phenomenon menaces to destroy life on planet Earth, astronaut Roy McBride undertakes a mission across the immensity of space and its many perils to uncover the truth about a lost expedition that decades before boldly faced emptiness and silence in search of the unknown.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>PG-13</value></rating><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/b614adff-fc4e-4670-9604-5d4149289cfd/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928173551 +0000" stop="20250928175933 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Scaredy Pants / I Was a Teenage Gary</sub-title><desc>It&#39;s Halloween and SpongeBob tries to scare some kids as &quot;The Flying Dutchman,&quot; but the kids just laugh at his silly costume. SpongeBob gets Patrick to shave his head round, so he will look more like a ghost. He goes to the Krusty Krab to show off his costume, but everyone is more afraid of what is inside the costume. / Gary becomes sick when Squidward forgets to feed him, so a doctor has to come and give Gary some medicine. The doctor has Squidward give Gary the shot. Squidward accidentally gives the medicine to SpongeBob instead of Gary, which turns SpongeBob into a snail.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E26</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.25.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/d2fe6463-75de-4594-b685-990e3a7eb96e/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928175933 +0000" stop="20250928182349 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Jellyfish Hunter / The Fry Cook Games</sub-title><desc>Mr. Krab&#39;s turns SpongeBob&#39;s idea for &#39;Jelly Krabby Patties&#39; into a colossal customer favorite, and it leads to trouble when the local population of jellyfish become hunted to near-extinction. / SpongeBob and Patrick compete in the Fry Cook Games after they get in a fight. Who will come out victorious?</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E29</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.28.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/38cfec35-07c3-4082-af8e-59b1594490ac/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928182349 +0000" stop="20250928184821 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Welcome to the Chum Bucket / Frankendoodle</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob is forced to work at the Chum Bucket. / SpongeBob creates DoodleBob.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E3</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.2.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/bbdbf121-f310-46e5-beca-78c3688e5a28/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928184821 +0000" stop="20250928191250 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>I Had an Accident / Missing Identity</sub-title><desc>After SpongeBob shatters his buttocks in a sandboarding injury, he becomes paranoid of everything and confines himself to his own home with inanimate objects for friends. / While at a diner, SpongeBob tells the story of when he lost his name tag.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E33</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.32.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/6e527d23-0a85-4df4-9f54-f29d04efcf69/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928191250 +0000" stop="20250928193607 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>All That Glitters / Wishing You Well</sub-title><desc>When a customer orders the one thing that no one has ordered for years, the monster krabby patty, SpongeBob tries to lift it, but old Spat cracks in two. So he sells every single thing he owns (plus his clothes) for a new spatula, but the spatula refuses to flip a single patty, so SpongeBob tries to get his old spatula back. Will Spat forgive him? Will SpongeBob ever be dressed again? / Mr. Krabs makes SpongeBob go down the new wishing well after experiencing one for himself, and Patrick and Squidward accidentally join in. So, will they be able to get out and watch everybody&#39;s wishes come true? Or will Mr. Krabs just make them stay down there when he enjoys the money?</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E21</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.20.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/eb3eeb44-5556-4e80-86a7-e5a63d4a6692/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928193607 +0000" stop="20250928194754 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Mrs. Puff, You&#39;re Fired</sub-title><desc>Mrs. Puff gets fired from her boating school job due to her lack of passing Spongebob. Instead, a more-intense new instructor takes her place.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E16</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.15.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/a22e4ad1-5c33-45c8-a97b-069b394cbaa6/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928194754 +0000" stop="20250928201226 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Nasty Patty / Idiot Box</sub-title><desc>A health inspector shows up at the Krusty Krab, and while he is there, SpongeBob and Mr. Krabs see the news about a guy passing himself off as a health inspector to get free food.  Mr. Krabs is so mad he and SpongeBob make a Krabby Patty made with a bunch of nasty things. After it is served to the inspector he chokes on a fly and the two think he died from the patty. They later find out that he was a real health inspector, and that the other one was caught. Now, what will SpongeBob and Mr. Krabs do with the dead health inspector? / SpongeBob and Patrick buy a big screen TV, just so they can use the box using imagination, while Squidward refuses to believe that they are using their imagination inside the box on account of all the noise they are making.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E7</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.6.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/40f3e7aa-ef44-43c5-9b24-295361aeae42/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928201226 +0000" stop="20250928203622 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Fear of a Krabby Patty / Shell of a Man</sub-title><desc>Plankton unleashes a new plan; to get the Krusty Krab to work 24 hours. SpongeBob thinks this is a dream, until he thinks he is being chased by killer Krabby Patties. / Mr. Krabs is going to a naval reunion, but molts (leaves his shell) before he goes. He asks SpongeBob to go in his shell and imitate him for the reunion.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E1</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.0.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/444a57a4-c5a7-4979-a9a4-a273fa19352a/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928203622 +0000" stop="20250928210007 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Pizza Delivery / Home Sweet Pineapple</sub-title><desc>A customer calls and asks the Krusty Krab to deliver him some pizza. Mr. Krabs orders SpongeBob and Squidward to deliver it. SpongeBob will stop at nothing to get the pizza to the customer, even if that means getting lost. / One night, some nematodes feast on SpongeBob&#39;s pineapple house. All that is left is a tiny pebble. Now, SpongeBob must live with his parents! How will he get a new house?</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E10</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.9.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/0c2ec1cd-a1c5-458a-b9ad-39ec35733113/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928210007 +0000" stop="20250928211212 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Squidtastic Voyage</sub-title><desc>While Squidward is playing the clarinet, he accidentally swallows the reed. SpongeBob and Patrick take a microscopic submarine to try to retrieve it from inside Squidward.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E25</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.24.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/f5b4d61c-18b4-4a09-949e-e9252ca18201/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928211212 +0000" stop="20250928213555 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Culture Shock / F.U.N.</sub-title><desc>A talent show is taking place at the Krusty Krab to get more customers and more money, and Squidward is in charge. He will do anything to prevent SpongeBob from doing participating in it. / SpongeBob thinks that Plankton is evil only because he is lonely and has no friends. SpongeBob becomes Plankton&#39;s friend and plays with him. But, Mr. Krabs is convinced that Plankton is evil and that SpongeBob should not be hanging around with him.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E20</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.19.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/8def535d-0f8c-4b98-bde8-608085a78efc/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928213555 +0000" stop="20250928220026 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Party Pooper Pants / Chocolate with Nuts</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob buys a &quot;Throw The Best Party Ever&quot; kit and invites all 177 of his closest friends to a house party. But when he accidentally locks himself out of his house during the party, he must try to get back in. / SpongeBob and Patrick decide to become rich entrepreneurs by selling chocolate bars door to door.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E19</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.18.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/a0897a95-9cd6-47e0-8c1c-802f946dd95b/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928220026 +0000" stop="20250928222409 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Sandy&#39;s Rocket / Squeaky Boots</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob and Patrick accidentally launch Sandy&#39;s rocket, and land back in Bikini Bottom. They think they&#39;ve landed on the moon and that everyone in Bikini Bottom are aliens. / Mr. Krabs gives SpongeBob a pair of &quot;special&quot; boots because he bought them for Pearl, but she didn&#39;t want them. SpongeBob loves them, but the squeaking drives Mr. Krabs crazy.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E16</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.15.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/c9cc6c84-91b6-4199-a9f6-70e05e3ce674/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928222409 +0000" stop="20250928224837 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Clams / The Great Snail Race</sub-title><desc>In celebration of Mr. Krabs&#39; one millionth dollar, he takes Squidward and SpongeBob on a fishing trip. After a giant clam snatches his precious dollar, Mr. Krabs tries to get it back. / When Squidward gets a purebred snail named Snelle, SpongeBob challenges him in the great snail race.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E27</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.26.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/ca74044b-fc4b-4148-a720-772dbdebab88/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928224837 +0000" stop="20250928231218 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Nature Pants / Opposite Day</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob wants to give up his current life to live with the jellyfish against the wishes of all his friends. But, SpongeBob learns that a jellyfish life is not an easy one. / Squidward gets so mad at SpongeBob and Patrick, he decides to sell his house. Squidward needs to get rid of his annoying neighbors so he can sell his house. He tells SpongeBob and Patrick that it is &quot;Opposite Day.&quot; Squid hopes that they will act the opposite of what they usually are, annoying. Of course, it doesn&#39;t work out as planned.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E18</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.17.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/de044219-8ff3-4a0a-906c-e66902a63bc8/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928231218 +0000" stop="20250928233621 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Big Pink Loser / Bubble Buddy</sub-title><desc>Patrick realizes that he has never won any awards in his life, so he decides to copy everything that SpongeBob does. SpongeBob has won countless awards, so Patrick is sure that he will win one. / When no one will play with SpongeBob, he creates his own bubble buddy, but it causes many problems around town.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E5</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.4.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/18cf9388-3afa-41f4-b340-9782096a3689/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928233621 +0000" stop="20250929000030 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy V / Club SpongeBob</sub-title><desc>After being treated too much like a child by everyone, Barnacle Boy quits being a superhero and decides to be a supervillain. / SpongeBob and Patrick&#39;s club is too small for Squidward... literally. But Squidward forces his way in, &quot;propelling&quot; the clubhouse into the middle of nowhere.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E21</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.20.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/84a67dcc-171d-41e7-b78e-4919efff0737/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929000030 +0000" stop="20250929002456 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>My Pretty Seahorse / Graveyard Shift</sub-title><desc>It&#39;s spring in Bikini Bottom, and SpongeBob finds a wild seahorse and decides to keep her. / SpongeBob and Squidward work the night shift.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E23</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.22.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/f5f0d31b-3852-4cb4-a2ab-7018e652a285/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929002456 +0000" stop="20250929004927 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Mid-Life Crustacean / The Sponge Who Could Fly</sub-title><desc>When Mr. Krabs feels like an aging old man, he tries to feel young again, so he goes out with SpongeBob and Patrick for a night on the town. / SpongeBob tries his best to make an invention that allows him to fly. When all of them fail, people start to think that SpongeBob is crazy until he puts a hair dryer his pants. The hot air in his pants allows him to fly! But then, people start asking SpongeBob to do things for them, stopping him from flying with the jellyfish.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E29</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.28.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/cc23dbea-dfb0-47be-a3b7-7cda08830a8a/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929004927 +0000" stop="20250929011238 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Patrick SmartPants / SquidBob TentaclePants</sub-title><desc>After Patrick accidentally falls off a cliff while jellyfishing, he wakes up with superior intellect. / Sandy&#39;s experimental teleportation device malfunctions, melding SpongeBob and Squidward into one body.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E11</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.10.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/45e4df65-5e90-46c5-b8e0-6ce294d8cdf1/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929011238 +0000" stop="20250929013627 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Texas / Walking Small</sub-title><desc>Sandy gets homesick, so SpongeBob and Patrick do as much as they can to cheer her up. When they want to throw her a surprise party and she won&#39;t come, SpongeBob and Patrick make Sandy chase them to the Krusty Krab, where the party is being held. / Plankton&#39;s newest scheme involves getting someone to scare everyone away from &quot;Goo Lagoon&quot; so he can create his new restaurant, &quot;The Mega Bucket.&quot; He tricks SpongeBob into scaring everyone away from the beach, until SpongeBob realizes what he is doing is wrong.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E36</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.35.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/3c0ca5c2-6b53-47c4-ad9b-1028b1bdb581/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929013627 +0000" stop="20250929020040 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Skill Crane / Good Neighbors</sub-title><desc>Mr. Krabs gets a new toy vender by the name of &quot;Skill Crane.&quot; At first, Squidward doesn&#39;t like it, but when Mr. Krabs lets him and SpongeBob give it a try, Squidward becomes obsessed with it. Can he win anything from the Skill Crane before it ruins his life? / It&#39;s Sunday and Squidward just wants to relax. But when SpongeBob and Patrick elect him as Good Neighbor President, they won&#39;t leave him alone.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E5</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.4.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/0232b25a-96ad-4d10-8c02-d696d3fcc2df/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929020040 +0000" stop="20250929022519 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Patty Hype / Survival of the Idiots</sub-title><desc>The Krusty Krab hasn&#39;t had costumers in weeks, so SpongeBob comes up with an idea, but Mr. Krabs and Squidward laugh at the idea. So SpongeBob opens his own restaurant and becomes a huge success in Bikini Bottom. / Despite Sandy&#39;s warning, SpongeBob and Patrick sneak into her treedome, during a terrible snowstorm and since the doorknob is frozen, SpongeBob and Patrick realize they have to wait until spring. Will SpongeBob and Patrick be able to survive the entire winter? Or will Sandy, and the cold weather, stop them first?</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E13</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.12.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/f3fcc296-b27e-4b03-ab1b-0d59ecf300e8/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929022519 +0000" stop="20250929024932 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Squid on Strike / Sandy, SpongeBob, and the Worm</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob and Squidward go on strike after they don&#39;t get their paycheck from Mr. Krabs. How long will the strike last? / An Alaskan Bull Worm is on the loose in Bikini Bottom, and Sandy must stop it from destroying the town.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E33</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.32.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/be6dccef-a403-4c56-8c8c-e209adc905d4/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929024932 +0000" stop="20250929031243 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>The Lost Mattress / Krabs vs. Plankton</sub-title><desc>Mr. Krabs complains that his back hurts, so SpongeBob and Patrick buy a new mattress and Squidward tries to take credit for it. They give the new mattress to Mr. Krabs, but Mr. Krabs put his money in his old mattress, which SpongeBob, Patrick, and Squidward must find while Mr. Krabs is at the hospital. / Plankton tries to steal the formula, but slips and sues Mr. Krabs. Mr. Krabs hires a lawyer, but his lawyer slips and is hurt, so SpongeBob must try to help Mr. Krabs win the case by trying to open a briefcase that has something very important in it.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E3</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.2.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/3d4f92aa-5d70-41e9-b870-a1df04d4ef5e/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929031243 +0000" stop="20250929033713 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Krusty Love / New Student Starfish</sub-title><desc>Mr. Krabs falls in love with Mrs. Puff. / Patrick gets bored everyday when SpongeBob goes to boating school, so SpongeBob insists that Patrick could join him. But what happens when Patrick makes SpongeBob lose a Noodle Student Star?</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E25</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.24.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/d4b1ccf0-2632-444d-bba3-e18909e6f7da/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929033713 +0000" stop="20250929034841 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Best Day Ever</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob is going to have the best day ever. But when work, karate, jellyfishing and Squidward&#39;s clarinet recital don&#39;t go as planned will his day be ruined?</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E27</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.26.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/40ce708c-922c-4268-8dde-2c4f0ce0156b/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929034841 +0000" stop="20250929041242 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Valentine&#39;s Day / The Paper</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob wants to give Patrick the best Valentine&#39;s Day gift ever, a chocolate heart shaped hot air balloon. Sandy starts to drive it over to SpongeBob and Patrick at the Valentine Day fair but, scallops attack the balloon, and SpongeBob must stall for time. Patrick goes crazy waiting for his gift, and starts to attack people at the fair. / SpongeBob gets a small piece of paper from Squidward to play with. Squidward thinks that the paper is useless and just gives it away. SpongeBob soon does many fun things with it, and makes Squidward very jealous.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E32</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.31.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/9a6dd9dc-c746-4fda-89a5-77d80df1c995/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929041242 +0000" stop="20250929043624 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>MuscleBob BuffPants / Squidward the Unfriendly Ghost</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob thinks he can get more attention if he becomes physically fit. But he soon finds that exercise is hard work, and orders &quot;anchor arms,&quot; which he inflates with air, and looks buff. Everyone finds out how fake he is when Sandy signs him up for the annual anchor toss competition at Muscle Beach. / SpongeBob thinks he accidentally killed Squidward, so Squidward decides to use it for his advantage. Threatening to haunt them for the rest of their lives, Squidward makes SpongeBob and Patrick his servants.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E22</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.21.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/b96a23c2-f768-4381-8c8d-cad3844bede1/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929043624 +0000" stop="20250929050013 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Squidville / No Free Rides</sub-title><desc>Squidward is fed up with living next to Spongebob and Patrick, so he finds new neighbors who are more like himself. / To avoid another year with SpongeBob in her class, Mrs. Puff passes him with bogus extra credit and lets him have his license, but soon realizes that the consequences are beyond bad. When SpongeBob receives a new boat-mobile from his parents, Mrs. Puff attempts to steal it, and SpongeBob will stop at nothing to stop her.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E17</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.16.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/95aac363-89a7-41f4-bdd7-7a83aed1975d/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929050013 +0000" stop="20250929052330 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Wigstruck / That&#39;s No Lady</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob finds an old-time wig and starts wearing it everywhere he goes. / A misunderstanding over a vacation getaway advertisement causes Patrick to think he must &quot;get out of town&quot; or face dire consequences. SpongeBob can&#39;t bear the thought of his best buddy moving away, so he decides to do what he can to hide Patrick&#39;s identity from his &quot;pursuers.&quot; After many failed attempts at disguises, they finally settle on the perfect one: Patrick is transformed into a girl, Patricia, to be exact. Patricia catches the eye of Mr. Krabs and soon she becomes the most charming waitress/waiter at the Krusty Krab.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E28</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.27.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/e25b49ea-8720-487d-91df-2c51cefc4623/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929052330 +0000" stop="20250929054744 +0000" channel="C32.101.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>SB-129 / Karate Choppers</sub-title><desc>Squidward becomes frozen while hiding from SpongeBob and Patrick. He stays frozen for so long, he wakes up in the future. Once he&#39;s in the future, he thinks he will be able to get away from SpongeBob and Patrick, but it seems where ever he goes, they are always there somehow. / SpongeBob and Sandy just can&#39;t stop practicing karate, even after Mr. Krabs warns SpongeBob that he will be fired. Soon Mr. Krabs finds them in the park using karate to make sandwiches, so he hires them both to make Krabby Patties at a super fast rate using Karate.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E28</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.27.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/11d7c178-ed6d-4f1c-9fc5-49e17500c2e1/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928165424 +0000" stop="20250928173924 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Tulsa King</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>The Fifty</sub-title><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.1.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/805a03b8-c869-41b8-b20c-7b97ca12bc57/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928173924 +0000" stop="20250928184437 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>The Boys</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Dirty Business</sub-title><desc>Vernon Correctional Services provides compassionate rehabilitation to those in our care to prepare them for successful community reentry. At Vernon, it&#39;s not about custody. It&#39;s about family.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E6</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.5.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/bd43e201-66f6-4406-9769-65f52aa2a0cc/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928184437 +0000" stop="20250928191035 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>BoJack Horseman</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Brrap Brrap Pew Pew</sub-title><desc>Diane&#39;s tweet lands Sextina Aquafina in hot water. Prankster and A-list actor Jurj Clooners gets under BoJack&#39;s skin.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.5.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/b6c9f274-07f0-4f84-9cb5-38d972b19db8/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928191035 +0000" stop="20250928193206 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Abbott Elementary</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Breakup</sub-title><desc>When Barbara&#39;s church choir uses the gym for rehearsals, Ava notices tension in the group. Jacob&#39;s eagerness for a full social calendar worries Gregory. Melissa and Janine investigate a new substitute.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-PG</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.4.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/fb5d445a-1263-4233-894b-64d9baeb40a5/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928193206 +0000" stop="20250928195430 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>South Park</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Fantastic Easter Special</sub-title><desc>Stan wants to know the real reason kids have to decorate eggs for Easter, and what, if anything eggs and bunnies have to do with Jesus dying for his sins. To get to the bottom of it, Kyle and Stan get wrapped up in a bizarre society that guards a legendary secret.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-14</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S11E5</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">10.4.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/f3e61c22-d16e-46e9-ac58-0f59ff77f9d9/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928195430 +0000" stop="20250928204630 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Demon Slayer: Kimetsu no Yaiba</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>A Connected Bond: Daybreak and First Light</sub-title><desc>Tanjiro continues the fight against Hantengu. Amidst all his injuries and the Superior Four&#39;s skill, will he be able to defeat him? As the battle draws to a close, the Demon Slayer Squad must race against time to end the fight before dawn.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E11</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.10.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/e9ae9fcf-4af3-4672-a59b-61ec1a0b512e/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928204630 +0000" stop="20250928215051 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>For All Mankind</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>The Sands of Ares</sub-title><desc>After a sudden crisis, the Martian crews pull together.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E8</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.7.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/a9bca652-6012-4edd-a8ea-d0f020aee47a/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928215051 +0000" stop="20250928220250 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Phineas and Ferb</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Undercover Carl</sub-title><desc>When the boys build an Anti-Gravity Fun Launcher, Carl accidentally intercepts their plans and assumes they are working for Dr. Doofenshmirtz, so he is sent undercover to figure out what they are doing. Meanwhile, Perry tries to find a lost agent, and Dr. Doofenshmirtz also acquires the blueprints to help with a parking issue on his street.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E42</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.41.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/dd058fc8-c0c2-4235-ad26-69ee6b557ac9/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928220250 +0000" stop="20250928225124 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>INVINCIBLE</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>WE NEED TO TALK</sub-title><desc>Feeling lost and confused, Mark looks for advice from Eve. At the same time, everyone&#39;s looking for him.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E7</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.6.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/bc324b77-8604-4b37-9df1-05a824744a76/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928225124 +0000" stop="20250928234749 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>For All Mankind</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Goldilocks</sub-title><desc>A discovery sends teams across Earth and Mars scrambling for answers.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S4E5</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">3.4.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/488609dd-5aa7-4e07-81cd-0d4818e062ff/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250928234749 +0000" stop="20250929001125 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Toradora!</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Fireworks</sub-title><desc>The gang plots an elaborate stunt to scare Minori with a trip to a nearby cave where Yūsaku has planted scary traps, but Yūsaku and Minori disappear.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-14</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E10</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.9.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/3e007db0-1a4f-4d3d-84ab-a4f0a32f3fce/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929001125 +0000" stop="20250929003350 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>South Park</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Butterballs</sub-title><desc>Stan wants to raise awareness about the dangers of bullying by shooting a big dance video, while Butters falls victim to an unlikely bully.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S16E5</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">15.4.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/79efec20-84b0-4307-a7bd-ce3ce0fe9288/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929003350 +0000" stop="20250929005609 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>South Park</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>The Big Fix</sub-title><desc>Stan’s horrified to realize he’s misinterpreted some of the greatest writing of all time.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S25E2</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">24.1.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/3592a26a-bd54-4f37-a5b1-392fa9880c50/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929005609 +0000" stop="20250929011719 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Community</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Competitive Wine Tasting</sub-title><desc>Jeff is suspicious of Pierce&#39;s engagement to a pretty classmate. Troy invents a childhood trauma to impress Britta, and Abed challenges a professor.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-PG</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E20</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.19.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/e36460c1-b2bc-44de-bdda-650761c2470a/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929011719 +0000" stop="20250929014150 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Sailor Mouth / Artist Unknown</sub-title><desc>SpongeBob and Patrick pick up a &quot;bad word,&quot; and start repeating it to the shocked patrons of the Krusty Krab, but Mr. Krabs doesn&#39;t like this! / Squidward starts to teach an art class at the Recreation Center, but SpongeBob is the only person who shows up.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-Y7</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E27</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.26.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/813d1f6b-4952-42ee-a7e2-00db430946b9/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929014150 +0000" stop="20250929025204 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Black Mirror</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Smithereens</sub-title><desc>A London rideshare driver ignites an international crisis when he kidnaps a worker from a social media company.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S5E2</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">4.1.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/5070a363-b941-467c-9e88-e6ab2dc6c3dc/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929025204 +0000" stop="20250929030251 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Phineas and Ferb</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Backyard Aquarium</sub-title><desc>Phineas and Ferb have a new pet, Goldy the goldfish, and to help make Goldy feel less lonely, Phineas and Ferb have built an aquarium with many other creatures. Meanwhile, Perry must stop Doofenshmirtz from a food related childhood revenge story.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-G</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S2E5</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">1.4.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/f92d23b6-2e40-4472-898e-19ea431c0ed3/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929030251 +0000" stop="20250929035913 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>The Boys</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>The Female of the Species</sub-title><desc>On a very special episode of The Boys… an hour of guts, gutterballs, airplane hijackings, madness, ghosts, and one very intriguing Female. Oh, and lots of heart — both in the sentimental sense, and in the gory literal sense.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E4</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.3.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/feb09326-1406-4058-b0c2-036ec803434e/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929035913 +0000" stop="20250929042136 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>Rick and Morty</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Mortyplicity</sub-title><desc>The Smiths suspect they&#39;re being hunted. But who&#39;s even real?</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-14</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S5E2</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">4.1.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/698e8164-576a-4949-9360-e858aca9efdf/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929042136 +0000" stop="20250929044650 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>BoJack Horseman</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Zoës and Zeldas</sub-title><desc>BoJack decides to mentor Todd; Diane&#39;s ex-boyfriend writes an article about Mr. Peanutbutter.</desc><rating system="MPAA"><value>TV-MA</value></rating><episode-num system="onscreen">S1E4</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">0.3.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/408bc241-c81f-4270-bee0-5090425d71e9/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme><programme start="20250929044650 +0000" stop="20250929054513 +0000" channel="C1.49.tunarr.com"><title>The Summer I Turned Pretty</title><previously-shown/><sub-title>Last Name</sub-title><desc>Now that Adam&#39;s onboard, the wedding is growing bigger by the day and Belly&#39;s overwhelmed. But after a surprise at her bridal shower, things finally start looking up.</desc><episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6</episode-num><episode-num system="xmltv_ns">2.5.0/1</episode-num><icon src="{{host}}/api/programs/a126fb98-7247-458e-a90d-cc8168ae9e1e/thumb?proxy=true"/></programme></tv>