[Opening theme music playing]
[electronic warbling]
- [birds chirping]
- [wind whooshing]
[ominous music playing]
[crows cawing]
[waterfall rushing]
[indistinct chattering]
[metal clanging]
[horses neighing]
[insects chittering]
[sounds stop]
[inaudible]
[metal clanging]
[horse snorting]
[sounds stop]
- [ominous music]
- [man eerily vocalizing]
[soldiers chatting indistinctly]
- [insects chittering]
- [birds chirping]
[sounds stop]
[sounds resume]
[tense music playing]
[sounds stop]
- [birds chirping]
- [soldiers chattering indistinctly]
[water sloshing]
[ominous music playing]
- [insects chittering]
- [horse neighing]
[men chanting indistinctly]
[jewelry clanging]
[woman shrieking]
[all gasping]
[all clamoring]
[intense music playing]
[all cackling, clamoring]
[shrieking]
[muffled sounds]
[woman shrieking]
[soldiers yelling]
[man shouting, grunting]
[soldiers screaming]
[muffled sounds]
[sounds resume]
[soldiers yelling]
[horses neighing]
[muffled screaming]
[gurgling]
[woman shrieking]
[muffled screaming]
[woman shrieking
[shrieking subsides]
[insects chittering]
[shrieking]
[sound stops]
[woman gasping]
[horses neighing]
[ominous music playing]
[man breathing heavily]
[horses neighing]
[sounds stop]
[horses neighing, snorting]
- [metal clanging]
- [man grunting]
[sounds stop]
[man screaming]
[man screaming, grunting]
[tense music playing]
[birds chirping]
[man coughing]
[groaning]
[retching]
[horse neighing]
[horse groaning]
[horse moaning]
[sounds stop]
[metal clanging]
[river running]
[man grunting]
[muffled sounds]
- [river running]
- [metal clanging]
[crows cawing]
[ominous music playing]
- [crickets chirping]
- [insects chittering]
[woman's breath shuddering]
[unnerving music playing]
[birds chirping]
[sounds stop]
- [birds chirping]
- [river running]
[muffled sounds]
- [metal clanging]
- [jewelry jingling]
[both breathing heavily]
[man wincing]
[dramatic music playing]
[sounds stop]
[waterfall rushing]
[man screaming]
[man groaning]
[squelching]
[ominous music playing]
[inaudible]
[sounds muffled]
[jewelry clanging]
[inaudible]
[man roaring]
[sounds stop]
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music swelling]
[flies buzzing]
[waterfall rushing]
[dramatic music playing]
[voices vocalizing]
[jewelry clanging]
[man yelling]
[muffled splashing]
[birds chirping, warbling]
[horse neighing]
[voices stop vocalizing]
[insects chittering]
[women vocalizing]
[deep rumbling]
[muffled sounds]
[man grunting loudly]
[vocalizing stops]
[sounds stop]
[water gushing]
[muffled sounds]
[gurgling]
[eerie breathing]
[birds chirping loudly]
- [man shouting]
- [flies buzzing]
- [birds chirping, warbling]
- [man shouting]
[man screaming]
[scream echoing]
[inaudible]
[man panting]
[birds chirping, warbling]
[man snorting]
[groaning]
[shouting]
[laughing]
[dramatic music playing]
[horses neighing, snorting]
[insects chittering]
[horses nickering, snorting]
[woman wailing]
[screaming]
[crying]
- [shrieking]
- [man screaming]
[whimpering]
[man screaming]
[shrieking]
[grunting, groaning]
[woman shrieking]
[man screaming, laughing]
[shrieking]
[man screaming]
[dramatic music crescendos]
[inaudible]
[man screaming]
[woman shrieking]
[dramatic music stops]
[ominous music playing]
[music fades]
[electronic warbling]
[closing theme music playing]