- Susan! Sorry.
- Oh.
So sorry, have you got the turkey now?
Taxi!
Oh.
You all right?
Never mind.
♪ I'll see you again ♪
♪ Whenever spring breaks through again ♪
♪ Time may lie heavy between ♪
♪ But what has been ♪
♪ Is past forgetting ♪
♪ This sweet memory ♪
♪ Across the years will come to me ♪
♪ Though my world may go awry ♪
♪ In my heart will ever lie ♪
♪ Just the echo of a sigh ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ I will see you again ♪
♪ Whenever spring breaks through again ♪
♪ Though my world has gone awry ♪
♪ Though the years my tears may dry ♪
♪ I shall love you till I die ♪
♪ Goodbye. ♪
What a melody.
My God, what a melody.
It's the door at the end
of the corridor, sir.
- Ah.
- Betty?
- What?
- Can I borrow some lippy?
Again? You're terrible.
- Bring it back.
- You never gave me mine back last time.
Excuse me, can I...
Nice show tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
- Mmm.
- Don't forget, it's the matinee tomorrow.
The half will be at five to 2:00.
Ah.
Hello, Barrow.
You got our note?
I-I hope we're not being a nuisance.
Not at all, my lord.
Mr. Dexter.
Hello.
How about a glass of champagne?
You mustn't let us hold you up.
It's so thrilling to be backstage.
Bitter Sweet seems to be a big hit.
We're living in the age of Noël Coward.
Exactly.
Although I don't suppose Noël
would put it quite like that.
How would I put it?
- Oh.
- We were just saying
how your star shines more
brightly with every new show.
- Ah.
- Do you know Lord and Lady Grantham,
Lord and Lady Hexham?
- The show was marvelous.
- Yes.
Although we're not
qualified to judge, of course.
Everyone is qualified to say
something nice, Lady Grantham.
Mr. Dexter's dresser used to work for us,
so we thought we'd look in.
Guy made that picture
at your house, didn't he?
I so enjoyed it.
I hope you'll return one day
to the scene of your triumph.
Oh, we'd like that very much, milady.
And we better run.
We're dining at the new Ivy on West Street.
My favorite haunt
if it weren't for the prices.
The last time I dined there,
I asked for the bill and a pistol.
How much was it?
Ten pounds for three of us.
Ten pounds for three people?
Well, I suppose we don't have to go there.
Oh, yes, we do.
We must get a wiggle on if we don't want
- to lose our table.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
- We loved it.
- Thank you.
- Ah. Thank you.
- Milord.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
The stage door will be closing in 30 minutes.
They're very hearty
with each other, aren't they?
Dexter and Barrow?
They must travel a lot together.
That's right, of course.
How long did you work for them?
- Quite a few years.
- And were you happy?
Not as happy as I am now.
What a lovely night.
The London season's always good fun.
Then back we go to Downton.
Oh, they're still up?
MRS. HUGHES:
Oh. There you are.
How was it?
It was a lovely night.
So, we walked back along Piccadilly,
then down through the Green Park.
Oh, we saw what they've built
to replace Devonshire House.
You mustn't do too much,
not in your condition.
I feel fine. Honestly.
It was good to be out in the air.
It looks as if the new Grosvenor House Hotel
is open at last.
I'm impressed.
It's sad to think of London being stripped
of its private palaces.
MRS. HUGHES:
It had to happen, Charlie.
What with these new taxes,
no one can afford them anymore.
MRS. PATMORE: Well, who could
that be at this time of night?
No, no, no. I'll get it.
Oh, tell us more about
Mr. Dexter's show.
There was one song which keeps
- going round in my head.
- Sir, do you have
- something to say about Lady Mary?
- Certainly not.
♪ I'll see you again... ♪
Thank you, Miss Baxter.
Hey, don't let her put you off.
Oh, who was that?
Some fool asking impertinent
questions about the family.
I shut the door on him.
It is odd to think tomorrow is your last day.
What will we do when you're
no longer here to protect us?
Andrew will-- I should say
Mr. Parker will look after you instead.
How do you feel about
your imminent promotion, Andy?
I feel ready.
I've served my years before the mast.
I only hope you're right.
Charlie...
Was that about Lady Mary?
Oh, there's bound to be some interest.
After our little exchange,
he won't trouble us again.
Hmm.
Lord knows what I'd have worn
tonight if it wasn't ready.
You will be a sensation.
Did I hear that one
of the Petersfields' daughters
- is engaged?
- Gwendolen.
They've just announced it.
Someone nice?
Lord Belsay.
Very suitable.
♪ London Pride has been handed down to us ♪
♪ London Pride is a flower that's free ♪
♪ Whoa, Liza, see the coster barrows ♪
♪ The vegetable marrows
and the fruit piled high ♪
♪ Oh, Liza, little London sparrows ♪
- Oh, Catherine.
- ♪ Covent Garden Market ♪
♪ Where the costers cry ♪
♪ Cockney feet mark the beat of history ♪
♪ Every street pins a memory down ♪ - ♪
♪ Nothing ever can quite replace ♪
♪ The grace of London Town. ♪
You are good to stay in London
for Uncle Harold.
Do you think he's finally made
sense of Grandmama's estate?
It seems unfair that both Papa and Mama
should lose their mothers
in such quick succession.
- At least Papa was there for Granny.
- Hmm.
It's been much harder for Mama.
To be the grieving and dutiful daughter
from across the ocean.
All the more reason to hope
Harold has settled things.
We've already spent half the money.
That dress won't have helped.
- Hello, Mary. Edith.
- Mrs. Vanneck.
- How are you?
- Very well.
I saw your parents at
the new Lady Rosebery's party.
As full of energy as ever.
Yes, they're holding up.
How are Henry and Bertie?
We're all pretty good, I think.
So, Henry's home from his travels?
Uh, yes.
- Yes, he is.
- I'm afraid we have to run,
but we'll give them all your love.
Oh.
Thanks for that.
Happy to help.
Jump on.
I don't mind admitting it.
After tonight, I'll be ready
to go back to Downton.
The London season's endless.
I'm worn out.
You enjoy the season.
You know it.
I used to, but now the girls are out,
I'm not sure
I see the point anymore.
This has just been delivered.
So nice of you all to stay on
for my cousin's bash tonight.
An invitation to Petersfield House feels like
quite a hot ticket.
I'm glad they've held on to their HQ.
- Not for much longer.
- Oh, no.
The Petersfield ball has been
an institution all my life.
You can't blame them for not wanting to run
a fully staffed house the size of Selfridge's
in order to give one party a year.
I suppose not.
It's been a while
since we've seen Mr. Levinson.
He's been busy settling
my late grandmother's affairs.
He and Mama are both executors,
but with the estate being in America,
it's really fallen to him.
I'm sure he and Her Ladyship
can manage things between them.
You must tell me when it's too much for you.
I can always share Baxter with Mama
until the baby's born.
There's time yet, and anyway,
I've done it before.
Right.
I think that's everything, milady.
Last day with Carson in charge.
And Mrs. Patmore leaves in a few weeks.
But I think Parker will do well enough,
even if it will feel strange without Carson.
Things change, milord,
and somehow, we must change with them.
Very true.
Did you see they're pulling
down Dorchester House?
We used to go there a lot
when the Reids had it.
But plenty of families
are throwing in the towel.
I hope Grantham House is in no danger.
How long has it been in the family?
Oh. We bought it in about 1760,
and my grandfather rebuilt it in 1854.
- Quite a time.
- You're right.
Quite a time.
And that means something to me.
Would you tie this?
Darling, how nice you look.
But I wish you were coming home
with us tomorrow.
Someone needs to be here
to welcome Uncle Harold
when his ship gets in.
I'll give him dinner and bring
him north for the weekend.
The weekend?
I'm glad Mama isn't alive
to hear you say that word.
The car's outside, milord.
Divorce in high places!
Get your paper!
Come on, read all about it!
There you go, love.
Thank you so much.
This way. This way, please.
My lady, my lord, this way.
You got a quote for the Herald, have you?
Lady Mary, you look exquisite.
Why do they all want a picture of Mary?
Because she's so pretty, of course.
Ah, it's Mr. Carson's last night in service.
I couldn't let that pass unnoticed.
Oh, you won't be far behind him,
which I'm sure your husband
is very glad about.
Mr. Mason has been very patient.
You've seen the Crawleys
through some testing times,
- Mr. Carson.
- Oh, they've been good to me, too.
Not everyone would have taken
in a former song and dance man,
not back then.
You don't often talk about that.
And he's not going to now.
At the end of a career,
you look back more than you did
and think about all the changes
you've witnessed.
Shall we raise a glass to Mr. Carson?
- Yes.
- I'm not going far.
But we will miss seeing you each day.
I would like to thank you,
Mr. Carson.
You've taught me so much,
and I hope one day
I'll be a worthy successor.
Mm.
Mr. Carson.
Uh, uh, Lady Mary.
Could I have a quick word?
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
Mama?
What's going on?
Are you all right?
Uh, I'm so sorry, but a...
A rather tricky situation has arisen.
Why? What's happened?
Uh, my maid just told me...
Your maid just told you what?
That Lady Mary is divorced.
She said it was in the evening paper.
This is nonsense.
It's not nonsense.
I got the decree nisi today.
Well, that explains the photographers.
You mean it's true?
I'm sorry to say that it is.
Well, then
I'm afraid you can't stay.
Prince and Princess Arthur
of Connaught are on their way,
and the princess simply
cannot be in the same room
as a divorced woman.
I do apologize, but Lady Mary must go now.
- Sarah, is this really...
- No, I really must insist.
You're chucking my daughter
out of your house?
Oh, most reluctantly, I assure
you, but their Royal Highnesses
would be badly compromised
if anyone found out.
I've never heard anything
so ridiculous in all my life.
Papa, it's all right. I'll go.
I'm very sorry,
Lady Petersfield.
I shouldn't have come.
Wait.
It's going to be hard for her.
Very hard, I'm afraid.
The young crowd may be all right,
but you have to remember,
my mother wouldn't have
a divorced woman in the house.
It's just shocking.
I do thank you
for your kind understanding.
I've asked the footman to bring your coat.
Ah, there he is.
Ah, thank you.
I am sorry.
Well, so you keep saying.
Your Royal Highnesses.
Oh. Quickly.
Hide, hide!
Your Royal Highnesses.
What a splendid evening
you've laid on for us,
Lady Petersfield.
Your presence is what lends
its splendor, ma'am.
Let me take you up to the ballroom.
What an enchanting
little house this is.
What an absurd woman.
There's no need to sound so indignant.
You knew Henry and I were getting a divorce.
But not that it had come through.
Well, it has.
And you never thought to tell us?
Why on earth not?
Because I'm a fool.
And I suppose I thought
I could have one last night
before the sky fell in.
Of course, it's all ludicrous.
Ludicrous or not, it's time for me to leave,
and with little fuss as possible.
Then we're coming with you.
Uh, don't try and talk me out of it.
Papa, you know perfectly well you can't leave
before the prince and princess.
Go back up and come home when they've left.
I mean it.
What will you do?
I'll take a taxi.
If I can find one that
will carry a divorced woman.
Lady Mary, one photo, please.
Lady Mary, one photo!
Lady Mary, a photograph, please!
Is it true what they're saying?
What's the reason for the split?
It was stupid.
I don't blame anyone but me.
I bet His Lordship was furious.
Yes, but it wasn't fair.
Lady Petersfield did what she had to.
I'm divorced and not wanted
in respectable company.
Don't say such a thing.
Why not, if it's true?
What do the servants know?
They knew it was coming, and...
Tonight they know it's happened.
It was in The Evening News.
So I gather.
Was it bad?
No.
No, not too bad.
Just how Mr. Talbot's gone and...
...You run Downton with His Lordship.
Which is all true, I suppose.
But now the other papers will pick it up.
I'm sorry if the newspapers
made you unhappy, milady.
The divorce has made me unhappy. -
Mama, if you've left the party...
The royals left before us.
They went early, thank God.
But I've decided I won't visit
anywhere you're not welcome.
- Will that be all, milady?
- No. You can hear this.
And sit down.
Mama, I forbid it.
Papa would be in a hopeless situation.
You'd make the whole thing
much worse than it is.
- But what can I do then?
- If you want to please me,
you'll behave completely normally.
- How?
- I don't know.
Some friends will be happy
to break the rules.
But the rest, you'll go without me.
I couldn't.
We'll just have to get used to it.
Good night, my darling.
Try and sleep.
Well, now we know what I'm up against.
I admire you, Lady Mary.
You're very brave.
- MRS. PATMORE: Good morning.
- Is it?
I haven't slept a wink.
We knew it was coming, Charlie.
We've known as much for months.
It'll change our lives, though,
now it's out in the open.
How's Lady Mary taking it?
She's not happy. I can say that.
Well, I'm just glad the
old lady didn't live to see it.
Oh, he forced her into it.
Mr. Talbot,
with his airs and graces and
his fast cars, I don't think.
He pushed her and tricked her
and brought scandal
on this once great family.
We don't know everything.
I know enough to recognize a bully
and a feckless playboy when I see one.
I don't know, Mama.
The more he drove,
the more he toured the world,
the less he cared about me.
What else can I say?
It still annoys me that Henry's girlfriend
wasn't named in court
and he hired that tart instead.
You know the rules.
The husband names a paid trollop,
not his real mistress.
It's all very proper in its prim dishonesty.
I still blame Mrs. Baron.
She wasn't the problem.
Henry had made up his mind,
and that's all there is to it.
That is what's happened,
and now we must just get on with it.
Thus spake the Englishman.
I am English, and I thank God for it.
We know.
Thank heaven we'll soon be home.
Home sweet home.
Have you missed me?
Of course.
Hello.
Don't tell Nanny.
- Thank you.
Where's Mrs. Patmore?
Have you left her behind?
She stayed in London with Lady Mary.
They'll be back on Friday, but
you'll have to cook until then.
I don't mind.
It's not long till I take over.
So this is the start of our time.
Hello, Andy.
Can we go and see
Mr. Mason's pigs?
Good idea, Master George.
After you.
Is Mama back, too?
Lady Mary will be here on Friday.
"Man overboard!
It startled everybody."
I'm so sorry.
It must have been terribly upsetting for her.
How much does George know?
- Oh.
- I'm not sure,
but I think we should leave it to Mary
to tell him.
I keep thinking about Mary.
Will she be treated that way up here?
Not if I can help it.
She won't find it easy being an outcast.
She was always the belle of the ball.
What's happened, uh, since we've been away?
Mainly Isobel organizing the County Show.
You don't mind they made her president?
Are you joking? She's my savior.
Mama enjoyed it.
She always complained, of course.
The hardest task
is hauling Sir Hector Moreland
over to her side.
Good luck with that.
Mama couldn't stand him.
Daisy!
- Daisy.
- Hello, Mr. Molesley.
What have you got there?
Latest copy of Picturegoer.
Has an article on my new film.
I bought some copies for the house.
How exciting.
But it's-it's quite a responsibility, too.
What is?
Being famous in the film world.
Always remember--
An actor is nothing without a good script.
If audiences like them,
it's only because
of what we tell them to say.
You don't think of that when
you're sitting in the stalls.
Yeah.
Well, cheerio.
In many ways, the writers
are the real stars of cinema.
What do you mean, a tribute?
Will the late Lady Grantham
approve of our disrupting
the established traditions
of the County Show?
Perhaps we can establish
a new tradition in her honor.
Hmm.
I'll need to be convinced.
Here are the entrants
in the farming categories.
They're confirmed.
Thank you.
That will be very helpful.
And this is my list of prize-givers.
Including the present Lady Grantham?
She can say something nice
about her mother-in-law
that will give you what you want.
Even if I didn't find
old Lady Grantham very easy.
She could be so sentimental.
Violet sentimental?
She wanted children's prizes for everything.
And since she was president
and I was only chairman,
there wasn't much I could do.
Thankfully, I put a stop to
all that the year before last.
Well, I hope it won't annoy you,
but I do have some ideas of my own.
Really?
If you'll take my advice, I...
I shall be so grateful
for your advice, Sir Hector.
When I ask for it.
Uncle Harold.
Oh.
Do my eyes deceive me,
or is this vision the great Lady Mary Talbot?
I'm so pleased to see you.
- Yeah.
- We are eager for your news.
- Well...
- Please introduce us,
- Harold.
- Oh.
May I present Gus Sambrook.
Oh. Have you come to see
my uncle, Mr. Sambrook?
I-I've come with your uncle.
- Didn't you warn them, Harold?
- Well, I meant to.
I must have forgotten.
But is the house not big enough?
Oh.
You mean you want to stay here?
Is that a terrible nuisance?
- No.
- Thank you.
I went to make some old-fashioneds.
There's one for you.
You should've rung the bell.
I did, but no one knew how to make them.
Mr. Sambrook will be staying with us.
Mr. Levinson said, milady.
I've put him in the Bird Room.
Very good.
Gus wasn't sure he could come
until just before the boat sailed.
And why did you come?
Oh, he knows all about business.
He can help me explain things to Cora.
Well, it's a long way to travel for that.
I've also got a horse running
in the Gold Cup at Ascot.
Ooh. This is very strong.
You know, I should run.
I'm having dinner at the Savoy, and I'm late.
Uh, I suppose the night
watchman will let me in?
The night watchman is a thing of the past.
But I've got a key for you.
I'll see you out.
Here you are.
So let me guess--
Robert is furious
and Cora's sympathetic.
Papa's miserable as much as angry.
Now, Cora's a Yank.
She knows society can learn
to live with divorce.
It'll be true here before too long.
But it's not true yet.
Still, Downton keeps me busy.
- What are you up to there?
- Mainly renovating the cottages
and doing up the old smoking room.
I thought a music room
would be a wonderful memorial
- for both my grandmothers.
- Mm.
That's a nice idea.
Even if my mother was more
Gershwin than Rachmaninoff.
It's a lot to get done,
but that's where you come in.
I really got to go.
- Enjoy your dinner.
- Good night.
Good night.
Can I do anything to help?
Everything's under control.
And I've enjoyed myself.
It's been a while
since I cooked for the family,
and that was with Mrs. Patmore in charge.
You'd better get used to it.
I think they'll be pleased.
- I'm sure we will.
- Oh. Lady Merton.
What can we do for you?
It's Daisy I've come to see.
Me, milady?
Yes.
It's a straightforward request,
but it will require some of your time.
As you may know,
every president of the County Show
is supported by a committee,
and I want you to be a member.
But why me?
The show has always been run
by a rather narrow group of people.
I want to bring it more up-to-date,
and I would value some fresh eyes to help me.
Mm, a wise choice.
I-If I may say so, milady.
Please,
do think about it.
She will.
You've paid her a great compliment,
and you won't regret it.
Not in a month of Sundays.
Why would any of them listen to me?
For your experience.
Here and on the farm.
But suppose Lady Merton disagrees with me.
It's a good sign you
already know you'll be arguing.
Why didn't you join Harold?
So I could have dinner with you.
Do you have many horses?
A few, but I've never had one
in the Gold Cup before.
We should get up a party.
Although I suppose
Ascot's finished for me.
If you can come,
it would reward me for
my efforts on Harold's behalf.
Can I ask about those efforts?
Are you a sort of business advisor?
I kept him out of some trouble a while back.
But, really, we're friends.
Can I top you up?
Oh, I shouldn't.
I've had more than enough.
Oh, go on then.
Hello.
Oh.
I didn't expect you back for hours.
Her Ladyship sent me home early
so we could have dinner together.
Oh.
How was London?
Busy.
For them, anyway.
I've been busy, too.
Working on the script of Held to Ransom.
Are you pleased with it?
It's taking a bit longer
than the last one, uh...
You work too hard.
Ease up.
No, I can't.
This is my moment.
After years of being in the background, I...
I'm changing lives.
You were changing lives
when you were a teacher,
weren't you?
Yeah, you're right, but this, it's different.
It's-it's...
You know,
I-I've got to crack on then.
Some of us went to see
Mr. Dexter's new play.
Mr. Coward's new play,
I think you mean.
How I would have loved to have seen that.
To think Mr. Dexter relaunched
his career at Downton.
I wonder if he'll be back.
This place will be a desert for him,
without anyone to talk to.
- Well, he's got Mr. Barrow.
- Mr. Barrow's a servant.
I'm a servant.
And I've told you, you can give it up.
And I've told you
I don't want to.
Anyway, Mr. Barrow's not a servant anymore.
Yeah, well, the fact remains,
Mr. Dexter and I, we understand each other
in a way that none of the rest of them can.
Sounds like Isobel may regret
taking on the County Show.
She's got her work cut out
with that stuck-up fool
Moreland.
She was shocked when I told her
about Lady Petersfield.
I don't think she'd quite taken in
what a divorce was gonna mean.
If that's her reaction, imagine
what everyone else will think.
Henry's decision has made Mary an outcast.
- Somehow we will have to live with that.
- Mm.
Isobel included.
Thank you.
I won't be surprised if people
start avoiding Downton
in case Mary's here.
Then we must challenge them
and change their minds,
mustn't we?
As a guest,
can I offer you another drink?
I really think we should stop.
Nonsense. You said yourself
you'd lost your position.
Let's celebrate.
Is there any of that wine we had at dinner?
Milady?
Just bring some champagne.
Carson would have left
a bottle in the icebox.
- I thought you might like...
- Please.
You're right.
I have lost my position.
Have you ever been thrown out of a house?
It's quite the experience.
I hear the Prince of Wales
is taken with my compatriot
Lady Furness,
and she's divorced.
The prince's interest will not enhance
her standing in society.
There's nothing wrong with
finding someone attractive.
- You can't blame him for that.
- Mm.
Or me, either.
Meaning what, exactly?
Meaning this.
Just put it there.
We'll look after ourselves.
You can go to bed.
If you're sure, milady.
I'm quite sure.
- Who?
- Daisy Parker.
She works in the kitchens at the abbey.
Sir Hector isn't going to like that.
Next I'll ask Carson.
He's well thought of in the area,
so he'll be very helpful.
So you really mean to bait Sir Hector?
I mean to bait him very much indeed.
My God.
Good morning.
Don't say "good morning"
as if everything's fine.
Isn't it?
No.
This is not who I am.
This is absolutely not how I behave.
I suppose we were both quite drunk.
Oh.
I had a marvelous time.
Well, I didn't.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, I don't mean that exactly.
But I do not jump into bed with strangers
at the drop of a hat,
and I don't approve of people who do.
Have you never done anything
you don't approve of?
That's not the point.
Well, you just got your divorce,
and some old hag insulted you.
Surely you're entitled to drink too much
and have some fun with me.
No one would blame you.
I would blame me.
And so would everyone else.
Now get back to your room
before my maid arrives.
I was hoping for a second round.
I won't tell if you don't.
Just go.
Please.
- Go.
- All right.
But I'll go with a song in my heart.
I hope you slept well, milady.
Could you find me some aspirin?
I've rather a headache.
I thought you might have, milady.
You'll find two on your tray.
What's your plan for the day?
I've got my first meeting
with Lady Merton's committee
this afternoon.
Oh, yes.
It's flattering of her to ask you.
Quite the compliment.
If I can be helpful in
some way, then I'll be pleased.
I'm sure you'll be very helpful.
I'll come up to the house for lunch.
Oh, Charlie, there's no need.
You'll only tire yourself.
If you mean that I look worn out,
you're right.
London finished me off.
Then rest.
Enjoy your freedom.
Thank heavens for this cottage.
Did you worry
Lady Mary might turn us out?
She'd never do that.
I just hope Mr. Talbot
doesn't want to make trouble.
He might.
No one knows how to behave anymore.
- That's harsh.
- If it wasn't for him,
Lady Mary would never have gone
for a divorce.
Plenty of the gentry lived
with husbands and wives
who were difficult or boring
or-or just plain nasty.
And what do you think they did?
They put it in their kit bag
and they kept on marching.
How are you getting on?
Pretty well, I think.
- We're nearly there.
- You are good.
At least the things
Mama loved are safe now.
It made me nervous knowing the Dower House
was full of her possessions
when no one was living here.
What will you do, find a tenant?
I suppose. Any suggestions?
Maybe. Let me think about it.
Let's go home if we're to meet
Mary and Harold
and the mysterious Mr. Sambrook.
How could Harold have landed us with him?
And why is he here?
It's not very English behavior.
Well, we're not English, my brother and I,
which I know takes some getting used to.
Goodbye, Mama.
Ah.
Cora.
Still so glamorous, I see.
If you say so, my brother.
- Hello, Mary.
- Mama.
And you must be Mr. Sambrook.
Welcome to Downton.
But I hope you won't be bored.
Harold and I have a lot to talk about.
You can talk in front of Gus.
Come in and have some tea.
We thought the funeral was splendid.
Mother would have been very touched.
Pity you couldn't stay on
in New York for a bit longer.
We would have if I'd known
the time it would take
- to settle things.
- Mm.
Uh, Robert, how are you getting on
with Mary's plan to plumb the cottages?
Not Mary's plan. Our plan.
If it was sensible remains to be seen.
- Seems sensible to me.
- Does it?
I must get you to go through
our accounts while you're here.
Perhaps you can tell me
how we're going to pay for it.
Papa, what's the matter with you?
Mama's inheritance will cover the new work.
I just don't see why everything...
Oh, never mind.
I'm going for a walk.
Where's Teo?
Afternoon post, Your Ladyship.
Thank you.
- Why don't you all go?
- Oh. Good idea.
Not you, Harold. We have a lot
to talk about, you and I.
I'll go.
He's so touchy lately.
I suppose we've got
the divorce to thank for that.
The divorce and the realization
that his days as king of the
castle are coming to an end.
Oh.
Mama, is something the matter?
I thought a dinner might help
restore Mary's faith in humanity,
so, I wrote to some neighbors,
and everyone has refused.
All of them? Golly.
Even Anne Manville has said no
when she's always been so fond of you girls.
We can't just give in.
Are you coming, or what?
- Oh.
- We're coming, Papa.
I'm sorry you've arrived when
tensions are a little high.
I got something for you.
Mm.
- My goodness.
- Yeah.
I had this made for her when she lost
the brooch she'd worn at her wedding.
She wanted you to have it.
Maybe we should go for a walk as well,
because the news is bad, isn't it?
How could you tell?
I've known you since you were born.
Gus should come with us
since he can help me explain everything.
Oh, I'd be happy to.
Is she coming?
She'll be here any moment.
You'll have met Mr. Carson.
Not really.
Of course, I've seen him
when we've dined at the abbey.
Now, I want to get going.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Ah.
I had to finish luncheon.
Come in.
This is Mrs. Parker.
Lady Manville, Mr. Saunders,
Miss Bell, Mrs. Dewlish
and our chairman,
Sir Hector Moreland.
Welcome.
- Hello, Mr. Carson.
- Daisy.
That is, Mrs. Parker.
Lady Merton believes
our new members will give us
a different perspective.
We don't want to disrupt anything.
But we might have something to say.
- Oh, I hope you do.
- We shall see.
So, now, finally...
We can start.
What I don't understand is,
since we survived the crash,
where's the money gone?
Gus took everything out
of the market before the crash.
If it wasn't for him,
our mother's money would have been lost.
You mean it would've been lost sooner?
Gus, please explain.
Well, Harold has been unlucky, it's true,
but he wasn't alone in his suffering.
I lost quite a bit myself as it happens.
And now you'd like to
sell the property that's left,
and for that you need my permission?
Well, it will help him to recoup and rebuild.
Harold...
...You lost the capital
I left in your care.
How do I know you won't lose
the rest of the money?
I want the chance to make the money back.
I have to live, and I have to repay Gus.
He's been bankrolling me
until now, but it can't go on.
No.
We'll work out a plan to repay Mr. Sambrook
but that doesn't involve
putting what's left at risk.
So, item six,
on the day itself, we've settled
that last year's arrangements
will, for the most part, stand.
Yes, absolutely.
Is that a good idea?
Mr. Carson?
Hmm?
- What?
- Well...
To be honest, last year was chaotic.
The livestock were hardly supervised.
I don't think anyone else
would agree with you there.
Mr. Carson.
Remember what you said.
Daisy.
- What does she mean?
- Please,
I have no wish to be rude
to Sir Hector or Lady Merton.
Oh, please enlighten us.
What did you say?
Only that...
She's right.
Things were pretty hopeless,
and they were running around
all over the place, but I'm sure
that Sir Hector would soon
have got things under control.
Are you?
You see what you've done?
You bring in people like this...
People like what?
Surely, we can let them speak.
So, the livestock were badly managed?
And there was no provisions
for lost children, either.
No one to help find them,
no safe place for them to go.
We can't be held responsible
for every child in the county.
But aren't we responsible?
For every child that is a guest at our show?
Restrain yourself, I beg you.
I'm sure Sir Hector will be glad to know
where he got things wrong.
I beg your pardon?
Shall we stick to the agenda?
Well, I can't see that it would hurt
to consider these points.
Please.
I really must insist.
So, item seven.
Lectures and demonstrations on beekeeping
and bottling fruit
at intervals during the day.
Are we to gather that
your talk did not go well?
A great deal of my mother's
fortune has been lost.
What?
And now we need a new plan
to protect what remains.
What happened?
What part did you play in all this?
None of it is Gus's fault.
Without him, things could be a lot worse.
I made the decisions.
Why didn't you share them with me?
And why didn't you tell me
when it was all going wrong?
You put me in charge.
God's sake, Harold.
Don't you see what this means for Downton?
Is it really as bad as you say?
Has everything gone?
Well, there's some property,
including the house in Newport.
- Which Harold hopes to sell.
- But what does that mean
- for the work going on here?
- I'm afraid we've spent money
we don't have on a project
we haven't finished.
But I won't allow a fire sale
when what's left would not
be enough to settle things
at Downton and cover
what we owe Mr. Sambrook.
My God.
Is this the time to think
of selling Grantham House?
What?
Where did that come from?
We must be realistic, Papa.
Keeping a London house is
a huge drain on our resources.
It would give us the capital we need.
Sell Grantham House?
What absolute bloody nonsense!
I'm going to change.
Oh, the other side of cuddly Lord Grantham.
I don't think I've ever seen it before.
Well, you're the one who made him angry.
We seem to be living
under rather a dark shadow
at the moment.
If not Grantham House,
what other options do we have?
It's a good thing the dinner didn't work out.
What dinner?
Only that I invited some locals for dinner
and they couldn't come.
Because of me?
Golly.
A house full of Yanks, and I'm
the one keeping people away.
Just when I thought
I couldn't sink any lower,
down I go again.
Maybe you should be grateful for the Yanks.
We're going to change.
Come on, Bertie.
- I'm so sorry.
- Maybe now would be
a good time for me to show Gus
the della Francesca.
Don't present it as a way to raise capital.
Papa's not being fair.
You must know that, at least.
Don't you think he's entitled
to be a little unfair
with Granny's death, your divorce
and Harold's foolishness?
Harold's made a real mess
of things, hasn't he?
It's my fault, really.
It was like putting a drunk
in charge of a bar.
♪ I like America ♪
♪ I have played around every
slappy-happy hunting ground ♪
You go ahead. I'm going
to make a telephone call.
♪ But I find America okay ♪
- ♪ Come what may ♪
- Put them here.
♪ I shall return someday ♪
♪ To the good old USA ♪
♪ Hey, hey... ♪
That didn't go too well.
It's not over yet.
Not by a long shot.
I couldn't help wondering how it's happened.
And we were supposed
to double my mother's fortune,
and now most of it's gone.
But it's coming back
with interest, I promise.
It's a new market.
- I understand it better.
- Hmm.
But I have to have a free hand.
They're changing for dinner.
They'll assemble in the library at 8:00.
Thank you very much.
So, you did see him leaving my room?
I'd never have mentioned it, milady.
You'd never have forgotten it, either.
Thank you, Anna.
I hope Papa didn't upset you.
Not as much as you did
with the dinner that never was.
Bertie shouldn't have said anything.
By the way, Tom rang--
He's coming to stay.
I know.
He's meeting Henry in York.
They finally sold the car business.
Let's hope he can soothe
your father's spirits.
I'm not trying to push Papa
into anything, you know?
Well, I think you are.
I suspect you're trying
to push him into quite a lot.
But I believe you have good reasons.
We should go.
I'll wait for your father.
Are we the first?
Looks like it.
I know you like champagne.
Don't remind me.
You should try America, you know.
We don't care about divorce over there.
I think Downton needs me.
What will Harold do now, do you think?
Mama won't change her mind.
I wonder.
Don't wonder. She won't.
I love my uncle,
but he's hardly proved
to be a titan of business.
But unlike your uncle, I know
how to get the money back.
Won't you help me?
- Catch it! Catch it!
- That was a great shot!
Come on, girls, who's going to get it?
Thank you.
Sybbie, darling, have you come, too?
How lovely.
Aunt Edith.
Go and say hello to the others.
Welcome back to Downton, sir.
- Thank you, Parker.
- George!
- Edith.
- Tom.
Don't go in yet.
I want to bring you up to date.
How is Mary getting on?
Divorce has damaged her badly,
- as we knew it would.
- Mm-hmm.
I wanted to help her rebuild
while she ran Downton
- to take her mind off things.
- But?
- Socially, it's more difficult
than we expected.
- Oh.
And with the estate,
Papa's reluctant to give her
the power she needs.
We'd love you to talk him into
letting Mary take the reins properly.
Of course.
Does Harold being here
mean at least Mrs. Levinson's
estate is finally settled?
I'm afraid not.
He's made a complete bish of things.
How's Lucy? Well, I hope.
We're all well, and it was
a relief to sell the business.
Money's coming in for a change.
So you've made the full journey
from revolutionary to capitalist?
I prefer to call it being sensible.
Oh. Go get it. Go get it.
Very good.
♪ I'm old-fashioned, but I don't mind it ♪
♪ That's how I'll always be ♪
♪ If only you'll agree ♪
♪ To stay old-fashioned with me. ♪
Tom's here.
He's gone to his room.
You should know
I telephoned Guy Dexter.
His play's over, and he's coming to stay,
and he's bringing Noël Coward.
- How exciting.
- It'll cheer Mary up.
And, of course, they couldn't
care less that she's divorced.
I also thought it might tempt
the county back into the house.
Clever girl.
If we can find a way to let them know.
- Have you told the kitchen?
- I'm going down now.
- Edith.
- Hmm?
Thank you.
Mr. Carson, can I help?
Yeah, I've been thinking about
these Lamerie candlesticks.
His Lordship likes to see them on the table.
We often use them.
And you clean them with soap and water?
Not those awful creams
they keep coming up with now?
Everything is done as you
would have it, Mr. Carson.
Then I shall sleep more easily.
- Well, that sounds like Lady Hex...
- Lady Hexham.
And don't forget,
it's a secret from Lady Mary.
Of course, milady.
What did Lady Hexham want?
She just came down to tell us
there's to be a dinner
the night before the County Show.
Mr. Dexter, Mr. Barrow and Mr. Noël Coward
are coming down from London.
I note you list Mr. Barrow
between Mr. Dexter and Mr. Coward.
Will he attend the dinner, too?
MRS. HUGHES:
I shouldn't think so, Charlie.
But please don't be unkind about him.
I hope Mr. Molesley doesn't get too excited
that Mr. Coward is coming.
Let's not mention it.
- Hmm.
Your last dinner.
Yes, but shouldn't we make it
the first dinner
where Daisy's in charge?
Well, I'll be here, of course,
but, oh, I'd like to see her
in action before I go.
Are you looking forward to leaving?
Oh, I don't know the answer.
I'll have Mr. Mason, so I won't be lonely.
None of you can stay away!
Ah, Mr. Molesley.
How nice to see you.
I thought I'd look in to say hello.
We've read about your latest film.
- We're all so proud of you.
- Oh, well.
We're just talking about plans
for Daisy's first big dinner.
Mr. Dexter and Mr. Barrow are coming.
And Mr. Coward, too.
Noël Coward?
At Downton?
It just slipped out.
Well, of course, they won't invite us.
You can't expect Her Ladyship
to ask her own lady's maid to dinner.
This isn't Russia, Mr. Molesley,
and we are not Bolsheviks.
Oh, I've had an idea.
You haven't got a footman now,
so why can't I be your footman for the night?
You're not a servant now, Joseph.
You've left all that behind.
No, no, but don't you see?
I'll come in with the first dish,
and when I get to Mr. Dexter,
he'll recognize me
and introduce me to Mr. Coward.
Even if he doesn't,
I could use some extra help
in the dining room to...
No, he will, he will, and it'll be fun.
See, this is what writers do.
We-we make things up to entertain people.
Oh!
They'll-they'll be telling
this story for years to come.
You've a horse running at Ascot?
Oh, which day?
We'll be there on the Thursday.
My horse is in the Gold Cup,
so you'll be able to cheer it on.
Oh, not me.
I'm no racing man, I'm afraid.
Some bad bets at Belmont cured me for good.
If only it had.
All right, if we're talking about it,
I'd like you all to hear Gus
on how to deal with the losses.
You mean y-your losses?
Discussing money over dinner?
Granny would not have approved.
Pay no attention. Go on, Gus.
Well, I'm sure you know,
the crash changed everything.
Fortunes were lost, men killed themselves.
It was a terrible time, and
we're still living with that.
But Cora's money was not lost in the crash.
Thanks to Gus.
Mm, maybe,
but things changed, and we have
to deal with that change.
You have a house in Newport,
which is not as sought-after
as it was before the war.
So Harold should sell it
before its value sinks further?
You could recover some of the losses
and use part of it
for the work going on here.
And repay you, I imagine?
But if we're speaking openly,
Harold has not done well
since Lady Grantham asked him
to manage things.
He was extremely unlucky.
If you want big gains, you have to be bold.
But the market is not safe, even now.
- I'd stay in bricks and mortar.
- I agree.
Lady Mary, what do you think?
I think Mama knows what she's doing,
and I'd back her instincts.
I'm sorry, Your Ladyship,
Lady Mary's not come up yet.
Oh, no, it was you I wanted to see.
Did you know that Her Ladyship
planned the dinner for Lady Mary
before Mr. Coward was invited,
but that all of our local friends refused?
Miss Baxter did mention it.
My plan, if Mr. Coward
and Mr. Dexter agreed to come,
was that they'd change their mind.
But now that I've managed it,
I'm not sure how to tell them.
Can you leave this with me, milady?
Thank you, Anna.
Are you interested in art?
Well, I'm interested in a lot of things.
Good night.
But I was a little sad
that you didn't stick up for me at dinner.
I'm sure you don't need my help.
Well, maybe not,
but I thought we were friends.
What would happen
if I told them we were lovers
on the day that we met?
That would put a cat among the pigeons.
Are you threatening me?
Just, the English are so easily shocked,
the thought of their expressions
if I just blurted it out, it's tempting.
Then it's a temptation
you must resist, Mr. Sambrook.
I wish I understood
Sambrook's part in all this.
I suppose he's making sure
he gets his cash back,
but Tom's going to look into it.
I didn't like him fishing for Mary's support.
- How's she doing, do you think?
- Well, you know Mary.
She likes to look in control,
whether she is or not.
Don't tell her, but we're
giving rather a special party
to take her mind off things.
Will anyone come?
Oh, they'll come.
Mary may have lost her footing
lately, but I haven't.
There she is.
Hello, Miss Grant. How are you?
Very well, Mrs. Bates.
You remember Miss Grant,
Lady Osborne's maid?
Of course.
I'm sorry she isn't able to
come to Her Ladyship's dinner.
They were sorry, too,
but I'm sure
I don't have to explain.
But it is a pity they'll miss
meeting Noël Coward.
Noël Coward's coming to Downton?
Hmm.
And the film star Guy Dexter.
So, it'll be fun for us anyway.
Oh, it certainly will be.
I should get a move on. Goodbye.
Bye.
I'd say Lady Osborne will have telephoned
by the time we get home.
I don't know.
It looks more like a funfair
than a County Show.
Well done, Mrs. Parker.
I hope you'll be here early on the day.
I'll do my best, but I've got
a big dinner the night before.
Oh, that's still happening, is it?
Certainly is.
We've got Noël Coward
and all sorts coming.
Noël Coward will be at the dinner?
To me, the whole thing looks wrong.
I hate to contradict you, Sir Hector,
but aren't we giving them a proper day out
with good food and rides
for the children to enjoy?
These people work hard.
Don't they deserve it?
You see, Carson, we'll make
a socialist of you yet.
You will not, milady.
We're turning it into a circus.
It may come as a surprise,
Sir Hector,
but we want our visitors to have a good time.
- Oh.
Steady.
Lady Manville was on the telephone,
and Lady Osborne and lots of the others,
saying things have changed
and they can come after all.
Well, you know the reason.
Mr. Levinson telephoned, milady.
He said he and Mr. Sambrook
won't be back in time for dinner.
Thank you, Parker.
Whip that into stiff peaks for me.
Hello, Charlie.
How was the meeting?
Oh, uh, fine.
Uh, but I noticed in the dining room,
the dinner has been laid
with the Sèvres service,
so I've asked for the Meissen instead.
It's all right, Mabel.
Leave the Sèvres as it is.
I have no wish to undercut you, Mr. Parker,
but you may not understand.
The Sèvres is a soft-paste porcelain,
much more fragile
than the hard-paste Meissen.
I understand perfectly,
Mr. Carson.
Her Ladyship asked for the Sèvres.
Thank you, Mabel.
Let him do his job.
So be it.
It's nice to have a night off
from the watchful eyes of Mr. Sambrook.
He's very confident, isn't he?
- Rather a contrast to Harold.
- Let's be nice.
We'll cheer him on at Ascot,
then we'll go home
without a cross word being spoken.
Hmm.
Robert, you were asking about the sale.
It seems to have gone through very smoothly.
Hmm.
Henry's not been at all difficult.
Mm, hmm.
He asked about Downton, if
you were farming more cattle.
That doesn't sound like Henry.
He's not usually interested in anything
that doesn't run on petrol.
I told him I didn't know the answer.
There is no answer.
I have yet to decide what the answer will be.
I know what this is.
What you're all thinking.
I bet you don't.
Have you put them up to this, Mary?
So you can have it your way?
Oh, really, Papa?
You told me I was captain of the ship now,
or has the divorce somehow ruled me out?
Robert, you've worked hard
for this family for many years.
It's time to put your feet up.
Leave the heavy lifting to Mary.
And what am I to do?
What is my job?
To walk around in my tweeds,
smiling hello at the tenants
so that when I'm dead
everyone can say what a nice chap I was?
As long as they do.
Oh, speak up, Bertie.
You're nodding away.
Thank you, Parker.
I got Brancaster when I was
young enough to make changes.
I'd say the place
and the people who live there
are better off as a result.
When you took charge,
there were emperors in Moscow,
Vienna and Berlin,
and your parents were king and queen
of this part of the county,
but that world is gone now.
- It's a different place.
- Oh, so everyone keeps saying.
And it's not different
because we can get to Cape Town
in a few days instead of half a year.
We're changing, too.
The way we talk, the way we dress,
the way we deal with each other.
This is Mary's time.
She's in step with how to run this estate
in the '30s, the '40s and the '50s.
- And I'm not?
- You know this system
doesn't work if people hold on too long.
I'm pleasantly surprised you
think the system works at all.
I have something to add.
The missing detail in this
is that we all, every one of us, loves you.
Very much.
MRS. HUGHES: They're all coming,
Her Ladyship's told me.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you.
And some are angling for invitations
when they weren't asked in the first place.
- Then well done to us.
- Sad, though.
They were happy to throw over Lady Mary,
though they've known her all her life.
Now they'll do anything to
have dinner with a famous face.
That's the way the world is these days.
There's not a lot of point
in objecting to it.
- Oh, thank you.
- Mr. Branson was
really giving it to His Lordship at dinner.
It's funny to think
he used to clean their cars.
I'm sorry for His Lordship.
He's always done his best.
MRS. HUGHES:
Oh, Mr. Mason, come in.
These are happy times,
getting your wife back.
Oh, it is.
But she'll miss all of you.
It'll be odd to cook for two instead of 22,
and in silence rather than
the running commentary.
Oh. I'll be back soon.
So many changes.
And we do need a new footman, you know.
Andy can't do everything.
I'm not sure
Lady Mary would agree.
She's looking to economize wherever she can
when she takes over.
It won't be easy for her
with that divorce round her neck.
Well, then, we must all show
that we support her
- where we can.
- I agree.
- Here we are.
- MRS. PATMORE: Oh...
Thank you, Daisy.
This looks delicious.
MR. MASON: Splendid.
To Mrs. Patmore.
To Mrs. Mason.
Mrs. Mason.
Now, are you quite set
for Mr. Coward's dinner?
MRS. HUGHES:
Oh.
When my time ends and yours begins.
Does that make you feel sad?
A bit, but I don't fight it.
Our lives are lived in chapters,
and nothing's wrong when a chapter is done
and a new one begins.
It's your time now, and I...
And I'm prouder of that than anything.
You're the daughter I never had.
I'll treasure those words.
I will.
Milady, telephone call.
Lady Falmouth.
See they get coffee when they come in.
Edith, can I grab you for a moment?
If you like.
Am I in for another pummeling?
No more pummeling.
But I know how things are,
and I wondered if the money
from the sale of the business
might help tide you over.
Oh, Tom.
My dear chap, don't think of it.
I'm serious.
You and all of Sybil's family
have given me everything.
Isn't that worth something?
It's worth a great deal, but not money.
Now help yourself to some port and pass it on
before we all burst into tears.
You went to bed with a stranger?
Well, of course it sounds terrible
when you put it like that.
How should I put it?
He's not Turkish, is he?
I found him attractive.
I still do,
but I think he feels he has a hold over me.
He wants me to help him convince Mama,
which, of course, I won't.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm not sure.
The truth is, I'm in a fix,
and a great lady like you might
have an opinion worth hearing.
Don't patronize me.
I wouldn't dare.
But what do you think?
Should I try to placate
Sambrook or just ignore him?
Can I ask Bertie about it?
- Must you?
- I think I must.
If he gives me funny looks
for the rest of my life,
I shall blame you.
Tom offered us the money from his sale.
Of course, I said no, but I was touched.
- And it's made me think.
- What about?
Mary is right.
We have no option but to sell Grantham House.
It's time to move on.
Does she know you've seen the light?
Not yet.
And what about her running Downton?
What about it?
I don't wear a sack over my head.
I see how you treat her.
Don't you want her in command?
No, I do. I've said so.
But now the moment's come...
You can't bear to relinquish the crown.
Well, I hope it won't overload you.
And you have the show the next day.
Lady Merton let me make a real difference.
If you're clear about your arguments,
you can make things happen.
Even with His Serene Highness
Sir Hector Moreland.
I knew you would more than hold your own.
No wonder you say
you won't always be in service.
Well, I won't, but I don't have
bad memories of my time here.
This is a, a great honor, milord.
I don't know about that, but the truth is, I...
I need your advice.
Uh...
How? Uh, about what?
Oh, do sit.
We were young men
when you first came to Downton.
You were by my side when I inherited,
and here we still are
however many years later.
I've enjoyed a good life
in your service, milord.
I hope so.
You've run the house well, of course,
but I believe you've made it
a happy place, too.
That's important to me.
We were well suited to each other, milord,
which was our good fortune.
Have you come to discuss Lady Mary?
You're ahead of me as usual,
and you'll know
Lady Mary thinks it's time
that I hand over.
Her Ladyship agrees, and so,
I suspect, does Lady Hexham.
More surprisingly...
maybe I do, too.
But do you really?
You think I'm foolish to drag my feet?
I'd never say that, milord, never.
But I do believe that you could enjoy...
A calmer time from now on,
free from worry.
But I do worry.
I worry the divorce has changed things.
Can she play her role in
the county as a social pariah?
Or...
...should I s-stay on for a few years
until things settle down?
Lady Mary will be a kind
and reliable landlord,
so her place in the county
will soon be secure again.
You think she could manage?
I know she could manage very
well, milord, and so do you.
Why don't you grab that one on the end?
- Pickwick Papers, sir.
- Oh.
Excuse me.
Really.
I think a day at Ascot
will be good for us all.
Not for me.
The gates of the Royal
Enclosure will be firmly shut.
But you must come.
Uh, tell her, Bertie.
I'm, I'm going to arrange
lunch for us in White's tent.
So you won't have to go near the Enclosure.
I'll keep you company.
The Enclosure holds no delight for me.
What about you, Mr. Sambrook?
Do you enjoy these odd
English rituals?
I do. Very much.
Edith will line up plenty of Royal Highnesses
to add to the fun.
Boy, I'm feeling rather jealous,
but, uh, not jealous enough
to risk joining you.
No, I'm gonna stay here
and peruse Mr. Charles Dickens.
- Ten shillings on...
- There you go, sir.
Come on, ladies and gentlemen!
Here we go!
Columbus Boy seems to be doing terribly well.
Is that the one there?
- Green and white. The green and white.
- Green and white.
Come on, Meadows Barron!
Oh.
Was he the favorite?
Shouldn't you wait to see
if there's a steward's inquiry?
Not when it's second last.
Shall we go to the Royal Enclosure?
Don't make him wait any longer, Bertie.
He's panting for it.
I would like to see it.
Uh, go, all of you.
We'll stay here.
You sure?
I am.
- Two pounds on Bosworth to win.
- Bosworth it is.
Tom Branson.
John Bevan, as I live and breathe.
I thought you were still in New York.
Well, so I was till about a month ago.
Tell me, that man you were with earlier,
does he still call himself
Gus Sambrook?
Why? Do you know him?
I'm very sorry to say I do.
Can I give you a card in case
you're ever in New York?
If we'd known you were coming,
we could have given you all luncheon.
Don't worry,
Your Royal Highness.
We were happy in White's tent
with my father-in-law.
Is Lord Grantham here?
He's with Lady Hexham's sister.
I'm afraid Lady Mary is having
rather a difficult time.
We shouldn't talk about that
in front of Lady Petersfield.
I did what I had to do.
Lady Mary will be just fine.
Of course she will, but those
are the rules we live by.
Cora.
Tom, where have you been?
What's wrong?
I have some news for all of you.
It's about Sambrook.
He's a confidence trickster
of the worst sort,
and it looks like Harold has been his target
and his latest victim.
- Why hasn't he been prosecuted?
- He was.
Some sharp lawyers got him off
on a technicality,
but he's a crook all the same.
He should have done ten years.
He kept Harold out
of the crash to gain his trust,
then stole the money.
And now he's trying to get more from us.
- You're sure of all this?
- Quite sure.
Bevan was a witness at the trial.
I'm going to speak to Mr. Sambrook.
What formidable daughters we have.
Have you only just noticed?
Tom, let's get you a drink.
You've earned it.
Are you surprised Sambrook's
turned out to be a bad'n?
I can't decide.
I feel sorry for Uncle Harold.
Sambrook could probably
have fooled any of us.
He certainly nearly fooled me.
I know you're not going back
to Downton tonight with Mama.
She said you want a second look at a house
you've found for us all.
Not a house.
A flat.
I might stay and come with you.
Would you like that?
Very much.
But please be open-minded.
You can be when you try.
I will try.
Very hard.
You have a horse in the next race?
That's right.
There she is.
I do hope you've enjoyed today...
...But please enlighten me.
I'm told you not only stole
the money Harold entrusted to you
but that you now plan to steal
what's left of Mama's estate.
And it's not the first time, is it?
I'm told you used the chaos after the crash
to cheat your way into a fortune.
I'm sure you know how preposterous that is.
Furthermore, according to some,
you were nearly convicted
of theft and fraud in New York.
I was not convicted.
I was found not guilty.
On a technicality.
Now Mary says you slept with her in London
and you're threatening to tell the world.
She doesn't care, of course--
Classic Mary-- but I care.
I didn't threaten.
I was joking.
She must have misunderstood.
I know you think we're all
much stupider than you.
- I've never suggested that.
- But I'm sure you realize
Lord Hexham and I have a little social power.
Maybe in a perfect world
we wouldn't, but we do.
What are you saying?
Only that if I hear of any
threat from you to my mother,
to my uncle, to my sister,
to anyone, in fact,
I promise Lord Hexham
will make you untouchable.
- You wouldn't do that.
- Wouldn't we?
Try us.
Then you have to find another
place for your playground.
England will be dead to you.
So the new contacts
you've been making all day
will avail you to nothing.
Have I made myself clear?
Oh, dear.
It's not your lucky day, is it, Mr. Sambrook?
Your race is about to begin.
Maybe your horse will turn
things around for you.
See that one!
Come on!
Come on.
Come on, Hasteway!
Come on, Hasteway, go!
Which one were you,
Mr. Sambrook?
The guy in spots.
Oh, well, better luck next time, eh?
I'm glad I found you.
I'm leaving,
and you're the only one
I wanted to say goodbye to.
Do you know what saddens me?
You probably don't even remember the names
of the men and women
whose lives you've ruined.
Well, I hope I haven't ruined yours.
Goodbye, Mr. Sambrook.
Oy, no one could say The
Pickwick Papers is too short.
No, sir.
Is there a murder mystery
I could read?
Agatha Christie, something like that?
There might be some in the nursery.
They're catching the last train,
so they don't want dinner, just
sandwiches and a glass of wine.
So, what's Mr. Levinson
gonna do with all this?
I should think he'll make light work of it.
This one over here.
Please come in.
Thank you.
So, this is how the world ends.
Not with a bang but with a whimper.
What's that?
I don't know.
The family upstairs.
"The family upstairs"?
What about downstairs?
Is a family there, too?
I don't know if it's a family.
How peculiar.
A sort of layer cake of strangers.
And what about when I want to go up to bed?
You don't go up. You go along.
Extraordinary.
Isn't it odd to live in
a building full of strangers?
You sleep in a house of strangers
at every shooting party.
I know you think
I've been holding you back.
- Well, I...
- You're right.
So is Tom.
I did encourage you to take control,
but it's hard to accept that it's time to go.
Families like ours
must keep moving to survive.
One day, George will say
it's time for me to go.
I won't be spared, either.
You're not very sentimental, are you?
The hereditary system
can't afford to be sentimental.
But now it's time to think of things
for you and Mama to enjoy.
More travel, more London.
No more Downton.
Nonsense.
You'll be the éminence grise,
the power behind the throne.
No, I won't.
You'll be the power on the throne.
Thank you.
We'll let you know...
If you can sell Grantham House,
we'll take it.
Very good, my lord.
If Lady Mary does take over,
will she want her parents to move out?
You'll have to ask her.
You mean you're not gonna tell me?
But is that right?
Should wives have secrets
from their husbands?
Definitely.
But not the other way around.
If they do go, where would that leave us,
with you working for Lady Mary
and me with His Lordship?
Whatever happens, we'll find
a way to make it work.
After all, we'll soon have
a new life to think of.
Very true, Mrs. Bates.
There they are.
We need to decide
who'll present the final cup
for the Local Hero.
Have you a candidate in mind?
I thought perhaps that
this year I might present it.
Oh, no.
We couldn't possibly ask you.
Not with everything else you have to do.
No, I thought I would ask
Lady Mary Talbot.
Definitely not.
She is known for her interest
in the future of farming.
She's also a divorcée
and a figure of scandal.
I should think her very presence at the show
would make most decent women feel uneasy.
Decent women are tougher than you think,
and marriages fail in the best society.
Ask Henry VIII.
I see. So we're living in
a moral cesspit now, are we?
Lady Mary Talbot is a responsible,
intelligent and generous woman.
We would be lucky to have her.
Don't you agree, Mrs. Parker?
Well, I work in the kitchen,
so I don't know her as Mr. Carson does,
but I haven't got any complaints.
I'm not interested in the opinions
of a toadying kitchen maid
or a bootlicking butler,
and it will be a cold day in hell
before Lady Merton's divorced
ex-daughter-in-law
gives away our prizes.
Please, say what you really think.
I doubt you're ready for that.
Humph.
Never leave me alone with him.
I'm not much help.
He hates me.
But you're a great help.
Oh, you should have rung, milady.
I wanted to ask if everything's ready
for Mr. Coward's dinner.
If Daisy cooked blindfold
for the king in his palace,
she'd not let anyone down.
High praise from you,
Mrs. Patmore.
Only it's our first party
since Lady Mary's troubles,
and I do want it to be a success.
But she didn't come back with you?
She's showing His Lordship a flat.
Oh, th-that sounds like a big step.
It is.
Might we have tea
on the terrace, do you think?
Of course, milady.
Um...
It's a big step for me and all.
Oh. Retiring?
After 50 years
and going to live
in your cottage with Mr. Mason.
I should think so.
Mm, no. That's-that's not what I meant.
What did you mean?
Well, you're right.
I've never lived with Mr. Mason.
Not... properly.
Not yet.
Oh.
I see.
And I wondered,
since you sent me to Mr. Carson
all that time ago...
I'm not going to question
Mr. Mason.
Only I'm nervous.
If he should want us to...
You know, uh...
And from what he's said,
I think he might.
You mustn't be nervous.
Why not?
Because I'll tell you one thing.
It's terrific fun.
Oh, yes.
Are you sure?
Tom knows what he's talking about.
If Sambrook isn't a convicted
felon, he should be.
How did he convince you to part with so much?
It was the Argentinian currency.
Gus said the exchange rates
from gold to paper
offered by the Banco de Córdoba
were yielding far higher profits
than anything on the stock market.
And you took his word for it?
Well, he was very convincing,
so I gave him the money
to put into the company making the deal.
But shortly afterwards, he told me
the company had collapsed
and all the money was gone.
Who knows if there was a company?
But we can be sure
that the money made its way
into Mr. Sambrook's pockets.
Why did you bring him to England?
Well, he had his horse, as you know,
and he said if we...
Persuaded Cora to give us what was left,
he'd double the amount I'd lost.
Can we take him to law?
Prosecution in this sort
of case is notoriously hard.
After all,
Harold agreed to everything.
I'm afraid it's gone.
I can't believe I was so naive.
Oh, here they are now.
Well, you must be worn out
after your journey.
- I am.
- Well, Robert, how was it?
Are you all right, Uncle Harold?
Not when I've been
as big a fool as a man can be.
Mm. It was rather a shock to us all.
We'll find a way to cheer you up.
Some neighbors are coming
for dinner before the show.
Won't they take one look at me
and run for the hills?
Don't be silly.
Thank you.
The stately homes of England.
How beautiful they stand.
Where are you going?
In this house, my place is in the kitchens.
Well, then we'll all go together.
- Good afternoon.
- Oh, Thomas.
- Oh, Mr. Dexter.
- Hello.
Mr. Coward, this is a great honor.
Not at all.
We had to meet Thomas's partners in crime.
You should say hello
to Lord and Lady Grantham.
Did you work with Thomas?
I did.
Mr. Parker has just started.
As the butler.
So you've retired now,
Mr. Carson?
Well, you wouldn't think it
from the time he spends here.
At least you're still around,
Mrs. Patmore.
Oh, only until now.
Daisy's cooking dinner tonight.
By tomorrow morning,
I'll have retired as well.
So bring your complaints to me.
What a merry-go-round.
Daisy, you look very familiar.
- I'm sure I don't.
- Yes, you do.
Very familiar indeed.
You should go up.
And you're staying down here?
Well, we can't change how
England works in one afternoon.
We'll see about that.
They'll be in the music room at 8:00.
I'll let Mr. Dexter know.
Goodness.
Have they arrived?
Mr. Molesley, you're in good time.
You've just missed them.
Mr. Dexter remembered me.
Well, I look forward to him
introducing me to Noël Coward.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I must have miscounted.
I thought this was my room.
I don't believe so.
Unless they're planning
a cozy night for us both.
Oh. Mr. Coward.
You know, it's good of you
to come all this way.
It'll make a real difference.
Oh?
Oh, to Mary's rebirth.
Was she punished for her divorce?
It hasn't been easy,
but you're about to make it
a whole lot easier.
That's my role.
To spread sunshine wherever I go.
Edith tells me no one can refuse
the chance of meeting you.
The sprat to catch the mackerel.
Mm, the mackerel to catch the sprats.
See you at dinner.
Milady.
What are these?
I wanted ideas for the Dower House.
Really?
You may want to sit down.
If you like.
But I'm not going to fight you.
On what?
Our moving into the Dower House.
That is a surprise.
Why?
It's a good idea.
When will it be ready?
It's ready now.
I've had it cleaned
and put all the things back.
Oh. You have been busy.
I have,
and your understanding makes
things a great deal easier.
I'd say my favorite is Madeleine Carroll.
She's never let the stardom go to her head.
I saw her in American Prisoner.
Mm. We talk about England
whenever we're together.
The three of us.
And Miss Dalgleish, is she well?
Yes, but she doesn't mingle
with the English much.
She has been reborn as an American.
Do you dine with these people?
Of course I do, Mr. Carson.
It's a bit unconventional,
Mr. Barrow.
You can allow Mr. Carson that.
I suppose actors and servants
are not so very far removed.
Mr. Barrow isn't a servant now.
Well, I'm still the organizer.
I make sure things run smoothly.
What would you call that?
I've got a few suggestions.
Charlie.
I'd better get back to the duck.
Good. You look just right.
Are you checking before I go down?
Maybe.
I didn't want any trace
of sackcloth and ashes.
You mean you're trying to relaunch me
as socially desirable?
Why are you always in a contest
for who wins the prize?
You're much tougher than you used to be.
Has being a great lady given you armor?
So you could force Sambrook
not to cheat Mama?
I almost feel sorry for him.
Almost.
You can't be grateful, can you?
Ooh. Are we going to have a fight?
There's no point fighting you.
You never admit when you've lost.
I'll admit it now.
I've been very lost for a while...
But I think I'm coming out of it at last.
Thank God for that.
A perfect martini is made
by filling a glass with gin
and then waving it in
the general direction of Italy.
- Mr. Levinson.
- Oh.
No, no, no, these things
really are delicious.
- Never too early for a cocktail.
- Finally.
What's Molesley doing here?
Isn't he writing films these days?
Search me.
- Who knows?
- Lady Mary.
Come and meet Noël.
Oh, I thought it was just a few locals.
It's so good of you to come all this way.
It's wonderful to be back here
and to see you looking so well.
I was talking earlier to
your uncle about your divorce.
What happened?
Well, I doubt I'll be asked
that again tonight.
Or is it research for a play?
Maybe.
But don't worry if you'd rather not say.
No, I'll say.
We fought like cats.
He wanted to be kingpin,
but I was the heiress
and he was just the husband.
He hated that.
How intriguing.
Mr. Coward must be used to being served
the best food in England.
Maybe, but Mr. Molesley read in Picturegoer
that his favorite is bangers and mash.
Well, tonight he's getting
coquilles Saint Jacques and Gressingham duck,
and he better like it.
Mr. Coward, can you say what's next?
- I have an idea for a sort
of spectacle with music.
- Mm.
With the Titanic on stage...
...and the world in the grip of the war.
Oh, I like the sound of that.
Uh, two of my cousins died on the Titanic,
so I may find it hard to sing along.
But we all lost people we loved in the war,
and yet wonderful plays have come out of it.
I'm sure you'll have a long run.
Oh, no. Noël hates long runs.
Only if I'm in them.
Three months, then on to the next thing.
- That's my way.
- Hmm.
- Excuse me.
- Oh.
I suppose this is all your doing.
Mine and Mama's, and Anna helped, too.
All to bring me in from the cold.
To show you still have a life in Yorkshire.
And with patience, you can
have one in London again, too.
I am very grateful.
Don't be.
You're my sister.
- I'm gonna...
- Bye.
- Ah.
- Thanks, old boy.
- Hurry up.
- Yes, Mrs. Parker.
There's lots to do.
I'm relying on you.
- Now quarter the melon.
- Right away.
They won't eat it, but make it look nice.
I hope your presence here
means you have happy memories of Downton.
Very.
Downton changed my life.
- I'm glad.
- I don't get it.
He's playing with me.
He's pretending not to know me.
I don't approve of long speeches,
you'll be happy to hear, but I
couldn't let this evening pass
without some thanks to you all for coming.
Mary has been through
some testing times lately,
and your friendship
has never meant more to her,
to all of us, than it does now.
You should know that from now on,
she will be the mistress of Downton.
You may even be glad
since you will no longer be dealing with me.
Cora and I have decided
to move into the Dower House
while Mary presides here.
She knows this estate better than I do
and loves it quite as much.
I can promise with all my heart
that she is more than worthy of the position
that she has been called to.
You've been good neighbors to Cora and me,
and I hope you still will be,
but the future of Downton Abbey
is now in Mary's and, later,
George's hands.
May God bless them.
I give you Mary and George.
Mary and George.
- That was marvelous.
- Well done, Robert.
Now let's go through together.
All this Queen Mary talk
kind of makes you forget
her grandfather was in dry goods.
Can I help you with anything more, sir?
Haven't we all finished?
I expect you're puzzled to see me.
Uh...
Joseph Molesley.
I...
I wrote the film.
Oh, of course.
But you're a footman again now.
Never mind, old chap.
It's a fickle business.
- Oh...
- Guy.
Go and invite Barrow to join us.
What? Upstairs?
Oh, he doesn't work here anymore,
and for you, he's clearly
more a friend than a servant.
You're right.
The old divisions don't seem
to mean as much as they did.
I'm not convinced
they ever meant much to you.
Can I come with you?
Why?
Well, he wants to see their faces
when you make the suggestion.
This way, Noël.
All I wanted was to meet Mr. Coward,
and now he thinks I'm a footman.
The last supper.
Oh, no, don't get up.
Thomas, Lady Mary wonders
if you'd like some coffee or a drink.
Lady Mary wants Mr. Barrow
to join her upstairs?
Well, he doesn't work here
and he's in the house now as a pal of mine.
That's true.
This really is the night
that shook the world.
Oh.
I suppose you think
Lady Mary's lost
her moral compass, Mr. Carson.
Perhaps we should all have
a different compass these days.
Well, are you coming?
Do you think I should?
I certainly do.
Right.
Cheer up, Mr. Molesley.
You've a good marriage.
You're a successful screenwriter.
Isn't that something?
Wait a minute.
So, you wrote The Gambler?
I did, yes.
Well, you were lucky with Guy.
Writers can wait years before they get a cast
that shows them at their best.
I-I do know that,
and I know that it's an honor
to have you here, Mr. Coward.
Oh.
I don't understand, if you're a writer,
then why are you a footman now?
Oh. It's a... it's a long story.
I hope you've enjoyed your stay at Downton.
Certainly.
And Lady Mary's given me an idea.
What do you mean?
Well, she was talking about her divorce,
and I can see the play in my head.
Oh, but is it right?
To use what people confide
about their private lives?
Private lives.
Very good.
Thank you, Mr. Molesley.
I'm grateful.
Until the next time.
But, Joseph, you've made a good life for us.
A lovely life.
Won't you please let us be happy?
I will try. I promise.
That's all I ask.
Are you all right?
I wish I was in the right clothes.
They look perfectly right to me.
- Good Lord.
- Who is that?
Is that Barrow?
Oh.
Yes, and you're not to make a thing of it.
Thank you.
They're very informal.
I suppose that comes with living in America.
We're all looking forward to the show.
Oh, I hope it's one
that Violet would have been proud of.
I feel it's the last thing
I could do for her.
She terrified the daylights out of me. -
Maybe, but in truth, she was kinder, funnier,
wiser than most people knew.
- Quite irreplaceable.
- Oh, I don't agree.
I think Mary will replace her,
- if she hasn't already.
- Mm.
I do wish you'd sing for us, Noël.
I never need to be asked twice.
Wonderful.
Should we gather round?
Noël's going to sing something for us. -
- Oh, Mr. Branson.
- Thomas.
Good to see you.
♪ Poor little rich girl ♪
♪ You're a bewitched girl ♪
♪ Better take care ♪
♪ Laughing at danger ♪
♪ Virtue a stranger ♪
♪ Better beware ♪
Is this funny or impertinent?
Find it funny, please.
♪ The life you lead
sets all your nerves a-jangle ♪
♪ Your love affairs are in ♪
♪ A hopeless tangle ♪
♪ Though you're a child, dear ♪
♪ Your life's a wild typhoon ♪
♪ Poor little rich girl ♪
♪ Don't drop a stitch too soon ♪
Very good, Mr. Coward.
Very good.
♪ You're only a baby ♪
♪ You're lonely ♪
♪ And maybe someday soon you'll know ♪
♪ The tears you are tasting ♪
♪ Are years you are wasting ♪
♪ Life's a bitter foe ♪
NOËL and GUY: ♪ Poor little rich girl ♪
♪ You're a bewitched girl, better take care ♪
Ooh.
♪ Laughing at danger, virtue a stranger ♪
♪ Better beware ♪
- Shall I join in?
- Yes.
♪ You're weaving love
into a mad jazz pattern ♪
♪ Ruled by pantaloon ♪
♪ Poor little rich girl ♪
♪ Don't drop a stitch too soon. ♪
Bravo!
- Bravo!
- Bravo.
We should be off, too,
after a really lovely evening.
But first I want to apologize.
Apologize, Anne? What for?
When you first asked, we hung back.
It was cowardly.
Convention makes cowards of us all.
Lady Osborne said her maid told her
Mr. Coward was coming, but how did she know?
Our servants always know more
about us than we do about them.
Mary's overcome her trials, and I'm glad.
I hope she'll thrive from now on.
I'm not sure I'm cut out
to be the prodigal daughter.
I want my virtues to be celebrated,
not my sins forgiven.
I should take what you can get.
You're leaving before the show?
Yeah. I'll have left
by the time you get home.
Dinner at Southampton,
then on board the Leviathan next morning.
Oh, Harold.
I hope I haven't let you down.
Don't be silly.
I'm the one who's let everyone down.
You trusted me, and I wasn't
worthy of that trust.
You're worthy of my love,
and that won't change.
Wish you weren't so far away.
Well, perhaps I'll move here.
I'm sure I'd be more English
than Robert in a trice.
Let's stay more in touch
in future, and we'll see.
The theater is a wonderful investment,
if you like a bit of a gamble.
Well, what's the name of your new show
with the-the Titanic and the war?
I think I'll call it Cavalcade.
Well, I might try my luck as an angel.
I'm very glad you found someone
to take over from Mrs. Patmore,
but isn't the time coming
when we cook for ourselves,
at least in London?
Certainly not.
One day, the 20th century
will catch up with you, Mary,
and swallow you whole in a single bite. -
Not if I see it coming.
Uh, here's a surprise for you.
I'd like to persuade Cora
we should invest in Mr. Coward's new play.
I hope you don't value your shirt.
Nonsense, Guy.
Haven't you heard? I'm a genius.
It's been a productive visit.
In fact, Lady Mary's given me
an idea for a comedy.
No, I can't think how.
It's about a divorced couple
who are still in love,
but they drive each other mad.
What do you think?
I think I'm not still in love,
and I'm not quite ready
to find divorce hilarious.
You know, I'm gonna miss
Downton when I go.
But you love America.
Oh, yes. And we're always being
told that Europe is yesterday
and America's tomorrow,
but, uh, I don't know.
Sometimes I feel like the past
is a more comfortable place than the future.
How proud your father would be.
I hope that's true.
Shouldn't you be at the show?
I came to ask my son for luck before I go.
Can I give you a lift?
That would be kind. Thank you.
Mr. Dexter must have been so grateful to you
for writing the film.
Well, the best playwright
in the world is nothing
without good actors.
I've learned that much at least.
Here we go.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Uh...
Sorry.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen,
and welcome to the
Yorkshire County Show, 1930.
We hope you all have a wonderful afternoon.
Where have you been?
Are you all right?
You look a bit shaken.
Molesley drove me.
And on behalf of
our new president, Lady Merton,
we hope you're all enjoying
the new additions.
The fairground I see is proving very popular.
Oh.
The sheep shearing
demonstration is taking place
right now at the south end
of the County Show ground
in the sheep pens.
Nothing's changed here since 1850.
Well, you can see women's ankles now.
That's not much use to us.
Anna.
Afternoon.
Thank you for your help with the dinner.
It was everyone really, milady.
Well, then, please thank them all.
- I most certainly will.
- Good day.
In the main arena now,
the judging of the Highland cattle.
And in the lost children's tent,
there's a young girl dressed as Guinevere.
She's too shy to tell us her real name.
Mm.
That's you, that is.
Oh, look.
Want to pet him?
He's so lovely.
Hello, Raffi.
The main prize giving will take place
at the end of the show at 4:30
precisely in the marquee.
Take your seats early.
- Thank you.
- You have a lovely day.
Cora.
Mary.
Follow me.
Are you sure?
Shouldn't I just hover in the shadows?
- Oh, of course not.
- Lady Merton.
There you are.
Lady Grantham.
And, Lady Mary,
I didn't know you were coming.
Let me find you a seat.
Lady Mary is sitting in
the front row with the family.
- Are you sure? Because you have plenty...
- I'm quite sure.
Ah, Lord Grantham.
We have a place reserved for you.
Ah, how kind, Sir Hector.
How was your dinner last night?
Just a supper, really.
I know all about it.
Hell hath no fury like a snob scorned.
Congratulations, Mr. Anderson.
- Ah.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
And now our final prize today
for our Local Hero.
But first, as a tribute to my predecessor,
we have renamed this the Violet Grantham Cup.
When was that decided?
And I would like to invite
Lady Mary...
- Ah.
- ...To present it.
What?
Quite right! Go on!
Firstly, I can't explain
how much your support today means to me.
But I want you to know
that you are, all of you,
more important to me than I can say.
Now, this prize is for someone
who's made a real difference.
A farmer for 60 years until his retirement.
It gives me great pleasure to present the cup
to Mr. Albert Mason.
Huh?
Oh. Go, go, go, go, go. Go. Now.
Oh. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you.
Uh, thanks so...
Thanks to you all for this great honor,
and thanks to Lady Mary,
the new mistress of Downton Abbey.
Like all of us, I wish her well.
Well, everyone seems very happy, Sir Hector.
When standards are lowered this far,
that is usually the case.
We just had to be patient.
I'm all but finished, milady.
Mr. and Mrs. Bates will go ahead,
and it should all be ready when you arrive.
You're kind to have allowed this.
Not really.
You know Mrs. Bates well, and, of course,
I'm glad to work for Lady Mary.
She'll need all the support she can get.
She'll not be disappointed.
Not if I can help it.
Thank you, Baxter.
So, off we go for our next adventure.
I'm looking forward to it, milord.
I'm honored to be doubling
as valet and butler.
I won't let you down.
Do you ever think
of where it all began, Bates?
That day at Tugela Heights,
under General Buller,
waiting to march on Ladysmith?
To be honest, milord,
I didn't think we'd get out of that alive.
I wouldn't have done without you.
- I don't know.
- I do.
I know it very well.
You took a bullet for me,
and I think about it often.
I wanted to catch you before you left.
I was just coming up to say goodbye.
We'll see a lot of each other,
even if your new duties keep you busy.
I'll look forward to that, milady.
But... I do have one thing
I'd like to ask, if I may.
Of course. What is it?
When the baby's born,
might you consider being the godmother?
I should be honored.
That means so much to me, milady.
So much.
Now, I think I've told
Miss Baxter
all she needs to know.
I'm sure you have,
but I'll still depend on you.
You know that.
I think we all depend on each other, milady.
The way people should.
We'll just say goodbye
to Robert and Cora and Mary,
and then we'll be off.
Ah. I'll say goodbye now.
I promised Lucy we wouldn't be back too late.
You've been so helpful, Tom.
With all of it.
You know I'll never be off the telephone,
asking advice.
I doubt I can offer much
you don't know already,
but I'll always be happy to help.
Goodbye, darling.
Sybil would be so proud of you.
Goodbye, Aunt Mary.
Dear Sybbie.
I had good news in the post.
Good news for you anyway.
An offer on Grantham House.
I didn't know things had gone that far.
You were right.
It was time.
We should go.
They're all waiting.
We've decided to walk.
Come along, George.
Goodness. Thank you.
Like the old days.
The kitchen staff weren't
included in the old days.
That was then, this is now.
I'm glad to see you,
Mrs. Patmore.
I heard you were going, milady,
and I-I wanted to say goodbye.
Thank you, milady.
Please thank Mr. Mason
for what he said at the show.
I will, milady.
Ooh.
Mm.
It was very kind of His
Lordship to lend us the car.
I think you've earned it.
And my plan was to swing
through that window up there...
Would you like a visit to the Dower House
to help you settle in?
Give us a few days, and we'd love it.
Off they go.
Yes.
We really must be going, too.
You ready?
I am.
Right. Back to work.
Mr. Carson.
Thank you.
Please say you're not sorry to leave.
I'm not.
We've done our duty.
I've given half my life to Downton,
and I'm glad I have some left to give to you.
I think we'll be happy
living in the Dower House.
Sharing it with Mama's ghost.
She's part of our story.
And it's all part of our story.
And I love you.
That's what makes it all worthwhile.
Give my love to your brother.
Are you sure you won't stay?
We ought to get going.
And I'm eager to see Peter.
And you're pleased with the way
things have worked out?
Every time a place like this
passes to the next generation,
it's a victory in itself.
Long live Downton Abbey.
Amen to that.
♪ I'll see you again ♪
♪ Whenever spring breaks through again ♪
♪ Time may lie heavy between ♪
♪ But what has been ♪
♪ Can leave me never ♪
♪ Your dear memory ♪
♪ Throughout my life will come to me ♪
♪ Though my world has gone awry ♪
♪ Though the years my tears may dry ♪
♪ I shall love you till I die ♪
♪ Goodbye. ♪