Can't believe it.
They're right on time.
Let's get these boys
to their party.
Mama!
It's 10:48
on Fat Tuesday, Mardi Gras.
Now let's go back
in time to 1964.
The Beach Boys on 105.3 FM,
the heart of New Orleans.
♪ Well it's been
building up inside of me
♪ For oh I don't know
how long ♪
Okay. Take it out wide.
Give the pig some room.
♪ When she says
don't worry baby
♪ Don't worry baby,
don't worry ♪
♪ Don't worry baby
♪ I guess I should have kept
my mouth shut
♪ When I started to brag
about my car
♪ But I can't back down now
♪ Because I pushed
the other guys too far
♪ She makes me come alive
♪ And makes me wanna drive
when she says
♪ Don't worry baby,
don't worry baby
♪ Don't worry baby
♪ Everything will turn out
all right ♪
♪ Don't worry baby,
don't worry ♪
My daughter's on that ferry.
Please. Please.
Oh, God, my daughter!
Do the other side?
ATF New Orleans,
Agent Donnelly.
Listen,
call New Orleans PD.
I want all surveillance
from the Algiers dock.
Then call City Transit.
I want the Crescent City
Bridge surveillance,
westbound between
10:00 and 11:00.
All right, got it.
Hey. Seen an ATF
agent around here?
Yeah,
he went down below.
How do I get there?
The south side
of the bridge.
You Agent Minuti?
Larry Minuti, ATF?
No, Larry's my partner.
I'm Doug Carlin.
Paul Pryzwarra, FBI.
How you doing?
Where's Minuti?
On vacation.
Not anymore. We're calling in
half the region on this one.
You can, uh, reach him?
I tried. He's not
picking up his phone.
Well, try harder.
It's important.
Obviously.
What are you
looking for?
Anything that
doesn't belong.
You want to give me a spot?
Uh, yeah.
ANFO.
Ammonium nitrate,
water-soluble.
Fuel oil would have burned
off during the blast.
Between the river and the
rain, if ANFO was used,
the only place you'd
find it would be...
Underneath this bridge.
That's right.
We can't rule out an accident
at this point.
It's not officially
a crime scene yet.
Here's a thought.
Why don't we
double the perimeter
so we don't have wall-to-wall
trailers down there?
No, we're gonna need
all our manpower
for evidence control
and witness processing.
Now, we need to keep it tight
until we can determine that
it is a crime investigation.
It is a crime investigation.
Got a piece of electric blasting
cap and a strand of leg wire.
About a million of
those blue particles
washed up on
the Algiers side.
It's probably from a plastic
container or a barrel.
ANFO?
Most likely.
There was post-blast residue
under the Crescent
City Bridge.
The insulation on the
leg wire will inform us
of who the manufacturer
of the blasting cap is.
Then we go after
the switching mechanism
and the bomb's
power source.
We probably don't need
to wait for the lab
to tell us what
we already know,
that this is an explosive
and a trigger.
And you are?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm Doug Carlin, ATF.
Who's in charge?
We're working on that now.
Gentlemen, please.
Ed Elkins. I'm in charge.
Oh, good, good, good.
Yeah.
You're in charge, then?
Okay.
First things first.
Where's the coffeepot?
Ed?
Come on, this is a police
investigation, right? Operation.
We gotta have a coffeepot.
Yeah, uh, uh,
you'll find it in the back.
Back there?
Yeah.
He is in charge.
Thank you, gentlemen.
See anything?
Uh, traffic.
Hit rewind for me.
Hey, did Larry call?
Still not answering his cell.
We left another message.
All right.
Say, that girl ever get ahold of you?
What girl?
You know, sexy voice, asked if you
were tall, dark and handsome.
I gave her two out of three.
Two out of three. That's very good.
Hit play.
Thank you.
Hey, Larry, this is Doug.
How you doing?
Listen, I know you're maybe
still pissed off at me,
but you need to get your
behind down here, all right?
Doug.
Yeah?
Doug, Orleans Parish on line one.
It's Sheriff Reed.
They pulled a body out of the
water, and they want a profile.
All right, tell him
they don't need a profile.
Just tell him to bag it.
I'll call him back.
Okay, got it.
Put this on
a candy wrapper?
It's all I had.
Cutting back, huh?
Hold it right there.
Yeah, this is ATF Agent Doug
Carlin returning your call.
My cell number
is 504-555-0130.
What's that?
Looks like
a dude on a bike.
Run it forward
a little bit.
Stop right there.
What is he doing?
Going to the bathroom?
Run it forward,
run it forward.
What time does it say?
10:47.
That's before the explosion,
isn't it?
Right before.
McCREADY: Can I have
your attention, please?
Thanks very much for coming.
I'm Jack McCready,
special agent
in charge of
this investigation.
First, let me say
our hearts go out
to all of those
affected by this tragedy.
Early estimates place
the number of casualties
at 543 men,
women and children.
Now, Lord knows this city
has seen its share of pain,
but unlike Katrina,
this disaster was
not an act of nature.
After careful review of evidence
retrieved at the scene,
we have concluded this was
a deliberate act of terrorism,
and the President concurs
with our assessment.
On our end, we have to
ask for your patience,
as the investigation
will take time.
It's a unique and complicated
crime scene.
There's no baggage checks.
There's no flight data recorder.
There are maximum casualties,
and most of the evidence is
under 100 feet of muddy water.
There are no shortcuts.
Kevin, where's Doug?
You just missed him.
Well, his car's still here.
Took the streetcar.
What? Streetcar?
Hey, don't look at me.
It's part of his process.
He says it helps him think.
Sheriff Reed.
How you doing?
It's Doug Carlin returning your call.
Hey, Doug. I know you got
your hands full right now.
Yeah, that's okay.
What do you got for me, Bob?
Well, a couple of kids
found a woman
face down in the waters
off Algiers Point.
She was burned
over 30% of her body.
Right, well, you're gonna see a lot
of that over the next few weeks.
We've just set up ECC.
Just have Crime Scene
bag it for us.
Well, we already done that.
The body's at the ME's right now.
Crime Scene's
already been there?
Yeah, they've been and gone.
Well, exactly what time did
this woman wash up on shore?
Kid called it in
at 10:42 a.m.
You mean 11:42, don't you?
No, I mean 10:42.
I got the sheet right in front of me,
and I got my
reading glasses on.
Immediately evident is the focal
charring of the limbs and torso.
Anterior face, neck and chest
are intact,
though swollen from apparent
immersion in water.
Hold her hand
for me, will you?
Right here.
There we go.
Each digit of the right hand
has been severed
between the middle and
distal phalanges. Thanks.
Angle of shearing indicates
a single sharp-force trauma,
possibly caused
by shrapnel.
No. No, it's too even
to be shrapnel trauma.
Posterior charring
gives off a strong odor,
suggesting perimortem
immersion in burning fuel.
Diesel.
Accelerant, maybe?
I don't know.
If she was that close
to the bomb,
she probably wouldn't
be laying here now.
What are you doing?
You got a UV gun?
Yeah,
on the table behind you.
You see that?
Duct tape.
Mmm-hmm.
What's that stippling?
You see that?
Adhesive probably retained some
substance against the water.
Yeah.
Yeah, go ahead.
I ran down
those MPRs for you.
A Claire Kuchever was reported
missing this morning.
Supposed to pick up her
father from the airport,
pulled a no-show.
Okay.
All right, Phil, I want
you to do a full autopsy.
Concentrate on
time and cause.
Full spread of lab tests.
Everything.
Just pretend like the ferry explosion
never happened today, okay?
Absolutely.
Claire?
She's beautiful, huh?
Yeah.
Very.
You'll need a photograph for
your investigation, right?
There's plenty in the house.
Plenty to choose from.
Mr. Kuchever,
I'm sorry about this,
but I'm gonna need you to confirm
your daughter's identity.
Okay.
Uh, now, anything
that you can tell me
about your daughter's
activities over the weekend,
or any time, anything at
all, will be helpful.
Well, I don't know.
My flight got in
at 8:00 a.m. this morning,
and she was supposed to pick
me up, but she wasn't there.
I thought maybe
she just overslept,
so I took a cab and I went
straight to her house.
Her and Alan's car was gone,
so I thought maybe she'd
just finally sold it.
Who's Alan?
Her fiance.
Or ex-fiance.
They broke up
a few months ago.
And where is he now, Alan?
He moved to Montreal.
Okay.
She was too good
for him, anyway.
I got a sweater that she left,
if you want to take it.
No, that's okay.
But if you have keys
to her house,
I would appreciate it.
Oh, she--she had a date.
Last night on the phone,
she told me that
she was gonna
meet someone,
but she didn't say who.
Her friend Beth
set it up.
Beth.
Beth Walsh. Claire baby-sits her
daughter, Abbey, sometimes.
Okay.
Thank you.
That's good for now.
Somebody'll be in touch.
Agent Carlin?
Doug.
I want you
to take these.
Well, that's...
Just go through them
when you get a chance.
Well, it's really
not necessary.
Yes, it is.
See, I know how these
things go, Agent Carlin,
and I need her
to matter to you.
Monday, 7:48 p.m.
Hi, Claire. It's Dad.
My flight gets in
at 7:55 tomorrow morning,
so don't stay up too late.
Love you. Bye-bye.
Tuesday, 9:44 a.m.
Claire? Hi, it's Beth.
Are you there?
I'm sorry
to call you so early,
but you said you were gonna
call me when you got home,
and when you didn't,
I started to get worried.
- Beth, is this a joke?
- Oh, hey, hey! No.
Like--Like I said, I was just
worried about you, that's all.
I can't talk right now. Someone's
here. I'll call you later.
Claire...
Tuesday, 9:50 a.m.
Tuesday, 10:04 a.m.
Claire, it's Dad.
I did say 7:55, didn't I?
I'm here at the airport,
waiting for you.
If you're not coming, I hope
you're sending Beth or someone.
Call me.
Tuesday, 1:18 p.m.
Yeah, this is ATF Agent Doug
Carlin returning your call.
My cell number
is 504-555-0130.
WOMAN Tuesday, 1:18 p.m.
Yeah, this is ATF Agent Doug
Carlin returning your call.
My cell number
is 504-555-0130.
The blast wave initiated
here, hit the bulkhead
and propagated fore and aft along
the path of least resistance
until it hits
this access hatch.
Uh, and that's where
it gets really bad.
The blast wave continues
into the engine room,
bursting the fuel tanks.
This utility shaft here
acts like a chimney,
draws the thermal components
into the engine room,
which ignites the fuel vapor,
causing a secondary explosion
of far greater magnitude.
Essentially,
the initial device
turns the whole ferry
into a bomb
and detonates it.
And so our early guess
is that the bomb vehicle
was a minivan or SUV.
Possibly red or tan.
McCREADY: Make and model?
Take weeks,
maybe months.
I got a partial on
the license plate.
Shit.
Check all the SUVs and minivans
that are registered in the state.
Anything recently
rented or purchased,
anything tied to a theft
or a missing persons report.
Agent McCready?
Yeah.
Doug Carlin, ATF.
Oh, yeah. Oklahoma City.
Right. That's right.
This afternoon,
I witnessed an autopsy
of a young woman who washed
up off the Poland Wharf.
Heavy fuel burns,
traces of PETN on her face.
PETN, that's the base explosive
used by domestic terrorists.
She also lost several fingers in
what appeared to be blast damage.
Appeared?
That's right. I checked the tide tables
against the position of the blast.
For her to have washed up that
early and that far upriver,
she would've had
to have been killed
two hours before
the ferry exploded.
Before?
She died before
the explosion?
the explosion, yeah.
Her name is
Claire Kuchever.
She washed up before the
explosion and against the tide.
Do you have a scenario?
Yes, I do.
I believe that somebody abducted
her in her home, taped her mouth,
bound her wrists, burned her
alive, dumped her in the river
so she would appear to be
just another disaster victim.
A disaster that
hadn't happened yet.
But the PETN tells us
that the bomber came in direct
contact with the victim.
You solve her case,
you solve this case.
Why this woman?
Good question.
Her SUV is missing.
It's a tan and red Bronco.
It could have been stolen to
drive the bomb to the ferry.
Oh, one more thing.
The victim called
the local ATF office
the morning
of the explosion.
Yeah.
We'll look into it.
Okay.
All right.
Where's Larry?
What?
Larry Minuti, my partner.
That's his car right there.
Is he here?
I thought you said
he was on vacation.
Yeah, that's right.
What?
Those cars were brought here from
the Algiers ferry parking lot.
They're the vehicles
that belonged to the victims.
Sorry.
So he's a former Marine?
Yes, sir. Yeah. Local, too.
He's born and bred
in New Orleans.
His family
still in the area?
Nope. Nothing, really,
but his job.
You like him?
He's smart.
Yeah, I like him, too.
All right.
Let's go find him.
Oklahoma City.
Yeah.
You and Larry were close?
Yeah, you know, close enough
to get on each other's nerves.
Doug, I've been put in charge of a
newly-formed investigative unit.
The ferry disaster is our first
case, and I want you on the team.
Why me?
We've got some unique
time constraints.
I need someone who can look at a
crime scene exactly one time,
tell us what's missing, tell
us what shouldn't be there,
tell us what
we can ignore
and, especially,
what we need to pursue.
Also, you're local. You know the
people and you know the area.
But why an ATF guy?
Why not?
It's your shot.
You want to find the guy
who killed Minuti, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I guess you've
got some questions.
For me to have questions, first
I'd need to know something.
Now I do have
some questions.
Don't touch anything.
We don't need you yet.
Doug, you remember
Dr. Alexander Denny.
Where's my audio?
Compensating for audio delay.
Just a second.
Oh, compensating for a technical
blunder by a tech guy...
Solid stream.
Minus four days,
six hours, three
minutes, 45 seconds.
And 14 and
a half nanoseconds.
Okay.
Anytime you want to jump
in here, be my guest.
Me?
Yeah.
What are we looking for?
You know, clues, suspects,
anything out of the norm.
When was this taken?
Four and a half
days ago.
Gunnars, try the guy
with the backpack.
Oh, that's tender.
I wish I had someone.
Okay, widen out.
Let's cruise the car deck for
a while, see what we got.
How can you
change the angle
on footage taken
four and a half days ago?
This is a digital recreation.
We're combining all the data
we've got into one fluid shot.
Any angle, any view
within the target area.
Okay, um,
let's cruise the breezeway,
see what we get there.
It's a brand-new program.
It's called Snow White.
Our primary data comes from
seven orbiting satellites,
but at any given time, as many as
four are surveilling one area.
It's like having
multiple eyewitnesses,
each with their
own vantage point.
Snow White?
Well, which one
of the seven dwarfs
can explain to me
how you get the audio?
I don't understand.
Why do you gotta
look at four days ago?
Why don't you just fast-forward
it to the day of the explosion?
We have to wait.
It takes four and a half days
to render this
single fluid shot.
The only thing
that matters
is that we have exactly
one look at any one time.
Yeah. We can't go back
10 minutes, you know?
Can't look back and see
if there was a second gunman.
We can't watch the agent buying
10 pairs of cargo pants in 1983.
All right?
But given enough lead time,
we can look anywhere within
the target area, all right?
It's the when
that's always constant.
It's always four days
and six hours ago.
Always. You understand?
It's like a single trailing
moment of now, in the past.
Okay. So if--if--if--if you can't
move forward or backward in time,
how is it the image keeps
speeding up like that?
It's not the image
that's moving faster,
it's just our
shifting point of view.
The passage of time
remains constant,
but we can shift
our point of view
within the data stream
as fast as we want.
You understand?
Yeah. Yeah. No.
Yeah, I know.
So four days from...
Well, actually, three days from now,
since it's after midnight,
you'll be able to look back
to the day of the explosion,
see who did it,
how they did it
and what they did it with.
Yeah, you got it.
The only thing is, you need
to tell us where to look,
'cause, you know,
we could miss it.
Besides, three days could be
too late. He could leave the country,
could strike again.
We need to do
whatever we can now.
We know he's out there
planning this.
We just don't
know where to look.
So, Agent Carlin,
where do we look?
Claire Kuchever's house.
Address is in range.
All right, match the viewer
settings to the signal.
Signal's solid.
All right, dazzle me.
What?
You see, with Snow White
we can track through walls.
It's part of the same infrared
thermal-imaging stuff
they're using in Iraq.
Hello. This is 877-504-8423.
We triangulate
from four satellites,
pick up the heat signal
and reconstruct.
Basically,
we can walk through walls.
Claire Kuchever.
Claire? Hello?
Did you know her?
We held hands once,
but no, I didn't know her.
Just checking in,
wondering how you're doing.
Montreal's fantastic,
but my boss is an ass.
Can you, uh, rotate the view,
see what she's looking at?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want you to
come visit, though.
The city's phenomenal.
You're gonna love it.
Claire? Claire?
555-0118.
Somebody got that?
Yeah.
Claire, you there?
Listen, I've had-- I've had
a lot of time to think,
and I need you to sell the
Bronco as soon as possible.
Or at least
pay me back my half.
I just really need the money.
I love you, honey. Call me.
Unbelievable.
Where's she...
Can you follow her?
No problem.
Yeah, I'm coming,
I'm coming.
What?
It's Stalhuth, at that house you found.
Female murder victim, Claire?
Right. What do you got?
We got some
bloody cotton swabs
and gauze strips
in the bathroom,
some blood in the sink trap.
And, oh, hey, Carlin?
Man, when did
you completely forget
how to investigate
a crime scene?
What do you mean?
This place is lousy
with your fingerprints.
They're all over the place.
Do me a favor.
Just describe
what you see for me, okay?
Just humor me.
Uh, woman's bedroom.
Vanity mirror.
Dressing table with makeup,
knick-knacks.
Okay, okay, okay, I get it.
Is there anybody there?
Anybody brushing their teeth?
No. Just a couple agents, including
Hendricks, who's bent over,
and I have a fine view
of the crack of his ass.
Okay, I get the picture.
Talk to you later.
You satisfied?
She was supposed to go on a
date the night before she died.
I want to get her
appointment books
and everything
brought down here,
you know, her phone records,
credit cards, diaries, anything.
I wanna know everything there
is to know about this woman.
Well, shouldn't we be
concentrating on the ferry?
Well, yeah,
it's likely that our guy
cased the ferry first,
but we don't know when.
We don't even know
what he looks like.
I mean, we could stare him right
in the face and not know it's him.
But we will notice a change, even
a small change, in her life.
- Hey, Beth.
- Claire.
That guy I've been telling you
about really wants to meet you.
Okay. Tell him
I'll meet him Monday night.
Monday.
How about Sunday
if you're not doing anything?
No, Monday.
Great. I'll give him your number.
No, do not give him my number.
I'll go meet him.
He's not some psycho killer.
Who? Him who?
I don't even know if I can
do it Monday. Hang on.
Show me the book.
Monday works.
Damn!
Shit!
Can we go back?
No.
Seriously?
No, it's far too much data for
any existing storage system.
It's a constant stream.
There's no rewind,
no second chances.
We can record what we're
seeing, but we can't go back
and choose to look
at something different.
Okay. You said we
can record, though?
Yes.
Okay.
Tell me,
is there any scientific
or forensic insight
likely to be gained
by spying on this woman
in the shower?
Shanti, we're trying to make
sure the woman's clean.
All right, why don't you,
you know, look around the rest of
the bathroom? Can you do that?
Gunnars.
Yeah.
You back?
Sorry.
All right.
Icy Hot, Band-Aids, baby oil.
This woman needs a vice.
What's on the other
side of that wall?
Kitchen.
Let's take a look.
Hello? Hello?
Maybe there's someone out there.
Maybe there's a stalker.
Someone there?
Hey, Ginger.
Hello?
Does she know I'm here?
Does she know we're here?
No, impossible.
Strictly one-way.
You sure?
Mmm-hmm.
Hello?
Okay, let's check
the perimeter.
Nobody.
Who's watching her?
We are.
They will also take up
a request for more money for the...
God, thank you
for blessing me
with this food
and with my life.
I know today's
gonna be a great day.
Amen.
You guys singing?
You singing a love song? Huh?
You singing a love song
to one another?
What you doing?
Hi.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Everything God has done
will remain forever.
There is nothing to add to it,
nothing to take from it.
God has done this so that
men should be in awe...
Ex didn't show.
Would you?
Whatever is
has already been,
and what will be
has been before.
God calls forth the past.
Claire loved music.
There's a church
near our house,
and gospel fills
the neighborhood.
When she was little, Claire saw
a jazz funeral procession.
She asked me that day,
"Why do they always
wait until the end
"to play the good music?"
Claire, honey, the music's
playing for you now and forever.
Were there four
limo drivers or five?
Four limos.
Must have been four drivers, right?
He was here.
Address is in range.
Palace Restaurant.
They got good food there.
I'm so sorry
for the wait. I really am.
Listen...
Your table will be
ready in a few minutes.
Drinks are on me,
all right?
It is gonna be a few more
minutes for your table...
Go upstairs and see if Table
45 is ready for desserts.
- All right?
- I will.
Hold on. Hang on.
Hello? Hello?
Hey, are you the lady
with the Bronco for sale?
That's him.
How do you know?
Well, call up the phone list.
Let's see if it's
a number we've tracked.
Yes, that's me.
Just a second.
Cover for me,
all right?
Keep that tape
running, too.
I'm gonna want a recording of this
conversation for voice analysis.
- I'm here. Can you hear me?
- Well, hello, there.
Let me tell you, first off,
I'm what you could call
a real motivated buyer.
I bet you are.
I'm ready to get
something right away.
That sounds great.
I need to sell something right away.
Your price looks good,
model, mileage...
So where can I
come by and see it?
Don't tell him.
Um, I'm at 827 Kings Oak,
in the French Quarter.
Need directions?
Now he knows where she lives.
No, no, I'll find you.
Is tomorrow night good?
Actually, I...
Tomorrow night is not good.
Tomorrow?
I'm going out tomorrow.
Mmm-hmm. He wants to wait for the last
possible moment to steal her car,
then it's too late
to report it.
How does Tuesday sound?
Got it. 504-555-0147.
I see it. Tracking.
I think that's
gonna be too late.
See, I need the vehicle
Tuesday morning.
Is there anyone else there
that can show me the car?
No. Sorry.
He's thinking.
I'll tell you what.
There's a K5 Blazer...
A date means somebody's
gonna be expecting her
and will miss her
if she doesn't show up.
That could ruin his plans.
Shanti,
I want to see this guy.
No good.
It's an outdoor phone booth.
Three miles out of range.
I hope to hear from you.
Can we get someone out there
with a goggle rig?
What's that do?
Extend the range?
Yeah, it's immediate
line of sight.
But we can use it to gather
data outside the target area.
Provided there's
any data to gather.
How long is this guy
gonna be at the phone booth?
Not long.
Have a good night.
Thanks.
Bye.
Story of my life.
Yeah, story of my life, too.
All right, now we heard
the voice of our bomber,
now we're gonna go after him
the old-fashioned way.
Can we get video surveillance
on that phone booth?
We can access
all surveillance
available to any
government agency.
Okay, this is from the ATM
camera across the street.
All right. Let's fast-forward to the
exact time of his phone call to Claire.
Where are we
supposed to be looking?
Behind the guy
on the left.
Can you enhance it,
Gunnars?
Not enough for an ID.
Wait, go back.
Can you rewind it just a little bit?
Stop. What is that
on the ground?
Looks like
a camcorder bag, maybe.
We have facial
recognition software?
Yeah.
Let's use it on the bag.
Cross-match it to all the bags
on the south side of the city
in the 48 hours leading up
to the explosion, all right?
Don't think it's
ever been used this way.
Yeah, that's kind of a simple
image to go for a match.
Well, we got
nowhere else to go.
Look, same bag.
Bingo.
Okay, freeze it.
Yeah, looks like the same guy, too.
Where is this?
Security camera
at the Algiers ferry dock.
Okay, when is this?
Two nights
before the explosion.
Seven hours from now.
Two nights before the explosion
is seven hours from now?
Seven hours from now,
we will be able
to access this point
in our time window.
Gotcha.
Kind of creepy, seeing that
lady's life go down in flames.
Yep.
Makes you
appreciate life.
I suggest you go home
and jump on whoever you got.
That's what I'm gonna do.
Nobody home.
How'd you let that happen?
Everything you have,
you lose, right?
Mother, father, gone.
Good looks,
Pryzwarra, gone.
Loved ones
gone in a second.
That's what this job
teaches you, doesn't it?
No matter what,
no matter how hard you grab onto
something, you still lose it, right?
Well, we're gonna grab onto
this guy in a couple hours.
We're gonna nail
this son of a bitch.
What's wrong?
No matter what,
we still lose her.
Right?
...dot-com for
a link to the FEMA Web site.
Military helicopters that
have served as an emergency force
are leaving the city. Hundreds of
thousands of New Orleans residents
have been unable to come back
home, and entire neighborhoods...
Did you talk to him?
...are still
waiting to rebuild.
This while
governmental agencies...
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
Mom asked me to say a prayer for
David this morning, but I forgot.
Okay.
Mom is gonna be so mad at me.
She's not gonna be mad at you.
Come on.
We'll just say
one now, all right?
It's too late.
It's never too late, sweetie.
We'll just pray that David
had a good day, all right?
How about this?
You pray for David,
and I'll pray
for my mom, okay?
Okay.
All right.
What's going on?
Give it a second.
- Gunnars.
- It's rebooting. It's coming back.
Are we online?
Wait.
Gunnars!
What the hell's going on?
Shanti, are we back online?
I don't know.
Something broached the field.
What broached the field?
That broached the field,
right there.
That's what
broached the field.
Now, you wanna tell me
what the hell this thing is?
It's not surveillance, Paul.
It's not
electronic thermal imaging.
You guys have
figured out a way
to look into the past.
Yes or no?
No.
You're lying.
You're lying,
and you know it.
I've told you
everything I can.
She saw it, Paul.
I pointed this thing at her just now,
and she responded to it from
four and a half days ago.
Explain that to me.
All right.
Somebody explain it!
Hit it, Shanti.
For three years,
Cambridge has been working
for National Reconnaissance
on an R & D grant.
Okay.
We were attempting to use
concentrated bursts of energy
to enhance the sensitivity
of optical telescopes.
In the process,
we had a breakthrough.
Given enough energy, we could
warp the very fabric of space.
I said explain it to me,
not talk science.
They found a way to...
Look, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you guys just keep talking?
I'll just sit here
until you figure out what it
is you really wanna tell me.
They found a way to fold
space back onto itself.
All right, look. Uh, we're used
to viewing space as flat, right?
- Like this piece of paper.
- Right.
To see something
from a distance,
light has always
had to travel
the long way across
the flat space in between.
But given what I
was trying to explain,
we can fold the space,
bring the target closer to us,
create what's known as
an Einstein-Rosen bridge,
otherwise known
as a wormhole,
suspend it via
gravitational field.
That's what we're looking at?
That's it.
What's on the other end
of the bridge?
Claire's house.
Wow.
Basically, we're folding
space in a higher dimension
to create an instantaneous link
between two distant points.
Instantaneous?
Well, that's what we hoped for
and that's what we expected.
But the electrical force...
We used huge amounts of
energy to create this bridge.
All right, how huge?
You remember that little blackout
we had a few years back?
Yes, I do.
New York blamed Canada.
Right.
Canada blamed Michigan.
Half the Northeast.
You're saying you guys...
50 million homes. Right.
My bad.
Well, I still say
we blame Canada, but...
Okay, so why can't
I see this bridge?
It's not visible to the human eye.
I mean, it's real, though.
It's just as real
and just as solid
as a cell phone signal
or a radio wave.
Right. Well, I don't know
how a cell phone works.
I just know how to use it.
So how do we use this?
We can look back
four and a half days.
And what,
we can look anywhere?
Limited radius.
Right, right, right.
Looking into the past.
In a sense, we're always
looking in the past.
Even light reflected
from yourself in the mirror
takes some time
to reflect back.
Let me get this straight.
You're trying to tell me that on
the other side of this bridge
is the actual past?
Yes.
- Wow.
- Yeah. But look, look, look.
We created this thing by pure accident.
All right?
This--This--This
space and time...
This--This time window
is a complete fluke.
All right? And--And
everybody is terrified
of screwing with it
for fear of losing it
or suffering the consequences
of God knows what,
which is why it can only be
used as a retroactive tool...
Hey, let me ask you something.
Is she alive or is she dead?
You went to her funeral, Doug.
I know that,
but I think
the question still applies.
Is she alive
or is she dead?
All right.
Life, like time and space,
is not merely
a local phenomenon.
All right!
Am I asking a hard question?
Looks like I picked
a bad week to stop snorting hash.
All right,
I tell you what.
I'll speak slow,
so those of you
with Ph.D.'s in the room
can understand.
It... Here. Look.
Here's a monitor, right?
Now the monitor is broken.
It's dead.
It is not temporarily transitioned
to another state of entropy.
It's dead, right?
Now, is she alive
or is she dead?
She's alive.
All right.
Now we're getting somewhere.
All right, now, you said light
could go back. What else?
Nothing.
Something else could be sent back.
Come on, Paul. Something.
What? A body? A human being?
No.
Not a person. Not alive, anyway.
Why not?
Because you can't beat the physics.
The electromagnetic field.
Look, you transition across
what's known as the Wheeler
Boundary, all right?
An EM pulse annihilates
all electrical activity.
That's your heartbeat, that's
brainwaves, that's everything.
So what? You--You
haven't tried a person?
Let's just say that
we've done enough tests
to know that it's
not even possible.
It's not even
theoretically possible.
The hamster goes back, dead.
A drosophila fly, dead.
What about a radio signal?
What about that?
We could send a radio...
A radio signal?
Yeah, a radio signal.
Won't work. Electrical.
The field would scramble it.
All right, then a note, a warning note.
No.
A single piece of paper. One sheet.
If we keep the mass low...
No!
This could work!
It could work.
Sure. We know where
the guy's gonna be.
We can apprehend him
and put him away
before he even
blows up the boat.
And how do we
do that, exactly?
We send it to ourselves!
You send it to me. Yeah, send it to me.
Send it to my office.
Send it to my office
four and a half days ago,
an anonymous tip, and we can capture
this guy before he even meets Claire.
We know he's
gonna be at the dock.
Whatever you did,
you did it already.
Whether you send
this note or you
don't send this note,
it doesn't matter.
You cannot change the past.
It's physically impossible.
What if there's
more than physics?
Okay.
Something spiritual, right?
Yeah, something spiritual.
Okay, okay, okay. Look.
J-Just try to
think of it this way.
God's mind is made up
about this. All right?
I mean, you know, call it fate,
call it destiny, whatever.
But it already happened,
it will keep happening,
and it always will happen.
Maybe.
And why don't
we call it fate,
since we're
calling it something?
Maybe--Maybe you're right. Maybe you
guys are exactly right. I don't know.
All I know is this.
For all of my career,
I've been trying
to catch people
after they do
something horrible.
For once in my life,
I'd like to catch somebody before
they do something horrible.
All right?
Can you understand that?
Address is in range.
Two L's.
"Surveilling," two L's.
Since this is such a tremendous
waste of taxpayer money,
the least we could do
is get the spelling right.
That's not necessarily true.
Branching universe theory
holds that you can do...
Oh,
branching universe theory.
Look, hold it.
All right.
No, no, no.
I'll show you.
The traditional
view of time is linear,
like a river flowing from
the past toward the future.
But you can change
the course of a river, right?
Exactly. Introduce a significant enough
event at any point in this river
and you create a new branch,
still flowing toward the future,
but along a different route.
Changed.
Yeah, but that river
is the Mississippi,
and we're lobbing what
amounts to a pebble into it.
That's a very few
tiny ripples in a kind of
big body of water,
don't you think?
Traditionalist.
Say we do create
this new branch.
What happens to the old one?
To--To this one?
Ask the radical.
Well, it might continue
parallel to the new branch,
but most likely
it ceases to exist.
The idea is,
we cease to exist.
All right?
This version of us, anyway.
You know, we never came here.
We didn't meet Doug.
We don't remember
it ever happening.
Well, that's worth
$10 billion right there.
Would've been a lot faster
if you'd written it yourself.
Right. Then I recognize
my own handwriting
and the universe blows up.
We're ready.
All right, third floor,
southwest corner.
That's where we are.
- How'd you get that information?
- Good police work.
That's me. I can hear me.
I don't wanna play games with you.
Where am I?
I'm not playing games.
Yeah, you are.
No, I'm not.
There are protocols... Yeah, you are.
There I am.
Is that Minuti?
There's procedures...
Yep. That's my partner, Larry.
Look, I know how this job works,
you know how this job works.
Jesus, I forgot
all about this part.
All right, let's find a nice, happy
place to push the note onto.
That your desk?
Yeah, that's my...
Okay. Line us up.
When I peg a guy on a hunch,
that's good police work,
not some conspiracy to keep you
out of the loop, all right?
You know what, Doug?
Okay, kid, start pushing.
Expand the wave
past the note.
I can't watch your back
if you're holding out on me.
Why not?
If my memory serves me right,
we better hurry up,
'cause I think
I'm about to leave.
- I need more cowbell.
- I'm trying.
Okay, well, I...
Good!
Just give me a second.
Don't talk to each other.
Expand.
I'm about to leave.
...another partner?
How about that? How about that?
Everybody relax.
Okay. Yeah.
Let's go.
I'm working on it.
Prepare for the final
power surge. Ready?
Have a good vacation.
All right. Go, go, go!
Walk away.
What the hell happened?
I don't know.
It doesn't matter. Doesn't matter.
Pull it back!
Did it go through?
I don't know! I don't know!
Pull it back.
There it is.
It went through.
That's right.
It's through.
- It went through!
- Great.
Whoa, whoa.
No, wait a minute. Hang on.
It ain't great yet.
I don't come back.
Put it down, Larry.
I'm not coming back.
Larry, don't do it.
Follow him.
I'm on him.
All right, look, let's... You know what?
Let's cut away from Minuti.
The bomber's on
his way to the dock.
He's due there any minute.
We'll come back to Minuti when
he gets there, all right?
All right.
Okay, where is he?
Can we, uh, circle it?
We should be able
to see him by now.
That's him.
There he is. All right.
- Holy shit.
- All right.
Move in on him real close.
I want to see his...
That's him.
That's our guy.
At the bridge,
the cemetery, the ATM.
That's our guy.
Shanti, see if you can get
an ID, facial ID on him.
Give me some time.
Okay. All right.
Take your time.
There's your partner.
I see him.
Try to move in
on his truck.
See if we can
get a plate.
No plate.
Get back on him.
Stay on him.
Where's Minuti?
Federal agent!
Turn the engine off!
Tilt back down.
He's still breathing.
What can we do?
I don't know what to do.
He's traveling east.
He's traveling out of range.
Okay, what can we do? Anything?
I don't know,
but if we don't do something
fast, I'm gonna lose this guy.
We're losing the signal.
We have to boost the signal.
We need to chase him
with the goggle rig.
Yeah, well, Gunnars is
a little busy right now,
and he's the only one
who can use it.
Where is it?
What, the rig? It's...
Yeah, the rig.
Where is it?
It's in his--
It's in his Hummer.
Keys in there?
Yeah.
All right, quiet,
everybody. It's him.
Carlin.
Where's he now?
Is he going east?
Yes.
Okay, he's going east,
going up on De Gaulle.
All right, just try to keep him in
sight, and keep feeding me directions.
I'll try and track him
with this goggle rig.
Can he do that?
Yeah, if he can
catch up to the image
and keep him in sight,
that could work.
Hey, how do you
turn this thing on?
There's an on-off button
on the back of the rig.
Okay, I see it.
It's really simple. Wherever you look,
the eyepiece will auto-focus,
and we'll see what you see.
Okay, you're live.
You're on.
Try the goggles.
Hang on, hang on.
He's gone.
Out of range.
What?
Where's he headed?
He's headed toward the I-10.
East or west?
- I don't know.
We lost the signal.
We're blind in here.
I don't know.
All right, hang on.
Oh, shit!
What? What happened?
What happened?
This is trippy.
Doug, look straight ahead.
We've got the window slaved
to your goggles.
We are seeing what you're
seeing four days in the past.
Okay, I got him. I got him.
He's back in range.
He's going west, not east,
on the Crescent City Bridge.
There he is.
That's him. Opposite lane.
I got him.
That's him. That's him.
I got him!
Watch the traffic.
What was that?
I think he hit something.
Doug, you've gotta stay with him.
You're gonna lose him again.
Doug, what's happening?
I got him! I got him.
All right,
all right, all right.
Good.
Now stay with him.
Send paramedics
to the Crescent City Bridge.
Got that?
I lost him.
- I got him! I got him!
- All right. All right.
That's him.
He's headed for
the 10 to the bayou.
I can see him.
He's right in front of me.
Carlin!
What was that?
What the hell was that?
Doug, are you all right?
Doug!
Doug?
I think it's broken.
I can't see anything.
We still have a signal here.
You're still transmitting.
You can see?
We'll talk you through it.
Can you still drive?
Yeah, yeah.
Where is he?
Give us a 360
with the goggle rig.
There! There he is!
Pan the thing around.
Which way?
To your right.
There! There he is!
He's taking
the road to the bayou!
Right there?
The road is blocked.
Take the expressway.
It parallels the road.
Go. Go, go!
See him?
Pan right. Pan right!
You still see him?
He's at the end
of the bridge.
You hear me?
He's at the end of the bridge.
Keep talking to me.
I don't know what else
to tell you.
I feel very, very close
to you right now.
He took the exit
ramp beneath you.
Take the next off-ramp.
Take the next off-ramp!
All right,
I'm on the off-ramp.
Go right,
then double back on yourself.
All right, I got it.
All right,
take another right.
Still see him?
He's heading to the bayou.
Take a left here.
Good, good, good.
Take it easy, Doug.
He's dead ahead of you.
Okay, okay, okay.
He's slowing down, coming to a fence.
Do you see it?
Yeah, I see it.
Doug, if you're gonna leave
the Hummer, take the backpack.
It's the power
source for the rig.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we can hear you.
We can hear you.
All right.
What's he doing now?
He's pulled around
the back of the building.
Looks like a bomb went off.
Really? We--We see
an intact structure here.
No damage?
No, none.
Looks like
a vehicle's inside.
An ambulance.
You see that?
No. Nothing.
See anything?
He's dead ahead of you.
Doug, he's pulling Minuti
out of the car.
Where?
All right, now pan to the right.
Pan to the right.
- More right.
- You got him.
Yeah, he's dragging
him out of the car.
Do you see him?
Yeah.
Yes. Right in front of you.
Boost the audio for me.
Audio boosted.
Turn around.
Turn around behind you.
Larry?
Pan back to the right.
You've got him now.
Where is he?
He's being
dragged on the concrete.
Larry!
What's that sound?
What's the sound?
He's pouring some kind of
accelerant over Agent Minuti.
I think it's the diesel fuel,
like at the ferry.
He's waking up.
Brace yourselves. I think you're
about to witness a murder.
If we hadn't sent him there,
he wouldn't be dead now.
No, he was already dead from the ferry.
We just changed how he died.
We don't know that.
He could've been standing
right next to you,
right until we
sent that note.
You'd need a branching
multiple universe for that to happen.
Oh, come on.
We can't change anything.
We didn't change anything.
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
I'll tell you what we did.
The suspect used a stolen
Blazer to case the dock.
So now he has
a truck big enough
to drive a bomb
onto the ferry.
Now Larry shows up, right?
Larry puts bullet holes
through the windshield.
You want a mask?
No. No, I'm good, thanks.
Larry puts bullet holes
through the windshield,
leaves blood all
over the back seat,
so now our bomber
needs a new truck,
you understand?
Claire's truck.
You hungry?
Yeah, we changed one thing,
but by changing one thing,
we didn't change anything.
What's on TV?
Hey, hey, hey,
we got a name.
- Carroll Oerstadt.
- What?
Who is that?
Owner of that
bait camp Doug found.
Truck registration,
airboat registration, match.
And another property.
5874 Mullie Ave.,
Ninth Ward, New Orleans.
Is this a he or a she?
It's a he. Let's go.
Clear!
Testing,
one, two, three, four.
ATF New Orleans, conducting
interview with Carroll Oerstadt.
You've waived your right
to counsel, right?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
I'm fascinated
with your precision.
It's not very often we see that
level of expertise around here,
and if it's all right with you,
I'd like to use this interview
to educate my colleagues
in law enforcement.
Yes, sir.
Good. Good.
Let's talk about motive.
Why would you use explosives
against the US Navy?
Correction, sir.
US Government.
It says here that you tried
to enlist in the Marines.
You were rejected.
You tried to enlist in the Army,
you were rejected again.
Why do you think
they did that?
Because they
don't want patriots.
The military no longer recognizes
commitment and purpose.
They thought I was overcommitted
and psychologically unstable.
They didn't want to
understand my value.
They understand it now.
I believe so. Yes, sir.
You're ATF, right?
Yes, I am.
Got a smoke?
No, I don't.
But I can get you one.
Would you like one?
Yes.
Okay. Anything you want to
say, just talk into the mike.
A man can always use more
alcohol, tobacco and firearms.
I can think of
one more thing.
It's like the Revolutionary
War, you know what I mean?
"One man's terrorist is another
man's patriot," isn't it?
- Yeah?
- Exactly.
Yeah.
You get it.
This wasn't about revenge.
What was it about?
Destiny.
Destiny?
You've been asking me
about my motives.
Right. Right.
My methods.
They're all connected.
Everything's connected.
Okay. How was Claire
Kuchever connected?
I needed a car.
And that's it?
No, well, something
that couldn't be traced back to me.
Right.
I had one ready till
that cop showed up.
That cop was a federal agent.
Lawrence Minuti.
My partner. You shot him.
He... I was about to burn him
and he was waking up, you know?
I mean, I'm not cruel.
Well, why didn't you "do that"
for Claire Kuchever?
Well, because I needed her
to look like a ferry victim,
and a bullet
would've given it away.
I see.
I went to her house on the
pretense of buying her car.
I took her from behind,
taped her mouth
and threw
a hood over her head.
Then?
I bound her wrists
and her ankles
and I drove her
back to my place.
I loaded
the device into her car
and then I soaked her
with the gasoline.
Jesus.
And?
I think you know
what happened after that.
No, I don't know. I want you to tell me.
You gotta talk.
I mean, you know, come on, hero.
What happened after that?
I'll tell you what
happened after that.
You killed 543 people.
How do you feel about that?
I think that you were a murderer
right from the beginning.
Sometimes a little human
collateral is the cost of freedom.
To me, those people
were war casualties,
but to you,
they're just evidence.
That'll do. We got him.
What'd you say?
You think you know
what's coming?
You don't have a clue.
I know where you're going.
I know you're gonna be away
for a long time. I know that.
This case will
never even go to trial.
No?
Uh-uh.
'Cause I seen what's coming.
Did... Have you? What?
What is in this glass?
You've seen
what's coming, huh?
Okay, what's coming?
You tell me.
I told you earlier
I have a destiny,
a purpose.
Satan reasons like man,
but God thinks of eternity.
Well, I prostrate
myself before a world
that's going to hell
in a handbag,
'cause in all eternity, I am
here and I will be remembered.
That's destiny.
A bomb has a destiny,
a predetermined fate set by
the hand of its creator.
And anyone who tries to alter
that destiny will be destroyed.
Anyone who tries to stop it from
happening will cause it to happen.
And that's what
you don't understand.
We're not here to coexist.
I'm here to win.
So you'd better have some
divine intervention, buddy.
You're gonna need it.
You'd better
have some K-Y.
You're gonna need it.
What am I supposed to do?
We're shutting you down.
What?
Yeah, we got what we need.
The forensics, the suspect,
a confession. We're done.
Sir, perhaps we should continue
and watch the actual crime.
The ferry bombing.
Right. He's right.
I mean, we--we can't just
go on the confession alone.
We need an airtight case.
We need to collect
more evidence.
Well, collecting evidence
would've been fine, Agent Carly.
You took it
a little further than that.
Agent Carlin. Carlin.
My name is Carlin, not Carly.
We had protocols in place.
There's strict protocols.
And then you had to push it,
and now an agent's dead.
Sir, by one theory,
that already happened.
We're done.
Power it down.
Pack it up.
On to the next case.
What about Claire?
What...
Lookit, charging Oerstadt
in the Kuchever murder
is gonna raise
too many questions
about how we
obtained the evidence.
I understand that, sir,
but what about Claire?
Are we just
gonna drop the case?
We got him on
the ferry bombing,
we got him on
killing a federal agent.
That's enough to get him the needle.
I cannot accept that, sir.
Well, you know, I don't give a
rat's ass what you can accept.
She doesn't matter.
He's gonna kill her.
In 12 hours,
he's gonna kill her.
He killed her four days ago.
You were at the funeral.
What's wrong with you?
It had to happen.
I delayed turning in my report
till we caught the guy.
Hey, mission accomplished.
This is a victory, Doug.
Hey. Now, my job
is closure.
Your job is to help
facilitate that closure.
Then you tell me,
what do I tell her father?
We caught the son of a bitch.
We can't save the victims.
It's not our job to make
the relatives feel better.
We lose everything that we care about.
Those are your words.
Doug, it's not your fault
that Claire dies.
Yeah, that's one theory.
Lieutenant Junior
Grade Dianne Kerry.
Martin Kyle.
Commander
Francis Lacey, retired.
Elaine Lacey.
Chief Petty Officer
Darren McAndrews.
Lorraine McAndrews.
Electronics Technician
Lisa Melville.
Chaplain Rabbi
Benjamin Mendelsson.
Denny? It's Doug.
Well, I can't say
I wasn't expecting this call.
Look, you know what happens
if you try this.
We both know
what happens if I don't.
Well, not a lot of
guinea pigs volunteer
to die in the name
of science.
Well, then we have
to make sure
I end up somewhere
besides the morgue.
Can you help me?
I'll see you
when you get here.
Doug?
Do me a favor.
When you finish, turn off the lights.
You do that one more time, you set
off every alarm in the joint.
Can't take it.
Gotta keep the mass
as low as possible.
You gotta take
everything off.
You can keep
your underwear on.
Thank you very much.
Thought you said you didn't
believe in changing the past.
Right. Well, I also
believe in God.
Just don't tell anyone.
I'm gonna tell everybody.
Yeah?
You know, when I open up the
throttle on this thing...
Yeah, I know. EM field, flatline.
I got it.
Thing of it is, no matter
how clever we think we are,
the most probable outcome
of our little experiment
is that four
and a half days ago
you get a call from
the coroner's office.
"Hey, Agent Carlin,
I want you to come down here.
"There's something
you should see."
And next thing you know,
you're standing over a corpse
and it's you.
Well, you can be wrong a million times.
You only gotta be right once.
Besides, I think I'd remember
if that happened, right?
So I gotta face out
toward you?
Yeah, face out.
Just like the note, only bigger.
You ready?
No.
You don't have to do this.
What if I already have?
Right.
Doug?
Hey. Hello?
You okay in there?
Yeah.
You good?
Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
I'm beside myself.
Am I still here?
For now. You ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
All right.
Looking forward to walking
up to you four days ago
and blowing
your mind, though.
Well, if that happens,
maybe you can tell me
what it's like to
meet your younger self.
All right,
I'll let you know.
All right, remember,
the ferry blows
at 10:50 on Fat Tuesday,
okay?
Yeah.
Here we go.
See you yesterday.
God willing.
Good, good.
- You don't have to do this.
- Hello?
Maybe I already have.
- What the hell?
- All right, hold on, everybody.
The reserve generators
should kick in. Nobody move.
That was interesting.
Doctor!
Who the hell is that?
Where'd he come from?
All right, let's get him into Trauma.
Trauma 2, Trauma 2!
This is weird.
Defib.
Clear!
Recharge it again.
Recharge to 300.
Charging.
Clear!
Resume CPR. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
...thirty-four degrees.
Forty-nine was our low
temperature at the airport.
Gonna be at that or just maybe
above that for tonight.
Let me show you why.
Look,
the winds are starting...
...a few of them
come back.
I'm thinking about
getting a tattoo.
Whoa!
I'm a federal agent.
I need your keys.
I need a vehicle.
There's keys
in the truck there.
Which one? Right here?
Put your hands down.
Hands on the table.
Hold your donut. Hands right there.
Water it.
This might be a
metaphor for existence itself.
A fish
struggles instinctively
against an almost
formless antagonist.
The fish is
a largemouth bass.
Here's the news at 8:30.
Federal officials are still
baffled by the massive blackout
that darkened
the entire eastern half
of the country
early this morning.
Hey!
Jesus.
Wait a minute.
Hey, it's okay. Wait a minute!
Listen. Claire!
I'm a federal agent.
Hang on, hang on.
All right, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm a federal agent.
You're safe.
You're all right, okay?
I'm a federal agent.
You're safe.
Look at me. Come here.
He's gone. All right?
Get me out of here!
All right. All right.
It's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Get me out of here.
All right,
let me get your feet.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's all right.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
All right.
How'd you know there'd
be keys in this truck?
That's a good question.
I didn't know.
He's a terrorist?
Yeah.
His name is
Carroll Oerstadt.
I'm a part of a special
surveillance unit.
We've been tracking him.
He's planning on blowing up the
Canal Street Ferry today at 10:50.
So we're going
to the police?
No, it's too complicated.
By the time we get them up to
speed, the ferry will be gone.
We gotta go straight
to the Algiers dock.
I don't think
you're gonna make it.
You're losing
too much blood.
No, I gotta make it.
I only got an hour and 40 minutes
to catch up to this guy.
What if you don't make it?
What happens then?
If I don't make it...
What?
Your house is on the way.
We'll go by your house,
and I'll get cleaned up.
I'll drop you off.
All right?
All right.
Hey, Ginger.
She hates strangers.
You need anything?
You get cleaned up.
I'll take care of this.
You sure?
I could bind that for you.
No, I'm sure.
You go ahead.
I'm gonna need to borrow one of
your boyfriend's jackets, though.
Sure.
Hey, uh, listen.
You shouldn't wear that.
What?
Why don't you put on
a different one?
The blue and white one.
Anything. It's just...
Just trust me.
The victim wore a dress like
that and it wouldn't be good.
Okay.
Trust me.
All right, uh, I--I'll go change.
I'll be right out.
Stop right there!
Don't move!
Don't move.
I'm calling the police.
I am the police.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
No, you're not!
You didn't ask me
any questions.
You didn't take
a statement.
And you knew where my house
was, what's in my closet.
Who are you?
I'm Doug Carlin.
I'm an ATF agent.
I'm part of a special surveillance
unit that's been tracking the man
who was trying to kill you.
How do I know that?
I had a hood over my head.
You could be him.
Just think about it, Claire.
Look at my face.
You scratched the man's face.
Do I have a scratch
on my face?
You scratched him,
didn't you?
Get on the floor.
Now! Get on the floor!
All the way!
ATF New Orleans,
Agent Donnelly.
Yes, is there an Agent Douglas
Carlin working out of that branch?
Yes, there is,
but he's not here right now.
Would you like to
leave a message?
Can you describe
him for me, please?
How tall, skin color.
I don't know. He's 6'3",
black, not bad-looking.
Okay, have him call me back
at 877-504-8423.
Okay, wait.
My phone pad's empty.
All right, got it.
Hello?
Get up.
Are you gonna
tell me the truth?
Are you gonna tell me why you're
here, why this is happening
and none of it makes sense?
None of it.
What if you had
to tell someone
the most important
thing in the world,
but you knew they'd
never believe you?
What would you do?
I'd try.
You never know
what someone might believe.
I don't understand what's...
What's happening.
I gotta hurry up
and get down there.
Why are you the only one
who can stop him?
Well, because I'm the only
one that knows his plan.
I'm the only one that knows
where he's gonna be
and exactly
what he's gonna do.
How do you know that?
I mean, how'd you know
those things about me?
Well,
for the sake of argument,
let's just say that the
government has a special device
that allows me to know what's
gonna happen ahead of time.
Then how come you didn't know I
was gonna pull a gun on you?
I did. No, I didn't.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's good.
One second.
I think that's gonna stay.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's great.
Okay.
All right.
I'm not very good at this.
You're very good.
What's the matter?
Jesus.
I haven't changed a thing.
I gotta go.
And you gotta go with me. Come on.
What?
I thought you said
I was safe now.
I was wrong.
You gotta go with me now.
Right now.
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't answer it.
I'll prove it to you.
That's your friend
Beth calling.
Let the machine pick it up.
She's gonna say,
"Hi, Claire.
It's Beth. Are you there?
"I'm sorry to
call you so early,
"but when you didn't call me
last night I got worried."
Claire? Hi, it's Beth.
Are you there?
I'm sorry to
call you so early,
but you said you were gonna
call me when you got home,
and when you didn't,
I started to get worried.
Beth, is this a joke?
Oh, hey, hey! No.
Like--Like I said, I was just
worried about you, that's all.
I can't talk right now.
Someone's here. I'll call you later.
Claire...
Believe me, the only one you're
gonna be safe with is me.
Okay.
Let's go.
I don't understand.
Why not just call the police and
have them arrest him at the dock?
He'll set the bomb off
right there on the spot.
He can't know
he's been compromised
until it's too late for him
to do anything about it.
He'll set the timer, walk away
on foot, get on his motorcycle
and ride to the Crescent
City Bridge to watch.
Okay, then what?
You defuse the bomb?
Then I defuse the bomb.
There's my truck.
All these people.
There he is.
Where?
You see the military jacket
coming this way?
It's just what you said.
All right, you see those
officers behind you?
Yeah.
When the ferry pulls off,
I want you to tell them
about the bomb, all right?
They'll believe me?
They better believe you.
Come on,
they'll arrest me.
They won't arrest you.
They'll take you
into custody.
You'll be fine.
That's a good thing.
Don't turn around.
Doug...
Be careful.
Your attention, please.
Passengers are not allowed
on the car deck
when the ferry is in motion.
Sir! Sir.
Excuse me, sir, you're gonna
have to move to the upper deck.
Passengers
aren't allowed here.
Okay.
Can't believe it.
They're right on time.
Let's get these boys
to their party.
Mama!
Excuse me, sir? Sir!
There's no passengers allowed
on the car deck during transit.
No passengers allowed, sir.
Let's go! Let's go!
It's destiny, Oerstadt.
Satan reasons like a man,
but God thinks of eternity.
What did you say?
I'm saying it's gonna take a little
divine intervention here, buddy.
I'm coming out.
What'd you say?
I thought you were a patriot.
Oh, I am.
Patriotism
requires sacrifice.
I'm willing to sacrifice.
Yeah? Who? Her? Me?
You're willing to sacrifice
others, but not yourself.
The Tree of Liberty
must be refreshed
with the blood of
patriots and tyrants.
Right.
Sometimes
a little human collateral
is the cost of freedom,
isn't it?
Who are you, Oerstadt?
Who are you?
It's not supposed
to be this way.
You all right?
I killed him.
No, you didn't. I did.
It's 10:48
on Fat Tuesday, Mardi Gras.
Now let's go back
in time to 1964.
We're gonna die.
No, we're not.
...on 105.3 FM,
the heart of New Orleans.
Hit the gas.
Hit the gas!
Put your hands in the air and
step out of the vehicle now!
We get out now,
everybody dies.
You have until
the count of three!
Hit it.
One...
But my daughter's on that ferry.
Please. Please.
Oh, God, my daughter!
Chrissie!
Oh, Chrissie! Chrissie!
It's my mom!
Mom!
Ma'am? We're gonna need you
to stay right here.
Someone's on the way over
to take a statement
and ask you
some questions, okay?
Bobby.
Doug.
How you doing?
All right.
Got a live one over here.
Pulled her out of the drink.
Somehow involved
in all of this.
Okay.
How you doing?
Doug?
That's right.
You okay?
Yeah.
Have we met?
Yeah. Yeah, we have.
It's okay. Come on.
Come on.
You okay?
Yeah.
You sure?
Okay. I'll get you
warmed up.
♪ All right,
don't worry baby
♪ Don't worry baby,
don't worry baby ♪
What is it?
Hmm?
Doug.
What if you had
to tell someone
the most important
thing in the world,
but you knew they'd
never believe you?
I'd try.
No.
♪ Oh what she does to me
♪ When she makes love to me,
and she says
♪ Don't worry baby,
don't worry baby
♪ Don't worry baby
♪ Everything will turn out
all right
♪ Don't worry baby,
don't worry baby
♪ Don't worry baby
♪ Everything will turn out
all right ♪
♪ I've been here before
♪ I'll be back for more
♪ Maybe this time I can stay
♪ Forevermore
♪ Wonder what
the future brings
♪ Fortunetellers
and time machines
♪ I predict what they'll
predict for me
♪ That I'll keep
coming back to you
♪ Coming back to you
♪ I keep coming back to you
♪ Yeah, I'm coming back to you
♪ One day they'll get it right
♪ I will live and I will die
a million times
♪ As long as you are mine
♪ I keep coming back to you
♪ Coming back to you,
I keep coming back to you
♪ Go back and go
right head-over
♪ Again I'll meet you baby
♪ Tomorrow, yesterday
♪ It's impossible to
leave you, baby
♪ Every way and every day,
I'll take you baby
♪ They call it deja vu,
but I'm just in love with you
♪ They call it deja vu
♪ I'm just in love with you
♪ But I'm just
in love with you
♪ In love with you
♪ Forevermore
♪ I'm just in love with you
♪ I'm in love
♪ Forevermore,
I'm just in love with you
♪ I keep coming back to you
♪ Been here before,
keep coming back to you
♪ Coming back to you
♪ Maybe this time I can stay
♪ Over and over and again
♪ I've been here before
♪ I'll be back for more
♪ Maybe this time I can stay