[theme music]
- ♪ I'm goin' down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna have myself a time ♪
- ♪ Friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
- ♪ I'm goin' down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna leave my woes behind ♪
- ♪ Ample parking day
or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor" ♪
- ♪ I'm headin' on down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna see
if I can't unwind ♪
- ♪ [mumbling] ♪
- ♪ Come on down
to South Park ♪
♪ And meet some friends
of mine ♪
[bright music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- How was school today, bud?
- It was fine.
- Look, Stan, I know it's been
really hard for you
the past month,
with us not having a home.
- Yeah, it sucks.
- I've tried to find work,
but there's just not a lot
out there.
And with
the government shutdown,
I can't get my job back
with the USGS.
Times are hard,
and I know we all miss Tegridy.
- I don't miss Tegridy, Dad.
I just hate that our family
is living in a motel.
It's really embarrassing.
- Well, that's what
I need to tell you, Stan.
There's some good news--
we're moving out of the motel.
- Wait, really?
We can live in a house again?
- Well, no, we can't afford
a house, so...
we're moving in
with your grandpa.
- Moving in with Grandpa?
- This is a bunch of bull crap!
First you stick me
in this place,
and then you all come along?
- Pretty nice, huh, guys?
There's a TV, a microwave,
and we have Bingo on Thursdays.
- There has to be somewhere else
we can live.
- Come on, Stan.
You have that space over there
by Grandpa's shit pan.
- You can't make me stay here.
This is completely inhumane.
- That's what I said!
Didn't work.
[lively music]
♪ ♪
[hammers pounding, metal clangs]
- OK, so then over here
is where you're gonna have
the big golden pillars
that you guys wanted.
- Ah, yeah! That's great!
- OK, and then right over here
is where we're gonna put
your dance floor.
- All right!
- Wait, dance floor?
I thought we were
knocking the East Wing down
to make room for the nursery.
- The what?
- The nursery!
You said all this remodeling
was for the baby,
not to make room for more
of your stupid parties.
- Hey, relax, guy!
We can just stick the baby
in the bathroom or something.
- Wow! OK, so obviously I have
no say in this remodel.
- Mr. President, sir.
I'm very sorry, but we need to
speak with you urgently.
It's a matter
of national security.
[dramatic music]
We don't want to frighten you,
Mr. President,
but we've received intelligence
that someone might be trying to
stop your baby from being born.
- What?
Who?
- Hey! Relax, guy!
- We don't know who yet, sir,
but Pam Bondi has been
looking into it.
- That's right, sir,
we won't let any harm
come to the baby of the greatest
president that ever lived.
You are without equal, sir--
- Uh, hey, Pam.
- And we are honored to be--
Pam. Pam, sorry.
You got a little shit
on your nose there.
- Oh, do I?
Did I get it?
- No, it's still there.
- If someone is trying
to harm the baby,
then we must know who.
- Well, there is...
one theory.
[sinister music]
Some people believe that
by demolishing the East Wing,
we may have unleashed
some sort of...wrath.
♪ ♪
- What kind of wrath?
- Vengeful...
wrath.
[thunder booming]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
- What the hell is going on?
I was supposed to be
in Washington.
- There has been a change
in plan, Mr. Thiel.
They are on to us
at the White House.
- But how?
How did they find out?
- Someone must have heard us
talking.
Do you still have the child?
- Yes, he's here.
I have him heavily sedated.
It should last
another six, seven hours.
- [chortling laughter]
[mumbling] Six, seven!
- But I can't keep him here
forever.
- You'll just have to wait
until it is safe.
I think some brownnoser here
is after my job.
- Hey.
Come on in.
You guys can't tell anybody
that I'm living here.
- Stan, you shouldn't be
embarrassed, all right?
Everyone's having a hard time
right now.
- Yeah, everyone's having
a hard time.
And you know what
the problem is?
Nobody's doing anything
about it.
How many weeks has it been now,
dealing with one stupid thing
after another?
The truth is, I think a lot of
people are just afraid to admit
that South Park sucks now.
- South Park sucks now?
- Yeah, everyone knows it.
South Park sucks now.
And it's because of
all this political shit.
We're just getting totally
bogged down in it.
Remember when we
used to do stuff?
Just us guys?
Ever since all this
political crap took over,
it's like--what?
Like--like what happened to us?
Like, Kenny, I haven't even
heard you say anything
in, like, four months.
- [muffled speech]
- You see? That's what I mean!
We don't even know what to say.
South Park's getting ruined,
and all of us Gen Alpha kids
are just sitting here,
watching it happen.
- You're right, dude.
- [muffled] Yeah!
- But what do we do?
- I know exactly what to do.
Hey, guys,
are you sick and tired
of what's happening to our town?
Do you feel like it's broken
and going nowhere?
Then click below
and join our online community
at South Park Sucks Now.
Things are clearly
not right here,
and if you're like us,
you are fed up!
- South Park Sucks Now!
- So please, like and subscribe,
smash the button, upvote--
whatever the hell
you need to do,
because together,
we can make a difference.
[eerie music]
DAN SCAVINO: Mr. President,
we don't want you to be afraid.
Tell us exactly what it is
you think you saw.
♪ ♪
- Ever since I tore down
the East Wing, there's...
this thing
that keeps appearing.
- What kind of thing?
- Sometimes I see it
in a mirror.
Or in the hallway.
PAM BONDI: President Trump,
you are an incredible man.
Whatever this is,
we have your back.
- Uh, Pam. Pam, you got some
shit on your nose again.
- Oh, really?
- Mr. President,
this entity you speak of,
how many times has it appeared?
- It appears more and more
lately.
I-I can't get away from it.
It's everywhere I go.
[music stops]
[whispering]
It's here right now.
In the corner.
[ominous tone]
- I'm pretty sure
that's your wife, sir.
- My wife?
[whispering]
What does it want?
[ominous tone]
- Maybe it's somehow
trying to communicate.
Don't worry, we won't let
anything happen to you.
- Ah!
Where did Pam Bondi go?
- What?
- Pam Bondi! She's gone!
- But she was sitting
right here!
- Pam?
- Where's Pam Bondi?
- I'm right here, sir!
- [gasps] Look, it's back.
- What's back?
- You've got some shit
on your nose again.
- Oh, my God! What is going on?
- That thing!
It's not there anymore.
[ominous tone]
Ah!
[tones chime]
PA: Good morning, seniors.
It's 6:30 a.m.
Rise and shine
for your morning medication.
- Ugh, God, 6:30?
- Yeah, it fucking sucks,
doesn't it?
- Holy shit.
- What?
756,000 likes, you guys.
We just built a massive
online community.
- Wow. I can't believe
how many people agree with us.
- I thought we could get 50 or
60 kids from school to sign up,
but this is incredible.
- All right,
we've got everyone's attention.
So what do we do now?
- What do you mean, dude?
It's obvious.
It's time for phase two.
[gentle music]
Hey, guys, if you've come here,
then you're likely joining
the chorus of voices
that's fed up with the direction
our town is going.
We all want change
in our community.
And now there's an opportunity
to truly make your voices heard.
Introducing the South Park
Sucks Now cryptocurrency coin.
This digital meme token
is your way to be a part
of the fastest-growing community
in America.
This used to be a great town
before all the politics came
and ruined it all.
Get in on our crypto meme coin
with this incredible
presale offer.
Each coin is just $9.95,
but could be worth
ten times that overnight!
- Wait, a meme coin?
- Do you want South Park
to change?
Then order your coin today
at SouthParkSucksNow.com.
Stan Marsh is not
a financial advisor
affiliated with
any financial institution.
Digital assets
are highly volatile
and may involve
significant risk,
including loss of all funds.
Ownership of South Park
Sucks Now Coin
does not represent equity,
profit sharing, or ownership
of any company platform
or project.
Participation is voluntary
and should only be undertaken
by individuals who fully
understand the risks
associated with
block chain assets.
South Park Sucks Now Coin
is not registered with
or regulated by the SEC
or any financial authority.
Please review all disclosures
and consult a licensed financial
advisor before engaging in
digital asset transactions.
[thunder booming]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[scraping]
[shower curtain scrapes]
♪ ♪
[Towelie screaming]
[cabinet squeaks]
- Ahh!
[ominous tone]
Ah, fuck!
Fuck!
- What?
- It's the Woman in the Hat!
- What are you talking about?
- The Woman in the Hat!
She's in the fucking bathroom!
- We've double checked
everything, sir.
All the exterior doors
are locked.
No windows have been breached.
- And yet the president swears
something was
in the room with him.
- Is he going to be all right?
- Pretty shaken.
Pam Bondi is in there now
trying to calm him down
and make him feel better.
PAM BONDI: [screaming]
DAN SCAVINO: Pam?
Oh, my God!
- [groaning]
- Stan, what are we doing?
- What do you mean, dude?
We're trying to change things.
- By selling cryptocurrency?
- What's wrong with trying
to make a little money
while also pointing out the
things wrong with our town?
- [muffled]
Yeah, what's wrong with that?
- I have to do something, Kyle.
I'm nine years old
and I live in a retirement home.
- And you really think
crypto is your way out?
Do you even know anything
about how that stuff works?
- Well, actually, we have
a really strong crypto advisor--
your cousin on the east coast.
- My cousin?
- I'm back!
All right, looks like
we've got a lot of movement
on your coin, boys.
The presale really popped.
We cleared 100 grand in volume
before liquidity even locked.
The token's really got traction.
- And we don't ever have to pay
anything, right?
- Nope, you never pay anything.
You guys created the coin,
so all you do is profit from it.
- See? I told you.
- [muffled speech]
- Now we just need to keep
creating hype
around the South Park Sucks Now
digital coin,
so we need to come up with
things to give people FOMO
and make them ape even harder.
- You guys,
this isn't about a coin.
It's about a movement.
- Oh, that's really good.
- Yeah, yeah, that's perfect.
"This isn't about a coin.
It's about a movement."
Yeah, that's some savvy
Jew Jitsu right there.
- So what kind of time frame
are we looking at
to get our money?
I need it as fast as possible.
- Well, I think we're looking at
a classic rug pull
in just a few days.
Once we pump the coin
high as it'll go,
then I can register for an MSB
with the federal government.
- The federal government?
That sounds hard.
- Oh, no, it's gonna be easy.
The crypto corruption at the
White House is off the chain.
We're gonna screw a lot of
people out of their money, boys.
It's gonna be fantastic.
[thunder booming]
[heavy knocking]
[thunder booms]
- Yes?
- Uh, yes,
we're paranormal investigators.
We've been asked to come
and investigate
the mysterious Woman in the Hat.
- I am Stephen Miller,
Senior Advisor to the President
for Immigration
and Domestic Policy.
[thunder booms]
Won't you...
come in?
PARANORMAL INVESTIGATOR HUSBAND:
Oh, my God, it's incredible.
Subject is showing some kind of
viscous residue on her nose.
- Well, what the fuck is it?
- Sometimes there's
a physical manifestation
of spiritual energy--
a bridge between
the spiritual world and ours.
In this case, it appears to be
some kind of rectoplasm.
- Rectoplasm?
- What is it made of?
- It's unbelievable!
The rectoplasm seems to be 54%
Filet-O-Fish sandwich!
- Oh, my God!
I ate a Filet-O-Fish sandwich
last night!
- Jesus!
- And it's also...
28% Taco Bell.
- Oh, my God!
I ate Taco Bell this morning!
- What does it mean?
- And it's 14% its own cum.
- Oh, my God!
I ate--
[chuckling awkwardly]
Hey! Pam! Deal with them!
ANNOUNCER: This is a Fox News
Super Alert!
- Two paranormal investigators
were indicted today
on federal charges
of falsifying data.
The president said that the
bad people manipulated readings
and reports to make fake news.
The charges were filed
by Attorney General Pam Bondi,
who said that "the President
is a great man,
even if he does
eat his own semen."
In other news,
many people are saying
that South Park sucks now.
The small mountain town
in Colorado
has been a hotbed of political
activity in recent weeks,
and three local Gen Alpha boys
are vowing to put a stop to it.
- OK, we're mooning.
We're mooning...
All right, that's gotta be it.
OK, we're done mooning.
I think we're ready to dump.
[train horn blares]
COUSIN KYLE: OK, sounds good.
I'm on the Acela train
right now.
I should be in DC by 6:30
to meet with Don Jr.
Once I get
White House approval,
we should be able
to do the rug pull.
- I'm out, dude.
- Kyle?
Kyle, wait!
Dude, you can't quit now.
Do you know how much money
we're about to make?
- I thought you were sick of the
way South Park was going, Stan.
- I am!
- So then why are you trying
to engineer a rug pull
in conjunction with
the federal government?
- Bro, it's the world
we live in, OK?
I mean, at least we're being men
and taking some control.
Look at Kenny,
he--he's doing stuff now!
- [muffled]
Yeah, dude, I'm doing stuff!
- I know it sucks to be living
in an old folks home, Stan,
but you can't fix things
if you're only thinking
about yourself.
[thunder booming]
[heavy knocking]
[thunder booms]
- Yes?
- Uh, yes, I'm with the South
Park Sucks Now cryptocurrency.
We're trying to fuck a bunch of
people out of their money.
Is Don Jr. around?
- Ah, yes,
he's been expecting you.
Do come in.
[door squeaks]
- Oh, Jesus, it's a little
drafty in here.
- You'll have to excuse
the conditions.
The master has taken down the
East Wing and unleashed a wrath.
[eerie moaning]
[unintelligible groaning]
- Oh, Jesus! It's a mummy!
- No, no, that's just the head
of the FCC.
He's lost his freedom of speech.
- [mumbles]
- Come. Don Jr. is...
this way.
[thunder booms]
[eerie music]
- Thanks so much for taking
my meeting, Don Jr.
We've got an incredible
crypto opportunity here
and we just need your help
taking a big dump.
- That sounds really great.
There's nothing I like better
than a big crypto dump.
- So sorry I had to bug you
this late in the evening,
but time really is
of the essence here.
[door opens]
- We need everyone to gather
in the dining room.
Immediately.
- In the dining room? Why?
- We are going to have a séance.
It's time to confront
the spirit here.
- The--the spirit? What spirit?
[line ringing]
- [muffled speech]
- Yeah, I can see
the price is going down.
What the hell is he doing?
- [muffled]
He's not answering?
COUSIN KYLE:
Hello, you've reached
Pump and Dump
Crypto Advisors.
Let us know how we can help you
fuck people over.
Just leave a message.
[beep]
- Dude, what is going on?
Our token's value totally peaked
and it's starting to go down.
Whatever approval you have to
get at the White House,
we need it now!
[beep]
God damn it!
- [muffled speech]
- I don't know, Kenny, OK?
Shut up already!
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, Jesus,
this is a little creepy.
Are we having dinner?
I'm allergic to dairy.
- Everyone, please put your
hands on the table.
♪ ♪
I am speaking to the entity
in this house.
- Is this a good time
to talk turkey?
I just need to go over
some quick business.
- We know you are sad.
We know you are...lonely.
But we must ask you
to leave our president alone.
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God,
this is really scary.
PAM BONDI: The President
is a great man,
and he does not deserve
to be tormented like this.
- Pam! Pam!
- Oh! Oh.
Restless spirit,
we only wish to communicate!
[thunder booming]
- Holy shit!
She's right fucking there!
- What is that?
- [moaning]
Deception!
- Boss,
maybe we should stop this.
- No! I wanna hear
what it has to say.
- [moaning]
Epstein!
- Uh, no, no.
You're right. Let's stop this.
- You!
[eerie music]
- What? You?
What did he do?
- He lies!
- Oh, you fucking bitch!
- Corruption!
- She's not possessed!
Pam Bondi's trying to get
my fucking job!
[thunder booms]
- Oh, I can't do this!
- Lies!
- [muttering]
- I gotta get out of here!
♪ ♪
[face screaming]
- Oh, God!
Oh!
♪ ♪
OK! OK! It's all true!
We've been dealing in deception
and lies!
We've all been getting
filthy rich off of crypto!
Oh, Jesus.
We've lied and we've cheated.
Crypto's just a giant money
laundering scheme
for the rich to get richer.
Please don't haunt us anymore!
We're sorry.
We're all very sorry!
ANNOUNCER:
This is a Fox News!
Agh! America!
- A massive crypto fraud has
been exposed at the White House,
and the perpetrator
has been indicted.
A ghostly wrath that was
unleashed in the East Wing
exposed the traitor
at a séance last night.
The traitor is now behind bars
and serving 10 years for fraud.
Charges, of course, were once
again filed by Pam Bondi,
who said, "We will continue
to indict anyone
who says bad stuff
about our amazing president."
[gentle music]
STAN: I'm sorry, Kyle.
I should have listened to you.
♪ ♪
I guess there just no really
going back
to the way things used to be.
- Things will get back, Stan.
I know it's hard to see
right now,
but things will go back
to normal.
And in the meantime,
we just have to make the most
of where we are.
["If I Didn't Care"
by The Ink Spots]
- All right, seniors,
just move with the rhythm now.
♪ ♪
- ♪ If I didn't care ♪
NURSE: Good! Good, seniors.
Nice!
- ♪ More than words can say ♪
♪ If I didn't care ♪
♪ Would I feel this way? ♪
♪ If this isn't love,
then why ♪
[theme music]
♪ ♪