[agent 1] FBI! [agent 2] FBI!
FBI! Get on the floor!
-[indistinct shouting]
-[agent 3] Get out of the bed!
[indistinct shouting continues]
FBI! Don't move!
[speaking Albanian]
[Ray in English] Freeze! [agent 1] Where are you going?
[Ray] Off the bed!
Hands up! Show me your hands! Cuff him!
[woman shrieking]
[agent 4] Hey. Give me your hands.
[man] Take off these cuffs.
I have the right to an attorney.
You have no right here.
Do you understand? You have no right.
[speaking Albanian]
[all cheering]
-You got Mother Teresa.
-[both grunt]
You actually bagged that asshole.
Got his number one and number two also.
And two judges, district police cap...
A freakin' deputy mayor.
This is gonna be
a messy day for City Hall.
Yeah.
The Albanians had to be buying
those guys off with more than tail.
Burgos got their computers,
so we're gonna find their money.
Once we start tracking it,
who knows how far this goes?
Thank you, Wilson Fisk.
He's a gift that's gonna keep on giving.
[door buzzes]
[indistinct chatter]
Snitch!
[yelling]
[grunts]
No! No, don't!
[sobs] No! No! No!
No! [gasping]
-[alarm blaring]
-[guard over PA] All tier two COs,
we have a 10-49 in progress
in the weight room.
All tier two COs,
we have a fight in the weight room.
[Fisk grunts]
[guard 1] Guard! Guard! Guard!
[guard 2] You, up against the wall,
right now! Against the wall!
[theme music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[Maggie] What did you do, Matthew?
Where did you go last night?
-Hey. Don't pull that crap with me.
-[groans]
[Maggie] What happened?
Go away.
[chuckles] I put in way too much work
on you to quit now.
Up. Move your ass.
So you get beat by a guy
who wasn't even trying to hurt you,
and your brilliant next move
is to go out and pick another fight?
Here. Take these.
A word of advice, Mr. Daredevil...
give yourself time to heal,
or you're gonna get yourself killed.
[Matt] You're probably right.
Is that what you wanted?
I have a special gift, too.
I'm impervious to bad attitude.
So you can throw your self-pitying
bullshit at me all day, Murdock,
and I'll still be standing right here.
Pissed off, maybe, but right here.
You're gonna talk to me.
Why did you become a nun?
I heard God's call.
So you feel like being a nun
is what you're meant to be?
Yes.
Very much.
What if you couldn't be one anymore?
If it were taken from you?
Your point being
that if we can't fulfill our calling,
we might be better off as worm food?
-Answer the question.
-[scoffs]
I'll tell you what I wouldn't do.
I wouldn't lose faith.
I'd find some other purpose.
If you can be anything else,
it was never really your calling.
Just tell me, honestly.
If you could no longer be a nun,
wouldn't you grieve?
Of course I would.
Then please...
go away.
I understand what it's like
to feel lost, Matthew.
It happened to me, too, once.
A long time ago,
when I was still a novitiate...
I left the order for a while.
Why?
I was considering a very different life.
It was wonderful and terrifying.
I struggled to know which life
God wanted me to choose.
I prayed. I looked for signs.
In the end,
I just had to do my best to figure it out.
Well, there you go.
That is the difference between us.
I no longer care what God wants.
Oh, right.
Almost forgot.
You've seen his true face now.
[Lantom] Those are some
fancy moves, Matthew.
Sister Dora turned me in, didn't she?
This has to stop.
My Confirmation is in the spring.
I'm supposed to be learning the catechism,
and Sister D
can't even defend original sin.
She is not a theologian.
You already know more about it
than she does, I'm sure.
So I can skip catechism?
No.
Come on.
Sit.
How many fights
have you been in this week?
-[young Matt] How many guys complained?
-[Lantom] None.
'Cause no one wants to admit
they got their butt kicked by a blind kid.
-So you can't prove that I did anything.
-I don't want to, and I don't need to.
It's not about proving anything, Matthew.
Argumentation is a skill.
Being argumentative is a sign.
A sign like a prophecy?
A sign like you're angry, Matthew.
That's a perfectly understandable reaction
to your situation.
But it's not sustainable.
Or maybe it's a sign that Sister Dora
should stick to teaching math.
[scoffs and chuckles]
You're good...
at arguing and deflecting
and denying you're angry to other people.
[sighs] But you're gonna have to deal
with your anger, Matthew.
Find a way to... harness it.
-Or it will destroy you.
-Well, if that's God's plan for me,
then I guess that's how
it's supposed to work out, isn't it?
You know, maybe you don't understand
original sin, after all.
God gave us free will, Matthew.
Adam and Eve were not puppets,
and neither are we.
We make our own choices.
That's one reason we pray,
for help making good ones.
You should try it sometime.
I do pray.
I pray all the time.
I've been praying for years.
God doesn't talk to me.
So that's what this is about?
You feel God is... neglecting you?
Matthew, the burning-bush business
doesn't happen very often,
even in the Bible.
He's usually more subtle than that.
You want to hear God, Matthew,
you have to listen more carefully.
Because he speaks in whispers.
Veggie sub.
-No meat.
-Thanks.
You don't want it.
[chuckles softly] Why not?
When you see the way Ramsey
and Arinori are kissing Hattley's ass,
you're gonna lose your appetite.
They're in her office right now.
Doing what?
Hattley gave you this raid.
But now that it worked,
well, somebody's got to run
Fisk full time.
Right? There he is.
Man of the hour.
You see the client list yet? Holy shit.
-[Ramsey chuckles]
-A moment, ma'am?
Sure, Ray.
Congratulations. Pristine execution.
Glad to hear it, boss. I got a big ask.
You want Fisk detail. I can't.
He's my kill. I get to eat first.
There's a goddamn buffet
in that conference room.
You can't fill up on that?
That's today. Now, what about tomorrow?
Look, we play Fisk right,
there's plenty for everyone for years.
He can give us every criminal organization
on the East Coast.
Hey, Pryor.
Find out how Burgos
is doing on the computers.
Dozens of agents had their shot at Fisk.
None of them got shit. But I did.
We got some big collars out of this, Ray.
I'm gonna make sure D.C. knows about it.
Why do I feel like there's a "but" coming?
Shut the door.
I put you on Fisk detail,
your file is required reading.
You'll be naked. There will be questions.
I've got answers.
I've got a boss, too.
And he's got a hard-on for agents
in financial holes.
I'm sorry.
No. No way.
[Hattley] Easy, Ray.
No. You tell D.C. that none of this
could have happened
without the unexpected connection
between me and Wilson Fisk.
Because that's the truth.
And then none of the other shit
in my file will matter.
Come on, Tammy.
How am I supposed to get out from under?
Okay, he's yours. But you need
to keep him talking, Ray.
I got this.
He better last years.
Because he goes dry, we're both burned.
-[Karen] Hey.
-Hey.
"Rostam Kazemi." Mean anything to you?
-Uh, yeah, he's a real estate developer.
-Mmm-hmm.
Actually, his daughter, Neda,
is the mean one
on the Heiresses of Manhattan.
Not that I watch that kind of crap
or anything, but...
No, of course not.
Anyway, he and his daughter were attacked
outside a restaurant last night.
He's in a coma at Riverbank Hospital,
think it might be a kidnapping attempt.
No, you know what?
I think you should give TJ that story.
He watches her show. He'd love it.
Well, that's-- That's great.
That's nice. I'm giving it to you.
No, I'm in the middle of something here.
-Excuse me?
-It's not done yet,
but I'd like to stick with it
if that's okay.
What?
[sighs]
Uh, yeah, here.
What am I looking at?
Uh... They're reports
of respiratory illnesses
among residents
of a particular city block.
They've spiked.
They're up, like, 45% from last year.
-And which particular block would that be?
-44th and 11th.
-Midland Circle adjacent.
-Karen.
Come on. I know we've done
a lot of pieces on this,
but there are still questions about
that night we don't have answers for.
-You think the answers are in here?
-I don't know. Maybe.
Just give me a couple days.
It's not done yet.
What is it about Midland Circle, Karen?
I mean, it's not just a story, is it?
Look. The work you've done on this,
reporting, the writing...
it's excellent.
It's great. It's some of the best
you've ever done. I'm proud of it.
I'm even maybe a little bit jealous.
But it's done.
[smacks lips] So that's what we do now?
We just drop stories because
some socialite who photographs well
is down at the hospital?
That's a story, too.
And I thought that you might be able
to empathize with a young woman
who's been caught up
in the middle of a family crisis.
It's one thing to work a story, Karen.
It's another thing
to let a story work you.
-End of day tomorrow.
-Okay.
[door buzzes]
How the hell did you let this happen?
Don't try to pin this shit on us.
He's your snitch. [door buzzes]
[door buzzes] You okay?
They said it was superficial.
I find it quite profound.
Don't start.
We're not playing games here.
It's deadly serious for me.
What? Some guy with a shank?
It's not something I fear a great deal.
But we're not dealing
with one person here.
Word is out.
Everyone knows.
Guards and inmates, it seems
they know I'm cooperating with you.
Which you are going to continue to do,
Mr. Fisk.
This was not a one-off.
You want us to help Vanessa
clear herself of criminal charges,
you need to continue
to deliver actionable information.
Do you understand?
[inhales]
I have suddenly become a target
within these walls here.
Do you understand?
I'm helping you to help Vanessa.
I can't do either of those things
if I'm dead.
[indistinct whispering]
-[woman whispering] Please, God...
-If you can help, please just...
[man] Help me get this job.
I've got to keep paying them,
or they'll come for Mindy.
[overlapping indistinct whispering]
[sobs] Please just call her home.
End her suffering, I beg you.
-Her moans, I...
-[man whispering] Give Derek justice.
Please, God,
you know he didn't do this thing.
That lawyer's no damn good,
but you can touch the jury, God.
Help them to see the truth.
[Lantom] Glad to see you up here, Matthew.
I used to listen to people's prayers.
In here and out on the street.
You know, people asking for God's help
or justice or... vengeance sometimes.
See, it's always the same.
"Please, God."
I thought that God
let me hear the prayers...
so that I could answer.
So that's what I did. That's what I was
trying to do, was trying to help people.
But I am not what I was.
Can't do what I used to do.
Give it time.
Whatever your new reality is,
you'll adjust.
When I heard all those prayers,
all those...
suffering people,
I thought it was God's voice.
But I was wrong.
All I ever heard was people in pain.
And all he ever gave any of us was...
silence.
So now you believe your calling
to do what you do was a mistake?
I was deluding myself.
Maybe that's a good thing
to realize, Matthew.
Maybe...
it's time for you to stop.
Oh... [chuckles]
No, Father, uh...
My delusion was thinking
God had anything to do with it.
I'm not as capable as I was, but...
I don't get to choose who I am.
I'm Daredevil.
Not even God can stop that now.
-Excuse me. I'm looking for a dry cleaner.
-Not doing pickups right now.
But we're on 14th Street.
Address is on the side there.
[chuckles] Here's where it gets awkward.
I'm actually looking
for a different place.
I got a whiff
of their delivery van last night.
It didn't smell like this.
Not like chemicals. It was more... herbal.
Kinda grassy, maybe?
Yeah, sure, like that.
I know the place.
[speaking indistinctly]
[Karen] How is he?
You're a journalist, aren't you?
-I've seen your picture in the Bulletin.
-Yeah, it's Karen Page.
Not to be a bitch,
but I don't want this in the papers.
No, you're not a bitch. I get it.
Then go.
I'm sorry. I'm really, really sorry.
But you don't understand.
You think because you don't want this
in the papers, it won't be?
If I don't say anything--
They'll make up things
that sound good to them.
[sighs]
And that's what will get written and what
people will talk about behind your back.
For the next year. The next five years.
For the rest of your life.
You talk like you know what this is.
Maybe I do.
You grow up with paparazzi
on your ass, following you to school?
-No.
-Yeah, I did.
You know what I learned?
I learned that anything I say,
anything at all,
you people will turn it
into whatever you want to, anyway.
I'm not like that.
Yeah. Sure.
Believe it or not, I really do know
what you're going through.
Your father almost got killed?
Nope. But people said
that I killed my brother.
God, I'm sorry.
[Karen sighs]
You know, when Kevin died...
everyone wanted to know what happened.
And I wasn't like you,
not paparazzi or anything, but...
it's a small town.
Stuff kinda gets around on its own.
But since no one did know the story,
they made one up.
It was all bullshit.
If you thought about it for ten seconds,
it didn't even make sense, but...
why should that matter, right?
The problem was...
[sighs]
...once the story got out there, it stuck.
It grew, and it got darker and, um...
meaner.
And the things they said
about my family and about me...
it, um...
sort of tore us apart.
Piece by piece and lie by lie. And, um...
I didn't really know
how to deal with it back then.
Now I guess it's too late.
You're right.
-The truth can't be worse, can it? [sighs]
-[Karen chuckles]
I don't know.
I don't know if the truth
is any better, but...
Well, at least it's real.
[softly] Okay.
Just take your time.
We were at dinner.
We were trying to patch things up,
you know?
We were walking to the car, and...
these two men grabbed my father.
They tried to put him
into this van to kidnap him.
We only got away
because the other guy attacked him.
What other guy?
You said there's another guy?
Yeah. He came out of nowhere.
He had this black mask over his face.
[Tower] You're out of your mind.
Fisk's imprisonment would continue
at a private location
under the constant supervision of the FBI.
That's house incarceration,
usually reserved
for white-collar criminals awaiting trial.
[Hattley] He was shanked
by another inmate hours ago.
Good. He's a cop killer.
That wasn't proven in court.
-[DiMolina] Whose fault was that?
-We put on a good trial.
Five counts under RICO was a giant win.
Which you're about to give away.
You're the district attorney, Mr. Tower.
Think of the long game here.
We can't prosecute everything
Fisk is giving us at the federal level.
It's gonna trickle down.
[Tower] You're trying to buy the NYPD
with collars and me with convictions.
[Hattley] When Fisk's intel leads
to the biggest crime drop in a decade--
-[Tower] The guy is a piece of shit.
-You're right.
Wilson Fisk is a piece of shit.
After every time I'm in the room
with the guy, I want a shower.
But let's talk about the Albanians
for a minute, what they have done.
Four dead NYPD officers,
12 more riding desks with disabilities.
One hundred and seven civilian murders.
And even after five task forces
over seven years,
to the tune of $11 million, we got zero.
Those are some shitty numbers.
But here's another one.
With Fisk's intel, we beheaded
the Albanian syndicate in one day.
One single day.
No loss of life, no injuries, no mayhem.
I mean, look at the take.
We got their documents and data,
and we''re gonna get their money.
Best of all, we bagged corrupt officials
whose protection they were selling.
A lot of cases they've been
interfering with
may finally get somewhere.
Look, none of us like it.
It makes me want to throw up to admit it.
But New York is safer tonight
because of Wilson Fisk.
Now I need a shower.
If we keep him talking,
Fisk will give up others.
This deal will save lives.
Tell me you're not going for this.
[sighs]
-[kids screaming] Uncle Foggy!
-[Foggy exclaims and chuckles]
[groans] Okay, easy, easy.
Left pocket. Left pocket.
You're gonna save them
for after dinner, right?
-[kids chuckle]
-Don't tell your mother! Or my mother.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Hey! Foggy's here!
-[all cheer] Hey!
-Foggy!
Hey there, Counselor.
"How are your briefs holding up?"
[all laughing]
What's up?
Christ, that joke gets old.
[Foggy] Gets old?
Listen, Franklin, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
Hi.
-Try a little. I put cinnamon in it.
-Mmm! Delicious. So good.
Is he worse?
Your father's arthritis
gets a little worse every day.
He's having trouble holding onto things,
especially when he's tired.
I see him with the saws and slicers.
Ma, I'm sorry.
Isn't there anything they can do for it?
There's no cure for getting old, Franklin.
Your father needs to be on a beach,
not slinging meat in Hell's Kitchen.
[sighs] Forty years is enough already.
I know. You got yourself a life.
A good life.
But maybe it's time you came home.
I'm right here when you need me.
Your brother loves this place,
but Theo can't do it alone.
Come help.
Put those brains to work for your family,
not every uptown shithead
that comes into your office.
They're not all shitheads, Ma.
[sighs] I'm not telling you what to do.
You're a grown man. Just think about it.
That's all I'm sayin'.
Okay.
I will. I promise.
Good.
I love you, kid.
Hey! I can smell the candy
from here, Ruthie! Come here.
Where'd you get that? Where'd you
get that? Where'd you get that?
[all laughing]
-Hey, Pop.
-Hey!
-Do you want a glass?
-Damn sure didn't come to chat.
[liquid pouring]
The suits I understand, Foggy, but...
why you drink this expensive
crap is beyond me.
[chuckles]
[both laugh]
You know how proud of you I am, Foggy?
You're a big deal.
-Which is what you always wanted.
-Did I?
[chuckles] Ever since you could talk,
you went around telling people
that you owned the store.
They'd play along with it, too.
-Remember?
-Yeah.
I got it, Pops. I got it.
Yeah.
Sláinte.
Your lawyer almost screwed up
the whole deal.
Those terms guarantee my safety.
Beyoncé has fewer demands.
This way, convict.
[door buzzes]
[sniffs]
You want service, you gotta get in line.
Oh-- Oh.
Come on, come on.
You got a ticket, you just picking up?
-Me?
-Yeah.
Oh, no, I just ran in
'cause your clothes smell so good.
See, I got this real sensitive nose.
I thought--
Yeah, we use a totally organic process,
latest stuff.
Oh, cool. You got a flyer?
Not in Braille.
I-- I got seeing friends.
Here, have a coupon.
[Matt] Thanks, I appreciate it.
-Glad I found you. Really makes my day.
-[man] All right.
[indistinct chatter over police radio]
[clattering]
[man] God damn it.
We must have blown a fuse.
Hello! You!
[groans]
[both grunting]
[gasps]
[panting]
Yeah, I'd like to report an assault.
I didn't see what happened,
but there are a lot of guns here.
Maybe some kind of robbery.
[indistinct chatter]
I don't think I ever said it,
but thank you, Theo,
for taking over the shop.
They wanted it to be you.
[chuckles] Yeah.
For a long time,
I kinda wanted it to be you, too.
-You never said anything.
-What was there to say?
You got a head for other things.
You were always getting the prizes
and scholarships and shit.
Anyway, you can't make a sandwich
to save your ass.
[chuckles softly]
Theo, if we need to figure out--
Knock it off.
Go do what you're good at.
You're livin' the dream.
Am I?
You're shittin' me.
I had this idea
of how things were gonna go.
Matt and I talked a lot
about what we'd do.
Open our own firm. Help people. Get rich.
I was the get rich part.
He was the help people part.
When he was around, I knew who I was.
Now...
Matt was a good guy.
Sláinte.
[exhales]
You can always come back here.
[chuckles] Yeah, great. Thanks.
[panting] Hi.
Sorry, I...
Perfect timing.
Now everyone can stop worrying
about my career choices
and start worrying about
me cheating on Marci. Much better.
-Can I to talk to you?
-What's wrong?
[whispering] I think Matt's alive.
[whispering] So the guy in the mask,
he wasn't in a, you know, devil suit?
No, but he was wearing a black mask.
-So it could be anybody.
-It could also not be anybody.
Hell's Kitchen is ground zero
for vigilantes these days.
Believe me,
I want it to be Matt, too. But he's...
-gone.
-No, no.
-We need to get past that.
-There is no proof of that.
-And until there is--
-You know how I know he's gone?
Because if it was Matt,
if he was really still alive,
he would've reached out to us.
You know how I know that
you don't really believe that?
You keep saying "gone" instead of "dead."
Now, don't you want to take a minute
and just be absolutely sure that's
not your best friend out there somewhere?
I wish it was my best friend.
But it's not. He's dead.
[in normal voice] Karen, come on. Stay.
[sighs]
What? You.
[gasps]
Your father...
he's in a coma.
[Neda] He's alive.
Why did you help us?
The men who did this are in police custody
for another crime.
You head down to the 15th Precinct
right now, you can identify them.
You caught them?
You should go.
Thank God for you.
He didn't help you.
I did.
[Ray] You will be under
the strict supervision of my team.
You will not remove your ankle monitor.
You will not pass beyond
the boundaries shown to you.
You will continue to have
a strictly regulated schedule.
That means eating, sleeping,
shitting, whenever I say.
Do you understand, Mr. Fisk?
I've spent much of my life alone.
And for many years, I pretended
that this was the source of my strength.
I told myself I had free will.
And in that time, I achieved a great deal.
But I was not fulfilled.
I was longing for a connection
that I could imagine
but I could not achieve.
Searching and not finding.
Until Vanessa.
Until I discovered love.
I thought I would explode
with the sense of power
and freedom that she brought me.
That the world lay at my feet.
But then that passed when I discovered
the great lie at the heart of love.
That what I took for true freedom
was precisely the reverse.
You can build a prison of stone and steel,
but you merely present the prisoner
with a challenge.
[police sirens wailing]
Any truly determined man
will find a way out.
But love...
Love is the perfect prison.
Inescapable.
So you see, Agent Nadeem...
I am always in prison,
wherever I go.
And if these things
help me protect Vanessa,
then they are nothing to me.
I will do whatever I must.
[Ray] Go left! Left!
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Nadeem!
[gunshots]
[Fisk grunts]
[indistinct yelling]
[agent] Prepare to fire!
[agent] Grenade!
Stay in the car!
[grunts]
[man whistling]
[man 1 speaking Albanian]
[continues in Albanian]
[breathing heavily]
-[banging on vehicle]
-[man 2 speaking Albanian]
[man 3 speaking Albanian]
[metal cutter whirring]
[gunshot]
-[metal cutter stops]
-[gunshots]
[man 4 speaking Albanian]
[indistinct chatter]
-[gunshot]
-[man grunts]
[man 5 in English] Don't shoot!
Don't shoot! We surrender!
-[gunshots]
-[men grunting]
[Dex] Convict.
Don't move.
[police sirens approaching]
[paramedic 1] Put him in bay 3.
[paramedic 2] Excuse me, sir.
Sorry.
[sign buzzing]
[helicopter whirring]
[ambulance siren wailing]
-[paramedic 3] Multiple GSWs.
-[paramedic 4] First one up...
[agent 1] Goddamn Albanians
killed everyone except Fisk.
[agent 2] Somebody said
he's en route to the safe house.
It's a damn shitshow.
The FBI just let Wilson Fisk
out of prison.