[Opening theme music playing]
[electronic warbling]
- [ominous music playing]
- [owls hooting]
[crows cawing]
[tires screeching]
[hip-hop music playing on radio]
[talking indistinctly]
[man] Totally.
[Bottle clanking]
- [woman] Yeah?
- [Man] Yeah.
- [Woman] Yeah? [laughing]
- [man] Yeah.
[Both kissing, moaning]
[woman grunting]
[both breathing heavily, moaning]
[man grunting rhythmically]
[man] Oh yeah, that's it, right--
[Both grunting rhythmically]
[man laughing] Check it out! [grunting]
[man yelling]
[woman] Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh. Babe!
Oh my God!
[Woman screaming]
- [zombies moaning]
- [both] No, no, no!
- [Woman screaming]
- [zombies chomping]
[suspenseful music playing]
[zombies groaning]
[music fades]
[classical orchestral music playing]
[woman] Yeah. I found this apartment.
It's a lot cheaper, but I don't know
if I want to live in the Valley.
- Huh? Ew! He's all yours!
- [Zombies groaning]
- [zombies chomping]
- [woman screaming]
[zombies rasping]
[classical music intensifying]
[car horn honking]
[man screaming]
[man two] What the fuck?
[People screaming]
[ambulance siren wailing]
[tires screeching]
[crashing]
[zombies groaning]
[woman struggling]
- [woman screaming]
- [zombies groaning]
[woman yelling]
[train horn blaring]
[zombies groaning]
- [zombies groaning]
- [people screaming]
- [car honking]
- [man yelling]
- [organ music playing]
- [zombie chomping]
[dramatic music playing]
[zombies groaning]
[indistinct chattering]
[martial artists grunting]
[guns firing]
[officer] No, no, no!
Hold your fire! Hold your--
[Guns firing]
[man] Fuck 'em up, man. Fuck 'em up!
- [Man two] Shoot 'em in the dick!
- [Man] Oh shit!
[Shouting indistinctly]
[man screaming]
[intense music playing]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[people screaming]
- [phone ringing]
- [man] Hello.
Zombies? Not in our country!
[Indistinct chattering over radio]
[bombs whistling]
[dramatic music playing]
- [choir vocalizing intensely]
- [guns firing]
- [man talking indistinctly]
- [gun firing]
[man cackling]
[zombies groaning]
[trolley bell ringing]
[guns firing]
[vehicles screeching]
[firing ceases]
[zombies groaning]
[large zombies snarling]
[zombies snarling]
- [phone ringing]
- [man] Oh man! What are we gonna do?
- [Guns firing]
- [panicked chattering]
- [man] Oh, fuck it!
- [Button clicking]
[alarm blaring]
[man] Suck on these!
[Alarm blaring]
[penguins warbling]
- [intense music continues]
- [choir vocalizing intensely]
[flatulence]
[music stops]
[electronic warbling]
[closing theme music playing]
[music fades]