If you really, really,
really, really love me
Then you really, really, really
Gotta show me
Don't whine when I put it
in your booty
Or if I'm up all night
Playin' Call of Duty
Never hassle me because I'm unemployed
If I sleep all day, don't get annoyed...
I know I'm the last person
that you wanna hear from
- right now, Chris, and I can't...
- [imitates farting]
I can't apologize enough for...
- [blows raspberry]
- [laughs]
I know that you're mad,
but from the bottom of my heart...
[both blow raspberry]
I really am sorry. I'm just trying to...
What were you gonna say?
- I was saying...
- [blows raspberry]
I am just trying to apologize.
And I just thought
you were my fucking friend!
Set me up to take the fall
and then you try to send me to prison,
and you think
"I'm sorry" is gonna cut it?
- Cut it! [blows raspberry]
- Dude, we're off it.
We are?
I'm getting so many moral judgments
from people who regularly kill people.
I don't kill people
for nothing, all right?
- When my brother died, I made a vow.
- Right, the vow.
- Anyone I'd kill, I'd kill for peace.
- Oh, Jesus.
So unlike Keith, no one would
ever die for no reason again.
Well, that's fucking stupid.
So you're gonna make it
so that death isn't meaningless anymore?
Go fuck yourself.
I read your file, Chris.
It was an accident. You were a child.
Don't forgive me, that's fine.
But stop letting that shit
define who you are.
Are you guys serious right now?
We just had a really sick time
murdering Peacemaker's dad.
Then all these hilarious fart jokes.
Just like an all-time classic run
with my best friend,
my second best friend, Eagly,
my fifth best friend, Adebayo.
And now you guys are ruining it.
[theme song playing]
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
- Get it on
- Get it on top
Make a move extreme
- Make a pose
- Shortcut to your dreams
I float straight to the stars
On that flying thing
- Getting high
- Getting brave
- Getting snowblind, game
- Set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon
In a world beyond
Got a beat, got a heat
On a phony string
Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it?
Baby you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
[Eagly screeching]
Mom, there are way more butterflies
than we thought,
and the whole team is injured.
So I was thinking, like, maybe
you could call in the Justice League.
No, I'm not kidding.
Can you believe Amanda Waller's
her fucking mother?
- Yes.
- Do we have time to wait for backup?
No, they're teleporting
the creature out of here.
Mom, they're teleporting
This is our only chance to stop them,
then we're back to square fucking one.
Then we're back to square one.
All right.
All right. I will tell her.
Fine. My mom says you're in charge,
and Economos and I should stay back
in case anything goes wrong.
Copy, Mom.
Yes, ma'am.
[growling]
How much longer is it going to be?
The teleporter is nearly installed
and functional.
As soon as it is,
they'll move her to the eastern base.
Quickly, please.
Forces could arrive any minute,
and without her we're all dead.
If Waller is your mom,
why is your last name Adebayo?
I took my wife's name.
[Vigilante] Doesn't that make you
the girl in the relationship?
We're both girls
in the relationship, Adrian.
That's what being a lesbian is.
[Leota] Hey, Peacemaker.
What do these do?
This is Underwater World.
Allows you to breathe underwater.
Okay. Not sure how we can use that.
This one's Scabies for All.
Upon activation, it gives everybody
in one-mile radius scabies,
except, of course,
the wearer of the helmet.
This one is Anti-Gravity.
Allows you to float.
Aimlessly?
No, I carry a tiny hand fan
to guide me.
This is Sonic Boom.
That's the one I used
to stop the rocker chick.
How many booms
does it produce on one charge?
I don't know. Three. Maybe four.
- This one, we should just throw away.
- What is it?
Human Torpedo.
Just aim your head at whatever
you wanna destroy and you become a...
- Human torpedo.
- Sweet.
Yeah. Only sweet if you wanna risk
shattering every bone in your body.
That's just a prototype.
Okay, so let's say
I wanna get this Sonic Boom helmet
onto the top of that barn over there
without being seen.
Just the helmet itself?
No, I'm gonna put a walkie in it
and activate it from here.
And then maybe you can put on
Activate Anti-Gravity
and just float it over there.
- Okay, I forgot my tiny hand fan...
- Uh, guys...
But, you know,
once in the jungles of Cambodia,
I used two oversized palm fronds...
Guys!
Fuck! Deactivate anti-gravity!
Deactivate anti-gravity!
- Did you say "activate anti-gravity"?
- No.
- Maybe. I don't know.
- You can't fucking say that shit.
I didn't know
it was that voice sensitive.
Fuck it. No big deal. I didn't just kill
the only man who knows how to make it.
You did just kill the only man
who knows how to make it.
I know, bro! I was being sarcastic.
Well, if you're gonna be sarcastic,
you should really warn people
so there's no confusion.
Okay, so how do we get
the Sonic Boom helmet over to the barn?
Well, we can shoot
a fishing line over the barn
from one of these trees here
and just let the helmet slide down.
- Like Green Arrow?
- No, not like Green Arrow.
That dude goes to Brony Conventions
dressed in the back half
of Twilight Sparkle
with a four-inch wide butthole
drilled in the costume.
Maybe it's so he can breathe properly.
You actually believe that shit?
He has an insane story
for every single superhero.
No, I actually heard
that's true about Green Arrow,
but that's the first thing
he's said that's real.
- And Aquaman fucking fish?
- Well, yeah, obviously.
It doesn't even matter.
We don't have any bows.
But we do have a team member
capable of flight.
[screeches]
Get the fuck out.
That's right. Good. Okay.
I need you to take that helmet
and drop it on top of that barn.
No way can an eagle understand
what you're saying.
Oh, Eagly is no ordinary eagle.
[chuckles]
No.
Eagly, take it.
No, Eagly, just take the helmet.
Take it. Take it.
[screeches]
I know you don't like her.
The mean blonde woman
has nothing to do with this.
- No, no.
- Eagly, take the helmet.
- No, take the helmet.
- Take the helmet.
- Eagly, take the helmet.
Eagly, take the helmet.
Good, Eagly, good. Good boy.
You got it.
Go to the barn. Go the barn.
Shit.
I knew there was no way he knew
what you were talking about.
Peacemaker is a great guy
in almost every way,
but his biggest flaw is that he commonly
overestimates Eagly's abilities.
Okay, they could be teleporting
this cow at any minute.
We need to fan out
and look for the helmet.
[sighs]
Easy. Easy.
[snarls]
Do you see anything over there?
I saw a squirrel
a couple of seconds ago. Ants.
No, dude. I'm talking about the helmet.
Well, then you should be more specific.
We're looking for a helmet.
Why do I care if you saw ants?
Because the circle of life, bro.
What do ants have to do
with the circle of life?
They're one of the most
important parts of it.
How are ants a more important part
of the circle of life than, like, fish?
- Is that a serious question?
- What?
There are shitloads of ants.
How many fish are there?
I don't know, but probably
as many as there are ants.
[laughs] Not in one place
at the same time, dude.
Okay, I'm as confused as fuck
by this conversation.
Yeah, well, welcome to the fucking club.
Oh, fuck.
So... [sighs] Why'd you change your mind
and decide to come?
I saw an eagle hug a human,
so I thought maybe it was a sign.
- To risk your life?
- Yep.
Why wasn't it a sign to, like,
run in the opposite direction?
Fuck.
We are never gonna find
this dumb fucking hat.
You thought you could lose me
by killing me, boy?
I'm in your head.
I'm the reason you kill
and the reason you can't sleep at night.
My body may be gone,
but the rest of me is right here,
and I ain't going nowhere.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Getting my poison blowgun, fucko.
Why don't you just go
for your piece, cumstain?
You're metaphorical, douchewad.
My gun's real.
I don't want the butterflies to hear.
I almost tricked you, fuck nugget!
You didn't trick shit,
you ballsack-looking fuck.
I immediately went for my blowgun.
I didn't think for a second
of going for my gun.
[blows]
How do you like that, huh?
Thanks for coming back, ghost,
so I can kill you all over again.
Smith... what are you doing?
Nothing.
Holy shit.
Whoa.
I need you to do something else for me.
Are you fucking kidding me?
The only way for us
to get the helmet inside of the barn
is by one of us going in undercover.
They're gonna notice Adebayo and me
with these injuries.
Cool. I'll do it.
You can't do it, man.
Goff knows what we look like.
I'll wear a funny nose.
John, you're the only one.
I don't even wanna be here.
And why are these wet?
- I washed them in the creek.
- Why?
One of the things
us warriors seldom talk about
is how often people shit themselves
when they die.
It's a touch of gray
in the white cloud of kicking ass.
So now you want me to risk my life
while wearing diarrhea pants?
Hey, nobody said anything
about diarrhea. I said it was shit.
- Was it diarrhea?
- Yes, it was.
John, you can do this.
Just act like they act.
Don't show any expression.
- Yeah, like Harcourt.
- Eat my dick, Schwarze-never.
They're aliens.
Do they even speak English?
They retain the memories
of the bodies they've taken over,
so they seem to primarily use English
when communicating.
Fuck. Fine.
- Can you look away?
- Happily.
- John, you copy?
- Yes, copy.
Don't look back.
They're everywhere.
This is fucking stupid.
Remain calm.
Head towards the barn
like you know what you're doing.
- Relax your face.
- Shut up. I know.
Hey.
Fuck.
Where you going?
I'm going inside.
Why?
Fuck.
Because of this bag.
What the fuck does that mean?
Okay. Just wanted to make sure.
[gagging]
How the fuck did that work?
[vomiting]
[retches, coughs]
[retching] Sorry.
I have a real bad gag reflex.
Oh, shit. I'm good.
- I'm good.
- Would you shut the fuck up?
[sniffles, sighs]
I can't do this.
John, you're already inside.
You're doing great.
Please. What's there?
[exhales, coughs]
Uh...
Stairs...
and an elevator.
An elevator's noisy.
Head down the stairwell.
Yeah, of course.
You head down the fucking stairwell.
John, don't creep.
You have to act normal,
like you're supposed to be there.
We just need you to place
the helmet down as low as possible.
[creature growling]
Oh, no.
John?
John, you copy?
[growling]
Uh-uh.
Fuck it.
No more kaijus. No more kaijus.
- Fuck this.
- John, do you copy?
[Economos panting]
Jesus fucking Christ.
What the fuck is that?
Cow, my ass.
It's a motherfucking caterpillar
the size of the Empire State Building.
Get ready.
- We need to get the fuck out of here.
- Hey!
[Economos] Fuck.
The man you've taken over...
why did he do that to his beard?
Do what?
Why did the color his beard
all strange like that?
He thought it made him look
younger and more handsome.
He never had a girlfriend,
so he thought dyeing his beard
might help.
But he was also lazy
and busy with his job,
and he wouldn't dye his roots regularly.
And when he did,
he uses the cheapest brand
because he was incredibly underpaid.
Mostly, though,
he never thought anybody noticed...
until recently,
when one guy said it to him
all the time.
[suspenseful music playing]
Humans can be really pathetic.
Yeah.
Fine, I dye my beard, all right?
We all know it.
I guess I learned my lesson.
L'Oréal probably is worth
the extra few bucks.
Hey! That guy just put this down here.
- Fuck. Do it now! Do it!
- Activate sonic...
What the fuck?
- How'd that even happen?
- My hands are sweaty.
No, get the fuck off me!
Activate sonic boom.
No.
Wait.
- Now.
- Activate sonic boom.
Fuck. Oh, God, fuck. Fuck.
Activate sonic boom.
No.
[growling]
[grunts]
Activate sonic boom.
Well, that's it for the charges.
No.
[growling continues]
[gun cocking]
- Look, I can help.
- We need you to stay here, Ads.
If something happens to us,
you're the only hope.
What the fuck am I?
What's the plan, man?
Let's go kill a cow.
[theme song playing]
[snarls]
[grunting]
- [grunting]
- [butterfly screeches]
Oh, God!
[grunting]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
Chris, go kill the cow!
We'll hold them off here!
Don't fuck with my BFF.
[groans softly]
Oh, darn it.
- Oh, my God.
- What's happening? I can't see.
Harcourt is down.
What?
What the fuck do we do?
Wait. What are you doing?
No, no, Adebayo, you can't.
You'll get hurt.
You can't do this. Hey,
what makes you think you can do this?
Because I'm made for this shit.
Dude, God damn it.
You're gonna get hurt.
Fuck.
What the fuck? What the fuck?
Oh, my God! Oh, shit!
What the fuck?
[Adebayo screaming]
- [butterfly screeching]
- [Harcourt grunts]
[coughs, gasps]
Stay with me.
Help... Chris.
I have to get you out of here.
- Go.
- And do what?
[Economos] Leota. [coughs]
[grunts]
Be with me, baby Jesus.
Okay.
Oh...
[breathing heavily]
[machine beeping]
Oh.
[grunts]
- Goff?
- Yeah.
[both grunting]
[Adebayo grunting]
Activate human torpedo!
Adebayo, no!
[screaming]
[grunts]
Ugh, Jesus,
I told her not to use that one.
Listen to me.
I have no reason to hurt you.
Stop fighting.
Follow me.
[creature growling]
[coughs, whimpers]
[growling]
Holy cow.
It is.
All right, you found him.
I need three sets of hands
to teleport her away from here.
Come again?
See that switch?
I need you to flip that while Locke
and I work these two stations
to teleport the cow
to our cavern in Maine.
Why the fuck would I help you?
Because I know that
once I tell you the truth
like I did with Judomaster,
you'll join us.
Murn told us the truth already.
You've murdered innocent people
all over the country
by taking them over
in your dipshit quest for power.
We're not doing this for power.
We're doing it because we took a vow.
[crying]
[groans, coughs]
Our kind traveled here from a planet
that had become unlivable.
Your planet had the habitat we needed.
Water to drink and air to breathe.
Your food couldn't sustain us, but...
That's why we brought her.
The cow would help
the last of our people
survive for another 100 years.
But not long after we arrived,
we realized the people of Earth
were on the exact same trajectory
as our people had been.
Ignoring science
in favor of populist leaders
who tell you that the floods
and the fires and the disease
are unrelated to your own actions.
Valuing profit over survival.
Treating minor inconveniences
as assaults on your freedom.
And so we made a vow to do
anything we could to change your future.
We made a vow
to make the choices for you
that you were incapable
of making on your own
to save your people and your world,
no matter how many lives it cost us.
Murn disagreed with our methods.
He didn't think we had the right
to impose our will.
But you're one of us, Christopher Smith.
Please, God.
[groaning]
I'll do whatever you want me to do...
for peace.
Thank you for feeding me
and talking to me
and showing me kindness.
I see who you are
and I see your character.
I tried telling you yesterday
in the jar.
The peace sign.
Please... fulfill your calling.
Be the Peacemaker.
Join us in saving your planet.
What do you say?
Activate human torpedo.
What?
[Adebayo screaming]
[growling]
Sorry, Goff.
[growls]
What the fuck?
Ugh! Fucking disgusting! Fuck!
[spits, coughs]
[groans]
Oh.
Thank you.
Hey, guys, what's up?
You're late, you fucking dickheads.
Go fuck another fish, asshole.
I'm so fucking sick of that rumor.
It's... not a rumor.
Fuck you, Barry.
[triumphant music playing]
Let's go.
Dude, you're shot.
You gotta be admitted.
I'm fine, seriously.
All I need is a good nap.
Did you hear all that stuff Goff said?
Yep.
Did I just...
kill the world?
Maybe.
Or maybe you just gave us
a chance to make our own choices
instead of our bug overlords.
Why did you choose not to help them?
Because of your proto-fascist
libertarian idea of freedom?
Because I knew they'd hurt you
and the others if I did.
I'm sorry I betrayed you.
I know.
[breathes sharply]
Where are you going?
To do the right thing.
Ads?
Don't tell V, but...
After Eagly,
you're my BFF.
Well you know my game
Dirty like my name
And you're an angel
You're perfection in every way
Say I'm a bad man...
[microphone feedback]
Yes, that does mean
Christopher Smith never wrote any diary.
Both the Peacemaker
and the costumed crime fighter Vigilante
were working in a deep cover operation
for the US government
called Project Butterfly.
This is all part of a black ops program
known as Task Force X,
where convicted criminals
are undertaking
dangerous missions for the United States
in exchange
for time off their sentences.
It's been running for years
out of Belle Reve Prison
under the command of a...
of a woman named Amanda Waller...
What the fuck?
Who happens to be my mother.
Now I'm calling for an immediate
investigation into these inhumane...
- Mr. Smith?
- ...abuses of power.
...darkness into light
But I want you to know
That no matter how this goes
Are you listening?
Tell me are you listening?
I heard you've been out there for days.
Every time I made you wait
Every time you lied awake
And you swore my name for my bad mistake
Every time I lie to you
I wish I would have told the truth
For all those times
I apologize to you
To you
Oh every time I kiss your lips
It drives me crazy
Beautiful
Yeah
Every time I come home late
Every time I made you wait
Every time you lied awake
And you swore my name
For my bad mistake yeah
Every time I lie to you
I wish I would have told the truth
For all those times
I apologize
I apologize to you
Fucking... Go, go, go!
Fuck!
- Whoa!
- [Vigilante laughs]
Fuck!
- Whoa!
[both laughing]
Every time I come home late
Every time I made you wait
Every time you lied awake
And you swore my name
For my bad mistake yeah
Every time I lie to you
I wish I would have told the truth
For all those times
I apologize
- For all those times
- [Eagly screeches]
I apologize to you
To you
To you yeah yeah
To you yeah
To you
To you, yeah
[Eagly screeches]
Down down that beat to the floor
You can't kill my rock 'n roll
I wanna go out
I wanna go out tonight
Need to see the ones I like
No hard times just pure delight
I call you up, what's on your mind?
Why can't you come?
Let's not waste more time
Down down that beat to the floor
What we are living for
Don't be a whiny bore
You can't kill my rock 'n roll
Down down for rock 'n roll
If you're gonna be sarcastic,
you should really warn people
so there's no confusion.
What?
For instance, like,
I'm about to be sarcastic, okay?
- Okay.
- You're not fat at all. See?
Why are you all so obsessed
with my physical appearance?
Sarcasm, I haven't noticed
you eating way more corn chips
than any one human being should eat,
and I'm not worried
that you're gonna die.
- But I am worried that you're gonna die.
- Thanks.