[Peacemaker reading]
[Waller] This is Christopher Smith,
known as Peacemaker.
His father was a soldier
who trained his son
how to kill from the moment he was born.
You fail to follow my orders
and I detonate the explosive device
in the base of your skull.
Your mission is to destroy
every trace of Project Starfish.
I cherish peace with all my heart.
[groaning]
I don't care how many men, women
and children I need to kill to get it.
- Who are you going to show that to?
- Press. People deserve to know.
- [gun cocking]
- I can't let you do that, Colonel.
Miss Waller charged me with making sure
those records don't leave this building.
[groans]
[straining]
Peacemaker. What a joke.
[grunts]
Project Starfish.
It's headed towards the city,
and I think it wants to feed
on as many people as it can.
Not our problem.
We've achieved the objective.
[Waller] What are you doing,
Task Force X?
Turn around now, god damn it.
This is your last motherfucking warning!
- [grunts]
- [body thuds]
Task Force X.
Your clearest path is Calle Agüero.
[female doctor] You're shot
and a building falls on you.
And all you have to replace
is the clavicle?
You're the luckiest man alive.
- Can I ask you something, Doc?
- Sure.
Can you maybe up the contrast
of the x-ray a little more
to show the definition of my muscles.
This makes me look like
one of those guys
who works out only thinking about bulk.
I put a lot of time
in my small muscle groups
and according to this,
it was just wasted effort.
It's not for your Tinder profile, Chris.
You've healed well, but you're still
gonna have to take it easy.
Try to avoid lifting your right elbow
above your shoulder.
Sure.
So, as long as you agree
to keep up with the physical therapy,
I'm discharging you.
So I can leave?
Go home. Enjoy life.
Psst.
Jamil?
I don't have any weed on me, man.
- That was a one-time thing.
- It's not that, man.
Doctor said I was free to go.
Congratulations?
Jamil, you cool?
What does that mean?
Dude, can I trust you?
- No.
- No?
- I don't know you, man.
- Dude, I really need some man to trust.
Don't trust me, man.
We smoked weed together, man.
I was in a fucking wheelchair.
I can't pretend like
that wasn't a nice moment,
but that doesn't make me trustworthy.
- I ain't trustworthy worth shit.
- What?
Why do you think
I'm mopping floors, bro?
I went to MIT.
I don't like the responsibility.
- You went to MIT?
- Oh, yeah.
What the fuck you doing here?
That's my fucking point, man.
Why aren't you listening to me?
Fine. Fuck it. Don't be trustworthy.
Just let me ask you a question
and don't tell anybody about, okay?
I would never betray a secret.
It is the opposite
of everything you've been saying.
Truth is, I'm supposed to be in prison.
- For what?
- Superhero shit.
[laughing]
- You're a superhero?
- Yeah.
You're kind of bulky
to be a superhero, right?
- Bulky? what the fuck you mean bulky?
- All superheroes have a gymnast body.
They're ready to go.
- I'm ready to go.
- What superhero are you?
- Peacemaker.
- Get out of here, motherfucker.
- You're a fan?
- There's no superhero called Peacemaker.
- Dude, I'm fucking famous.
- Not that famous. Aquaman. He's famous.
- Fuck Aquaman.
- No, man.
- Don't say that. Why say that?
- He bangs chicks. Good for him.
He fucks dudes.
Got no problem with that.
He starts fucking fish?
That's taking it a step too far.
- Aquaman fucks fish?
- Yeah.
I don't believe it.
[scoffs] A guy on Twitter
works for the aquarium.
Said for 50 bucks,
he brings him in the back
- so he can have his way with a sturgeon.
- I refuse to believe that.
And I refuse to believe that
@PepeTheFrog89
is lying to me for no reason.
Fine. If you're a superhero,
what were you in prison for?
Integrity.
I made a vow to have peace,
no matter how many people
I have to kill to get it.
- Oh! Peacemaker.
- Yes!
- You're that racist superhero.
- No.
You only kill minorities, man.
I killed a fair amount
of white people too.
The ratio is suspect
is all I have to say.
- If somebody is committing a crime...
- Yes.
...am I supposed to control
what their ethnicity is?
No. But you need to watch white people
as closely as you watch people of color
so you see more of them
committing crime.
Fine. That's... That's a good point.
I will trust white people less
in the future
and kill a higher percentage of them.
Are you satisfied?
Yes, thank you.
- Now, what do you need?
- Doctor said, I was free to go.
So technically
I should go back to prison.
What I need to know is on the DL,
is there anybody out there
looking for me?
Not that I heard of, man.
No cops outside? Nothing?
I ain't seen no cops.
I'm thinking, I can just go?
Why not?
[scoffs] Guy's a total douchebag.
Go. Drive.
Yes! [grunts]
[theme song playing]
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
- Get it on
- Get it on top
Make a move extreme
- Make a pose
- Shortcut to your dreams
Float straight to the stars
on that flying thing
- Getting high
- Getting brave
- Getting snowblind, game
- Set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon
In a world beyond
Get a beat, got a heat
On a phony string
Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
I thought I was going
to be like James Bond now.
- We made it.
- [sighs]
Oh, yes.
- Does this look like James Bond to you?
- Come on.
Man, I want champagne in a bathtub
and some Octopussys and shit.
Okay, girl, you better not be getting
any "Octopussys" while we're up here.
What is an octopussy anyway?
Uh, that's who Maud Adams played
in the movie.
Okay, so she had eight pussies?
[laughs] As far as I know,
she only had one pussy.
- That's just her name.
- Okay.
This might be a good time
for me to bring up...
I've been thinking if we have a kid,
I'd like to name her Octopussy.
- [laughing] Is that so? Really?
- That's so.
- And if it's a boy, Sharknado.
- Okay,
Well, I hope then that it's a boy,
because I don't think
my parents would be too happy
with a granddaughter named Octopussy.
- Really?
- Yeah.
'Cause I think Lois and Chuck
would love that.
[laughs]
- What's wrong?
- Just worried.
This job of yours,
it might be dangerous or...
They got me filing papers
and making reservations.
Hope it stays that way.
Keeya. This is just a pay check.
It's just for now.
I know that I'm not made for this shit.
I'll save up a little
and we'll go back home.
- Okay.
- You promise?
- I got you.
I got you back.
I gotta go.
- Right now?
- Yeah.
- Okay, love you.
- Love you too.
[sighs]
- [driver] Here?
- Yeah.
[clears throat]
- So...
- So what?
And this, uh, it's Corto Maltese money.
I have no idea how much it is.
Come on.
You look like a scratch lottery guy.
Make a game with it,
take it to the bank.
See how much it's worth.
Maybe it's 50 cents,
but maybe it's a million bucks.
It ain't a million bucks.
What's in the bag?
[dogs barking]
[sighs]
[groaning]
[grunts]
Dad.
Fuck.
[beeps]
Yo, man. It's Vigilante. What up?
Uh, I was wondering if you wanted
to go out on a team up tonight.
Peacemaker. It's your BFF,
Vigilante here. What's going on, man?
Uh, what do you say we go
cruise some crimes and bitches?
whichever comes first.
BFF stands for best friends for...
P, it's V. Are you
watching this game, dude? It is so...
Dude, I realized in the last message,
I called you P and me V
as if you were a penis
and I was a vagina, like,
definitely, it was not my intention.
Peacemaker. It's Vigilante.
I just got the scoop on a big
heroin shipment coming in tonight.
- Let's go down there...
- Don't be saying that shit
- on my phone, man. What the fuck!
- ...and blow those
- motherfuckers' head up!
- [beeps]
[sighs]
- [gun cocking]
- Stay where you are, Smith.
- [twigs breaking]
Fuck.
Fuck. I knew it was fucking too good
to be true.
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
My life fucking sucks.
Ugh, fuck it.
I'm... I'm good. I'm fucking...
I'm good.
Fuck!
You only served four years
of your 30-year sentence.
I mean, you thought we were just
gonna let you go scot-free?
Yeah, I killed Rick Flag for you people.
No one ever told you to kill Flag.
Waller said do whatever I had to do
to make sure
those Project Starfish files
didn't get out.
I made the only choice I could.
Funny for you how often the only choice
in killing people coincides.
- What the fuck is he doing?
- I have low blood sugar, okay,
so I'm dizzy.
You showed you were loyal.
You're a born killer with expertise
in every weapon known to human kind.
And you've had experience
in black ops around the globe,
so I'm giving you the chance
to stay out of prison and work for me.
- And you are?
- Name's Murn.
Clemson Murn?
That's right.
I report directly to Amanda Waller.
This is Harcourt who you may know
from Waller's team at Belle Reve.
She'll be your handler in the field.
John Economos, who you may also know
as tech and tactics.
Hey, dude, you're eating four-year-old
olives out of my fucking fridge.
[chokes]
And this is our new recruit,
Leota Adebayo.
Which means she'll be doing
most everything else.
Glad to be here.
Ready to kick some ass, sir.
And really looking forward to getting
to know all of you.
Even you, Peacemaker.
[stuttering] Even though you're not
the best guy in the world.
And Economos, you seem like,
you're very easy to talk to, so.
- I look forward to working with you.
- [laughs]
Harcourt, I feel like
because we're the only women here,
we have to have each other's back.
Anything you need, I got you.
And Mr. Murn,
I have to say
your outfits are really dapper.
I'm really excited to be here.
And I promise,
you're not gonna regret this.
I know inside my mind,
I'm not supposed to be giving a speech,
but sometimes my mouth
just does what it wants, so...
Close mouth and bite my tongue
right now.
Not gonna talk again.
I'm done talking.
What's the op?
Domestic situation,
known as Project Butterfly.
As I recall, you guys aren't
particularly creative
with case file names.
Project Starfish
was a giant walking starfish.
So what, am I fighting
a Mothra right now?
[John snickers]
I am?
Fighting a Mothra?
What the fuck do I fight a Mothra for?
That's not what it is.
- Can I get a jetpack?
- No.
How the fuck am I
supposed to fight a Mothra
- without a jetpack?
- It's not a Mothra.
Still, my desire for jetpack remains
because you got me all excited about it.
We need you to do contract work.
- Kill people.
- Bad people.
- Whom we call "Butterfly."
- [sighs] What if I say no?
- You'll have to return to Belle Reve.
- What's to keep me from splitting?
Still have that bomb in your head
to track you with and if that fails,
we'll blow you the hell up.
We'll meet you for dinner tonight.
7:30 at...
- Where is it?
- Fennel Fields on Manchester Road
and the mozzarella sticks are dope.
Enjoy my food, Dye-Beard.
- [scoffs] It's not dyed.
- Yeah, sure.
Hard-edged two-tone grey
magic marker brown.
- That's natural.
- [laughing] No.
I'll be there. I just gotta
swing by my dad's and get Eagly.
Who's Eagly?
Don't you do your research?
He's my sidekick.
Welcome to the church of rock and roll
Hey!
- You that Peacemaker guy?
- Yeah.
- Evil supervillain?
- Not a supervillain.
That's a misconception. I'm superhero.
- [laughs] Batman is a superhero.
- Yeah?
Joe Blaggadashiocentro should send
for us to do work in his fucking garden.
Joe who?
Point is just 'cause some other
dumb motherfuckers out there
with shears clipping roses
doesn't mean you aren't. Huh?
If you're gonna make up a person,
why make up a person
with such a long name?
I'm so sorry.
I don't spend all my fucking time
thinking of realistic sounding
last names.
You wriggly old fuck!
Hey, Dad.
Fuck you.
[man on TV]...below their lying,
liberal human faces,
lurk extraterrestrial beings
who want nothing other
than our civilization to fail!
They are among us.
I got enough tension
to got to have you chatting up
- my fruity neighbors.
- The guy was talking to me.
He's being a total nad.
Got out of prison.
You don't say.
It's been kind of rough go for me
really, Dad. I was...
laid up in the hospital
for, like, five months.
Somebody shot me
and a building had fell on me.
You let somebody shoot you?
It's not like I invited them
to come shoot me, Dad.
Pathetic.
[sighs]
- New lamp?
- Huh?
The lamp, is it new?
No, it's three months old.
Been in prison for four years.
Doesn't make it all newer.
You know, I asked you to cancel
my phone service. It was still on.
I've been paying for service for years
because you forgot.
Oh, it's my fault now you fucked up
and went to prison.
- That's not what I'm saying.
- Then what are you saying?
It's my service. I got no money.
Jesus Christ, you're a fucking pussy.
- You've been taking Eagly out?
- Yeah.
Where is he?
[screeches]
Eagly.
[continues screeching]
Who's a good boy?
Yeah. Who's Daddy's boy?
[laughing] Dad, look how excited he is.
Dad, he's just awesome, right?
Oh, my God. He's... He's hugging me.
He's hugging me.
This is fucking amazing.
Dad, grab my phone. I don't wanna move.
Dad?
[metal clanging]
You think it makes this noise
all the time?
Yeah. I don't know.
Hey, new girl. Get your shit off there.
Damn.
This is the only desk with sun.
Take the one in the middle.
I don't know what you did
to piss off Amanda Waller,
but she's definitely fucking me
and John with this gig.
What agency
did you get transferred from?
Fucking you how?
We helped Task Force X
during Project Starfish
and this is her way
of getting back at us.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Hey, new girl's
an expert over here, John.
Well, she's entitled to her opinion.
- Thank you.
- Her stupid fucking opinion.
Oh, sweet. We have a piano.
That's useful for black ops.
This is the worst HQ of all time.
[clanging continues]
You guys hear that, right?
It's not just me.
- We hear what?
- The fucking pipe...
Nice gaslighting.
[chuckles]
You'll get a kick out of this, Dad.
The guy
I was working with, Bloodsport...
Big, tough motherfucker.
Mercenary. All this weapons and shit.
We find out he's got a rat phobia,
and not just... Not just any phobia.
I mean, like pure terror,
screaming like a little girl.
And this other member of the team,
Ratcatcher, she controls rats.
Dad, Dad, you know
how he got the phobia?
Of course, I don't fucking know
how he got it.
He was tortured.
His own father tortured him
by locking him in a crate for 24 hours
with nothing but starving rats.
[both laugh]
Right?
He had these horrible acne scars.
- Scars!
- Yeah, but they aren't.
They were rat bites!
For when the rats would gnaw
on his flesh when he was a little kid.
It's funny, right?
[coughs]
Dad?
I'll... I'll get water.
[continues coughing]
Here, here, here.
- This fag that was afraid of the rats...
- Yeah.
...please, God, don't tell me
he was the one who shot you.
[screeches]
You know, a lot of what happened
at Corto Maltese is confidential.
How did my fucking sperm...
grow into a nancy boy like you?
Look, I just came by to get Eagly
and see if you had
another helmet for me.
This one has full body force field...
and this has Sonic blast capabilities.
You need to breathe underwater,
then this is one for you.
And... this one has X-ray vision.
I didn't make these things
while you were in prison.
These are all from before.
I know.
I never gave you a second thought
while you're in there.
Fine.
Just tell me
which one you think is best.
I hesitate giving you any helmet.
As big a simp as you turned out to be.
But what the fuck!
If you can do some good work
and maybe take out a couple of commies
and Blacks, a papist
or kike or something,
better than sitting
in this fucking closet.
Dad, that's not my thing. Um...
I do what I do to stop criminals,
not a specific...
[sarcastically] Yeah, sure.
I forgot to close the balcony door
and when I came home,
my living room was full of pigeons.
Are you kidding me?
No, there was, like, ten of them
and they shit all over my couch.
No, this guy...
[laughs] Did this dipshit really show up
in full cosplay mode?
This is the guy Waller's giving us?
I told you she's fucking us.
She's not fucking us.
Is that an eagle in his back seat?
She's fucking us.
Hi, sir, welcome in.
I'm with them.
Can I just grab a menu, please?
Thank you.
Hey, scooch.
Why are you in your costume?
Costume? This is a uniform,
and it's brand-new.
So, I got to stretch it out,
make it more comfortable
before we're go on a mission.
Maybe I'm stupid, but why would you
even want to wear that on a mission?
A bright red shirt and white pants
aren't exactly conducive
to lurking in the shadows.
People see these uniform,
it strikes fear in their hearts.
What people? The other people
at the Village People try outs?
- [laughs]
- Why's there a bald eagle in your car?
That's Eagly.
You guys ordered without me?
- Eagly is your pet eagle?
- Yeah.
Is your dog named Doggy?
- All right.
- You have a daughter named Daughtery?
Jealous of a guy's pet eagle much?
[chuckles]
Hey, sweet cheeks.
Can you take my order real quick?
Hi, sure thing. What can I get you?
I'll have mixed green salad
and we'll do the garlic zoodles.
- Zoodles. Good choice.
- Thank you.
Good choice.
Zoodle are zucchini noodles.
"Sweet cheeks." Seriously, dude?
She had cherubic cheeks.
It's a compliment.
Sweet cheeks is your butt.
- No, it's not.
- It is.
It's like calling somebody,
I don't know, "sugar tits."
It's totally inappropriate.
Her tits are way too big for sugar tits.
Sugar tits are like smaller,
perkier tits like... yours.
Technically, I think
you may have sugar tits, too,
but, somehow,
that also feels inappropriate.
All right, Peacemaker, that's enough.
You don't have to be happy
with this detail,
but you do have to treat
your fellow soldiers with respect.
Yeah, I heard plenty of stories
about how you treat people
with respect, Murn. Plenty.
Why is that busboy staring at you?
I think that's my friend,
Gut Chase's younger brother.
He has mental issues.
Thank you. Just the old shell game.
- Take this home and study it.
- What is it?
It's the dossier on the first target.
U.S. Senator?
Don't look at it here.
Take our word for it.
The man's a serious threat
to the safety of American citizens.
Oh, my God. Could you at least
take your helmet off?
You're gonna get dressing all over it.
Dressing is easy to get off this helmet,
than a human lip.
That's a fucking fact.
We're in a dressing getting off contest
right now, dye-beard.
Okay, I don't dye my beard.
I've always had unusually colored hair.
Smith, just...
Fine. Fuck.
Are you always
going to be this difficult?
Yup.
Fuck, yeah! Peacemaker's back, baby.
Twerk it and twerk it
Get my little tushy out
It's my famous butt dance
My butt dance, my butt dance
It's my famous...
Hey, man. What's up?
What's up, Adrian?
Hey, the reason I'm excited is normal.
I just found out
this girl that I'm seeing...
she's pregnant, you know.
You got a girlfriend?
Yeah. Her name is Sharon Osborne.
Not...
Not the one that you may know,
she's a different one.
Why are you always trying to get me
to set you up with my cousin, then?
Well, I wouldn't... I wouldn't say,
like, girlfriend, you know.
And you're happy she's pregnant.
Yeah.
Because we are going to have
an abortion.
- Well, yeah, good luck.
- Thank you. Yeah.
Hey, you're invited if you...
I don't wanna come
to your abortion, man.
That's cool.
[grunts]
Peacemaker, baby.
And this. Hey, boy.
You learned to drive now?
You drive us home? Yeah.
He's friendly?
Oh, yeah.
I love animals.
Yeah, Eagly is amazing.
Hey.
Hey, bud.
Shit, man, I thought you said
it was friendly.
I thought you meant friendly to me.
Yeah, I know it's friendly to you.
I saw you pet it.
You know, he was so happy
to see me today,
he wraps his wings around me
and hugged me.
- An eagle hugged you?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I call bullshit on that.
You don't wanna believe in miracles.
That's on you.
You're the new girl?
Yeah, but I know my shit.
Don't worry about that.
I've done a lot of, you know,
notable things.
That's super vague.
Yeah, 'cause if I told you anymore,
I'd have to, you know...
[imitates gunshot]
Kill me?
Yeah.
- [both laugh]
- That's...
Oh, you hubbed up?
What?
Married, yeah.
That's cool.
I'm into old fashioned stuff, too,
you know.
Hummel figurines and capital punishment,
and Garbage Pail Kids and stuff,
you know.
Hey, what you mean when you said
you heard stories about Mr. Murn?
I know he's a mercenary.
I know he killed a lot of people,
not always for the right side.
I know I don't trust his ass.
Well, good night, Smith.
Good night, Eversmall.
It's Adebayo.
Adebayo.
Although, I do appreciate the confidence
with which you said something so wrong.
It's my thing.
That and having a big dick.
Yep, information I had no need for.
No, I'm... I'm serious.
It's too big, actually.
- It causes people pain.
- Okay.
Kids in junior high,
they called me "Chimp Arm."
Good night, sweet cheeks.
Sweet cheeks.
It wasn't inappropriate, was it, Eagly?
[Eagly screeches]
Baby woke me up this morning
She said "Hey man, we are through"
She said
"If you ain't gonna go to heaven with me
Then I ain't goin' to hell with you"
That's alright now baby
Just one last thing on my mind
I'm just trying to find a place
In a world gone mean and blind
So I say
Come on, Come on, come on, fuck yeah!
Come on, come on, come on
Fuck yeah!
[horns honking, tires screeching]
I said come on, come on, come on
Fuck yeah!
Come on, come on, come on!
Oh, yeah!
She's a babe.
Hey, Goldilocks.
Can I ask you a question?
As long as it's a question about
how to cure rotting fish breath, sure.
Fuck you, bitch!
I'm in love, yeah, yeah...
At least every minute or two...
Easy, buddy.
Until the next time a girl walks by
I think I love her too
Hey!
I can't help myself
- Crazy coincidence, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, this is uncanny.
- Right?
- What can I get you?
- I'll just have the same.
So?
- Harcourt, right?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
- What's your first name?
- Why?
Just curious. I mean...
You know, you don't have to call me
Peacemaker. You can call me Chris.
I'll call you Peacemaker,
you call me Harcourt.
How's that?
Okay.
Fuck, you kidding me? She said what?
- Just trying to say...
- Hey!
...it doesn't always
have to be about work.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
What the fuck did you say to my friend,
you ugly fucking...
[groans]
Jesus fuckling! [groans]
What was that next word?
- You ugly fucking what?
- Oh, God.
[groans]
Any of the rest of you
want to finish it for him?
[continues groaning]
Summertime Girls
You make my whole world go around
What were you saying?
That's so fucking hot.
I clocked you driving by
and then making a U-turn
to follow me in here.
[chuckling] Come on!
The way you say it,
makes it sound all stalkery.
No, the way that you did it
made it stalkery.
I just described it.
Look...
I have no interest in you
other than your ability to fight for us.
Just because you're handsome
doesn't mean
you're not a piece of shit murderer.
You think I'm handsome?
Oh, my God.
Please, fuck off.
Okay, look, I... I've been in prison
the last four years, okay?
I haven't been with anyone.
I haven't been with any woman
in a long time.
I'm not asking for emotional connection
here. I'm just asking for fun.
Genital-to-genital contact.
No touching above here.
No, fuck, it's got to be here.
I got to touch your boobs, sorry.
Just trying to,
I don't know, relief some of the stress
that's been building up over the years.
Cool and I'm just trying
to fucking have a beer,
but whether
it's those douchebags or you,
I guess that's just something
that I can't have in my life
because I don't know, I wear makeup.
You know what?
Go fuck yourself, Chris.
I feel your desire
As the moonlight lingers in the sky
I'm walking through fire
Can't you hear me when I cry
One night of passion
One night of hunger
And my attraction is getting stronger
I need to feel you, I need to hold you
I can't deny
'Cause my heart...
Freedom!
...is screaming out your name
[Waller] How's the team?
Okay, I guess.
Murn, I hear, is not such a great guy.
I don't care about
the quality of the knife
as long as the blade is sharp.
- John seems okay.
- He's pliable.
Harcourt is hard.
Barbie is ambitious. Watch out for her.
Shouldn't we just loop them in
on the whole plan?
No.
You're my eyes and ears, Leota,
while you're there.
And the only one I trust
with the big picture.
Did my forger get you the diary?
This goofy shit? Yeah.
Hide it in his trailer, the first chance
you get, somewhere he won't find it.
How's Peacemaker?
[scoffs]
Yeah, he's his own thing.
- Sexist.
- Yeah.
Probably racist.
- Oh, you know who his father is.
- Oh, yeah.
But there's something else
about him that's...
What?
...sad.
Empathy... in this business,
Leota, that will get you killed.
Yeah, well, it doesn't
really matter, does it?
I appreciate the work,
but after this job is done,
Keeya and I will be back on our feet
and I'll find a job I actually like.
Sure.
Ignore your God-given natural talent.
Yeah, I don't think so.
I'm not like these people.
All right.
I have an early morning.
- Night, baby girl.
- Night, Mom.
Well, they're still trying to
pull you in, huh?
Always.
Cool.
Oh, this... This is my jam.
You know, this is back
when men were real men
'cause they weren't afraid to be women.
None of this auto-tuned robots dry up
in the passes for music bullshit, right?
No way.
Quireboys?
Watched these guys when I was a kid.
God! I go to all the shows
when they came through Evergreen.
I went to see herjust this morning
To see how the child might be
She sat there smokin' all my cigarettes
At a table
Set for three
I could've cried
I could've cried...
When she said
I don't love you any more
Hey, I gotta thank you for tonight.
I was having a crazy fucked up day,
but when I was in your pussy back there,
I felt...
I don't know, fucking hope.
That sounds stupid, I just...
Maybe it's the big man
in the sky's way of saying,
"Chris, there's something more
for you out there.
You and Eagly.
Other than all this rancid shit
life's thrown you so far."
So I went and seen my friends
I tried to turn to them for help
But all that any of them said
You gotta look out for yourself
Fuck them!
I could've cried
I could've cried...
When she said
I don't love you anymore
I was slain and shown the door
[screams]
[groans]
Hey!
Please don't look to me for help
All the pain is with yourself
All the blame is with yourself
What the fuck?
[yells]
[grunts]
[groans]
You're all I ever wanted
All I ever needed
- [bones crack]
- Every time I see your face
Reminds me baby of what we had
I get so lonely
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
All our lives I've been down
Always seemed in emptiness
I say my prayers every night
But even God don't care less
Oh, yeah
[groans]
I could've cried
Fuck!
When she said
I don't love you anymore
I was slain and shown the door
Ain't no room here anymore
[yells]
[groans]
[sighs] Take it easy, Doc said.
[snarls]
[sniffs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[screeches]
[music intensifies]
[snarls]
Activate sonic boom!
[tires screech]
[pants]
[Eagly screeches]
[chuckles softly]
[screeches]
Thanks, Eagly.
You're not a lady
You're a love bomb baby
Love bomb baby, come n' blow me away
Can't get enough of your
Sweet, sweet lovin'
[screeches gently]
Keep it coming, oh, baby, fire away
Ah, ha-ah, oh, yeah
[sirens approaching]
Well I've been waiting so long
For a girl like you
A time bomb ready to blow
I know it can't be wrong
'Cause, baby, when I get you home
You're not a lady
You're a love bomb baby
Love bomb baby, come n' blow me away
Can't get enough of your
Sweet, sweet lovin'
Keep it coming, oh, baby, fire away
Love bomb baby, love bomb baby
Ah, ha-ah, oh, yeah
You're everything I need
You're dangerous
You're blue eyed dynamite
Sussssister TNT
You got the kinda love I need tonight
You're not a lady
You're a love bomb baby
Love bomb baby, come n' blow me away
Can't get enough of your
Sweet, sweet lovin'
Keep it coming, oh, baby, fire away
Love bomb baby, love bomb baby
Ah, ha-ah, oh, yeah
Direct hit, target destroyed
This one will give you scabies.
Gave me scab... Why would I want scabies?
Challenge yourself?
Every man should have scabies
once in his life.
Okay.