[grunts]
What?
What the fuck is Project Butterfly?
Well, we got a situation here.
- What?
- I hooked up with a chick.
And I'm not saying that
to make you jealous.
I'm saying it
because she was a meta-human freak
that threw me around the room
like an angry kid
with his little sister's
Cabbage Patch doll.
Oh, fuck!
Where is she now?
She spilled gumbo in the parking lot.
I need a new ride. I blew up my car.
Are you running?
I'm going back
to get my shit in her apartment.
Oh, shit! All right, I'm on my way.
I haven't given you the address.
I can track you
through the chip in your head.
Wait. You can't see me jerk off
or anything, can you?
It's inside of your fucking skull.
How could we...
I don't know. Technology is a beast.
Hey, Harcourt,
you want to see me rub one out,
all you got to do is ask.
Focus.
Pervert. Get your shit
and get out of there.
All right,
I'll meet you outside, somehow.
- [screeches]
- [sirens approaching]
Fuck!
New girl, you're driving.
Peacemaker just killed a damn butterfly.
[theme song playing]
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it?
- Get it on
- Get it on top
Make a move extreme
- Make a pose
- Shortcut to your dreams
Float straight to the stars
on that flying thing
- Getting high
- Getting brave
- Getting snowblind, game
- Set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon
In a world beyond
Get a beat, got a heat
On a phony string
Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
Baby you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
Baby you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
[screeches]
[siren wailing]
Where the fuck are my socks!
God damn it, Dad!
Oh, yeah, yeah
Fuck yeah.
You have him on the tracker?
[Harcourt] Yeah. Looks like
he's still inside the apartment.
We're almost there.
[Murn] Okay, get him out of there.
Harcourt,
I don't think I need to remind you
how important this operation is.
I've got it handled.
Don't worry, I'm almost there.
You know, in your room,
what you have in there,
that's not safe.
- What?
- You had someone in your room.
- Is it against regulations?
- I didn't say that.
- What are you doing?
- This op is off the books.
We don't have regulations,
but it's not safe, is it?
For her, I mean.
- I don't know.
- It's not.
- What are you doing?
- Watch the road.
I also have dogs.
- Okay.
- Do you think they're safe?
- Are they big dogs?
- No, they're pretty small,
but one of them, Emerson,
he likes to wear these little outfits.
Do you think that's gonna make him
a bigger target?
Jesus Christ!
[tires screeching]
[horn honking]
Almost hit that bitch.
Peacemaker's vehicle is at the scene.
Can you change the name
on the registration?
- Yep.
- Good.
[Song] What the hell?
The report said an explosion.
How'd the possum stay intact?
[sighs] I hope this isn't some
cape shit.
We've got enough trouble with that
maniac vigilante running around.
She said, "Tell me, son
What's your kind of thing?"
Shit!
I go whoo, ooh, hoo, yeah
Whoo, ooh, hoo, oh yeah
What's this?
Pizza?
Officer, put that down.
- Why?
- Because I think it's a face.
A what?
A face, a human face.
Back up, the medical examiners
are on their way, Detective.
[Emilia] Could you move
any fucking slower?
[Leota] I'm trying to be sneaky.
[Emilia] Oh, shit!
Can you believe
this idiot fucked a butterfly?
I mean, the man's been in prison
for four years.
There's not much
I'd believe he wouldn't fuck.
A bowl of oatmeal,
grapefruit,
some yogurt.
I'm hungry.
Look, I know you don't believe me,
but Emerson,
he really does like to wear clothes.
If you don't put him in something new
in the morning,
he'll just whine until you do.
Do you pet the dog
when he looks cute in these clothes?
I guess.
He doesn't want to wear the clothes.
He's just willing to humiliate himself
for your love.
I think he just likes looking smart.
Where the fuck is he?
Emerson?
- He's at home.
- Not the fucking dog. Peacemaker.
I used to love her
but she turned me away
She couldn't take me for another day
What is that, a cat?
Super neat.
I see cookies in my future.
[laughs]
Must have.
Love her once
then she'll love you twice
She got a hold of my dirty device
I go whoo, oooh, hoo, yeah
Whoo, oooh, hoo
Oh, yeah
What?
What the fuck
are you still doing in there?
I told you, I'm getting important shit.
Well, there too many cops
outside the front door,
so you're gonna need to find
another way out.
You see Eagly out there at all?
Your eagle?
Yeah. Could you, uh, could you
look for him? Is he out there?
No, man. I'm not gonna fucking
look for your eagle.
Harcourt, just do me a solid.
Just roll down the window,
stick your hand outside
and then crinkle a bag.
He'll think you have chips,
he'll come right out to you.
Why are you feeding him chips?
Is that somebody in the window up there?
Fuck!
[Song] What was that on his head?
[Emilia] Really?
You didn't fucking trust me?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Is there any other way
out of this building?
Just the front door here
and another on the side.
Okay, you two, with us.
You two, cover that side door.
There's no exit
on the back of the building,
so see if you can get to a balcony
on the second floor and jump.
"Jump"?
Go around back. Go around back.
[exhales deeply]
- Fifth floor, right?
- Yep.
[elevator dings]
Yeah.
[singing] Gonna catch a bad guy
[vocalizing hesitantly]
Damn! My heart is beating.
Is your heart beating?
No, my heart stopped beating.
[Song] You said four or five?
- You see that?
- Yeah.
Hey! Hey, stop right there!
[police officer] Song, just saw someone
going from the fifth floor to the sixth.
Was he wearing something on his head?
Well, that I couldn't see.
Head up onto the sixth floor then,
we'll check out
this apartment down here.
Hey, man, what's up?
Is Freddie there?
Freddie who?
Freddie... [mumbles]
No, there's no one...
No, you guys are doing
Chardonnay and charcuterie, right?
I saw it on the evite.
You guys sent me a...
Pondor... Flinder...
Tinder... Grindr...
Fuck!
Shit!
What are you doing?
Pick those up.
Knock on doors.
Fuck, man. Please, pick them up.
Okay, okay, okay.
Evan, what is going on?
This guy broke in, call the cops.
You call the cops.
Baby, he has a knife on me.
You're helping him.
Hey, hey. Shh, both of you.
- Well, thank you, sir.
- Yeah, no problem.
[indistinct police chatter]
I don't think anyone's in there.
All right, Peggy, remember,
we didn't get an answer from that one.
He's obviously a professional.
Look how he's dressed, Amber.
Okay.
I'm gonna need a rope, twine.
Why?
Unfortunately, I have to tie you up.
Okay. Okay, listen, I just want to
talk to you straight, bro.
Like one human being to another.
I will die of claustrophobia
if I get tied up, so...
Yeah, sure.
- [scoffs]
- Oh, fucking shit! I'm so sorry.
- It's clear.
- He's gotta be upstairs then. Come on.
- That's the best I can...
- Thank you, man. Thanks.
I found this.
That'll work.
I used to really love Cinderella.
Yeah. Tom Keifer and the boys
are the perfect mix of blues and metal.
Fuck yeah.
Yeah.
I appreciate that.
Thank you, ma'am. I'm sorry to wake you.
That's the only apartment
that didn't answer.
It doesn't hurt too much, does it?
No, not at all.
Nice negligee.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Evan says it makes me look fat.
You have better PJs.
That's all I ever said.
I don't see how that could be.
Geez, dude.
Thank you.
It's nice to be appreciated.
- Are you fucking kidding me, Amber?
- What?
Are you seriously trying to get him
to fuck you right now?
What? No, I just said
it was nice, god damn it!
And we also seem to have
a lot in common.
Like what?
We both love Cinderella.
Seven years,
not once have you mentioned Cinderella.
What? I talk about Cinderella
at least once a week, Evan.
You just never fucking hear me
because you're always going on
about Coldplay
and Foster the fucking People!
You're going to put down
my musical taste now?
How fucking low are you?
"Pumped Up Kicks," Evan?
Do you know what that song is about?
Murder! You are a murderer!
You are murdering my spirit!
Yeah? How do you think my spirit feels
when you're trying to fuck
this really cool, handsome guy
right in front of me?
I am not trying to fuck him.
But you know what, Evan?
Oh, my God. Maybe I will.
Who knows what's gonna
fucking happen, right?
Because I'm tied up, I'm helpless.
That means anything
can fucking happen, right?
I mean, seriously, who fucking knows?
- [Evan] You... [muffled speaking]
- [knock on door]
Evergreen Police.
Open the door or we'll break it in.
Fuck.
Evergreen Police.
[Evan laughs]
Asshole!
There he is.
[grunts]
- Fuck!
- Ow!
Oh, thank God!
[coughs]
Hey, hey.
[grunting]
Ooh!
Wow!
[sirens approaching]
Damn it.
- Come on.
- Where is he?
He jumped.
My wife is a dick!
You're a fucking dick!
[Amber] Because you don't have one!
Detective Song, this is Captain Miele.
Do you copy?
Copy, Captain.
I've arrived with back up.
Have you located the suspect?
They're saying he jumped off
the rear of the building, Captain.
You, come with me, back of the building.
[officer] Let's go.
[grunts]
[groans]
God damn it!
Fuck.
What do we do now?
Wait here.
Listen, I can help.
I'm stellar with weapons in combat.
Cool your jets, Jason Bourne.
Just be ready to take off
when we get back to the car.
Being a wheelman is also dope.
I got you.
[grunting]
[groans]
You, on the roof,
stop right there.
[groans]
Evergreen PD.
Do not move.
Step forward and into the light.
[both grunt]
Captain?
- Captain Miele, do you copy?
- [all grunting]
Hey, come on.
[grunts, groans]
Stop! Police!
Stop or I'll shoot!
[engine revs]
[whistles]
Shit! Should I take off?
No, he's not fucking here yet.
Come here.
[Eagly screeching]
Shit.
Let's go! What are you waiting for?
That thing better not shit back there.
Can't house-train an eagle, dude.
Not without stealing its soul.
[laughs heartily]
Hit the switch to ignition honey
Take a ride in my mind
Gotta say that I love this feeling
It's good to be alive
You change the car registration
into someone else's name?
Not only that,
I changed the fingerprints out
to the same person,
which they'll discover
when they get the lab results
back in a couple of days.
That's possible?
Yeah, for this guy
with two thumbs, it is.
That's not how that works, but, good.
Great. Who did you change it to?
Mr. Murn, you're gonna love this.
August Ransom Smith?
Yeah. What?
I was wondering if you wouldn't mind
answering a few questions for us.
Yeah, I mind. More from you than him.
Why more from me?
Let's just say that
egg foo young ain't my thing, baby.
Walking scrotum here
doesn't like egg foo young.
Got that, Fitz?
Yeah, I'll put it in my notes.
Where were you last night
from about midnight to 2:00am?
I was right here,
and I don't gotta answer you.
What's your fucking problem, pal?
You playing dress up again?
Yeah. You'll wish it was dress up.
Is that a threat?
No, I don't threat, I just do.
Now get the fuck off my property.
Maybe you can tell us why a 1976
Ford Comet registered in your name
was left at the Wild Estate's
apartment complex uptown?
I don't have a Comet.
That's my kid.
Your kid, as in Christopher Smith?
Peacemaker?
Arrest me or get the fuck out of here,
chopsticks.
Yeah, well, we'll be seeing you, fork.
"Fork"?
Why not "spoon"?
Everybody in the world uses spoons.
Yeah, but that asshole
doesn't know that.
That's true.
I mean, "spoon" would have been
more demeaning.
- Yeah.
- Makes it like a baby thing.
You know, little babies use spoons.
Okay, adults also use spoons,
but I get it.
You hear anything
about Peacemaker getting out of prison?
No.
You'd think
we would have been notified.
Yeah, you'd think.
You could have chosen anyone,
and you put the car registration
in the name of Peacemaker's father?
I had to act fast.
You were in the bathroom.
I didn't know
if you're going one or two.
Was I supposed to text you
when I'm taking a shit?
I would have appreciated...
I'm not gonna text you
when I'm taking a shit, John.
Okay, fine. I guess I'll have to guess
what's happening every time
you go in there.
We're trying to get this man
on our side,
and you thought the right way to do that
was to frame his father.
I don't want to be insubordinate,
but I kind of did
some magical shit here today,
and now I feel like you're angry at me.
No, I'm not angry at you, John,
but I am starting to think
you're an idiot.
Ugh, come on, man. Don't use
the "I" word. It's not cool.
Hey.
- What do we tell him?
- Nothing.
We just got shot at!
Like... [imitates gunshot]
Whoa!
Like, my adrenaline was pumping.
Pumping.
Like, glass breaking and everything.
You ever been shot at? [pants]
No.
[grunts]
- Kidding.
- You fucker.
You're doing great.
Why are they called butterflies again?
Again? We never told you.
Okay, Dye-Beard.
Hey, guess what? I'm done.
Dude, it's not finished.
I'm not gonna do this
if you keep calling me that name.
- What name?
- That fake name.
You saying I'm fake news?
No, I'm saying you're a fucking asshole.
I'd rather be
with Harley Quinn than you.
I'd rather be with the Weasel than you.
The only thing fake news around here
is the beard.
I'd rather be with fucking
Bat-Mite than you.
Who's Bat-Mite?
He's a two-foot tall
inter-dimensional imp who stans Batman.
I'd rather be with him.
- He's a real guy?
- Yeah.
- It's finished.
- Fuck is the world coming to?
From the beginning, I've kept
this operation completely off the books.
So how did this...
What's the dead woman's name?
Annie Sturphausen.
How did this Annie Sturphausen
know about Peacemaker?
Maybe someone's feeding
the Butterflies information.
- Who?
- Waller.
It's not her.
- [scoffs]
- I don't think it's Waller either.
You don't know her like I do.
I saw Waller knowingly sacrifice troops,
including a colonel
in the United States Army,
to meet her objective.
We could simply be a decoy team
from whomever else
she's really entrusted
with taking down the Butterflies.
Still no reason to give us up.
Well, the four of us and Waller
are the only ones who knew about it.
You're the one who brought
the Butterflies to our attention,
so it can't be you, and it's not me.
I just put my ass on the line
to save Muscle Man Weekly.
It's not Muscle Man Weekly
'cause he's the one
who almost got killed.
So if it's not Waller and it's not us,
maybe it's her.
Me?
Does anyone here know
how she ended up on this mission?
I got skills.
I got my Binks-Fendelmire
Strategic Combat Certification
at the age of 14.
Binks-Fendelmire is kindergarten shit.
What about since then?
What are your actual qualifications?
And how do I know
that you're not one of them?
[Peacemaker] It's not her.
I trust her the most
because Eagly liked her.
He tried to bite me.
Yeah, but not as hard
as he tries to bite everybody else.
It's obviously... [clears throat] Elmo.
Economos. Fuck you.
Why do all of you have
such weird last names?
- John didn't do it.
- Thank you.
- He's too big of a pussy to betray us.
- All right.
Not on purpose, but...
Okay, follow me, so...
He's, you know, hanging out,
having some fun,
maybe doing some fentanyl
with a prostitute
in the back of a hillbilly strip club.
He's fallen in love
'cause it's obviously the first time
he's put his balls in somebody's mouth,
and he starts getting loose lips,
you know, just showing off.
"I'm on a team
with the famous Peacemaker
and we're taking down
the notorious Butterflies.
- My beard's real."
- Are you fucking stupid?
Sounds more plausible
than I wish it did.
What? I don't even like when my balls
are in somebody's mouth, okay?
It gives me the wrong type of chills,
and all I can think about
is how long it's been
since I've gotten checked
for testicular cancer.
Too long.
You are so fucked up,
it's adorable, Dye-Beard.
Don't call me that!
- Fuck! Come on, bro. What the fuck?
- I don't think it's any of us.
Well, then, why did Sturphausen
try to kill Peacemaker?
Maybe she brought him back her apartment
for the purpose he thought she did.
But why would she decide,
after they hooked up,
that she needed to kill him?
- Oh, shit!
- What?
I gotta brush my teeth.
Cool.
You left the dossier of the person
you're supposed to contract kill
for the government in the apartment
of some rando who blew you?
Not some rando who blew me, man.
We fully fucked.
I thought it'd be safer on me
than in the car unattended.
What was I supposed to do,
drop it off at home first?
Yes!
You don't understand
what we're up against here, Smith.
The fate of the country
depends on this mission.
And nobody told me that.
Nobody's even told me
what a fucking butterfly is.
[cell phone vibrating]
Murn.
Yes.
You don't think that she left
any monster STDs on my dick, do you?
[Murn] Come again?
Wait, is being a butterfly
like a venereal disease of some type?
Fuck, am I going to become one?
Am I a fucking dick vampire now?
When were you gonna tell us
there were witnesses?
I kidnapped a couple for a minute.
Evan and Amber Calcaterra.
Can you take care of them?
Want me to take care of them like...
[imitating gunshot]
No, just convince them
not to finger Peacemaker.
[scoffs] More like, uh...
I have no clue what that is.
Why are we playing charades?
[speaking softly] 'Cause I don't want to
say it out loud.
I still don't know what that is.
Leota?
Bribery.
Yes, please. Go do it, now.
I need Harcourt and Economos here,
otherwise I'd send them.
Be straight with me, man.
I'm a dick vampire, aren't I?
No, you're not a dick vampire.
You're just a dick.
["Don't treat me bad" playing]
I never thought you'd hurt me
I guess you live and learn
When you're playing with fire
You're bound to get burned
[crying]
I've been mistreated
I've been used before
I get kicked in the face
Still I come back for more
[groans]
But I won't cry no more
'Cause the tears are all in vain
Everybody fucking hates you!
And Dye-Beard could be your friend,
but you push him away,
like you push everybody away
'cause you're a fucking dick.
You killed Rick Flag.
Flag was right.
Peacemaker. What a joke.
[man] Buddy?
Hey, what the fuck you doing,
you fucking stalker?
- Dude, are you all right?
- Fuck, dude.
What you doing? Are you looking at me
and jerking off right now?
Is your dick out?
What? No! No, man. Look.
I'm not gonna fucking look.
It's the oldest trick in the book.
I look and you're fucking rock hard
and you throw jizz in my face.
No fucking way!
What? No, dude. My dick is not out.
Is that what you get off on,
me seeing your fucking dick?
No, who the fuck said that?
Louis C.K. Piece of shit.
Louis C.K. said that?
I'll fucking kill that guy.
No, he didn't say it.
You, you're like Louis C.K.
Because I'm funny?
Fucking funny? Dude, no!
You show people your dick.
What does that have to do
with Louis C.K.'s comedy specials?
I didn't say shit
about his comedy specials.
What the fuck, man?
Louis C.K. was showing people his dick.
He himself.
- Because he's a ginger?
- Fucking... What?
Well, I don't fucking know.
I'm just trying
to figure out the connection.
Dude, Louis C.K.
showed people his dick, all right?
- He did?
- Jesus, man, do you read the news?
No, what for? It's depressing.
Look. Hey, I'm begging you.
Will you please,
please, just look at my crotch?
Come on!
[exhales]
See?
Can you see that?
[sighs]
Why the fuck don't you use
the front door like a normal person?
Well, I saw a light on in here,
and I thought
someone was creeping around.
- I'm really happy you're back.
- Yeah.
- Why are you crying?
- I'm not crying.
Fucking doing face muscle exercises.
I'm exercising the muscles in my face,
making my face more muscular.
I can tell under your mask,
your face is skinny as shit.
You don't do these exercises
for your face.
Some of them look like crying.
They're not crying.
Well, can you maybe teach them to me?
I guess.
Mr. and Mrs. Calcaterra,
I'm going to ask you some questions.
Yes, this is a real badge.
Fuck!
Evan, I can open the door myself.
I'm being a gentleman,
you fucking asshole.
Dick.
- Hey, Mr. and Mrs. Calcaterra?
- Yeah.
Just wondering if you would
answer a few questions for me.
We're on the way to the station now
to look at mugshots.
Yeah, well, that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Firstly, I'm wondering
whether you saw the guy
in your apartment
that you think you saw?
Or did you maybe see another guy
that you actually didn't see
but you think you did?
And secondly,
I'm wondering if you've ever had
an all-expenses paid trip
to the beautiful Lake Tahoe, Nevada?
Are you trying to fucking bribe us?
No.
Oh, I was hoping
you were trying to bribe us.
Yeah, yeah, I'm trying to bribe you.
[Peacemaker] When I was arrested,
the cops turned this place upside down
for evidence.
Need some help cleaning up?
I guess.
[grunts]
So, how did you get out anyway?
I thought you were in prison for life.
It's a secret.
- Dude, I'm your best friend.
- No, you're not.
Well, who's your best friend then?
Someone you met in prison? I knew it.
Dude, it's Eagly, obviously.
Okay, of all people,
who's your best friend?
- I don't even know your secret identity.
- Yeah.
I don't tell you my real identity
for your sake.
I don't want to put a target on you.
People will try to use you to get to me.
- Okay, where does this go?
- With the other tapes.
You think people are going to torture me
to get your secret identity?
I am extra special careful
in all my heroic endeavors,
which is probably the reason why,
and I don't mean to be a prick,
you went to prison and I didn't.
Where does this go?
The CD rack, dude.
See, when they put my mugshot up
in the post office,
it's just going to be a circle
with a red visor,
and they're going to have to figure out
what my head looks like
based on the shape.
And I know I have a bony face
'cause I don't do
face muscle exercises,
but that doesn't cut down very much
on the suspects.
Hmm.
[laughing] Hey! Holy shit! Look at that!
It's a funny smiley man.
Hey, do you want to come over and play?
Man, that's adorable.
- Hey, how'd you get out anyway?
- I work for the government, okay?
Post office?
You think they'd fucking
let me out of prison to deliver mail?
I don't know. It was the first
government job I could think of.
Dude, I kill people for them, okay?
I did it down in Corto Maltese,
and now I've got to do it here
in Evergreen.
That's why I'm out,
in exchange for that.
Oh, that's sick!
I... I used to think God put me here
for a purpose, for peace.
I always said I didn't care
how many people
I needed to torture or kill
to get it but...
You know, lately, I just think
I'm a fucking maniac, like...
I don't know,
I'm having feelings about things.
Okay.
[sighs]
Do you think I feel good,
when after some dude
does some atrocious act
that I have to kill them?
I don't know.
When I find out someone
murdered an innocent person,
or sold somebody heroin,
or did some graffiti,
and I kill that person
with my bare hands,
their eyeballs
popping out of their skulls,
you think that it gives me pleasure?
Phew. No.
Well, it does. [laughs]
It gives you pleasure too, Peacemaker.
That's 'cause we're born killers.
What separates us from other killers
is we only kill bad people.
Usually. Unless there's a mistake.
Now, do I sound like a fucking maniac?
Hey, what do you say we celebrate
you getting out of prison?
No, I have to study the dossier
of the senator I gotta kill.
I've been saving up appliances
ever since you were arrested.
I've got fire for a heart
I'm not scared of the dark
You've never seen it look so easy
I got a river for a soul
And baby you're a boat
Baby you're my only reason
If I didn't have you
There would be nothing left
The shell of a man
Who could never be his best
If I didn't have you
I'd never see the sun
You taught me how to be someone, yeah
[yells]
All my life
You stood by me
When no one else was ever behind me
All these lights
They can't blind me
[laughs]
With your love
Nobody can drag me down
All my life
You stood by me
When no one else was ever behind me
All these lights
They can't blind me
With your love, nobody can drag me down
[both laughing, yelling]
All my life
You stood by me
With your love
Nobody can drag me down
Nobody, nobody
Yeah!
[Peacemaker] Fuck yeah!
Nobody can drag me down
It's definitely this guy.
It's this guy.
[both] Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Jesus Christ, you again?
August Smith, you're under arrest
for the murder of Annie Sturphausen.
I don't even know who the fuck that is!
Get the fuck off me!
Fuck you!
[laughs]
- Go fuck yourself, old man!
- [laughs]
I'm ready to crash and burn
Sold you karma for some moolah
Pretty ugly and pretty young
I smelled you hookah
And follow your mantra
Crash-ing, fly-ing...
Keeya...
You know that I'm going to be working
some weird hours.
And I was thinking
maybe you and the fur kids...
Well, you know.
No, I don't know.
[exhales sharply]
Boots on rocks off
It's not that big of a deal.
[imperceptible conversation]
All this work for a one night stand
Learning my role
Or kamasutra
Amber?
Got no jingle
You know myjam
I fuckin' rocket ride
With his married bride
Crash-ing, fly-ing
White trash...
No.
I can't believe
they legalized that shit.
More for me.
Three years ago, I would have
shot both of you in the face for that.
Goddamn barrel is smokin'
Rattle and rollin'
[chiming]
Goddamn barrel is smokin'
Rattle and rollin'
What the fuck?
Dude.
Holy fuck!
[imperceptible conversation]
You got to burn that card
before the river.
Dude, how many times I got to teach you
how to play this fucking game?
Dude, seriously, you piss me off.
Holy shit!
Look who it is.
That's my spot between 5:00 and 7:00
during winter.
The fuck you talking about, old timer?
Ever heard of sunset?
That light there
comes in through that window,
and I like the feel of it on my skin,
so fucking move.
[scoffs] Yeah?
And if I don't?
Guess.
Fuck it.
I ain't dying for this seat.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
I thought we sent capes
over to Arkham or Belle Reve.
System's overcrowded.
He'll have to stay here
through his trial.
All hail
the White Dragon!
[all] Hail! Hail! Hail! Hail!
Hail! Hail! Hail!
Hail! Hail! Hail! Hail!
It's definitely not the hot guy.
- Fuck you, Amber!
- Eat me, Evan!
- This guy.
- Okay.
Can I keep this one?
Sure.