- ♪ MTV
[theme music]
- ♪ I'm goin' down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna have myself a time
- ♪ Friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
- ♪ I'm goin' down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna leave my woes behind ♪
- ♪ Ample parking day
or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor" ♪
- ♪ I'm headin' on down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna see
if I can't unwind ♪
- ♪ [mumbling] ♪
- ♪ Come on down
to South Park ♪
♪ And meet some friends
of mine ♪
[school bell rings]
- OK, kids,
let's take our seats.
Before we get started,
we have a guest speaker today.
Please give your undivided
attention to Kipling.
- Thank you, sir.
Hey. What's up, guys?
My name's Kipling.
I'm with the Webelos
of America.
I want to talk you guys about
the exciting opportunity
to join the Webelos.
- Is that a chick or a dude?
- Shut up.
- I'm sure some of you were in
Scouts before.
Webelos are an extension
of Scouts,
specifically for fifth
and sixth graders.
- You guys, is that a chick
or a dude?
- It's a chick.
- Nah, that's a dude, bro.
- [muffled speech]
- ...part of it as well.
Now, I know what y'all
might be thinking--
Webelos used to be
only for boys.
Well, now
they also allow girls,
and I myself, as a...
Webelo,
can tell you
it's a great organization
for everyone.
- I don't know, guys,
I'm like 60% sure
that was a fucking dude.
- I'm definitely betting
it's a chick.
What are the odds at?
- Looks like about
40 kids betting now,
55% saying the Webelo
is a dude.
- So I'd only win, like,
five bucks on a $2 bet?
- What are you guys
talking about?
- Prediction market app, dude.
You know,
online peer to peer betting.
- Yeah, it's social platform
betting.
People can make any bet
they want,
and then other users
take them up on it.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's pretty sweet, dude.
People bet on anything,
even stuff here at the school.
See? Will the girls' soccer team
win on Friday?
Will there be a snow day
this month?
Will Kyle's mom strike Gaza
and destroy
a Palestinian hospital?
Will school lunch have
tater tots next week?
- Wait, what was that?
- Will school lunch
have tater tots next week?
- No, the one about my mom!
- Oh. Uh...
Will Kyle's mom strike Gaza
and destroy
a Palestinian hospital?
- Why the hell would my mom
destroy a Palestinian hospital?
- 'Cause she's a Jew?
JESUS: Boys, put 'em away.
You know the rules--no cell
phones during school time.
Both: Sorry, Jesus.
[whistle trills]
- No phones, guys!
- Take that bet down right now,
fat ass!
- I didn't put it up, Kyle.
I'm not even betting on it.
It's 9:1 odds your mom won't
do it--those are terrible odds.
- This is such bullshit!
I'm gonna find out
who started this
and I'm gonna fucking
rip them a new asshole!
- Man, you just bring up Gaza
to a Jew and they flip out.
Maybe these are
pretty good odds.
[dynamic news theme]
ANNOUNCER:
You're watching Fox News!
- They're called
prediction market apps--
controversial online betting
that's found a loophole
around normal gambling laws.
And, of course, the number one
trending bet on the apps:
Will President Trump and Satan's
baby be a boy or a girl?
- That's right,
prediction market apps
are going crazy right now.
On Kalshi, 54% are betting
it's gonna be a boy,
while bettors on Polymarket
are at nearly 60%
the demonic butt baby's
gonna be a girl.
- Hello, boss.
Another gift for the baby.
- Another present for the baby?
What about me?
- Everyone is so excited
for the baby, boss.
You must be so excited as well.
- Uh, yeah, sure.
Real excited.
- It is going to completely
change your life, though.
- What are you talking about?
- Well, when the baby comes,
you will have to give it
all your attention.
No more dinner parties
in the Rose Garden.
No more baseball games.
No more travelling.
No more long nights
at Mar-a-Lago.
- Oh.
Ooh.
- Hey, Satan!
You wanna get in the hot tub
and smoke some cigarettes?
- Hot tubs and cigarettes
are really bad for the baby.
- Yeah, I know.
Let's do it anyway.
- Wait, do you want to get rid
of the baby?
I don't think your followers
would be very happy
if we got an abortion.
- Hey, relax, guy!
I don't want to get rid
of the baby.
- Good,
'cause we're not going to.
- Great!
- Jimmy!
- Oh, hey, Kyle.
- What the hell is this?
- That's a prediction
market app.
- I'm asking why did you bet yes
that my mom would strike Gaza?
- Oh, yeah,
I put some money on that.
I know it's not very likely,
but I like to bet on
l-longshots.
- Why are you betting on it
at all?
Israel and Gaza is
a very serious matter.
- Oh, I know, Kyle.
I told a joke about Gaza
on a Zoom meeting yesterday
and nobody laughed.
I guess it's not even
remotely funny.
Wow. What a terrific audience.
- What is wrong with you people?
Do you even know what Gaza is?
Do you seriously just care about
making a couple bucks?
You know what my mom would do
if she found out about this?
She would absolutely
lose her shit!
There's been a conflict in
Israel for thousands of years,
and Jews and Palestinians
are not football teams
that you bet on.
- Guys, phones.
all: Sorry, Jesus.
- Kyle, if you think
the bet isn't fair,
then you can just take it up
with the company
that manages the app.
- I can?
- Sure thing.
These apps aren't
r-run of the mill, rinkydink.
They're all run by
highly professional
strategic advisors.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Yeah, is this the "Strategic
Advisor for Predictive Markets?
- Yes, it is.
- Well, there's a bet
on one of your apps
that's incredible insensitive,
and it needs to be taken down
now!
- Oh, uh, all our bets are
actually regulated by the CFTC.
You need to talk to them.
- What's the CFTC?
- It's the Commodity Futures
Trading Commission.
It's the federal government.
They have to approve all bets
and deal with discrepancies.
- Fine! I'll call the CFTC then.
So stupid.
Commodity Futures Trading
Commission--here we go.
[line ringing]
- Hello?
- Yeah, I'm calling about
a prediction market bet
that's offensive
to Jewish people.
- Ooh, that sounds really bad.
If it's offensive, you probably
need to speak with the FCC.
- The FCC?
- Yeah, they're dealing with
all the offensive stuff now.
Here, let me connect you.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
- This is the same fucking guy!
- Who is it?
- Uh, apparently,
there's a really offensive bet
on an app
that the government is sort of
in charge of,
and I'm like
the strategic advisor.
- An offensive government app?
I better go speak with
the president right away.
[humming happily]
[rope boings]
Hey, Satan!
Can you come downstairs?
- What do you want?
- Just come down the stairs
real quick.
- For what?
- For just real quick.
- Oh, there you are,
Mr. President!
I need to talk to you.
- No, no, no, no!
Brendan Carr, don't--
- Whoa!
[grunting]
- [laughing]
The FCC guy must have
shitty ankles.
- You guys! You guys!
Have you checked out
the betting app lately?
- No.
- Ever since Kyle got
all pissed off,
the odds are going up
on his mom attacking Gaza.
- No way.
- Yeah, check it out!
Now 17% of people are betting
she's gonna do it.
We gotta get in on this, guys.
- Dude, Kyle's mom isn't going
to strike Gaza.
- Yes, exactly.
We know that.
And we can also influence Kyle
to get the odds raised
even more.
It's called a conflict
of interest, you guys.
It's a way to make free money.
- Isn't that illegal?
- Yes!
All we have to do is make sure
Kyle stays angry,
and at the same time, go talk
antisemitic shit about his mom
to goose the odds up even more.
- What are you guys
talking about?
- Nothing.
Just talking about
how messed up it is
everyone hates Jews now.
- You think it's messed up?
- Yes, I do, Kyle.
Why would an app allow a bet
like that to exist?
It's obvious race bait.
- Yeah,
that's exactly how I feel!
- Dude, you might just want to
let it go.
- See? "Just let it go."
That's how people want you
to deal with a crisis
that they don't even understand.
- Yes!
Thank you!
- You can't give up, Kyle.
It's not cool people would say
this stuff about your mom.
And honestly, if you don't have
her back, who will?
Hey, have you guys heard about
Kyle's mom?
Man, that bitch has it out
for Palestine, let me tell you.
Well, I don't know,
I would just hate to be
a Palestinian hospital,
that's all I can say.
Well, anyway,
good to talk to you guys.
Hey, guys!
Guys, have you heard about
my friend Kyle's mom?
[laughter]
- Oh, my goodness, can you
believe all the crazy apps
our kids are on these days?
- Ugh!
Who can keep track anymore?
- Kyle comes to me every day
with a new app
that he just has to have.
I tell him,
"That app costs money, Kyle.
"Then it charges you money.
Where you gonna get this money?"
- Yeah, you know what'd be nice?
Is an app where you can actually
make some money.
- [laughs]
Yes.
That'd be great, wouldn't it?
- [giggling]
Yes, it certainly would.
[clears throat]
So, Sheila,
how have you been feeling about
the current situation in Gaza?
- What?
- Uh, yeah,
just--just thought we'd sort of
take your temperature.
Which way are you thinking about
going with that?
- Well,
I think it's all horrible.
A lot of people are dying.
- Uh-huh.
- And do you feel like you need
to do anything about it?
- What would I do about it?
- I mean, probably nothing,
right?
You're going to do nothing
about it.
- Are you implying
the Jews in America
have some kind of obligation
to do something about it?
- Whoa, whoa!
- You want to vilify my faith!
Is that it?
- Sheila, it's OK.
- It's not
Jews versus Palestine!
It's Israel versus Palestine!
- Here we go with
the Palestinian stuff again.
- And maybe if you read books
instead of everything
Hollywood actors say,
you'd know the difference!
- What are you putting
your money on?
- I mean, it's a ridiculous bet,
but she seems pretty pissed off.
- There's really no money to be
made on betting she won't.
- Yeah, let's take
the long odds.
That makes these apps more fun.
- Yeah.
[laughter]
[stately music]
♪
- [humming happily]
♪ ♪
[mischievous music]
♪
[humming happily]
Hey, Satan!
♪ ♪
I made you some soup!
- I don't like carrots.
- Hey, relax, guy!
Carrots are good for you.
- I don't want carrots.
I ordered cheesecake
on DoorDash.
- Mr. President, I really need
to speak with you.
- Not now, Brendan Carr!
Satan won't eat his carrots.
- Oh, come on, Satan,
you're eating for two now.
Carrots are good for you, see?
- Ah, Brendan Carr, don't do it!
- Whoa, this is the best soup
ever. I--
[gagging]
Oh, God!
[farting, screaming]
- Whoa!
- Whoo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
[farting, screaming]
Wow-wow-wow-wow!
- [laughs]
Those carrots must have been
from Erewhon.
SHEILA:
Everywhere I went today,
it was the same thing.
What are  you going to do
about Gaza?
Like us Jews in America
have any control
over what's going on in Israel.
Why is everyone suddenly
confronting us
about the politics?
Have people been asking what you
think about Gaza, Gerald?
- No, for some reason,
they were just asking
what you think about it.
- You see?
It's just pure antisemitism!
I'm so sick of being grilled
about my views on Palestine
and my thoughts on Hamas!
And being judged for things
that are centuries old
and that non-Jews
know nothing about!
Well, if they all think
we should do something--
- You-- stop!
SHEILA: Then you better believe
I'll do something!
- You know, Mom, I'm starting
to think that us Jews
should just lay low
for a little bit.
- There!
Now my son is complacent.
This is one Jewish household
that will not put up with it
anymore!
- Ma, please.
Don't make things any worse.
- Worse?
How can it be any worse?
I'm going to find out where
all this is coming from,
and I'm going to give them
a piece of my mind!
- No! Ma!
[cat meows]
- Look, boss, another present
for the baby!
[cat meows]
- Another present for the baby?
Right!
- Isn't it cute, boss?
We must be careful, though,
cats can be very harmful
to a pregnancy.
- Harmful to a pregnancy?
- Well, yes, boss, it's a
parasite called toxoplasmosis.
It can be transferred
from cats to humans
and bring about
some complications.
[cat meows]
- Toxoplasmosis?
[cat yowls]
[humming happily]
[cats meowing]
[alarm buzzes]
[humming happily]
Hey, Satan!
Hey, Satan, you gotta come
see this, it's really great.
- What?
- Ay! I thought you were
napping in our room.
- No, I had to go get
the ultrasound.
I can't believe
you didn't show up.
It really makes me feel like
you don't care about this baby.
- Hey, relax, guy, of course
I care about the baby.
- Mr. President,
I'm feeling much better--
- No! Fuck! Brendan Carr!
- [muffled groaning]
[muffled scream]
[crashing]
- You guys.
You guys, I did it.
- You did what?
- I talked so much shit
about the Jews
that I got the odds
on the bet up to 95%.
- [muffled speech]
- Yeah, check it out.
I put 1,400 bucks on it
last night.
I am locked in.
- Where'd you get
1,400 bucks?
- I just took my mom's
debit card,
entered all the info
into the betting app,
and put all the money
she has on it.
- [muffled speech]
- Isn't she gonna be
pissed off?
- Yeah, not when I turn
her 1,400 bucks into 14,000.
This is the safest investment
ever.
Nothing can possibly
go wrong.
JIMMY:
Hey, fellas. Fellas!
Fellas, have you seen the news?
Kyle's mom's in Israel.
- Really?
- Oh, wow!
- I just put money down!
[dramatic music]
- [speaking Arabic]
- Dude, your mom's in Israel.
- I know.
- Well, you gotta call her.
You gotta calm her down.
- I've been trying to call her.
Her phone's not working
over there.
- Kyle this is no time
for weakness.
Whatever your mom is doing,
it is going to make kids here
even more anti-Semitic.
- You're totally right.
- Damn right, I'm right!
You have to get ahold
of your mom
and tell her to calm down,
Kyle.
Call the Israeli government
if you have to.
- How do I call
the Israeli government?
- Call a diplomat.
Call an embassy.
You just have to talk to
someone who works for Israel.
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Oh, you have got to be
shitting me!
- What?
- This is the strategic advisor
for predictive market apps.
- Tell him to take
the bet down.
- What?
- Make him take the bet down,
Kyle.
It is anti-Semitic,
and you have to fight
for what you believe in.
- I called before
about an offensive bet,
and I want that bet
taken down right now!
- That's right!
- Oh, yes, I believe
your complaint
was being reviewed
by head of the FCC.
- Well, then what's the head
of the FCC doing?
Where the hell is he?
- [groaning]
- Mr. Carr?
Mr. Carr, can you hear me?
- [groans]
- We understand you're the head
of the FCC, is that correct?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right, well,
I'm very sorry,
but you do appear
to have toxoplasmosis
from exposure to cat feces.
- Aww!
- We need you to get some rest.
Try not to move.
- Will the head of the FCC
be OK, Doctor?
- His bones are healing,
so he may regain
full range of motion.
But if the toxoplasmosis
parasite gets to his brain...
I'm afraid he may lose
his freedom of speech.
- Oh, no!
- We'll do everything we can.
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
- Mr. Carr, why do you keep
meddling in my plans?
- Huh?
- I've been trying
to convince the boss
to get rid of the baby.
I am next in line
to be president.
That baby cannot be born.
And if you continue
to interfere,
I will make things
very difficult for you.
- [groaning]
- We can do this the easy way,
or we can do it the hard way.
♪
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
Uh, yes, is this the office
of the president?
Yes, it is.
I've got a young man
who's saying one of our
predictive market bets
is offensive to Jews?
Ooh, that sounds bad.
Yeah, it sounds pretty bad.
Well, the president isn't here,
but I'm, like,
a special advisor,
so I can probably
get the bet taken down.
Ooh, I'm a special
advisor too!
Oh, really? That's great.
Can you email me
the bet in question?
Yeah, I'm emailing it now.
Oh, yeah, I see it.
OK, I'll need to approve
with the financial company
backing all the app since the
bet money needs to be returned.
OK, thanks,
I'll let all the Jews know.
- What the hell?
- They took it down.
We were all gonna win,
and they took down our bets.
- How can the app company
do that?
- I got in at nine-to-one odds.
This is b-b-bullshit!
- Yeah, these apps
are totally corrupt.
[whistle blows]
- Guys! For the love of God!
[laughter]
- Well, Cartman,
I just wanna say thanks.
You know, it's crazy,
but nobody else here
gave a crap about how I was
feeling except for you.
- Oh, that's all right, Kyle.
I'm just happy the bet
got taken down.
Now none of these sickos
can profit
off of what your mom does.
- Yeah, well, those people
would have all lost the bet
anyway.
- What do you mean they would
have all lost the bet?
- Well, I know the reason
my mom went Israel.
- It wasn't to bomb
a Palestinian hospital?
- No, when my mom
left the house,
she said she was gonna find
the person responsible
for all this
and give them
a piece of her mind.
KYLE'S MOM [muffled]:
You are not going
to talk to me like that!
I am extremely upset,
and I am not leaving
until I have said my piece!
There you are,
Mr. Netanyahu!
Just who do you think you are,
killing thousands
and flattening neighborhoods,
then wrapping yourself
in Judaism
like it's some shield
from criticism?
You're making life for Jews
miserable
and life for American Jews
impossible!
Oh, don't you roll your eyes
at me, mister.
You know what you're doing,
and you're doing it
on purpose!
Well, now you can just sit
in that chair,
'cause I'm not
going anywhere, buster!
I've been to every
PTA meeting,
every school board meeting,
and I can go all day!