My heart's like an open book
For the whole world to read
Sometime nothing keeps me together
at the seams
I'm on my way
Home sweet home
It's a bitch song, but it still rocks.
So cool.
Do this.
Is that white power?
Fuck white power. It's the devil.
It means rock and roll forever,
and tongue-kiss hot babes,
and smoke pot all day.
- Yeah!
[screams]
Home sweet home
Your old man's ready
for you two maggots.
[both cheer]
All right, motherfuckers.
Let's go. Bets right here.
Let's go. Let your money talk. Come on.
Yeah!
[all cheering]
[man] Keep going. Keep going with Keith.
Hold on. Cool it off.
No kicking, no biting,
no grabbing, no...
Fuck that!
- No holds barred!
- Yeah!
Hit it.
Come on, let's go.
Don't be a faggot.
Get in there and hit him!
Come on, Chris.
You're hitting like a girl.
[man]
...Glan Tai Bottling Plant massacre
Any leads on
where the Peacemaker might be?
Come on, Chris. Don't be a pussy.
He's doing the worm.
Keith?
Keith!
[man] We have a few leads.
Every cop in the country
is out looking for him.
Keith?
Keith!
You dumb fuck, you killed your brother.
You killed your brother,
you piece of shit!
You dumb fuck!
You killed your brother!
[knock on door]
You killed...
[Vigilante] You okay in there?
[knocking continues]
[theme song playing]
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it!
- Get it on
- Get it on top
Make a move extreme
- Make a pose
- Shortcut to your dreams
Float straight to the stars
on that flying thing
- Getting high
- Getting brave
- Getting snowblind, game
- Set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon
In a world beyond
Get a beat, got a heat
On a phony string
Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts
Do ya really wanna,
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
[Eagly screeching]
[knock on door]
[Vigilante] Dude? Dude?
[knocking continues]
Dude?
Hey, you okay in there?
We gotta get the fuck out of here.
That guy on the TV, he's supposed to be
the guy watching our backs.
Every police station in the country
has one mandate this morning.
Find and stop the Peacemaker.
- You think he's a bird?
- Bird?
- Like Goff.
- Butterfly.
Dude, a butterfly is a type of bird.
It's not a bird. It's fuckin' bug!
- Fucking Adebayo, she fucked me.
- What?
She probably planted that diary
in my trailer.
I knew I couldn't trust these people.
Where the fuck's Judomaster?
Judomaster was supposed to be there?
Fuck it, can't worry about it now.
- Move.
- All right.
I got all the Peacemaker helmets
programmed in.
These ones are at the police station.
They must've been confiscated yesterday.
But these ones...
That's gotta be Christopher.
- The diary is fake?
- Of course it's a fake.
If I was gonna write a diary,
it wouldn't be a diary,
it'd be a fucking journal.
Well, I would read
anything you wrote, dude.
I bet you could do some bomb poetry.
Dude, I thought you said
you didn't write a diary.
I didn't. Did you see that thing?
It looked like
it fell out of my fucking vagina.
Do I look like the type of guy
to stay up all night
collaging Jupiters and the aliens
and shit to put on the front
of my fucking diary?
First impressions, I'd have said no.
But after getting to know you
a little bit, I got to admit,
it's definitely something
I can see you doing.
You know what? Fine. Fuck it.
If I enjoyed it, I wouldn't let
people's judgements hold me back.
I'd collage all sorts of shit.
- That's cool of you.
- Yeah, it is fucking cool of me.
I'd make a collage of the three of us
fucking some chicks
with a bunch of dolphins around us
doing beer bongs in a Corvette.
I don't want a dolphin watching me fuck.
Where you going?
Vigilante and me might as well
get this done before they find us.
What done?
Kill this fucking cow.
We are? Cool.
- Coming?
- No.
- Eagly.
- [Eagly screeches]
Fuck!
God damn it!
Among the many items found
in the search
of Christopher Smith's home
was a diary
- written by the suspect...
- [knocking on door]
The diary links Smith
not only to the murders...
You did it, didn't you?
Waller sent you here
for this express purpose.
Did what?
Planted a diary in Peacemaker's trailer.
Yes.
That's why Peacemaker was chosen
in the first place.
You're gonna lone-shooter
the poor bastard?
He has a history of instability
and conspiratorial beliefs.
Couple that with violent outburst,
he was the perfect pawn.
He was your fucking friend.
- Maybe you should back off.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah, because you've been
fucking with me
from the first day I got here.
Well, maybe I could sense
your interior asshole.
My what?
Like inside of
all of this nice-person stuff,
you're really just a fucking asshole!
I thought you were bringing up
some weird medical condition.
Why would I bring up
a medical condition?
I don't know. Maybe because
you seem like the kind of bitch
who would pick on
someone's health issues
in the middle of an argument.
Well, I'm not the one
who just betrayed one of our own.
Oh! Okay, so, it is okay to shoot
an innocent man begging for his life,
but this you have an issue with?
He is a fellow soldier.
Pretty random rule
that the only lives that matter
are the lives of the ones
who fight beside us.
Yes!
[voice shaking] Well,
that is an incredibly clever way
of shutting yourself off
from the rest of the world's problems.
But for me, it doesn't work.
I'm not made for this shit.
I don't wanna be here no more,
so I'm leaving.
Well, then why the fuck
did you even come?
Because I lost my job
and my mother offered me this one!
- Your mother?
- Yes.
I didn't know that I was gonna get
caught up in Mars Attacks!
Holy fuck! Your mother is Amanda Waller?
Hey, we need to get out of here.
She's Waller's daughter.
Yeah, I know.
You think I wouldn't do
a background check
on anyone coming to work with us?
I don't know
how your weird butterfly brain works.
- She also planted...
- Planted the diary. I figured.
She probably shouldn't have done that.
And if she did, she should've waited
until after we'd completed the mission.
But that guy on TV,
he's our man on the inside,
which means he's compromised.
And since our weird butterfly brains
inherit human memories,
he'll know we're here.
So drop whatever differences
you two are having,
pack up what you need,
and meet me in the lot.
I fucking trusted you.
Fuck.
What are you talking about?
I feel like...
Every time we drink,
you talk about TV shows.
- I'm sick of it.
- Bro... [scoffs]
How have you not seen
The Boondock Saints?
It's a classic.
Vigilante... Jesus! Man.
That dude scared the shit out of me.
It's a fucking leprechaun, man.
Oh, my God, he's hilarious looking.
He's getting mad.
They're always after me Lucky Charms!
I love it.
If you have a message for Chris
or Eagly, please leave it at the tone.
[beeps]
Chris...
I just wanna make sure you're okay.
Let's try to figure this thing out.
Call me.
Fuck!
Come on, come on, come on
Love is all over me
Over me
You are the only one
Living in my fantasy
Aren't you guys being
a little nonchalant about all this?
Economos, are you insinuating there is
a wrong time and a right time to rock?
They're on the 395 North,
about the pass the exit
to Contorinis Road.
I've got eyes.
Got it.
[Eagly screeches]
[John] What the fuck was that?
[tires screech]
[thudding]
Dad?
Oh, fuck.
What are you doing?
What I should've done long ago.
That's it, man. We gotta go.
Come on, get up.
There's no wrong time to rock.
Vij!
- No!
- No.
Peacemaker, we gotta go.
[groaning]
Get the fuck away from me.
Well...
Your son went in the woods.
Lead the way.
How the fuck did he find you?
What?
Fuck.
He's fast.
You left your keys in the car?
I was rushing.
[Auggie] Ignore it. Let's go.
[both laughing]
I'm not kidding.
There was at least 20 girls...
You're an asshole, man.
You're an asshole.
So, what do you wanna do now?
You wanna go to the club or...
Mother...
[choking]
Kiai!
[tires screech]
[knocking at door]
Open up! Police!
- I know you're pissed, but...
- [whispering] Get down.
[Harcourt exhales]
He's right down there.
He's running like a spaz.
Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
Fucking racoons are hardcore, man.
It wasn't exactly inconsistent
with what I imagined would happen
if a man just walked up
and grabbed a wild raccoon.
[Eagly screeches]
Let's go.
[rock music playing]
[knock on door]
[Song] Open up! Police!
Police! Open up!
Leota, Harcourt.
Go now. Do you hear me?
You can do it.
Police!
I'm proud to have had you on my team.
Finish the job!
Kill the fucking cow!
How do you know about the cow?
Nothing you can do will make me...
We really need to hurry.
We need to get
the teleportation equipment
to the ranch.
Hey.
Ik Nobe Llok?
You could've just joined us.
You murdered him.
The alternative was what?
He was a warrior.
Without him, his outfit will have
no chance of stopping us.
Two clowns in costumes
and a couple of rejects?
We need to go.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[butterfly screeching]
How the fuck are we gonna do this
without him?
Kiai!
Ding dong, bitches.
Oh, you gotta be fucking
kidding me right now.
[both groan]
That's your last sucker punch, asshole.
[both grunting]
- Rope-a-dope, dumbshit.
- What?
You down now, motherfucker?
I think you got him.
He's right there.
[chittering]
Fuck me.
Fan out. Find him.
Wait.
I got something.
The door.
- Come on!
- Hey, dude. What are you doing?
Right, that dash.
Scoot.
Hey, hey!
My asshole!
What the fuck, dude?
What the fuck's wrong with your bird?
Bad Eagly! Stop it.
[screeching]
What you doing, man?
There's no wrong time
to rock, motherfucker.
Now is. This is the wrong time to rock.
You're gettin' me hot, Cherie
I want what you've got all over me
Isn't my love strong enough?
I'm ready to...
Eagly, stop!
How did they find you guys, anyway?
He put a GPS tracking device
in Peacemaker's helmet.
What?
[tires screech]
I didn't know.
I thought they were expensive.
I gotta pee so fucking bad.
No, Eagly, get back in the car.
John, can you get him in the car?
Sure, I fucking babysit birds.
Eagly, please get in the car.
He's not listening.
Get back in the car
and crinkle a bag or something,
he'll think you have chips.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Who the fuck feeds their bird chips?
Shit.
[screaming]
You want some chips?
Yum, yum!
Fuck no.
- What are you doing?
- [shushes] They're here.
Why the fuck are your pants
all the way down?
I can't pee
when clothes are touching my butt.
[Eagly screeching]
What the...
Eagly!
[growls]
I'll kill you, motherfucker!
You think so?
Forty years ago,
God challenged me as he did Abraham.
But I was too weak to listen.
But not no more.
- Kill that piece of shit, Dragon!
- Yeah!
I knew you was unclean
when you were born.
And even more so
when you killed your brother.
That was you...
Do it, White Dragon! Do it.
I knew
when you listened to that devil music.
I knew when you shaved your body
like a woman.
I knew when you slept with the whores
of polluted blood, and men.
And even more so when you conspired
with the forces of Baphomet
against the United States of America.
[all cheering]
And now, boy...
I give your life to God...
There are gaps in armor, man.
[screaming]
You killed my brother!
You killed Keith!
And you were only right about one thing.
I am a piece of shit.
I'm a piece of shit for listening
to you for all those years.
I'm a piece of shit
for not killing you in your sleep.
[laughs]
You hit like a girl.
Well, go ahead and do it,
you fucking pussy.
I knew you couldn't do it, you faggot.
Because I control you.
Whether or not I kill you,
you'll never be able
to get the fuck away...
[sobbing] Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Dude, this is a really weird time
to do your face exercises.
I mean, I guess you don't get
a totally sick, jacked face like yours
without dedication, but...
He's crying, asshole.
Oh.
Tender, nice touching.
Hey, dude, that's creepy.
Okay.
No, nothing serious.
Just some forms and stuff
I have to fill out before I leave.
Yeah.
I love you too.
Let me.
[grunts, sighs]
What was your job before this?
I ran a dog shelter.
Oh, Jesus.
Yeah. We lost funding.
I think my mother saw an opportunity
in my moment of weakness.
She always wanted me to do this shit,
so she asked me again
to come work for her.
Said she needed someone on the inside
of a group of people she didn't trust.
She doesn't trust anyone.
Hell, I know.
Did you tell her about Murn?
I couldn't decide if I was going to.
I guess it doesn't matter now.
I could tell you were hiding something.
I could tell you could tell.
Shit made me agitated.
Anyways...
Like I said, I'm not made for this shit.
I'm not supposed to be here.
That's why I was packing up.
I just wanna do whatever job I need to
where telling right from wrong
ain't advanced calculus.
Well, that would be a shame.
Shame, why?
Because you're good at the job.
And because we need every hand on deck
to try to go kill this cow.
How? It's impossible.
We couldn't even get there in time.
[cell phone vibrates]
[Leota] God.
Hey, John.
- Thank God you guys are here.
- What's going on?
Dr. Hurwitz kindly stitched up Eagly,
and Vigilante's being a total freak.
Dude, they saw us.
Peacemaker and I are wanted.
What other choice do we have
besides killing this veterinarian,
this nurse and this male nurse?
You could just say "two nurses," man.
If I just say "nurse," I think people
will imagine it as a woman.
He's standing right there.
We don't have to imagine anything.
Must be weird waking up every day
and being a male nurse.
You're a fucking busboy.
Oh, great. Now we definitely
have to kill them
because you're giving away stuff
about my secret identity.
Do we really have to kill these people?
No, we'll tie them up,
and by the time the morning staff
comes in, we'll be long gone.
They've seen our faces.
If we can't stop the butterflies today,
it won't matter.
[cell phone vibrating]
Okay.
We can't use duct tape. That'll hurt
their skin when they try to pull it off.
Where are you going?
Just to call my wife,
tell her I'm on my way back.
So, you're compassionate about tape,
but not brutally murdering people?
Yes.
[Peacemaker sniffles]
God, please bring back
my best pal Eagly. [sniffles]
I never should've left him
in my father's garage
for four years when I went to prison.
I should've found somebody better
to take care of him.
Like an ugly girl
who was desperate for love,
that would've done anything I wanted
when I was locked up and...
you know, I could just broke up with her
the moment I got out.
I probably wouldn't even
had to have sex with her, right?
Yeah, probably just once,
you know, to be nice.
And probably 'cause I was getting out
of prison, I'd have wanted to anyway.
It wouldn't even have been a chore.
But I was selfish.
And I was a bad friend to Eagly.
The only one besides Keith
that ever loved me for real.
Oh, fuck.
[sighs]
Please, God...
I'll do anything you want. [sniffles]
Just please, please...
keep Eagly alive.
[Eagly screeches]
[laughing] Buddy?
[screeches]
You know, he was so happy
to see me today,
he wrapped his wings around me
and hugged me.
- An eagle hugged you?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I call bullshit on that.
You don't wanna believe in miracles,
that's on you.
[camera shutter clicking]
[Keeya] Lee, where are you?
You said you were gonna be here
two hours ago.
Babe, I just saw an eagle hug a human.
With everything going on, what?
- Yeah.
- Fuck.
Maybe...
Maybe it's a sign.
A sign of what?
Hey. We should get a move on
killing this cow.
What about your wife?
She's upset, but she gets it.
- Sort of.
- Cool.
Okay, how do we do this without Murn?
We have someone else
that we can trust to lead us.
Me?
No. Fuck no!
The butterflies breathe our air
and drink our water.
But our food sources
don't keep them alive.
So they had to transport a creature
from their planet across the galaxy.
And now we know they keep it
in the cavern below the barn
on Coverdale Ranch.
Hey girl
You'll land it
You've got supplies
If they demand it
There, they milk the beast
for the amber fluid.
To stop the butterflies,
all we have to do is kill the cow.
Without it, they won't be able to stay
alive for more than a couple of weeks.
However, they almost certainly know
that we're on our way to do that now,
which means they'll do what they can
to move the cow out before we get there.
How?
According to what Ads and I overheard,
teleportation.
Yeah, they get by
I'm guessing they can move it to one of
their other enclaves around the country.
Which means, to us,
they will be lost forever,
and all of our work goes to waste.
Hopefully we can make it there
before they make their move.
And then we go in there and we kick ass,
like Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid.
They get slaughtered
at the end of that film.
Bro, there's a freeze-frame
and we hear a bunch of bullets.
That doesn't mean they died.
- Yes, it does.
- I don't think so.
I think they jumped over those bullets
right after that freeze-frame.
Well, that's an exceedingly
optimistic interpretation.
Both things are equally possible.
No, they're not.
Well, whichever one you believe
says a lot about your character.
Yeah, about how insane you are.
[laughs]
Economos, I love this
back-and-forth thing we have going.
It's not as deep
as what Peacemaker and I have,
but it's fucking cool.
Whatever the case, I'm in.
Hashtag "Me Too."
I guess.
Yeah.
- Fuck yeah.
- Let's do this shit.
- No.
- I think you need to calm down.
You can't come with us.
You sure you don't need the help?
No, you'll just die.
But we are gonna have to
sequester your vehicle out there.
Yeah, they get by
Surprisingly nice people, considering.
Except for the guy in the blue.
Yeah, that dude's a fucking mess.
They need, they yearn
They lust with cheeks unturned
Eagly.
Hands shake and heads will nod
They get by by the grace of god
Chris.
I just wanted to say...
I know what I did.
And I'm sorry.
- I shouldn't have...
- Forget it. I don't give a fuck.
You said we were a team,
that's obviously not the case.
Just can't wait till this is all over
so I never have to see
your stupid, dumb face ever again.
There's no wrong time to rock.
[growling]
1-2-3 let's go!
Rock 'n' Roll...
It's Friday night
we're gonna hit the lights
It's you and me, we're gonna
Rock 'n' Roll, All night!
It's Saturday, and there's just no way
we're gonna sit home
Alone, well, oh, no
Let me take you one step higher!
Rock 'n' Roll is gonna
set the night on fire
Yeah
We're the burning flames
too wild to tame
Yeah, yeah, yeah
We're gonna shock the world
All right
In Hollywood, wake up the neighborhood
All the boys and girls,
they're gonna scream and shout, hey!
Hey! Hey!
Let me take you one step higher!
Cleanliness is next to godliness,
and God knows I'm close to him.
Blood.
That's what you want to see.
If you're not seeing any blood,
you're not scrubbing hard enough.
Clean your toes.
Start at the bottom, work your way up.
Linger the middle.
Keep going a little higher.
Swing the hips.
When you're drying, especially,
it's important to swing the hips.
And we're finished now.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for attending.