For a number of years, there was
an unofficial company policy
on Cruise Lines that if there
was a serious criminal incident,
we could minimize the incident
to avoid negative PR.
-Incidents like--
-Theft. Sexual assault. Murder.
Oh, okay. The bad ones.
Yeah.
There's hundreds in there.
All you have to do is sign
out some boxes.
Do a little bit of shredding.
Meet some lovely guys.
Its not a big deal, Greg!
LOGAN ROY: We need this.
Bagging Pierce is the key
to our proxy defense.
Any thought given to whom you
might hand over the keys?
I really don't like to deal
in hypotheticals.
Oh, for fuck's sake, Dad.
Just tell them its gonna be me.
NAN PIERCE: Here we are.
We want to announce
the sale and Shiv
at the same time,
or there's no deal.
That's not quite
how I do things.
I could go to 25,
but it would have to be fast.
Then in that case...
Yes.
(YELLS)
That's goddamn fucking right!
Here's to us.
Money wins.
So, pilot apparently says
another half hour.
It's just slots,
it's, uh, 400 jets
fighting over 100 spaces.
If I find some tech fuck
gets landed before us,
I'm gonna kill 'em.
Okay?
-We okay?
-JAMIE LAIRD: On the Pierce deal
they're entrenching
on the break fee.
Very, very aggressive.
ROMAN ROY: Well, fuck 'em,
right?
I mean, they're empty suits,
they're not gonna walk away now.
LOGAN ROY: Maybe...
Maybe we just give them
what they want.
ROMAN: We just give 'em
what they want?
Excuse me, Dad, I think you
just had another stroke.
I wanna sign here. Today.
Well, I think the one thing
is just,
there could just be
a burnout issue
-in terms of the teams--
-No! (SIGHS)
Ken, go. I'm tired.
Impress upon them
that I need this done yesterday.
(LOGAN SIGHS)
KENDALL ROY: Okay.
We've been circling
for a fucking hour.
When can we expect
something in my hand?
-Imminently.
-Like when?
Soon. For confidentiality,
leak protection,
we kept the circle small.
-Everyone's spread pretty thin.
-It's not fucking good enough.
You're fucking me here.
I'm making good faith
fucking assessments
to my father, and you're
making me look like a hack,
and I will not have it.
Stop sucking each other off
back here,
and get fucking on it.
You pour the shit
I'm pouring on you
on your fucking minions,
and you ride them.
I don't care. 24 hours,
rolling shifts,
crack the fuckin' whip.
Everything you're doing
is fucking bullshit,
and I'm very disappointed
in you.
I swear to God,
I will fucking fire you
if you keep monkeying around--
Put the fucking snacks away.
I don't wanna fucking hear it!
LOGAN: We've been circling
for a fucking hour.
Tell them we're running out
of gas!
♪ (THEME MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
-(PHONE RINGING)
-FRANK VERNON: Okay, you.
It's time for that most magical
time of the quarter.
-Audit committee. 10-Q.
-Ah, sounds amazing.
Shiv. Come on.
Shadow me, Shadow.
Frank, my dad's a prick.
Come on.
Nothing-- (LAUGHS)
I got nothing.
You know what he promised me.
-And they're all up there.
-I can't get into that.
What, you like this?
You like being left behind?
There's limited attendance
at Argestes.
They only have a certain amount
of platinum passes,
-and that's all there is to it.
-(SCOFFS) Oh, yeah, right.
Because it would be impossible
for them to get any more, huh?
It'd mean finding printers
and ink, and...
Inconceivable, right?
This is humiliating
for you, too.
(SIGHS) Come on, soldier.
Let's go.
Now, I like to recite
Prufrock internally
while we check
we're GAAP compliant,
but feel free to use
whatever method you prefer
-to numb the pain.
-No. Fuck this. I'm going home.
-Whoa-- What--
-SHIV ROY: I am going home.
-Come on.
-I have shit to do. No.
-I'm making a call on this.
-Your dad asked me
-to take you through this stuff.
-Well, you can tell my dad
I made a decision. Okay?
-Hey.
It's Cruises.
(REPORTERS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY)
(REPORTERS SHOUTING)
Hi.
No, I can't talk, sorry.
Time is what
I'm indicating here.
ORGANIZER: Mr. Roy.
-Welcome back to Argestes.
-Thank you.
-Mr. Roy...
-ROMAN: Ah, yes.
-...welcome back to Argestes.
-Thank you.
Programs,
and suggested itinerary.
Oh, itinerary, great.
'Cause I'm really hoping to get
into some...
"Airbus culture hike",
that sounds heart-breaking.
-Thank you.
-ORGANIZER: Enjoy your stay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Look at you scanning
for influence
like a yuppie Robocop.
(SIGHS) So, what are you rocking
for the panel?
Jacket or no jacket?
Uh, right, like I'm gonna
fuckin' tell you, dude.
-Fuck off.
-Okay.
-Strategic advantage.
-Fine. But fair warning,
I'm thinking of no socking it.
Rockin' some horny
ankle cleavage.
-Ooh. Scary.
-ROMAN: Mm-hmm.
-I'm scared.
-Yeah, you should be.
Or am I just saying that
to psych you out?
-GREG HIRSCH: Hey there.
-Hey.
-GREG: Hey, sir.
-Hey, excuse me.
-Hey, my sherpa, what's cookin'?
-Yeah, just, uh-- just--
Might've just touched
Bill Gates.
Ooh. Hey, did you check out
the acoustics
on my room for my talk?
-I--
-And did you get me
on the culture hike?
And what did I-- what did I get
in my chalet?
Did I get the nut and fruit box
or the champagne
and paperweight?
Nuts.
Yeah.
But, uh--
But the talk venue's great.
Uh, it's the same one
as Roman and Ken.
-Oh. Okay.
-Yeah. And, um...
And don't worry about
the nuts. The--
The cashews are the size
of boomerangs.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
-So, uh--
-Thanks.
Hey. Nice vest, Wambsgans.
It's so puffy.
Thank you, Roman.
What's it stuffed with,
your hopes and dreams?
Oh, wow. Hiking boots.
They're pristine.
Oh. Here we go.
All right.
All rise for Pope Big Dick.
Hello, Rhea.
Mr. Roy.
You know what I need.
-Hey.
-Hey there.
Yeah, just to say, um,
I don't know how
up to speed you are,
uh, with all of the details,
but, um, just to say that
we're all lined up
for the ATN strategy
announcement.
Yeah, same shit.
-Different wrapper.
-TOM: (LAUGHING) Well, I hope
we're not gonna--
we're not gonna go with that,
um, banner, but we--
You know, we settled on,
"We're listening."
-It tested great.
-It tested fine.
Do me a favor.
Is that Sandy Furness?
-Uh...
-Uh, yes.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Well, keep talking.
Keep talking.
-GREG: Oh, yeah.
-Uh, I don't want a bump in.
-Not here, not now.
-TOM: Okay.
Vipers would love it.
GREG: Gladly-- We'd be honored
to be your talking partners...
So, basically, the talk
is a celebration of
putting audience input
front and center.
And hopefully be really
inclusive
and quite changey
after recent events,
because ATN Citizen
is essentially
very similar
but with the option of--
How's he-- How's he looking?
Is he healthy?
-GREG: Uh...
-He looks...
-GREG: Not really.
-He looks a little enfeebled.
-Yeah.
-TOM: I'd say.
I heard-- I heard, maybe...
maybe syphilis?
-Whoa.
-What? Really?
-Interesting.
-And that's definitely...
You don't really hear much
about syphilis these days.
Very much the, uh--
the MySpace of STDs.
Excuse me, Logan.
I, uh, just spoke to
Karolina.
It came through.
They're asking for a response.
Get a room. But slow.
No ripples.
A room?
Sorry. Uh, the magazine
contacted Cruises directly.
-Who at Cruises?
-Hello?
Just Florida PR.
Obviously, they thought
they could get someone
who might spew if they went low
on the food chain,
but I had 'em all briefed.
What have they got?
How much have they got?
We don't know.
All they're requesting
is a response on one element.
-Karolina said we had two weeks.
-HUGO BAKER: (SCOFFS) Yeah.
Well, I don't know where
Karolina got that from,
so, I-- I cannot speak to that.
Uh, so I have Shiv on the line,
if that's, um--
Uh-huh.
Shiv, you're on speaker.
SHIV: So, what the fuck
is going on?
I hear there's a big muck-rake
piece coming in on Cruises?
-KENDALL: Yeah, that's right.
-SHIV: So, what's in it?
HUGO: Uh, we don't know exactly.
SHIV: I'm sorry,
who is this?
Uh, Hugo Baker,
Senior Vice President Comms
for Parks and Cruises.
-Hi.
-Wait. Is Dad there?
Does he know I'm on this call?
-I'm here.
-SHIV: Okay, so,
tell me again, how--
how did this happen?
GERRI KELLMAN: Oh, well, we had
a tip off some time ago.
New York Magazine
working on a substantial piece.
They're, um, only giving us
limited allegations
and asking for a response.
Okay, so there's a bomb
about to go off,
and do we know
what the fuck is in it?
Why do you do this, Dad?
Why do you hoard information?
What you don't know
can't hurt you.
Obviously, uh, we are confident
on our position,
regardless of the allegations.
KENDALL: And, uh,
this'll drop when?
HUGO: Well, online first,
thirty-six to forty-eight hours.
Um, so, yeah. Not two weeks.
Again, I've no idea
where that came from.
So, this sinks Pierce, right?
If you don't get that done
and signed off
-before this drops, then...
-Can we kill it?
No, you can't kill it.
Key.
LOGAN:
I've killed bigger.
No, not in the last five years.
Respectfully, Shiv, take a beat.
You're new to this, yeah?
SHIV: Oh, yeah, and thank fuck
for you I am.
This stinks of stale,
pale male,
and you need an outsider
to advise.
-Cease and desist, right?
-Yes, Hugo. We're on that.
KENDALL: No, we go, how deep
are their pockets,
fuckin' scare the shit
out of them.
Yeah, get word around,
our lawyers will go
balls to the wall,
say he's super pissed.
Subtext is this is personal,
we're feeling vindictive,
get the senior management
asking where they'll go
-if we bankrupt them.
-SHIV: Dad, cease and desist
and a full-on shit-flinging
freak-out is very high risk,
but we could get them to delay.
Tell them we'll get into it all
with them,
we'll cooperate,
play it all out,
-and then stiff them.
-Um, we could offer up
morsels in exchange
for postponement?
HUGO: We might be able
to find something,
-maybe out of the studios?
-SHIV: No.
Bigger. Juicier.
-People who are-- Sorry.
-(HAND DRYER WHIRRING LOUDLY)
Fuck, I'm sorry.
People who are writing about
cruise abuse scandals
are not gonna be getting all
kissy for a plot twist
-on frat baby two.
-No. Delay is too soft.
SHIV: Dad, ignore him.
Accelerate the deal.
What the fuck do you think
we've been doing, Siobhan?
Well, I have no fuckin' idea,
Dad,
because you never tell me
anything.
Cave on everything,
get them to at least sign
a letter of intent
before the story breaks,
it should hold.
No, Dad, we go for the piece,
we scare them into thinking
what they have isn't solid,
just fuckin' kill, kill, kill.
LOGAN: Ken, you're on that.
Start sprinkling
how fucking unreasonable I am,
Gerri, foot down on the deal.
LOI if we need,
They're half-pregnant.
Let's finish the fucking job
-before this breaks.
-GERRI: Sure, but I have to say
-just legally--
-LOGAN: Now.
I need it now.
What money's floating this year?
You mean for a white knight?
I could see what Roman
could scratch up.
-Hmm. Tom?
-Roman's hungry.
All right.
Shiv, let's get you out here.
-I need your help
on the optics.
-Uh, excuse me?
No. I-- I am not
flying out to Argestes
to be the face of this.
Then what the fuck are you doing
on the phone, Siobhan?
NATURE GUIDE:
So, welcome everyone,
to the Airbus Cultural
and Leadership Walk.
We're gathered here today
with a commitment
to sustainability
and stewardship.
So, this place-based learning
today will focus on
creating opportunities
for you to gain the...
-Oh, sh-- Tom!
-GUIDE: ...perspective for...
GREG: Sorry, Tom?
-Tom! Hey!
-(GUIDE CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
-Hey, buddy.
-Uh, problem.
Uh, you're not picking up?
-Dude, this is a great group.
-Sorry.
You did good.
It's like I've fallen into
a barrel of deal tits.
-(LAUGHING)
-Yeah. So...
So, there's a thing
about your talk.
-Um...
-My talk?
Um, yes. Uh...
When it got circulated,
uh, legal and comms wanted
you to be aware that
maybe we shouldn't go
with "ATN: We're listening."
Uh, okay. I mean, I really
do like, "We're listening."
It sounds like-- I mean,
it sounds like we're listening.
-No. Sure, it's just--
-Yeah.
It's just, um, there's
apparently, in the EPG
on the set top boxes,
the voice activation mode,
it does, um--
Like, there's a gray area
in terms of our data collection,
so that we are kind of like,
uh--
We actually are listening.
We're listening?
It's complicated,
but-- but, yeah.
It seems that we are sometimes,
uh, listening
quite aggressively.
-We're listening?
-Yeah.
But it's just to, like,
maximize the user experience.
But if that was to break,
-maybe--
-Oh, fuck!
So, yeah.
So, the question is,
is it a smart thing
for you to be saying,
"We're listening",
when we are indeed listening?
Why was I not aware of this?
Well, it's basically legal,
the guy said.
But he didn't wanna put that
in an email,
-so--
-What am I gonna call it now?
I don't know. Maybe, uh--
They suggested "we hear you."
Is that any better?
We tested this, Greg!
God damn!
-Yeah, I'd love to. Yeah, yeah.
-WOMAN: Great.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Hey. Everything is okay?
Uh...
Marcia.
It's possible that some things
will come out.
Nasty things.
People will say things
about me, about the company.
I might need to know
you're with me.
Logan...
when I am with someone,
I am with them.
Look at me.
I know who you are.
Hey, Rome.
Hey.
You see that guy?
Asgarov.
ROMAN: Oh, Eduard. Him?
Your dad is intrigued
by sounding out big money,
in the event that
the Pierce deal goes under.
Well, it's a done deal though,
right?
Yeah, I don't know.
Could you start a conversation
in case we need
an emergency exit?
White knight, go private?
With Eduard?
In his loafers made from
the skin of... I don't know,
what is that?
Human rights activists?
-(ROMAN CHUCKLES)
-Uh-huh.
His dad has a hose attached
to the central bank.
He's apparently conceptualising
a 300-year investing horizon.
So, this is what, make-up sex?
This is you grinding yourself
against me
and saying sorry for not
telling me about Shiv and Dad?
Roman, your dad wanted Tom
on this. I said you.
Come on, please.
I don't know what the world
is gonna look like in 36 hours.
Just-- Just do what you can.
I don't know if it's wise
for us to be seen talking.
Oh, I can take
a bit of tittle tattle.
Well, you're an old rhino.
I'm just a flighty,
little sparrow.
We'd like to ink it here
tomorrow.
Sure, um... I mean,
we appreciate the need
for expediency from your end.
From what I understand,
we're still some distance apart.
The break fee? Oh.
Tell your crowd if they push,
we'll cave.
Undermining your own position?
Could you sue yourself?
(LOGAN SIGHS)
Listen, Rhea.
Uh...
Can you persuade her that if
she doesn't sign here tomorrow,
we might walk?
Later. Uh...
I hear the culture hike's
the hot ticket.
But I'm not sure
you're crazy about
either one of those things.
-KENDALL: For tomorrow?
-JESS JORDAN: So, um, 11:00 AM,
we've got Thomas Fisher
doing "Qualities of Inequality".
-What difference...
-Right.
Hey, hey. Look who it is.
Daddy's boy.
I hear your staff are all
killing themselves now.
Yeah, at the thought that
you could be their boss.
Which you never will be.
No, sure, because of all
the acquisitions
you guys are making,
like, really bloating
yourselves up, huh?
There's a 75-dollar Cobb salad
here.
Dude, you should buy that,
use that as a defense.
-Yeah. Yeah, maybe.
-Uh-huh.
Either the Cobb salad
or something else tasty.
(LAUGHS) Ooh, that's...
scary. What could that be?
Is it a hamburger?
Is it calamari?
Is it fuckin'--
Dude, is it Napster?
(KENDALL LAUGHS) Look,
I'm just gonna say, honestly,
we have something coming in,
and it's gonna make your deal
untenable.
So...
I thought, as a friend,
I should mention it.
Oh, that's kind.
That's like BFF shit
right there.
Look, I'm not fuckin' with you,
Stew.
I swear on my children's lives
that right now,
we have a deal in the bag
so big that it's gonna kill
your approach. Okay?
And I feel a certain level
of regret
about how things have panned out
between us.
The thing is, Ken,
and due respect...
I really don't trust you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
So-- So, wait a second.
So...
So, we're gonna go with,
we--
We're gonna go with,
"we hear you"?
"We hear you". Yeah.
Are you still worried?
"We're listening",
"We hear you"?
It's the same problem,
isn't it?
Well, it's maybe less active.
You know, it's-- it's more--
Couldn't--
"Couldn't help glimpse you
changing unless, uh,
we put a spy cam
in your shower."
"We hear you".
I think it's a problem.
Um, we're-- we're listening,
we're hearing you.
I think it needs to be like,
"We're hearing," but...
but nothing that's gonna
bite me in the ass.
Yeah, okay.
-You know?
-So maybe it's like,
"ATN: We're here for you",
and "here" spelled H-E-A-R.
"We're hear  for you"?
That's just jibberish.
"We hear for you"!
Okay. "We hear for you."
-Yeah.
So that might be like,
"We-- We-- We hear for you,
man, 'cause you don't need
to hear. We  hear."
-Yeah, we--
-And also-- also,
"we're here for you."
Right? Is that...?
-Yeah. "We're your guys."
-Am I making sense?
It's good, because it's like,
it's not clear exactly
what the hell it means,
-so, lots of wiggle-room.
-Yes.
-"We hear for you."
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Okay. Wamsgans.
-"We hear for you."
♪ ("LAST NIGHT A DJ SAVED
MY LIFE" BY INDEEP PLAYING) ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Excuse me, Eduard. Sorry,
don't mean to be rude.
I'm, uh, Roman Roy.
-Oh. Hey, man.
-How you doin'?
Do you think we can talk
for a minute?
Hey. Sorry. Thanks.
So, how you doin'
with...
(SIGHS) You know,
just walking around,
getting pitched to fuck.
Yeah, huh.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
I hear you're in trouble.
-ROMAN: The proxy?
-EDUARD: Mm.
ROMAN: No. I mean,
we're under pressure,
but, yeah, nothing
we're worried about.
EDUARD: Hmm.
(SNORTS AND SIGHS)
-ROMAN: Mm. Thanks.
-Right. So...
you wanna hit me up
for my big bag of swag?
Borat the fucking pipeline
piece of shit?
Oh, no. Come on, man.
You're a discerning fellow
that everyone, like--
You know-- Are you kidding me?
You're like fucking
Warhol of, you know...
-of, um...
-Of?
-Of? You know where I'm from?
-Uh, Stanford?
-(LAUGHS)
-I mean,
Originally... No, I don't.
I do not know where
you come from,
and you know what?
I'm embarrassed about it.
I would like to know.
Man, the shit happening
-in Baku...
-Uh-huh.
I'm serious.
You're laughing at us?
We're laughing at you.
What is it you're, um,
bringing to me?
Other than a begging bowl?
ROMAN: Oh, no begging bowl here.
Just, uh, you know,
offering you some, maybe,
investment, uh, opportunities.
You're a fucking news guy,
right?
-Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-Why is the news so...
-(PUFFS CHEEKS) You know?
-ROMAN: Yes.
-No, I know-- I know.
-Yeah.
It's very... Yeah. I don't know
why the news is like that.
-I hate that.
-We can talk about that.
-Sure. Absolutely.
-Mm.
Yeah, the news with
a positive agenda.
A positive agenda
for my region.
-ROMAN: Okay.
-Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
But independent. Real stories
we'd fund, but hands off.
-Right.
-Objective.
A hundred percent independent?
But from our point of view.
All right. Yeah. Hey,
that's a really, uh,
really enticing project, yeah.
I'd like to keep
the conversation going.
Yeah.
-Oh, great. Good talking to you.
-Yeah.
Oh, sorry. Hey. Hey, uh,
big fan, uh...
of-- of all your money.
-Yeah.
GREG: Yeah.
Thank you. Hey, hey.
What's going on?
You-- You doin' the old cocaine?
(WATER RUNNING)
Could I get-- Maybe get
a little bump?
Bump? Greg, what happened?
GREG: It's like a power party
out there.
Like, tech titans
and, like, supermodels, and...
I just need a little boost.
Okay. Well, good luck
with that.
-Dude, come on. Come on. Stop.
-No.
They don't have paper towels.
They've gone all green and shit.
Dude, seriously?
So, all of a sudden,
I find myself in charge
of like a billion-dollar budget,
and it's really exciting.
And it's-- And it's--
I thought I would--
You know, I would
suffer from the pressure,
but I fucking love it.
I really love it.
-Hey.
-Hey!
Oh, my God. Shiv!
What the fuck?
-Nice to see you too, Tom.
-Nice to see you. Hey.
Hey, how are-- Why didn't you
tell me you were coming?
It was a last-minute thing.
-Hi. Shiv Roy.
-Pleasure. Nia.
Oh, of course. Yeah,
congratulations on the IPO.
-NIA: Thank you.
-Would you just--
-Could you give us a moment?
-Yeah.
-See you later, huh?
-TOM: See ya.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-But you're here.
-Uh-huh.
-Hope that's not inconvenient.
-TOM: No! No.
No, I'm not being-- No.
It-- It's nice.
-This. It's just...
-Uh-huh.
You know, you're often...
It's unsettling.
I mean, the texts.
Yeah, sorry. It's, uh--
I've just been busy.
Uh, whatever.
There's a potential crisis
coming. Um...
(SNIFFS)
There's a journalist
looking into cruises,
and there's a big piece
coming.
Okay.
-What?
-We don't know exactly.
-Uh, come here.
-Oh, shit.
Are-- Are they scapegoating me?
Is the piece about me?
No, the piece hasn't come out
yet.
-No one's read the piece.
-Is this about-- No. Okay.
Nothing has happened.
No, we're jamming it up.
I'm just telling you
what I know, okay?
Okay. Have I gone red?
I feel like I'm going red.
Suddenly everyone wants me here.
-Gerri called. And Rhea called.
-Right. Rhea?
Yeah. Suddenly I'm everyone's
favorite piece
of blast protection.
-TOM: Right.
-Yeah.
-Bullet-proof tits or something.
So-- So what--
what do they want a quote on?
Did they ask for me?
Tom, the piece is not
about you.
But there's a trail from--
there's a trail from Mo
to Bill to me. You're safe.
-Which is good, but, uh...
-Yeah.
I'm on the outside.
I don't know anything.
-That's why I'm useful.
-Yeah.
SHIV: Okay.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-♪ (MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
Were you trying to bang
Nia Bayton?
TOM: Excuse me?
Nothing.
Well, no. God! No.
-Oh, Shiv.
-Right. Fine.
Shiv.
I mean, I wasn't.
But if I was, uh...
that would actually be,
under the arrangement, okay.
You know?
-Tom. I know her.
-Well, you know of her, but...
It would be a bit
fucking awkward.
Just use your common sense,
okay?
Right, 'cause I might say that,
you know,
spending the night
with an actor
in a play financed
by your brother
and not telling me for ten days
was a little bit... awkward.
Come on. Nia's a real person.
With a face.
Fine.
No.
Okay.
So, anyway. It's nice
that you're here.
Yeah, I missed you.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
-How'd it go?
-Uh...
He might be good for
infinite billions,
but he wants a front
news channel to spew propaganda.
-We into that?
-Um, I guess.
-Depends on the numbers.
-Right.
Plus, the whole... I mean...
Obviously,
it's an ethical minefield.
Sure. Of course.
But if we took a position of
"fuck it"?
Well, that's an interesting
ethical position.
Silo it off?
Well, what is it?
Why's he got me chasing this?
GERRI: He still hasn't told you?
Pathetic, isn't it?
-I don't know. I can't say.
-Right. Course.
Course not.
You know, right now,
if, you know...
If anything happens to him,
you're on the piece of paper
as the next ruler
of the kingdom.
Mm. I think I've been made
well aware
of how unlikely it is
that will transpire.
Sure. Right.
But you know how you're...
so efficient
and good at your job?
-Well, thank you.
-But also sort of, like,
invisible?
Like wallpaper, like a...
boring old sort of nothing.
Like a competent kind of
clever filing cabinet
that everyone seems content
to have around?
-Uh-huh.
-ROMAN: And I'm like a fucking
-rockstar moron.
-GERRI: Right.
I mean, obviously,
these are our public profiles,
not our true essences.
I have thoughts,
but continue.
Well, just floating, like,
is there an angle here,
for a team up?
Like, me, kind of
a Jagger-Tarzan,
fronting things up
and swinging through trees
with my little dick,
singing and killing shit,
and you, back home,
cooking us soup,
and making sure the numbers
are right. Hmm?
Rockstar and the
mole woman?
Wow, you're really selling me.
But it would be chair and CEO.
Or CEO and chair.
And you will get properly
"fuck you,
fuck you, I don't even care
about climate change,
I'm in New Zealand with
my own private army" rich.
Not like some pathetic
asshole beach house
on the Vineyard rich.
It's late.
Off you go.
Thanks, mole woman.
Thanks, rockstar.
Night night.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
God. Here I am.
Is he gonna make me
take off my shoes?
-RHEA: You slept okay?
-Couple of hours. The usual.
What am I supposed to do
with this?
-You wear it, Nancy.
-Oh, absolutely not.
Oh, come on. Join the fun.
A show of false humility.
Everyone wears one.
Zuckerberg wears one.
Hand me a pen and I'll write
my name across my face.
You okay for this?
I think I made my position
perfectly clear,
but for whatever reason
you felt it urgently necessary
to put me in transit
for grapefruit juice
-and a plate of eggs.
-You should go at your own pace,
absolutely, that's imperative.
I just think this is such
a good deal for you.
For-- For us.
That it's worth a little haste.
So, we have a little room
for signing right in there.
Just in and out,
and boom.
-(LOGAN SIGHS)
-KENDALL: You okay?
Is it the altitude?
I don't know. Maybe.
Um, what-- what's...
-What's with the...?
-Uh, yeah, let's--
-let's move you around.
-No, no. No.
I'm not in a fucking wheelchair.
You don't--
I'm good. I'm good.
-(LOGAN CLEARS THROAT)
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-LOGAN: Sunglasses.
-Yeah.
I just had a call
from Karolina.
The magazine is not cooperating.
They feel bullied,
and the piece might go up
this morning. Print, Monday.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Well-- (STAMMER)
When? How long do we have?
Hours. Maybe minutes. I...
What do we do?
Do we bail?
-LOGAN: Hmm.
-KENDALL: Dad?
I'm thinking.
We should leave.
We need to get out of here.
Let's leave. We go. Oh.
Apologies.
Well, I feel like
the belle of the ball out here.
Very discreet.
You're happy with this table?
Visible enough from all sides?
Oh, it's all quite adolescent,
isn't it?
So, we're there. Correct?
Happy about the break fee,
the rest?
Sorry, did I miss the preamble?
I heard that you were
going to apologise for
your outburst at Ternhaven.
Oh, I... I-- Sorry.
I'm tired.
Well, that's appreciated.
My dad is just reflecting
our desire
to get this concluded
as swiftly
-and amicably as possible.
-Mm-hmm. Yes.
Every day a letter,
a meeting, a call.
I'm afraid my metabolism
tends a little slower.
We're due a check-in
with the cousins later on
this afternoon.
LOGAN: Yeah, but we can sign.
We are ready to sign.
-Ken?
-Yeah. Uh, right in there.
We thought we could sign
and then have a nice breakfast
-out here.
-But before we do, I--
I think there's perhaps a wider
conversation to be had here.
-Uh-huh?
-We would be interested
in exploring the option...
Uh, I'm sorry. I--
I can't concentrate
until I order.
Good God, the prices.
I'll, uh. I'll just have
tap water, thank you.
-Um-- No, no, thank you.
We would be interested
in exploring the option
of a bonus based on PGM
performance.
Of course.
We could cover the legal fees.
Your side, outside counsel.
The whole thing.
Well, this-- this isn't really
for us to discuss here, surely.
Well, I think I've explained,
uh, there's a limit
to our patience.
Logan, I think perhaps
we're not going to agree
to anything over watermelon.
Well, what's it gonna take?
Why are we still fuckin' around?
I think perhaps we all need
a little less
sunshine and vinegar.
It always gets a little testy
at the end. We're all good.
Nan, is there not a way
we could sign the LOI at least?
(CELLPHONE CHIMES)
Dad, I'm wondering if
maybe we should get
to our next appointment?
Oh, yeah, sure. Sure.
RHEA: Why don't you do that?
Let us chew a while.
-Soon.
-RHEA: See you later.
So, what do we think?
It's bad, but not... (SIGHS)
I don't know.
We should have gone at them
harder.
Paper copy. Now.
Coming up from reception
in two.
Oh, so everyone
in the fuckin' world
has read it except me, huh?
Hey. Okay, so where's the link?
Why did no one send me the link?
Just fucking Google it.
Google what?
I don't know what we did.
Uh, "Brightstar
roller coaster rape."
-Give me something.
-Sending link now.
Thank you. (SIGHS)
Well, fuck me.
Do you think they could
make this text
any fucking smaller?
This is pretty gray.
Yeah, but also vivid.
Hey. Great work on frightening
them off.
Uh-huh. Good work on stalling.
I'm reading.
-Thanks for coming.
-SHIV: Yeah, sure.
Uh, is everyone here remedial
at reading? Come on.
Is it me or is this bullshit?
Maybe this, maybe that.
-Rome, careful.
-Is this one of those things
that I need a woman to explain
to me why it's bad?
-Shiv? Is it bad?
-Don't fuckin' ask me.
I'm not your grope
Geiger counter.
What do you think, Rome?
Um, I do think it's bad,
but it's not that fuckin' bad.
LOGAN: (SIGHS) Fuck.
What's the protein?
HUGO: They found a woman,
Keerson.
She was working the cruises
back in the mid '90s,
name-checks Lester McClintock.
She says Uncle Mo asked for sex
with her and the other dancers
to get their contracts renewed.
ROMAN: Were all of you
in on this?
Did you all know
this was coming?
-It's not ultra-detailed.
-Amazing.
-So they fucked.
-It says sexual exploitation.
Yeah, she's saying that she
was one of the only ones
who refused to sign an NDA
and that we derailed her career
as a result.
-Is that it?
-GERRI: No, look.
The old Hewson story, the woman
that jumped and drowned...
LOGAN: Uh-huh.
...what if something
happened to her?
It's-- It's just innuendo.
The dancer says
that she heard stories of
dozens of other women
who actually signed the NDAs.
Okay, but in terms of
actual stuff?
GERRI: There's not a lot
of specifics. It's spooky words,
you know, data wipes, NDAs,
shadow logs,
hiding cruise malpractice.
But cold hard facts,
it's one woman in the 1990s,
not like 20 women
four years ago.
Great. I'm glad we're able
to do such good victim math.
Gerri's just saying
it doesn't necessarily
-punch through.
-Sure. But you know...
-this is not okay.
-We know it's not okay, Kendall.
We're preparing
a corporate response.
Do we have outside PR?
Pinks passed.
We've got J Preston.
SHIV: No, seriously?
They're three disgusting,
old, white dudes.
They'll probably just say
they're money-grubbing sluts.
-It's bad PR to hire them.
-I mean, call me sociopathic,
but doesn't this all seem
a tiny bit...
quaint in comparison
to the past few years?
LOGAN: He's right.
It's cultural splash back.
We're being punished
for the sins of others.
No one real gives a fuck.
No, no. We-- We can't be seen
to minimize.
I think we need to loudly
and quickly say
that this is not okay.
I think the question is
what closes this down fastest?
Do we say it's something
and we'll fix it,
or it's nothing and fuck off?
Something.
There have to be consequences.
Nope. Condemn and move on.
It's just good advice.
LOGAN: If we get into it all,
they'll never be satisfied.
It's bullshit.
It's all about me.
It's not real, it's not honest.
They don't give a flying fuck
for these poor bitches.
They hate me.
So, no! Condemn and move on.
New circus in town tomorrow.
What about the, um,
panel? Kendall?
Roman? Do we cancel?
No! Fuck no!
No. Obviously not, no.
-I meant--
-Obviously, it'd be great
if we do go ahead with it,
to, uh, have a person
who could speak to it
in terms of...
A woman.
-Gerri?
-Well, not legal counsel.
That gives the wrong sign.
No, I mean...
It's something of a no-brainer.
I... I don't know, I...
-Come on. I just got here.
-Oh, Shiv.
Would you? Please?
Oh, come on. I'm not good enough
for an invitation,
and suddenly this blows up
and you wanna jam it up my...
fucking uterus and smother it
in estrogen? Please.
No, I--
I'm not fully briefed.
We don't need Shiv.
I can do it.
We can do it.
Fine. We could do with
your help,
but fine.
Okay. Let's get out there.
-ROMAN: Walk of shame?
-Yeah.
Everybody out.
Business as usual.
So, you want me to touch base
with Rhea,
-take the temperature?
-No, no, no, no, no.
No one speaks to Rhea.
-Me, Laird, no one else.
-GERRI: Right.
Shiv, you're with me.
ROMAN: Little miss
fucking credible, huh?
-(CELLPHONE CHIMES)
-Logan, your 6:00 PM canceled.
-Also, your 7:30.
-Qatari money?
Uh, he said he'd meet
for coffee.
Wary about dinner.
And Jack canceled dinner.
Playground bullshit.
Everyone's waiting to see
how it plays out.
-(LAUGHING)
-Hang back a second.
What's up, dude?
I guess if you did have
something going on,
you know, like, deal-wise,
it's kinda, like,
dead in the water now, right?
Like some of the women
that went on those cruises.
Ken, I'm so sorry, bro.
I feel for you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-Hi.
-SHIV: How are you?
-Okay.
-SHIV: Uh-huh.
-You?
-SHIV: Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Good.
Jamie...
-You've seen?
-Uh-huh. Yeah. It's not good.
-LOGAN: No.
-It's not good for the Pierces,
it's not good for
the proxy fight.
-I need to speak to Rhea.
-I've tried calling.
Several times.
I'm wondering, in any event,
if I'm the right flavor
of person to be reaching out.
Now my reputation seems to be
a fluctuating currency.
But, uh, young Siobhan,
she's as close to T-Bills
as we're likely to get.
-(GRUNTS)
-Dad?
(LOGAN GRUNTS, RETCHES)
-Christ.
-Oh, my God. Dad.
-Jesus.
-Dad?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. We're fine.
-Uh-huh. We're fine.
-(LOGAN GRUNTS)
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
-Okay. We're fine. Thank you.
-RHEA: Hi.
-Oh, hey.
Sorry I couldn't meet you
for coffee.
I've had wall-to-wall meetings.
No, it's, uh-- it's fine.
You're hiding from us.
I'd do the same.
How's your dad?
The rumor mill is saying
practically dead.
Uh... yes. Fine.
It's-- It's the altitude.
Uh, so...
The piece. I'm sorry
for all the fuss.
You know how these things are.
No, I-- I don't, actually.
Okay. Well, uh,
for a few days...
you know,
people step away from you
like you farted
on the dance floor
but you ride it out.
It's no big deal.
Uh-huh. But you're here.
Checking in.
Yeah. Well, I was surprised
that you called.
The acceptable face.
Right.
So, you heard the piece
was coming,
and you're still pushing this?
You must really want
this to happen.
Well, I'm easy come,
easy go.
Uh-huh.
And, uh, where is everybody
else's head at?
Well, some of the cousins
are still reading,
which is surprising,
because...
they have views on
the new Jonathan Franzen
three days before it fucking
hits the shelf.
(CHUCKLING) Uh-huh.
Comfy on the fence?
RHEA: Yeah.
What about Nan?
Um, she's quite unhappy.
-SHIV: Mm.
-She doesn't like a muddle.
Well, I'm around
if she has any questions,
or to allay any fears.
-Sure.
-SHIV: Thank you.
I guess our first question
might be
did anyone kill any girls
on your boat?
No.
And, you know,
statistically speaking,
liners have a high death rate
simply because of the alcohol,
and the profile
of the people who tend to--
Yeah, but the fact that
I'm even having to ask...
Dead girls, boats? Ugh.
It's unpleasant on the tongue.
Well, perhaps the family
would be more comfortable
seeking another source
of investment.
I like your dad.
-Uh-huh.
-But...
what sort of a problem
are we looking at here?
Are we in the middle
of the storm,
-or is this the first raindrops?
-No, my dad has assured me
that this is not
a major issue.
Oh.
Truth is it's in the balance.
Uh-huh.
I think we-- they feel that
if it was just a few
bad apples from a long time ago,
then maybe they can
grit their teeth.
Well, that's going to be
the line,
-so...
-Good.
Well, Nan is coming to
your panel,
so I'm sure your flacks
are getting you all
jumping through hoops,
but if you could apply
a nice tourniquet,
then maybe we could
patch this up.
Yeah, it's just gonna be
Roman and Kendall.
Right. Roman.
Okay. Lovely guys.
-I thought perhaps you might...
-SHIV: No.
No, I'm not, uh, fully briefed.
So...
-Uh-huh.
-Yeah.
Could you get briefed?
Uh... I guess.
This isn't really my mess
-to clean up.
-No. Sure.
But... And I mean,
I don't wanna overdramatize,
but Nan gets cold feet
and you can't buy us.
Your dad could lose control.
He could.
That's real.
There are many different angles
to me appearing on that panel.
RHEA: Oh, sure. I get it, honey.
But listen.
All I would say is
there is a time
to accumulate capital,
and there is a time to spend it.
But hey, whatever. My dad
worked in an asbestos plant.
So...
It's all gravy, right?
And Roman, the safe place
is the three Rs, okay?
-Yeah.
-HUGO: Regret.
It happened a long time ago.
Responsibility.
Belongs to individuals
and not corporations.
Remedy. Super tough,
super vague.
The move is condemn
and move on. Got it?
-Yeah, got it.
-Okay.
Right, and if you need
to smash glass
in case of emergency,
it's enough of that
and back to the session.
Family ownership and corporate
continuity in the digital age.
-Whatever the fuck that means.
-(ROMAN GIGGLES)
-LOGAN: Hey.
-Hey. Uh, so, listen.
I think maybe
I should help out and do it.
-The panel?
-ROMAN: What?
-Yeah.
-Right,
but it's like nine minutes
till show time.
Shiv, no.
We already decided.
ROMAN: Yeah. We're all prepped.
Oh, okay, fine. So, send out
the two cover stars
for Toxic Male Monthly,
and, uh,
why don't we get Ted Bundy
up there,
-make it a three-way?
-Shiv, don't fuckin' pull this.
-Okay? We-- We asked you.
-Yeah, and I thought about it,
and I changed my mind.
-What do you think?
-Me?
-Uh-huh.
-HUGO: Um... Well...
-It's difficult.
-LOGAN: Oh. It's difficult.
Oh, I'm sorry, buddy.
Would you like a handjob
and an Advil?
Fuck off then.
It's smart.
Shiv works.
It's smart? A sudden,
last-minute line-up change?
Come on, man.
It's panicky as fuck.
She's not even in the company.
It looks... kind of
fucking cheesy...
-ROMAN: Yeah.
-...to be honest.
Like, throw our token woman
at it?
Well, it can't be two men
up there right now. It just--
It can't. Right?
I mean, if disruption
is an issue,
the audience is expecting
just Roys,
so, maybe-- maybe we
stick at two, and...
someone relaxes.
-Romulus.
-What, pull me?
That looks like a humiliation.
HUGO: Well, we could just say
you got sick.
No. No, you don't bump me.
That's bullshit.
Fuck that. Respectfully, Dad,
why is she even here?
Because I was fucking invited.
No. I need to be out there,
okay?
We need to hang tough,
you know? Together. Family.
Oh, okay, so let's just
get Connor down here, then?
-ROMAN: Oh, yeah, get Connor--
-We'll all pile on
so no one's nose
gets put out of joint. Is that--
-That's the important thing.
-I will put your nose
-out of joint
-SHIV: Oh, you should say that
-on the panel.
-That's a funny joke, Siobhan.
If you wanna know what
I really think, I think
you should drop both these two,
and I'll do it solo.
Wow. Someone thinks
they're Beyonce.
Pretty desperate, Shiv.
You know,
exploiting the situation
for personal gain.
I'm just thinking about
what's best for the firm. Okay?
Oh, sure. Sure.
No, that's, uh... (CHUCKLES)
That's coming through
loud and clear.
She's a loose cannon.
She is out of control.
SHIV: Look, Dad. I don't care.
I can make this go away.
I know this in my bones.
I don't need fuckin'
flash cards.
I'm not officially in,
so I have freedom of movement.
But if you don't want me,
then I don't give a fuck.
I will go eat lobster
and watch the fuckin' roast,
because it's all...
it's all gravy, baby.
It's important to remember
two fundamental things
about the news.
One: it's new.
All the things that are new.
The many news. The news.
Your boyfriend's really
suckin' ass
-out there.
-Two...
Hey, I'm sitting on the right
when we're out there.
You know, I can see your bra
through your sweater.
-Your dick's hanging out.
-Guys.
-There's no way...
-Guys, come on.
-Focus.
-Ro, Ro, Ro.
Do you want me to get
a booster seat for you,
when you're out there?
That's hilarious.
Your period just came on.
We aim to evolve our coverage
into something that is, uh...
not only dynamic,
but democratic.
And something that truly serves
our audience's
ever-changing needs.
And that is why we like to say,
ATN: We hear... for you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
-Hey. Well done, baby.
-TOM: Good luck. Good luck.
Well?
Afternoon.
Where's Nan?
SALLY-ANNE CORDELL:
Thank you for joining us.
Next up, please give a warm
Argestes welcome
to Roman and Kendall Roy,
joint chief operating officers
at Waystar Royco,
and political and corporate
strategist, Siobhan Roy.
Welcome. You don't do many
of these, Siobhan.
-Uh, no. I'm-- I'm hard to get.
-(KENDALL LAUGHS)
I'm exceedingly easy to get.
(SALLY-ANNE CHUCKLES)
So, I love this idea of
corporate continuity
being a positive
in the digital age.
But first, I wanted to give you
the opportunity
to respond to the magazine
piece, which came out today.
-Well--
-Yes, well-- Uh, go ahead.
No, no. Go ahead.
I mean, uh, I think the thing
for us is...
we don't want to simply
condemn and move on.
You know, we'll--
we'll want to look into this,
investigate it thoroughly,
and then absolutely
do the right thing.
Uh, I think we all have
the same view on that.
SALLY-ANNE: Uh-huh
And give us an insight.
Tough day for the company,
Siobhan?
Well, uh, obviously
I've been, uh,
given the privilege
of growing up
around the business,
whilst also being able
to plow my own furrow
on the outside.
She's been working
in politics for ten years,
so don't hold out
for a straight answer.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
Oh, I'll give you
a straight answer.
Look, obviously, as you say,
yes, it's been a tough day
for the company.
Sometimes there are, uh...
not errors, not misjudgements
in corporate governance,
-but, um--
-Catastrophes?
Well, no, because
it's not really about
corporate procedures
here, is it?
It's about human decency
that transcends
management structures.
I mean, you know,
that's what's so abhorrent
about these stories when
they come to light,
in whatever sector.
And sometimes it feels like,
"my God, it's--
it's everywhere."
Yeah, that-- that's absolutely
right. Uh-- I mean,
the language--
I just would say, um...
Yeah, we don't know.
Right now, we just don't know.
We haven't started
the necessary investigation,
so that language is, uh...
But absolutely,
on the sentiment.
I think he's telling me
to calm down.
(PANEL AND AUDIENCE LAUGH)
No, no, no. Hell, no.
No, I'm not. Uh...
I-- You know, if this stuff
is true,
doesn't matter to the victim
if these were isolated incidents
that happened, you know,
-many decades ago, right?
-SHIV: Right, and just because
it did happen 25 years ago,
is not a reason to simply
condemn and just move on.
No. No. Absolutely not.
You know, we've been accruing
and maintaining brand loyalty
for decades, and that trust
is a result of
knowing and respecting
-our customers...
-Stop looking around.
You will hurt your neck.
KENDALL: ...to compromise
that trust,
we'll take the necessary steps
to make amends.
Uh, we'll do whatever it takes,
you know.
We'll do whatever anyone wants.
You know, it's-- it's about
being completely unimpeachable.
And sometimes companies
develop bad habits,
and you need fresh eyes,
clean hands,
and new ideas to address those.
KENDALL: Yeah, I mean, that--
that's, uh, the great thing
about a company
that's structured like ours.
We can do that while
retaining core values,
you know, manage change.
-He's good, right? He's great.
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
I think I'm a little more
aggressive.
Sometimes I think you just need
a good old fashioned
dinosaur cull.
SALLY-ANNE:
And who's the big T-rex
in your sights?
Oh, no. I mean
dinosaur attitudes.
Dinosaur values.
No, I would never go after
my dad.
-That's a sport others enjoy.
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
-Hey, Tom. You did good.
-Hey.
Sorry I wasn't there for you
before,
but, you know,
"we hear for you" now.
(TOM CHUCKLES) No worries.
You fucking shimmered.
-SHIV: Thank you.
-TOM: Was that all okayed?
Nice. Bring your daughter
to the slaughter.
Tell the old dinosaur
what you were gonna do?
KENDALL: Hey, I'm sorry.
"We will do whatever
anyone wants"?
-Yeah.
-Fuck it! Right? It played.
It's just words.
There was no press anyway,
so who gives a shit?
-Hey.
-What?
-What was that?
-I was just dancing.
Hey, I'm sorry about Nia
last night.
-You can do whatever you like.
-Thank you.
It's not like I really want to.
-Really?
-No.
Because, truthfully,
when I saw you talking to her,
I wanted to smack her
in the face and say,
"Back up, bitch. He's mine."
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
-You should've.
I would've really liked
to have seen that.
SHIV: Oh, yeah? (LAUGHS)
It was too much, Siobhan.
-Dinosaurs?
-Uh...
Yeah. It was over the line.
Shiv went over the line.
Oh, I-- I think it was
pretty clear
-that I was talking about--
-Oh, no, it was clear. Yeah.
You tortured the old dinosaur.
You barbecued him live, hmm?
Don't fuck with me!
Hey! No!
Don't fucking touch him!
SHIV: It's okay. Jesus, Dad.
It played well, okay?
Word is it played well.
-It's okay.
-SHIV: Ro, are you okay?
-(ROMAN SPITS)
-SHIV: Here.
-SHIV: You all right?
-KENDALL: You all right?
Yeah, I'm fuckin' fine.
Fucking leave me alone.
I'm fine.
It's just a tooth.
I'll get another one.
WOMAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
as it's traditional
to roast us home
from Argestes,
it's the Argie awards.
And please welcome your host
for this evening,
Zell Simmons!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Hey.
All right. How you doin'?
All right. Look at all you guys
with your blazers on,
coming from Burlington
Coat Factory, huh?
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
-That where y'all shop at?
I'm glad you guys
are out here,
solving the world's problems.
I don't see you solving
anything, jerk-off.
Yeah, that's like a guy
sitting on a grain silo
in the middle of a famine,
going,
"Why is everybody so down?
-They don't have WiFi here?"
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
Did you talk to Roman?
Is he okay?
Yeah. Uh, he said
he wasn't gonna come.
But-- But he was fine.
All right, who do we got here?
Who we got here?
Oh, we got-- The Roys are here!
What's up, guys!
Oh, shit,
I hope he doesn't do me.
Ahoy there! Permission
to never fuckin' board?
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
I think this is going to be
a long bit.
I don't understand
this tradition.
Why do we come to be insulted?
How is this entertainment?
ZELL SIMMONS: I shouldn't even
be joking about them like that,
because they're
in the midst of a...
"hands on investigation".
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
Yeah, I hear there's a lot
of deals going down here, too.
Man, someone's gonna
make a sale.
To Waystar.
Hey, I think that's great.
That's like the Hindenburg
going down,
and they're like,
"Yeah, hydrogen blimps.
Sign me up!
-That's the future, baby!"
-(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
No, that's a horrible idea.
It's worse than that,
at least nobody was forced
to give a blowjob
on the Hindenburg!
(AUDIENCE GASPS, LAUGHS)
-Where are you going?
-SIMMONS: Oh, man.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
SIMMONS: Look at Logan Roy, man.
I love that guy, man.
-I mean, he's a very nice guy...
-It's funny 'cause it's true.
Fuck off.
LOGAN: Hey. Hey, Nan.
-Nancy!
-Let's talk later.
Oh, here comes Rhea.
Of course.
Oh. Let's talk.
I-- I hope you're
not swayed by--
I mean, you get these hothouse
atmospheres,
-but we're good.
-NAN: We'll talk.
-We're good though?
-No.
But we can explain.
(SIGHS) Look, it's, uh...
It's a tempest in a tea kettle.
Relax. I drink them
by the pint.
(LAUGHS) Oh, thank you.
I am perfectly relaxed.
But if you want to talk
about it,
-it's over.
-RHEA: Oh, Nan.
-Come on. Calm down.
-LOGAN: A few bad jokes,
what, and you bend?
I think you're made
of stronger stuff
-than these Palo Alto pricks.
-Oh, it's intolerable.
I had a call
with the family tonight,
on a number of matters,
and they've left it
in my hands.
Which call?
After-- After our call?
Rhea, may I ask you something?
Have you ever had
any communication
or meetings with Logan Roy
-that I'm not aware of?
-What?
Um... Not--
-Not in terms of--
-Are you trying to figure out
what your attorney
would let you say?
-No! I have always acted with--
-I have been rolled.
I have been sand-bagged.
This is a good deal!
You spoke to Logan
on the 13th.
What was the nature
of that discussion?
I do not recall. It could
have been any number of--
I would like your resignation.
I don't appreciate
being hustled.
This is a good fucking deal!
You won't get a deal like this
again.
RHEA: It is a good deal,
and I have never had anything
in mind
other than what's best
for Pierce.
Oh, horse potatoes.
You work for Rhea Jarell.
And as long as our interests
were aligned, it was fine.
You'll be hearing
from the lawyers.
Hey. Hey, hey!
I haven't finished.
NAN: Good night to you both.
Good riddance to bad rubbish.
You turn this down
and you're fucking
your whole family.
Oh, I think my family
will be fine,
but thank you for your concern.
-Let's go.
-LOGAN: Hey, wait!
We haven't finished!
We haven't fucking finished!
Do you hear me?
We haven't-- Hey! Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Do-- Fucking--
(SCREAMS INCOHERENTLY)
Stop! Stop!
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
TOM WAMBSGANS:
We need to end this now.
The copies. I want them.
Well, in case things
were to turn nasty--
They're not gonna turn nasty.
No one's gonna break your legs.
Yeah.
Okay, well, that feels
a bit nasty.
The Pierce pursuit
has played badly.
A significant chunk of stock
is wavering.
Caroline.
I need her three percent.
I think we got a problem.
KAROLINA NOVOTNEY:
They're saying you punched him
which caused him
to drive his car into the river.
ADVISOR: How about we offer
a visit to the family?
GERRI KELLMAN: It might be time
to start getting worried.
LOGAN ROY: I've never run away
from anything in my life.