[Rick] Ugh. Guess this is how it ends.
I thought I was better than this.
Dramatic voiceover while stranded in space?
I guess when you're dying,
the first thing to go is your creativity.
Citadel's gone
and the saucer we escaped in is out of power.
I'm so scared in here.
[Rick] The extra Mortys went feral.
[screams]
Ah. Some problems solve themselves.
Been drinking a lot-- Morty, write this down.
I don't have a helmet like that Avengers guy did.
Been drinking a lot of my piss.
Portal gun's still broken--
- I guess that was all part of Evil Morty's plan.
- Evil Morty? Can we stop flattering this guy?
His plan was to monologue and fuck off.
He basically threw a tantrum
to announce he was quitting Twitter.
Nobody quits Twitter.
Hey, remember, like, a second ago
when you pretended not to know
who Iron Man was? Who was that for?
Shush, shush, Morty.
This is how we go. Bear it with grace.
Spinal cord, Robitussin as a base,
then surprise me.
[groaning]
[tapping on glass]
- Mom!
- Beth, maybe!
[inaudible dialogue]
Is she trying to say something?
We can't hear you.
How dumb are--? Beth, you're in a vacuum.
Sound travels on air. Why am I yelling?
- Wow, great.
- Yeah, that's-- Wow.
Really worth it. That was not worth it.
It's corny. You. Corn.
Dying of starvation here.
Oh, my God. Stop explaining. Stop explaining!
Are you finished?
She's not finished.
- Nice.
- Real mature. Real classy.
[theme music playing]
- It was a good line.
- I didn't need it to be.
- I don't care what you think.
- Oh, my God. She found you. Eat.
Oh, hell, yes.
Hold on, buddy.
Our systems could go into shock from solid food.
Digestibot, convert to nutrient mass.
I'm just gonna risk it.
Since when do you guys get stranded?
- Thank you.
- Almost left them there.
Portal travel's broken. Mm.
Are these heirloom tomatoes?
Digestibot, try these.
- Yum, yum.
- You can't hop realities anymore?
That mean you'll finally have to wash your robe?
Good point.
I need to reboot the portal index immediately.
Basically a hard reset on the fluid.
Hold tight. The Earth's gonna shake a bit.
- Um...
- Oh.
- Oh, shit.
- Wait. What? What's happening?
Instead of resetting portal travel,
I may have reset portal travelers.
Too late to apologize.
Rick, why am I pulsing green?
Don't say you don't know,
because you're pulsing green.
- Are we about to die?
- No, we're about to vanish from this reality.
- That's totally dying.
- No, it isn't.
It's everyone from this reality
returning to their reality of origin.
- Back to our original universes.
- I explained it fine, Morty.
You're spoon-feeding spoons.
Where's Summer?
Oh, nice. You guys are back. Whoa.
Three of us are one-way blind-hopping.
You gotta help us get back.
There's protocol for this
in your chores server, file name booger-aids.
- Every file is booger-aids.
- I hate naming things.
Just search for words
like "one-way blind-hop, reset nav beacon."
- Why do I have a reality of origin?
- No time to explain, Jerry.
Counting on you, Summer.
One-way blind-hop beacon protocol.
Here we go!
So there was time to explain.
Don't waste extra precious seconds
with your pettiness, Jerry.
- Summer, let's run down--
- One-way blind-hop reset beacon. Booger-aids.
Cool.
- Wow.
- There was so much time to explain!
Fine. Hindsight is 20-20.
Who has ever taken this long to vanish?
How did I end up not in my own universe?
Oh, my God. The Jerryboree.
[both] The Jerryboree!
Deep cut.
But where's our real Dad and our real Morty?
Buried in the backyard.
That's what the possums are after.
Dad's got you in the family business too?
Yeah, Morty is an easy mark,
but Rick pays me in things like...
Wolverine claws.
Well, looks like you got this.
See you guys in another two years?
Or you could stick around for this one.
Looks like it involves Grandpa's grotty citadel.
We could, you know, break things, loot stuff.
I should probably get back to saving the galaxy.
Please?
Uh, guess I could loot some stuff.
Fine. Let's make it quick.
Awesome. I've never been.
Let's do this. Adventure family.
Whoo!
Uh, okay.
Fuck.
Excuse me? Bro, Ricks don't pass on this.
[Diane] Rick, is that you?
Yeah, Diane.
You've been gone so long.
Did you find our daughter's killer?
Not yet, sorry. Still looking.
You'll find him.
You always do everything you set your mind to,
except keep your family alive.
But that was hardly your fault.
Mute.
If I could be muted, I wouldn't be too good
at haunting you, would I, you dirty bear?
- I forgot I wanted to be haunted.
- You predicted you might.
That's where haunting comes in handy, huh?
Very good point, sugar.
Rick?
Hello? Original family?
Sorry about last time.
Rick, he was in space prison.
We couldn't just-- Hello?
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
[screams]
Oh, jeez.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Ah. Fuck. Damn it, Morty.
There's no doctors anymore.
Dad?
Figures it's underwhelming the one time I visit.
Yeah. Sorry. Usually there's cowboy
Rick and Mortys and stuff.
Looks like they could use
a couple repairmen Rick and Mortys, right?
Oh, tight. Little scavenger dudes.
If they shoot at us, I'm allowed to...
do this. Shit, yeah.
Space Mom, get in on this.
- Cool Mom.
- Keep it moving. I don't have all day.
[Beth] I got it.
[screeching]
I got it. I got it. Sorry.
Sorry. I got it. Sorry.
I was gonna do it.
Terrestrials, am I right?
[Diane] I kept up the search in your absence.
You want a new list of potential locations?
You're always just one room away, huh?
Yeah. Remember, you thought
if you could see or touch me,
it might give you a level of com-com-comfort.
Right. Can't have that. Come on, Summer.
Who's Summer? Should I be jealous?
I hope Summer knows
what happens to the people you love.
[doorbell rings]
[gun cocks]
Hey, Rick.
Hey, Mr. Goldmanbachmajorian.
Still alive, huh? What's up?
I was wondering if you could help me
make sense of a note I found this morning.
It's written by someone claiming to be me.
They say my mind is "held captive in a time loop,
trapped in the day of a traumatic event
by the agony of a formidable intelligence,
but also that my captor forgot about aging,
that my body spoils and yearns for death
while my soul remains stuck in place,
caught like a fly in amber."
Right. I used to "drink" drink.
- Uh, no clue, pal.
- That's okay.
I found other notes in the trash just like it.
Poor weirdo. I pity them.
Wish they could let go and move on.
- Sounds healthy.
- Sure would be.
- [Goldmanbachmajorian groaning]
- [thuds]
[Goldmanbachmajorian] Sweet death.
[Diane] Was that symbolic? Are you letting go?
I understand, baby. I forgive you.
You don't get to say that. You're not her.
You're a thing I built to torture myself.
This timeline is cursed. I gotta get out of here.
Because you wanna move on.
Because I don't.
[burps] And I have to.
I came back on accident.
Guy I'm looking for, he's not findable, Diane.
I live with a version of Beth now.
Sounds like a version of nice.
We have grandkids. That's who Summer is.
She'll get me out of here.
She reminds me of you.
Oh, really? Is she dead too?
Bye, Diane.
You're not honestly gonna fly into that rift
without coordinates, are you?
Don't give up on us, Rick.
I don't make the rules. Haunters gonna haunt.
Baby, are you killing yourself?
I'm more embracing the win-win
of risking my life.
[dramatic music playing]
- Where's Mom and Summer?
- Oh, they're gone. Sorry, Morty.
"Gone" gone?
We spent a long time in that ice.
A gentle mutant licked us out,
but Beth got sick and Summer didn't thaw right.
[groaning]
With no one left to blame,
I finally had to deal with myself.
Buried my grief at Barnes and Noble.
Four Agreements, Eat Pray Love,
Frank Miller's The Dark Knight Returns.
Learned to accept things for what they are.
In a few of these, the whole brain is still intact.
Makes you wonder if some people
were still in there just trapped in the horror.
Anyway, it's awesome protein.
I'm so sorry, Dad,
but my real, original Dad beat the apocalypse.
I guess we all underestimated you.
Hey, what's that game
we used to try to play as a family?
- The one we never finished?
- Downbeat.
Yes. Let's play Downbeat.
I can find it. We can finish now.
Yeah. You should totally do that.
Hey, yeah, cool. I got it.
We'll play Downbeat and we'll camp here
tonight, then rebuild the house.
You know, we got food,
fresh water, and we've got family.
The fuck?
[Hermit Jerry] I wrote this note in advance
in case you're wondering how I left so fast.
My plan is to wait for you to turn your back,
then I'm going to grab all your shit and split.
Depending on how long you're out of the room,
you'll probably be thinking,
I can't be that far away
and you'll want to foll--
Wrote this fast because had to set trap.
- Thought you'd have cooler shit. See other note.
- Motherf u--
Whoa, whoa, slow down! Slow down! Not cool!
What the hell, Dad?
Don't take it personal. One of the four agreements.
I don't remember the other three,
but I know Commissioner Gordon
was cool with Batman moving on.
- Batman doesn't abandon people.
- You abandoned us.
I deserve that. But, you know, it improved you.
Oh, am I cool enough for you now?
Well, that was easy.
It only cost me fucking everything.
Whoa, hey, I--
You came back and talked about us
like we weren't people, Morty.
Then you bailed and left us to freeze.
I was apologizing for that earlier.
Your mom and sister died, Morty!
And I moved on.
From caring.
And that is the best deal
you will ever get. So take it.
Please don't go.
If Rick comes back,
we can find you a new reality,
a new Mom, a new Summer, a job.
Oh, you don't get it, kid.
Except for this conversation,
my life is perfect.
Rick was always right.
Everyone needs to let go.
[sobbing]
[leaves rustling]
Aw. You came back.
I guess we really did form a bond.
Ow! Hey, stop it! Get away from me!
No! Help!
All right. Pin dropped, Grandpa.
Come and get us.
[Rick] Come on, come on, come on!
[Diane] Baby? Something to keep in mind.
If you were pulled home by whatever happened,
it's likely our target was as well.
It's also likely he's having
as much trouble leaving as you are.
He's trapped.
- [Summer] Grandpa!
- Oh, fuck, yes.
- [Summer] Grandpa? Grandpa?
- Summer! Gold star, always believed in you.
- Now the hard part.
- Hard part?
Way worse things than me
can see that beacon too.
Hunker down and protect it while I grab Morty.
Rick, out. Try to survive.
Oh, shit.
Domestic Mom should hide maybe.
- "Domestic Mom"?
- I mean, she's the cool space one.
Look, I'm not looking to get caught
in whatever this is.
- You guys can both hide maybe, hash it out.
- Quit talking down.
I'm you with the patience to do laundry.
Stop being jealous of our bond.
She ran from our choices.
I have to parent them.
It's not like I didn't care.
That's what the clone was for.
- [both screaming]
- Moms!
[sobbing]
[loud whooshing]
- Morty!
- Rick?
I knew it.
I knew you wouldn't leave me. Ow.
- The fuck?
- Did you see another Rick here?
Nondescript haircut, sci-fi jacket.
Of course you didn't see him.
You'd be dead or you'd be a bomb.
Do you feel bomb-y?
Nah, you would have blown up by now.
Wasn't the Rick here dead?
That's why you picked places, right?
Uh, well, your Rick, yeah, not dead.
More like not around.
When I met you, I was sort of hoping
he might turn up one day.
You son of a bitch. I got you.
- Where are we going?
- To kill your grandpa, little buddy.
Wait, what?
I don't understand.
My original Rick killed your family
and you were just waiting for him to come back?
You understand fine. That was A-plus re-piping.
We're here.
This guy, Morty, he hates being found
but loves building elaborate shit.
Like playing a ton of Minecraft,
but all on a private server.
Am I in a fucking K-hole right now?
What is going on?
Whoa, you found me.
I shoot the first monitor too.
Listen, I'm not here. Or am I?
There's the clone you found.
Or maybe it's me all naked.
Just a little Keyser Söze.
Why would I admit it's not?
Yeah. Look at him. Look at him go.
Look at him dance. Or me.
Again, it might be me, like a Saw thing.
I'm very sneaky.
Here's a bunch of killbots to deal with
while you wrestle with that.
I don't know who I'm talking to.
It's all prerecorded.
But if you got this far,
you probably think you're real special.
Tell you what.
There he goes. Maybe that was me.
If you follow him, we could do a big fight.
50% chance I'm not lying.
[Space Beth] We're in trouble, asshole.
I shouldn't have to beg.
- Wait, my moms are in trouble?
- Those versions of them are.
We gotta save them.
Rick, this is an obvious trap.
- If you go down there, he's gonna kill you.
- Good.
What?
Now what?
If you don't care if you die,
why do you care if I die?
Knock it off. Get out of here.
You did this last season.
You're like a suicide bomber.
- Takes one to know one.
- You get it from him, not me.
I don't know him.
You're my grandpa, Rick.
Rick and Morty. A hundred years.
This place totally might go up.
Here's a bunch of count downs.
One of them's probably accurate.
Fucking stupid fifth-dimensional stomach juices.
Sorry for the sitcom fight
and maybe getting us digested.
You've got incredible timing.
Don't be a bitch. I'm parenting.
Makes sense you don't recognize it.
You've been out of practice.
Good. Glad they have you.
I don't want to be Space Mom.
You've made that clear.
Just don't let Summer mistake
your rejection of her for good taste.
I'm not trying to. It's all her.
It'd be cool if you were around more.
I don't wanna get married.
I'm 17. My affection is the wind.
Don't try to compete for it.
I could hear every word of that
through the helmets.
Thank fuck I only had to kill most of them.
Jesus, that ship really has sailed.
And now we feast!
[screaming]
This emergency was oversold to me.
- Grandpa!
- Morty!
Moms!
- Wait, if they had to wear helmets--
- I do childproofing stuff while you're asleep.
- Why don't you childproof Dad?
- Great reminder.
- Wait. Ugh.
- Time to get Jerry.
Maybe I wouldn't be so uptight if I wasn't married
to an unemployed receptacle of human fear.
Get a job, Dad. It's been a decade.
Brutal. I know a good alligator park
if you wanna kill yourself.
- I got expelled today.
- [doorbell rings]
- You are so fucking dumb!
- What a horrible thing.
- Too bad, Morty.
- Hi, hon.
[gasps]
Oof. Some real Season 2 vibes in there.
You know what I'm saying?
Never thought I'd say this,
but I think I'm glad we spent that time divorced.
- Uh, one second.
- I'll build a swing set.
I may technically be from here,
but I'm a goddamn interdimensional traveler now
and all of you can kiss my sci-fi ass. [grunts]
[all laughing]
It gets me every time.
Wow, what an amazing joke I just told.
And also, what an adventure.
It doesn't matter where we're from
if we're together.
- Good final moral thing.
- This is everyone's original dimension now.
Great wrap-ups, kids.
- Ugh. You're back.
- Oh, shit. Season 2 Jerry.
Before you bust my balls,
can someone help with the shower?
It's colder than Beth on our anniversary.
Also, look who I found in Rick's room.
Mm, I'm Mr. Frundles.
I don't care how cute he is,
we agreed no Boogens in the house.
- Season 2 Jerry, don't!
- Ow!
- [Beth] Mr. Frundles!
- Everybody in the car.
I'm Mr. Frundles!
- I thought he was Mr. Frundles.
- Everybody in the car! Now!
[all] I'm Mr. Frundles!
What the fuck, Dad?
Why bring that thing into our house?
It was cute. Fuck.
We gotta find a new timeline now.
You know how hard that is without portals?
We gotta do the thing
with the rift and the beacon again.
The whole fucking episode
all over again.
Car, fabricate some vomit bags.
Can't we just go back and fix it?
[groans] I'm Mr. Frundles!
I can't believe portal travel's broken.
- I'll get to it when I get to it.
- Lift with your knees.
How many times have you done this?
[retches]
Oh, God.
- And you swear they die of natural causes?
- Mm-hm. Yep.
The same as our old timeline? Even my stuff?
Bit of a rush job.
So they do say "Parmesan" weird.
- How do they say--?
- Parmeesian.
- Jesus Christ.
- I could have left you guys.
You think the concept of family matters to me?
I'm not even your Rick.
- "I'm Denial Rick."
- [Beth] See you inside, Dad.
Sorry I was such a dance mom about Summer.
She's your daughter too.
No, boundaries are good.
But speaking of, maybe I've put up too many.
- Is it okay if I come around sometimes?
- That could be nice.
- That's a cute outfit.
- The one we always wear?
[groans]
Yes, Morty?
You promise I'm not bait
to make that Rick come back.
What? For you to be bait,
the guy would have to value something.
He truly does not give a shit.
He's the real deal.
Parmeesan.
Parmeesian.
Parmees-ian.
- Parmeesian.
- Gross. I hate it.
- Yeah.
[theme music playing]
Hello? Morty?
- That one big rat?
- Whoa, this is a development.
- [shouts]
- Whoa, whoa, little guy.
Easy. You're a Jerry, right?
Never got too close to the concept.
Boy, you have really arc'd out.
Were you putting on pants?
What? No, I was naked to fuck with a guy.
Speaking of,
did you talk to me or a little kid around here?
Maybe. Why?
If you hate them too,
I could be down for a little team-up.
I don't "team up" anymore.
Managing people, such a headache.
- Fatality. Jerry wins.
- [gasping]
Oh, goddamn, dude. Badass.
[groaning]
Why are you here?
Buddy, I have been asking myself
that exact same question.