Good morning and happy, my second
favorite holiday after Christmas,
Development Day every...
Ooh. Donuts. Come on.
Oh, that's nice, but I am cutting today,
so I will just have a yogurt.
Hmm, how am I feeling today, right?
Am I feeling sophisticated
or am I feeling nutty?
Am I feeling chocolate frosted?
- Janine.
- [Janine] Oh.
Classic. Thank you.
You know me well, Mel Mel. Hmm.
Well, six years will do that to you.
Oh, did you guys hear
about the ceiling falling in at Addington?
- [Gregory] Mmm.
- And that building was built after ours.
- Really? Wow.
- [Barbara] Mmm.
Morning, y'all. I did get finer.
We don't have to talk about it.
And thanks to whoever
brought in these donuts.
- I thought you did.
- Now, why would I do that?
They were here when I came
to get my coffee this morning.
Hmm. "Donut worry about a thing."
[Jacob] Oh, that place is great.
Remember I brought donuts
for the last day of school last year.
- [Janine] Oh, yeah.
- [Gregory] Oh, yeah.
But none of us got any
because we were determined
to clean our classrooms and get the hell
out of here before rush hour.
[laughing, exclaiming]
[Ava chuckling fades]
[spits]
Mr. Johnson, um,
you cleaned out the kitchen
at the end of last year, right?
- Yeah.
- [teachers mumble]
- Wait, did you say last year?
- Yeah.
- Nah.
- [trash bag rustling]
[Ava groans]
Be kidding.
- [Gregory grunts]
- Guys, this year's still gonna be great.
- [loud clattering]
- [Melissa] Whoa!
I wasn't living here.
Ooh, donuts.
[♪ "Hold 'Em" playing]
Welcome back lolly? Okay. [chuckles]
Y'all know what time it is.
It's Development Day. [chuckles]
Some of the, uh, "grown-ups" are
dreading school starting,
but let me be the first to say
"welcome back" with a lollipop.
- Here you go. [chuckles]
- Thank you.
Melissa.
My lolly.
Barbara, you don't want
a welcome-back lollipop, do you?
I'd love one. Thank you.
[Barbara] Oh, I'm elated to be back.
At the end of the last school year,
I really found a groove
with the music class,
so I spent all summer lesson planning
and familiarizing myself with the music
that the students love these days.
I've just been re-energized.
It's a new chapter in the book of Barbara.
Can y'all come take a look
at something real quick?
Like this? [grunts]
See we won't be having any fun
this school year. [huffs]
Somehow the stove got all out of place.
We cannot have the hookups
exposed like that.
Not my jurisdiction.
I'll have someone come check it out.
Oh, please. [chuckles]
You don't got to call anybody.
Step aside. I got this.
It just needs a little... love.
The rumors are true. I'm in love.
His name is O'Shon, and he works in tech.
You know, when we first started dating,
everybody was against us.
The district even fired me
to try to break up our relationship,
and Janine tried to keep me
from getting my job back.
But... [chuckles] ...in spite of it all,
we... we made it through.
[♪ presentation playing
moving, emotional music]
[Ava chuckles]
In summary, I go above and beyond
because I'm in love and O'Shoned.
Ava, for the dozenth time,
you really shouldn't show us that stuff.
It is an HR violation.
So is your shirt.
Okay. What else? New counselor coming.
Boring. [inhales sharply]
Oh. Everyone, please welcome our new
fourth-grade teacher, Dominic Clark.
Where do I know that name...
- I don't know.
- Dominic Clark.
Did you star in that new Tyler Perry movie
Madea's Destination Wedding?
No, Mrs. Howard. It's me Dominic.
I was in your kindergarten class.
[gasps] Dominic, how could I forget?
You colored everything red.
Still do. I'm just playing.
I don't do that anymore.
[staff laughing]
It's just an honor
to be your new colleague.
My new colleague.
- Hi, everyone.
- Hey, how you doing?
Wow, imagine that.
My kindergarten student of nearly, whoo,
20 years ago is my new colleague.
Which is crazy, Barbara,
because you guys look the exact same age.
Yes, we do. Uh...
This is not gonna be good.
This is a minefield, okay?
That guy is gonna set Barbara
back to old grumpy Barb.
Yeah, no, I'm on this.
All right. Due to an increase
in middle school students,
Ms. Schemmenti will no
longer be teaching second grade.
She'll be moving up
to teach middle school math in homeroom.
[staff exclaiming]
No, no, it's all right. I already knew.
And, you know, every app is
like sports betting these days,
so I figured that this is an opportunity
for me to refresh my percentages skills.
And since there aren't enough
second graders for two classes,
- Ms. Teagues will now have 40 students.
- [staff exclaiming]
I, for one, am excited
to see if it will break her. [chuckles]
It won't.
- It might.
- Okay, now you're just doing crowd work.
We're gonna go finish
setting up our classrooms.
Yep, Development Day over. Good job, team.
Well, did someone say "team"?
- Who's the suit?
- [Ava] Oh. Right.
This paper skeleton is Craig.
The district sent him for some reason.
Uh, yes. Good morning,
Abbott Elementary, and welcome back.
- All right!
- There it is.
Uh, Principal Coleman is right.
I am here for a reason.
The district thinks Abbott is
a very special school,
and we wanted to make it more special
by reaffirming
some core district principles
and moral guidelines
through team building.
- [staff groaning]
- This is a result
of their no-longer-trusting-us
because of last year's lying.
Extortion of businesses.
Yep, and our annual tradition
of unpermitted shows and festivities.
Maybe. Yes.
So, this is a punishment couched
in team building activities?
Yes. To show we're all one big team
and rebuild the trust
between the district and Abbott
that you all shattered,
I will be leading everyone in a day
of mandatory team building activities.
So without further ado,
let's all obligatorily
scoot to the library.
- [Craig] Whoo.
- [staff groaning]
Oh, come on, everybody.
A few team building games might be fun.
Oh, not games, activities.
So, when I was in your
kindergarten class 20 years ago--
Let me stop you right there, Dominic.
Oh. Uh-oh. Here we go.
Um, hey, Dom, you should probably--
You know, I'm trying to keep my cool.
But you got me so excited.
My former student is now my colleague.
Oh, what a blessed day to be alive.
- Yes!
- Hey, poindexter.
Whatever this is, can we hurry it up?
Some of us got real jobs to get back to.
Yeah, okay.
Uh, to start us off,
you're gonna share
something people know about you,
and something they don't.
So, I'll start.
Uh, something people do know
about me is that I love my job.
[staff groaning]
Uh, something you don't know is
that I wear a cross,
but I don't believe in God.
But he believes in you.
I'm Barbara Howard,
and one thing you all know about me is
I have a very strong and loving
relationship with God and Gerald.
Oh, but one thing you don't know is
I never use the Lord's name in vain.
Mm-mmm.
Melissa.
- Sweet baby Jesus...
- It doesn't count 'cause it's a baby.
[Melissa] So, sure.
Uh, something that you know about me is
you already know everything
you need to know about me.
Something you might not know about me is
that I will smack you in the mouth.
Okay.
Uh, Mr. Johnson.
Something you know about me is
I used to work at Chippendales.
Hey, hey, hey.
Something you don't know is
I swam an entire triathlon.
- Well, that's just an "athalon."
- Wait, why swam?
Easier than riding a kite.
I think you mean a bike.
I wouldn't know. Never rode one.
That's why I swam the whole thing.
What do you mean you never rode one?
You have a Tour de France trophy
in your closet.
[Mr. Johnson] That's for culture,
which you'd know if you...
if you took the time to admire it.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but w-what's that smell?
- [Jacob] I love this game. [chuckles]
- [Janine] Oh, yeah.
Uh, it smells like dead squirrel.
- [Janine] Ah, y-yeah.
- No, it's raccoons.
- It's raccoons.
- [Jacob] Oh, no.
I... I know what that smell is. It's Morton.
[laughs]
It's not me.
Although it does smell like gas.
I told you a professional needs
to look at that stove.
[scoffs] Probably is Morton's nasty ass,
but I'll go check it out.
Well, I smell a little somethin'-somethin'
but nothing too crazy, right?
Right?
Oh, damn.
Oh, damn!
Okay, who would like to go next?
Nobody panic, but I'm gonna need
everybody to leave with love.
Outside. Immediately, lovingly.
Did I mention I was in love?
Who else got something to live for?
- What?
- [Melissa] Let's go. Come on.
All right. So, the district will have
someone out here to fix the gas leak,
but what it won't be able to fix is
the fractured moral infrastructure
of this school.
Now, split up into five groups.
Each one will have a different activity
that I will walk you through.
- [groaning]
- Look, the sooner we finish this,
the sooner you'll be able
to get back to your day.
All right, so what is this?
Some kind of metaphor
about how we need
to jump-start our school year?
No, I just didn't realize
how many people there would be,
and those were in my trunk.
You are welcome to come to me
with any problem or concern.
Big or small, I am here to help.
She does have an office hour though.
So, you might wanna, you know, store
a bunch of problems over several weeks.
But if I'm in the office,
those hours are open.
In fact, let me just give you my cell.
What the heck?
Just giving that sucker away for free?
What?
You mad 'cause your real mom left you,
and now your fake mom is leaving you too?
- [Ava chuckles]
- No, it's just...
Barb's all happy now, which is great,
but this guy is getting the Barb
I had to work three years for.
Besides, I'm supposed to be the recipient
to her mentorship, you know.
The up-and-comer to her veteran ways.
The Scrappy-Doo to her Scoobs.
Now, he's Scrappy? I just...
Ooh!
Way to go, hoopers. A fun new wrinkle is
to try with your eyes closed.
And what else is left up for grabs
in the Mystery Gang, you know?
Because Gregory's Fred,
and Jacob is Velma, and Melissa's Daphne.
I'm Daphne. Oh, my God, Janine.
Your perception is damningly awful.
My point is, who am I at Abbott now?
Who am I?
Hey. You know, I was thinking
about what you said about the triathlon.
- You really can't ride a bike?
- Never had time to learn.
That is wild.
You've lived such a full life.
I just don't know
how riding a bike got skipped over.
I worked a lot as a kid.
Well, if you want,
I can teach you how to ride a bike.
- It's never too late to learn.
- [scoffs, sighs]
- What about your group?
- They're fine.
Gregory, um, which direction do I turn?
Uh, Gregory?
Middle schoolers, huh?
Surprised you didn't mention it
all summer since, you know,
I teach middle school
and, well, we live together,
so we see each other every day.
Well, what's to mention? Kids are kids.
The only difference is the math.
I spent the summer learning
to do that, so...
Well, there's a lot more
to it than math, okay?
Preteens are very different
than second graders.
Uh, not really.
Just add a few years and puberty.
I talk to the older girls all the time.
Talking is great. Talking is fun.
But teaching... [chuckles]
The second you become their teacher,
you become their enemy. Right, Morton?
They're gonna eat you alive.
Okay, no offense,
but this sounds like a you two problem.
Okay, well,
you have no idea what they're capable of.
Yeah, you want a taste?
Aight, gross, but yeah. Do your worst.
Yeah! Craig, we finished in what
I can only imagine is record time.
Amazing.
You'll never guess what level two is.
Don't tell me. It's reverse.
It's reverse.
Yeah! Look alive, people.
Reverse, reverse.
Okay. So, I'm young enough
to be the ingenue,
but that's been usurped.
Barbara's doing
the optimistic-and-positive thing.
There's not a grump on the first floor.
I could be the downstairs grump.
Now see, if you had a better personality,
you wouldn't have to search for one.
[chuckles]
You could use that time to find a man.
Okay, you know that I'm dating Gregory.
That's still happening? [chuckles]
Sorry, I haven't been able to keep up
ever since I started dating
the world's only real man, O'Shon.
[chuckles]
Good for you. No one cares. [chuckles]
[stammers] That was my attempt
at being a grump.
I may have overshot it a bit.
All right. I got us a bike.
Okay, Mr. Johnson, get on up here.
Maybe not right now.
My knees aren't feeling so good.
It's actually better
for your knees than walking.
Well, I forgot my baseball card
to put in the spokes.
All right, come on, no excuses, okay?
I'll even hold on
until you get the hang of it.
- [sighs]
- Okay? Here we go. Yeah, there you go.
All right, there it is.
- Promise not to let go.
- I promise.
Okay.
Pinky promise?
Well, I can't now,
I'm holding on to the bike.
[Melissa clicks tongue]
Look, these kids are mean.
One told me,
"That's why your bitch left you, bitch."
I think you're overdoing it on the B-word.
I don't think he's doing it enough.
Hey, why'd you rat out your brother
and get him locked up?
What? That never happened.
And scene. I was being a kid.
We live in a post-truth landscape
and these kids hit below the belt.
Which is where you haven't been touched
in years, snitch,
unless you count Sweet Cheeks.
You keep my son's name
out your filthy mouth.
And don't even think about talking back
to them, or you will get written up.
Every day is
like an episode of Scared Straight!
Take your shoes off!
- Okay, who are we in this scenario?
- Everyone.
You still got me?
Hey, I got you. I got you.
And you have to handle
all of this while teaching. [chuckles]
And if even one kid gets the best of you,
that could be a wrap for the period.
- Or the year.
- Oh, no. Uh-uh.
These kids are gonna... [bleep] ...respect me.
Uh-uh, don't curse. They will report ya.
- Yeah, I'll... [bleep] ...report you.
- He just cursed.
He can do that, you see.
He's a little boy.
Actually, I'm a little girl.
You ain't hard, homey!
- Okay.
- [Jacob] That's right. You ain't hard.
Just keep moving forward!
- What?
- You're doing great!
- Eight.
- Eh, a seven.
- What are we doing now?
- Rating you to your face.
Have you ever been called a one
on a day you just knew you were a ten?
- You're a one!
- One.
- One!
- Okay, stop it!
- Stop!
- [Dominic] Stop?
[Tasha] No, no, no.
Don't stop. Walk forward.
- There you go. You got it.
- No, I told you...
- Turn left!
- [Dominic] Left?
[Tasha] No, no, no. Go-Go right.
Go right! No, that...
- [Mr. Johnson clatters]
- [car alarm blaring]
[Mr. Johnson yells, groans]
You promised.
You promised you wouldn't let me fall.
- [Janine inhales sharply]
- [car alarm continues]
[sighs]
Looks like we're gonna be here all day.
Mm-mmm-mmm.
New year, same old Abbott.
Mm-mmm... No, just at the top.
I don't have to do it twice.
You a organ donor, Gregory?
- Why?
- 'Cause whatever I break,
you're gonna donate to me,
and I like those shoulders, Gregory.
Well, today was supposed
to be about building trust
and working together as a team,
and the only thing
you accomplished together is
how to fail in unique ways.
Progress.
And now you get to start over
and do it again.
- [staff groaning]
- Well, I, for one, can't stand this.
Right? 'Cause this guy sucks.
You all suck.
And this whole day sucks, right, guys?
Well, it may suck,
but if we don't finish today,
- we can always come back on the weekend.
- [staff gasping, muttering]
- No.
- [Craig] Oh, okay.
Hey, Ava, listen up. Um...
You know, I was thinking
about this whole grade switch thing,
and I think it might be better
if Janine did the swap instead of me,
'cause, uh, Sweet Cheeks is
afraid of heights,
so for him it's ground floor or nothing.
Um, no, guinea pigs are from the Andes.
They're not afraid of heights.
All right, listen. I...
A change this big, I just don't know
if I'm, like, exactly up for it.
[sighs]
"Zero problem whatsoever. Bring it on.
Those kids are about to get
a lesson in learning lessons,
and you can quote me on that."
That's what you said in June
when I asked you about this.
There's no going back.
Here, this will cheer you up.
- That's O'Shon shirtless in Wildwood.
- It is.
No, actually it kinda helps.
- It sure does. [chuckles]
- Good job.
Hey, Mel. So, about before...
You were totally busting my chops
about how the sixth graders act, right?
- I knew it.
- [Mr. Morton] No, we weren't.
And those were just the experiences
that I haven't repressed yet.
Morton...
[stammers] Sorry.
Janine. I could really use
a positive spin on my situation.
You're screwed.
- You are not the two, you are the...
- One.
Girlfriend, I have
seen you handle challenges
far more difficult
than a bunch of sixth graders.
You got this.
Thanks, Barb. I appreciate it.
Hey, you wouldn't wanna take a shot
at the sixth grade this year, would you?
[laughs]
I'd rather retire.
I'm so lucky to be around
such a veteran like Ms. Howard.
- Duh. She's the greatest teacher ever.
- Right?
I just wish I could ask her
a couple more questions.
But I don't want to keep bothering her.
You think maybe I could text her later?
Oh, my God, we get it.
You have her cell phone number.
What'd you wanna ask her?
Ah, it's pretty basic. I just...
Should I take roll
as soon as class starts in the morning?
Oh, no. Ten-minute grace period.
A lot of the kids take SEPTA.
It's a whole thing.
I learned the hard way in my first year.
I'm sure I'm gonna have to learn
the hard way a thousand times.
Oh, yeah. You definitely will.
And you're gonna wanna scream
and contemplate your life choices, and...
it's all normal.
If you have any more questions
and-and Barbara's busy,
you can always just ask me.
I appreciate that.
It's what I'm here for.
[Janine] That is who I am now.
I don't have to be a grump.
I can be me and be a mentor.
I'm gonna put the me in m-mentor.
"Me-ntor." The teacher has become...
the teacher.
I need to get out of the sun.
I just can't ride a bike, okay?
Look, they say you fall down seven times,
you stand up eight.
I gotta fall six more times?
Hey, how's it going over here?
- Bad.
- He's scared to get back on the bike.
Okay, well, I could help.
I'm a brand new me. [chuckles]
- What you mean? You sound the same.
- Oh. You missed a whole thing.
I went through a bunch of different
personalities, landed here.
- You still sound the same.
- Uh, I'll tell you about it later.
- Okay.
- But, Mr. Johnson,
I know you can ride the bike,
because I believe in you.
I know what to do.
Uh, everyone, stop what you're doing
right now and come over here.
Mr. Johnson needs our help.
No, no, please don't do that. Please.
If we don't finish,
you have to come in on the weekend.
You look like a guy
that loves coming in on weekends.
Monday through Friday,
the best days of the week to you, huh?
- No, my weekends rule.
- Yeah, okay.
[Janine] All right, let's go, Mr. J.
Yeah, what's the worst that could happen?
I fall over and die.
Well, that's just... fair.
Look, Mr. Johnson, if you fall,
we will catch you. I promise.
Okay? All right.
Ready to get back up on this horse?
Riding a horse is easy.
It's bikes I'm afraid of.
Hey, you got this, all right?
All right, here we go. Ready? Here...
- [Melissa] Come on, Mr. J.
- [Janine] Go, Mr. J.
[staff cheering]
[Mr. Johnson] Yay!
Yeah!
[Melissa] Go, Mr. J!
- Go, Mr. J!
- [cheering continues]
Uh, I feel like we're starting
to lose focus.
You all need to prove your virtuousness.
Craig.
Isn't that
what we're doing right here, huh?
- Yeah.
Well, maybe this qualifies
as completion of team building.
- Wait, really?
- Yes.
Also, I have tickets
to the Ren Faire this weekend,
- so I'm gonna need this to count.
- [scoffs]
Okay.
Fixed the leak.
Good news,
killed a bunch of mice in your walls.
Bad news, ain't my job to get rid of 'em.
Worst news,
I noticed you have HVAC issues.
You mean, like, AC and heating stuff?
Yep, and you're not gonna have any of that
if you don't get a specialist in here.
You got someone to handle this?
Well, I'm sure Mr. Johnson's on top of it.
He's around here somewhere.
[Mr. Johnson screams]
Gregory didn't teach me how to stop!
- Just use the handlebar brake!
- It's a fixie! Just stop pedaling!