I can't hold them off, Rick. There's too many.
Richard. Your fortress is a salty waste
of coral and clam. Relinquish it at once.
[groaning]
Submit, you continental cunt.
Got a better idea.
- Oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit.
- [alarm blaring]
[shouting]
- Happy?
- Of course I'm happy.
You're acting like you won,
but this is exactly what I wanted.
I am Mr. Nimbus.
Whatever. Come on, Morty.
- Man, that was intense.
- Yeah. [burps] Nice work, buddy.
- Sorry, I had to blow up your bunker.
- Not so fast, Sanchez.
It is I, Cookie Magneto.
- What the fuck? I'm not engaging this guy.
- That's hardly up to you, Rick.
I'm sorry, do you control things
that people agree are cookies?
- Yes.
- But cookies aren't a substance.
- They're more of a name we give to--
- To the things I control.
Do you control cookie ingredients?
Because, you know, that sounds dangerous.
- You know, everything has sugar in it.
- Fight me and find out! [screaming]
- Jesus, Rick!
- Sorry, Morty,
I know you're gonna say it's punching down,
but I can't fight another goofball super villain.
I'm not the Tick. I'm exhausted.
Okay, but if you really have
a lot of these guys gunning for you,
- maybe you should look into what you're doing to--
- Oh, don't start that crap, Morty.
I don't do anything
for these dip shits to seek me out.
I am Mr. Calypso.
Face me, you ugly, drunk, ugly piece of shit.
Okay, I might look into it.
[theme music playing]
- Why don't you have a seat?
- This isn't a therapy session.
I'm asking you what people in your racket say
about handling this situation.
First, we'd want you to define the situation.
I'm a walking target
for a never-ending sea of angry nerds
that think getting in a fight with me
is some kind of, I don't know, platform?
I mean, look at this guy.
He shows up and calls me an "ugly drunk."
Because that's the angle of attack
that's gonna undo me, right?
You don't shoot Batman
in his fucking Batman logo.
And you think locking this man
in a chamber and milking him of cosmic fluid
will somehow resolve this?
I think it's the best I can do to profit
from a situation and maybe set an example.
But you've set this example many times
and it's not changing your situation.
Yeah. Now you're gonna tell me to ignore them.
But guess what, they want that too.
- And why would they want to be ignored?
- You really believe if I let a guy like this
do whatever he wants,
he gets bored and vanishes?
Rick, would you be interested
in proving me wrong?
- Yes.
- Then show me data.
- Ignore them for a week and see what happens.
- Oh. You're on, bitch.
Is that man dead?
- Is everything in here confidential?
- Everything but murder.
Then he's fine.
I think it's pretty big, you know?
Big step for the big cheese.
- Yeah, Dad, I'm impressed.
- Can we not make it a big deal?
It's worth celebrating, Rick.
You accepted the concept of therapy
without turning yourself
into a pickle or a housefly.
Jerry, for fucks sake,
that was a regular fly in her office that day.
- What the hell?
- Rick. How about a little piss?
Rick, why is there a man shooting piss
on our front lawn?
- I'm sure he'll tell you.
- I am Pissmaster.
Here to flush the toilet
that is Rick Sanchez.
He's spraying my lavender bush.
My bees need that lavender.
Remember five seconds ago
when you guys were stoked about me changing
because it made you feel superior?
Ooh, whole family is here. Who's that redhead?
Wouldn't mind spraying her with a golden shower.
Oh, my God, what?
- Hey.
- Okay, that's it.
Think about this. if you fight this guy,
I'm either an asshole for not helping
- or an asshole for helping.
- My daughter just got spoken of in porno terms
and I'll respond how I choose.
- Wait, Dad, don't.
- Honey.
- Hey.
- You want a piece of piss?
If that's your stupid, rude way
of saying I have to fight you, I will.
Take your shot, pussy.
- Don't talk to me that way. Go away.
- Make me.
Go away!
Ow.
Careful, honey.
- Just stay down. I don't even know you.
- Yeah, you don't know me.
But I'm gonna know your whole ass,
you son of a gun.
- Hey, none of that.
- Break it up, guys.
Come on, you dirty motherfucker.
No!
No, no, no!
Stop!
Uncle! Mercy! Mercy!
Stop! I give up!
Apologize to my daughter.
- For what?
- You know for what.
[sobbing] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I sexualized you.
It came out wrong.
That's my dad.
That's my fucking dad.
[crowd cheering, clamoring]
Honey, I'm so proud of you.
- Ow.
- Oh, sorry.
Thank you, Rick.
Damn. Hashtag "Flamingo Dad" is everywhere.
Buzzfeed made an odd-numbered list
of other people's observations about you
and you're getting a lot of hand clap emojis
on white Twitter's impression of Black Twitter.
Jezebel's offering a cash reward
for evidence that you're a bad person.
- That is their highest honor.
- So this is what it's like to trend.
Feels good. Feels right.
Now a bunch more assholes
are gonna know they can get a rise out of you.
- [both] Boo.
- Rick, let a dog have one day.
I'm letting, I'm letting.
- Whoa. Are those orbs?
- This is what I'm talking about.
Some asshole saw that fight
and they were jealous of Pissmaster.
I am Blagnar the Eternal.
We seek the earthling who beat up Pissmaster.
- That's my dad, Jerry Smith.
- Jerry Smith.
Our Galactic Orbship thirsts for justice
and those who deliver it.
- Wait, what?
- Our great council would like to offer you
this silver orb.
And with it, a place amongst us.
Whoa, it's sticky.
That means it's found a pure heart
it wants to bond with.
You guys saw my son-in-law on the news,
now he gets a sticky orb. What's the catch?
- We're not rubes.
- Yeah, your power is well-known
in our jurisdiction, Rick Sanchez,
and it should come as no surprise
that our orbs are unsticky for you.
Oh, no. First, I get banned
from the Nextdoor app, now this.
I'd be honored to join your organization.
So, what do I do, rub the orb
when I see crime or eat the orb like spinach?
The orb is raw power.
Trust your heart, Jerry.
It will know what to do.
[groaning]
[microwave turns on]
Did you turn on the microwave?
No. Maybe. I was trying to fly. I--
- What?
- I mean, come on, Rick.
- Orbs and goblets, this is your thing.
- Orbs and goblets.
You're the orb guy in the family.
Can you please help me?
Jerry, I give you raw power,
you'll end up miserable like me.
- Trust me, I'm helping by not helping.
- Seriously?
What the eff? Some creep tried to pee
on my tits and you did nothing.
Now you're gonna sit there
and hold our dad back from being a hero?
- Are you that petty?
- You know what? Fine.
Here. Here's your suit.
I hardwired the orb's infinite energy right into it.
This shooty thing looks cool.
That shooty thing
is a nuclear disruptor that can blow up planets.
- So tight.
- Kind of hot.
Okay, show me acts of evil
happening around the galaxy.
Whoa, Space Hitlers?
Space Hitlers are convening on Zeplar Prime.
My God.
Each one of them is their own type of Hitler.
- Yeah, that's a problem.
- Oh, shit, do that one. Oh, you guys.
That's my parents.
Wow. Well, family,
looks like Jerry Smith has his first orb mission.
Lawn flaming-ho!
Just a reminder, you guys asked for this.
Soon our Legion of Hitlers
will bring about a new galactic order.
A Reich, if you will.
- Riddle Hitler me this.
- Sorry, are we just letting in all Hitlers now?
Auf Wiedersehen, bad guys.
Exterminate him!
Oh, shit! Oh, Jesus, one at a time.
Oh, my God.
Uh, hope there weren't other people
on that planet.
And there were no other people
on the planet. Only Hitlers.
Each one ready to start their own holocaust,
meaning an estimated 30 billion lives
were saved by a single blast.
And the galaxy owes it all to Jerry Smith.
Hashtag "Flamingo Dad."
- You gotta be fucking kidding me.
- Up next-- Oh, actually, nothing.
I guess we're gonna talk
about Jerry Smith some more.
[Goldenfold] I don't know.
Therapy is starting to feel hopeless.
I've got so many issues. [shouts]
We need to talk.
Hey, no. I will not speak with you if you refuse
to treat me and my patients with respect.
Oh, Lord.
I was a fly.
So unburdened.
So free of shame.
Welp, I'm officially cured.
Here. Here's your data.
Hard proof that God hates me.
I ignored a troll and Jerry beat the guy's ass.
Now he's got this orb and he's using the power,
which I gave him, to annihilate planets of Hitlers
and everyone's popping champagne.
Rick, you came here because you wanted things
to change. And they're changing. It's working.
Oh, so if my bumbling moron
of a son-in-law beats up people, it's working.
- But if I do it, it's a cosmic abuse of power?
- Rick, listen to yourself.
You're complaining about how you have
to be careful with your immense power
and that Hitlers are dead.
Everything you're describing is positive.
Oh, shit, not reacting.
That really is the kill move?
I don't know if you need to think about it
in terms of murder, but, yes, just stay the course.
- Okay, good talk.
- What you're describing is therapy.
And if you'd like to keep receiving it,
start scheduling your visits with Judy up front.
Thank you.
Thank you, Flamingo Fam.
When they asked if I wanted to be the first human
to drive a Mitsubishi Space Lancer,
I thought, I don't know.
I got this cool orb suit that goes fast.
But you know what sold me?
[alarm system chirps]
The council said I could pick my own bridge crew.
Morty, Summer, Beth, what do you say?
- What? Are you serious?
- Oh, shit, yeah, I love Mitsubishi.
- Me too. I've heard of them.
- [Beth] This is so exciting.
Oh, my, God, this is so cool.
All right, gang, orbs away!
Oh, me, oh, my. Can it be?
A giant piece of shit I see?
I am Mr. Stringbean.
No one resists my rhyming scheme.
Hey, douchebag, why don't you chill out?
Who's this asshole?
I am Dr. Buckles.
Here to tighten the belt on your opinions.
Oh, you wanna see the Bean get mean?
[shouting]
I'll be damned.
- I'm out.
- Stop it.
I'm out.
Oh, my God, this Piss Guy
is getting wailed on.
Look at him.
He tried to crawl under the car. What a loser.
- Hey, you watching the Pissmaster video?
- Yeah.
He has to be the biggest piece of shit
in the galaxy, right?
Oh, without a doubt. Who could relate
being that much of a piece of shit?
[somber music playing]
[doorbell ringing]
Goddamn it.
Fuck shit.
Come on, man. Fuck.
Come on, where is it?
Shit, shit.
[grunts] Fuck.
Come on, Pissmaster, come on.
[grunts]
[speaking indistinctly]
Damn it.
[doorbell ringing]
[knocking on door]
[woman] It's me.
Please.
Please, just open up.
Dad, Mom told me you weren't responding
to her calls and I'm worried.
I said terrible things about you on my podcast.
It's just, I've been so frustrated with you.
If you were to do something,
I'd never stop blaming myself.
- Just please. Please let me know you're okay.
- Goddamn it.
- I'm okay, honey. We're good.
- I thought something happened to you.
I can tell you, if anything happens to me,
it's 100% not on you. It's my own choice.
You still sound like
you're gonna do something bad.
Just promise you won't, okay?
Okay, yeah. Promise.
Love you, Dad.
[groans] Fuck.
[Pissmaster] Welp, this is it.
I'm killing myself because of Jerry Smith.
The Earth man.
Flamingo Dad.
Seeing them all cheer as I got my ass whipped
made me realize people just wanna see me fail.
All I've ever wanted to do
is prove them wrong.
[dramatic music playing]
[screaming] Help!
Wait. Who are you?
Pissmaster.
Make sure you tell everybody
Pissmaster saved you.
Those were heat-seeking pissiles,
by the way, not just missiles.
Oh.
- Okay.
- ♪ Y'all ready for piss? ♪
Yo. Pissmaster. You saving that cat
to make people forget you suck?
- Nope, just saving it to save it.
- Okay, we got nothing.
♪ Piss ♪
♪ Pee ♪
♪ Urine ♪
♪ Number one ♪
♪ Pee ♪
♪ Piss ♪
Look, it's Pissmaster.
- Dr. Wong, what's up?
- [Wong] You're late for your session.
- Cancel it. Bill me. I'm good.
- [Wong] You're good?
[Rick] See, I put on the suit
of my enemy and I love it.
Now I'm gonna make a giant bomb,
plant it in a city, and then have the suit
autopilot the bomb into space.
Everyone will think
Pissmaster sacrificed himself.
He dies a hero,
I get a win I'd otherwise never get myself,
nice wet bow on top.
I'm tempted to second guess a lot of that,
but I think you might be nailing it.
- What?
- If it's free and fun, do it.
It sounds healthy.
Oh, that wasn't my goal,
but good to know. Shit, gotta go.
[all cheering]
No, exactly. And the slave planet thing,
I hear he broke their chains
with pure urine, so...
Hey. Sorry, I'm late.
Lot of traffic on the orbway.
Take a seat, Jerry.
We were just discussing
Pissmaster's honorable rise.
Who cares, right?
Uh, people are talking about him.
He's becoming likable. Good, even.
But he's Pissmaster.
People change.
Everyone loves a comeback story.
I agree.
- Everyone.
All in favor of offering Orbship
to Eugene Michael Piss, aka Pissmaster?
[all] Orb-yes.
All those opposed?
Obviously, orb-no.
The Orbship has spoken.
You know what, Jerry? This is a good test for you.
If you can't let go
of your pettiness enough to recruit Pissmaster,
maybe you don't deserve your orb.
And, Jerry, don't come back without him.
[reporter] Absolute chaos.
No one knows
who planted the bomb, but one thing is clear.
Orphan Island, a city populated entirely
by orphans, now sits on the brink of doom.
The Orphan Island bomb squad
is trying to dismantle it as we speak.
I can't stress enough.
I'm 8 years old. I have no idea what I'm doing.
Look, it's Pissmaster.
Oh, no, there's no time to dismantle it.
Come on, it's not safe here.
[orphans cheering]
Pisspop? Pisspop? Pisspop?
- Pissmaster.
- What are you doing here?
[groans] Eugene Michael Piss.
By decree of the Andromeda Strain,
our great council presents you with this orb,
- which you have to take.
- Fuck off, Jerry, I'm in the middle of something.
Excuse me? Hey,
this is the greatest honor you could ever be given.
- I don't want it.
- You have to take it.
Jesus Christ, get out of here.
He's flying it into space.
He's gonna sacrifice himself.
Get back here, you ungrateful shit.
What is your problem?
You're screwing up my hero death.
Good.
Flamingo Dad wants us to blow up?
When did he become a shit heel?
Life comes at you fast.
- Dad, people are filming.
- Yeah, maybe dial it back?
[gasps] Rick?
- PissSuit. Autopilot the payload.
- [PissSuit] Confirmed.
That's my fucking dad.
[Jerry shouting]
- Jerry?
- Dad, are you okay?
Your father is the fucking Pissmaster.
Grandpa? What the hell?
Jerry, what is this?
People are saying you turned shit heel?
Well, my father-in-law is Pissmaster,
so why don't you ask him?
What the--? Rick Sanchez, the Pissmaster?
Okay, this is not a good look.
This family, man. Look,
I don't know what weird shit you two are pulling,
but it's completely unstick worthy.
We're done here.
But I didn't know.
I'm a good guy.
I made you all famous.
I'm a thousand years old.
You know how many Flamingo Dads I've seen?
Don't orb us.
I don't get it.
You were Pissmaster the whole time?
Obviously not, Jerry.
I put the suit on once Pissmaster kill--
Uh, when you made him--
Um, yeah, I've always been Pissmaster.
But that would mean you let my dad beat you up
just so he could, like, feel more confident?
- Damn, Rick.
- That's amazing.
Hold on, what?--? Everyone's just accepting this?
Wait, wasn't Pissmaster an alien?
- Probably a robot.
- He obviously Avatar'd it.
But why?
Why would Rick even prop me up like that?
Jesus, Jerry. Rick did something nice
for once, okay? He's trying to change.
[ship] You are no longer worthy of Mitsubishi.
Proud of you, Dad.
Or should I say, Pissmaster.
Yeah. Grandpa, sorry I yelled at you.
And sorry for trying to stop you
from killing yourself with a nuclear bomb.
I just really liked having an orb.
Ah, don't sweat it, Jer.
Piss under the bridge.
Man, I guess the therapy worked, huh?
Opening up,
doing all that just to make my dad feel good.
- That's pretty great of you, Rick.
- Yeah. That's right, Morty. That's right.
You have to promise not to tell anyone,
but your dad made Pissmaster kill himself.
- Oh, man, what?
- Yeah, I mean, I found him dead
and I put on his suit.
But look at this. He literally blames your dad.
Holy shit. Wait, you kept the suicide note?
That's so messed up.
I know. I had to tell someone, Morty.
I couldn't just sit on that.
- And you expect me to?
- Morty, no, what are you doing?
[Jerry screams]
- What the hell? He killed himself?
- Jesus, Dad, you should've told us.
- Especially if Jerry murdered him.
- Wait, don't say that.
- I didn't murder.
- I thought it was cool
- that I withheld that information.
- But you didn't.
- You're walking around with the note.
- Gotta keep it in your heart as a great sacrifice.
- That's the cool move.
- How am I the bad guy? He sprayed piss on us.
- You all cheered me on.
- Don't drag us into this.
Again, I told you this would happen.
- Oh, get off your high horse.
- Boo.
Go ahead and boo.
I was breathing piss. Think I care?
Is this what it's like to trend?
This is a nightmare.
I should've just let him pee on my daughter.
[Summer] What the hell, Dad?
[theme music playing]
How about Jack Miller, aka carjack?
He lifted a car off a stranger.
- I guess.
- Next.
Orb-no. We're fresh off a dad and a piss guy.
- Maybe we add someone that's already powerful?
- We have to be realistic about who we can get.
- I have a pitch.
- We're not going to add Scarlett Johansson.
- Next up, Mr. Nimbus. Lord of the oceans.
- Oh, I hear he controls the police.
- The police?
- [all] Orb-yes.
Guys, I already checked.
His reps say he's really busy right now.
- Everyone says that.
- Oh, and we're not busy?