I'm Cameron Crowe, the
writer/director of Jerry Maguire.
I'm feeling very
fortunate right now...
...to have Renee, Tom and Cuba
with us to watch Jerry Maguire.
-Awesome.
-A rather momentous reunion.
Thank you for being here, guys.
Let's check it out.
Can we turn the lights down?
How the hell we gonna see
the screen with the lights on?
-That's an excellent idea.
-Oh, this part I like.
The Tom-ster.
This is the world. There are
almost six billion people on it.
I did the voice-over in London
while doing Eyes Wide Shut.
Yes, indeed.
The movie always, for me...
...began with "Magic Bus"
by The Who.
On the day where, Tom, you said,
"Let's make this movie together"...
...we played "Magic Bus"
in my office.
You did the voice-over in the office.
It felt like, "This is the movie."
I remember that.
I went out of my mind.
In Seattle, Dallas Malloy, 16.
Dallas is a real boxer.
-Kicking ass.
-Yeah, you got that right.
Check out what pure joy looks like.
That baseball hit one of the crew on
the head and caused major problems.
-He went straight to the hospital.
-That was that lawsuit, right?
That's funny.
Jerry O'Connell.
-There he is.
-Allan Graf, the stunt coordinator.
Crazy son of a bitch
killed half the stuntmen.
-He tried to kill you.
-He's a good guy, but good Lord!
I'm the guy you don't usually see.
That was a fun day of shooting,
with the owners.
The coaches.
Players.
That was a blast.
Let's talk about the hair
for a moment.
What's up with that hair?
It's rocking. This is
the true sports agent look.
It is.
I'll just write it down.
14 Million x 5
-I can't afford that.
-Winning isn't cheap.
-It's probably a good--
-You're proud, aren't you?
Easy, Renee, your part's coming.
Hang in there, be patient.
-Jay.
-That would be Jann Wenner.
-Publisher of Rolling Stone.
-Really?
-Your first employer.
-Oh, that's classic.
-He returns to--
-He's in Almost Famous too.
Yes, he is.
...in a new commercial
starring you...
...broadcast during a Super Bowl
game you're winning.
-You can't beat that.
-He was just, "Say it faster."
-Take a deep breath.
-That was awesome.
Was the girl 16 or 177
Wanting the big dollar,
things went wrong.
There's no proof of anything.
This guy is a sensational athlete.
Are you Calvin Nack?
Can you sign my card?
You had the flu during this. You had
103 temperature and were puking.
-That scene directed itself.
-Do you remember that day?
It usually works better
when I'm not in the room.
Not true. You still directed.
Hi, baby.
-She does the voice of Babe. Yep.
-Oh, is that true?
This was the first day of filming.
Am I right?
Yeah.
How do you remember that?
Because I was asked down to the set
even though I wasn't filming.
I didn't think that was first.
I think we were rehearsing out
in the hall in between shoots.
My agent. My agent.
No pressure.
Absolutely. The first day.
The first shot is coming right up.
-This is the first thing we filmed.
-Right here?
This is his fourth concussion.
Shouldn't he stop?
It would take a tank
to stop your dad.
It would take all five...
...Super Trooper VR Warriors
to stop your dad.
The sincerity is oozing, Tom.
Fuck you!
I remember being in this hallway
thinking, "There's no road back now.
We have started filming. Jerry
Maguire lives." It was on this shot.
That's awesome.
That kid couldn't wait
to say, "Fuck you."
-Really?
-Couldn't wait.
I remember this shot,
the day we shot it.
We met a lot of people doing
research for the movie...
...and many people helped. I travel led
around the NFL and met many agents.
And almost everybody now says
they are Jerry Maguire.
It's all based on them.
It's the best-case scenario that
so many think that it's their story.
But it's a fictional character
created on-screen by Tom.
I'm very happy to say that
because it is writing of another kind.
Just watching him do a scene
like this is cinematic literature.
And it is a fictional character...
...that I was so happy to watch happen
from behind the camera.
We shot this with The Who playing,
so it feels like The Who.
I came down to the set and was like,
"Are they filming? But there's music."
It keeps you in the spirit.
I began writing what they call
a mission statement, not a memo.
A suggestion
for the future of our company.
This is the beginning of us
playing music during the takes...
...when we were filming.
Originally people said,
"You're gonna cover up dialog!
Watch out, it's terrible.
Nobody does this, it's really wrong."
But beginning with this sequence
and a few others...
...you began to see how playing music
would seep into the performance.
It was helpful.
All during rehearsal, we kept
music playing a lot during scenes.
I loved having music play
during this sequence.
-Oh, Dicky.
-Dicky Fox.
Billy Wilder's role.
"And especially you."
We wanted Billy Wilder to play Dicky.
He thought about it briefly and said:
"You must find an actor to play
this part. I am not an actor.
This is a real lesson of directing.
You must hire the actor."
Then he saw the movie
and, happily, dug it and said:
"Who is that guy that played my part?"
That's great!
I said he was a lawyer at TriStar.
-And Billy Wilder said, "He was good."
-That's great.
That's classic. Classic.
Jerry Cantrell from Alice in Chains
making his screen debut.
Oh, that's where that guy's from.
That was 4 a.m.
or something, right?
-It looks like it, Tom.
- I know.
Jack Lord. I always wanted
to direct Jack Lord.
I talked him into
that cameo appearance.
Actually, we just bought a clip
from Hawaii Five-O.
We searched for a definitive Jack Lord
as McGarrett moment, and here it is.
Boom!
That's great.
This is Jerry Maguire.
Did those manuscripts--?
"Oh, they did?"
No, that's fine.
-Janusz Kaminski.
-Janusz, oh.
No one lights like him,
that's for sure.
He's great.
We're seeing the beginning
of Renee here, are we not?
-There's Renee.
-And my plant.
-There she is.
-Right, you're there.
James L. Brooks.
-He was there a lot.
-The gang.
I remember this shot.
-That was an expensive plant.
-Yes, indeed.
When you introduced Renee
that way...
You talked about just
wanting her in that frame.
Written and directed
by Cameron Crowe, the man.
-How long do you give him?
-About a week.
-And that's the moment that turns it.
-That's great.
It was such an emotional moment,
you in the lobby.
Remember that long crane shot
to get down into that moment?
-Courtney Love read for that.
-Right.
We have tape of the audition,
and she was great.
-Yeah, she was great.
-Very Carole Lombard.
And there's Renee.
-I'm sorry if I was rude just now.
-That's okay. We're in it together now.
Why is it so easy to talk with you?
Tell me about your fiancée.
I realized Jay Mohr's sitting
behind you. I never saw that before.
-Lipnicki.
-Oh, God!
How was it on that plane?
The flying was a good day.
It was an excellent day.
He was so cute. When he walked in,
he looked like that.
-Sweet.
-Oh, man.
I know, that's him.
He put his little arms up,
and I said we had to pretend to sleep.
And he goes, "Okay,"
then he put his arms around me...
...tucked his head in,
closed his eyes.
He was so professional,
it was scary, like a grown man.
You didn't have to patronize--
-He's such a life force.
-He's extraordinary.
-A beautiful heart, that kid.
-I love Renee listening here.
She is just strapped in
for the whole story. It's so great.
One thing we worked on in the script,
it's the genius of James Brooks, is...
...while we worked
on the script for years...
...Jim said, "Let's put a goal
out for ourselves...
...that this movie begins
where an '80s movie would've ended.
The guy that finds the religion
of goodness. Let's begin with that.
And then have him
have to battle back...
...from what would've been the ending
of a movie 15 years ago."
And we worked on that structure
for a long time.
It used to be a better meal,
now it's a better life.
-Great, Renee.
-And he's just smiling.
-Jonathan just giving it to you.
-Yes, "Here you go."
That's what I loved about this script.
Cameron, I remember I went nuts.
I remember seeing Say Anything.
And I called you that night after it.
Because we'd met earlier, before.
I was like, "Who directed this?
Is that the same Cameron Crowe?"
That's great.
I was honoured to work with you...
-Brother, it's mutual.
-...and these characters.
You read the script in zero time,
called and said:
-"Let's talk about it. Jerry Maguire."
-Let's go, brother.
Listen, Dorothy. Dorothy?
While I go look for him,
grab this gentleman here.
So cute.
You scared me. You scared me!
-Don't do that again, ever!
-Okay, Mommy.
Ever, ever, ever! Okay? Ever!
Dorothy?
Now, how do you catch that entire
harried, loving mother feeling?
Accident.
-You did?
-Yeah.
What a day.
That was a huge day.
That was a great day.
You just stood there
and had this smile on your face.
You knew I was scared to death.
It was the first scene that we did...
...and I'm scared to death.
You just had this--
-You were just so right there.
-You were on fire.
You were the greatest guy
on the planet that day.
It wasn't hard! Like, he walks away,
and there was some goofy look.
It wasn't too hard to play
that day, I have to say.
But since I've gotten to know
you better-- But on that day...
-It was a beautiful day.
-This was the day where I said to Tom:
"Add a 'whoo' in the middle
of what you're saying."
He said, "Okay."
And I thought, "This is really fun."
Then I get to watch little Jonathan
swinging between you guys. It was...
...yeah, so great.
-Here's the real Renee, right there.
-That's Renee!
-Shut up!
-That is so you!
That's our girl.
-That's so great!
-That's so her.
-Laurel, the buzz killer.
-"There's my sister, Laurel."
...Dorothy.
Pleasure.
Bye.
-Look at those looks.
-Oh, I love it.
That's great.
-So many rich characters.
-My wife, Nancy Wilson's score.
-No kidding.
-Beautiful.
Really caught the feeling of love
starting to blossom...
...before either of them knew it.
The dog!
-Okay!
-Kelly!
Sooner or later we'll have to stop!
Aerosmith, wasn't it?
Aerosmith, we played?
Did you really? Oh, you're kidding.
The dog! "You're doing it wrong.
It's the wrong position!"
I can't watch that scene.
I can't watch that scene!
-Why?
-I've never been able to.
Tell us about that, Renee.
Let's rewind this scene.
Let's dissect it.
-What troubles you?
-It's too much information for me.
Too much information
I never need to know.
"You don't have to tell me everything."
-That was classic.
-Great writing.
"If you ever wanted..."
That's great.
We did this the night before,
trying to figure out...
...how do we just show two people,
post-sex, just kind of hanging out?
And we just put them at the table.
This is great.
Mark Pellington, great director,
good friend of mine...
-...playing Dooler.
-There they are.
Tim McDonald, the first guy
when he walks in--
Excuse me.
Eric Stoltz, ladies and gentlemen.
-Do you make fun of him too?
-No. There's still time, though.
This is what it's all about, man.
Everybody loves you.
Pisses me off!
This guy's from the This is Elvis
film. "Whether you're young or old."
...Jerry Maguire will still
be the king of rock 'n' roll.
-Little black book.
-When I think of him, my heart pounds.
We went too far with the bachelorette
film. We have about 50 minutes...
...of women talking about Jerry.
I hear, "I was in Jerry Maguire.
I got cut."
From the film? From the
bachelorette film. That's funny.
He's almost phobic.
Jerry is great at friendship,
he's just bad at intimacy.
-He can't be alone.
-He can't say, "I love you."
-He's an agent. He lies.
-Love her.
-She's ready to fistfight.
-Love you too.
-Love you.
I love you, man.
There's a seething wrongness
in the room.
That's insane.
A shout out to
Joe Hutshing, the editor.
Just did an amazing job on this movie.
If you really think about it,
the beginning of this movie...
...Is all characters,
setting up who Jerry is.
-Behaviour.
-Behaviour, acting and editing.
Regina King, ladies and gentlemen.
-Tyson, no!
-Okay, Mommy.
-Tyson, hello.
-Long time no see!
-The boy's cute too. He was awesome.
-He was great.
-In the bathtub scene.
-Tyson destroyed that set.
-He was genius.
-He loved it!
-Knock.
-Pleasure.
-Oh, she's great.
-She's great, Jay Mohr was great.
He rocked.
The finger's here.
We are just counting down
to Rod Tidwell now.
-This is the Tidwell countdown.
-Oh, we can feel Cuba coming!
-Wow.
-He and I majored in marketing.
We came to play!
So sweet.
My little family.
An agent we interviewed said:
"Fear the protective wife most of all.
She'll be the one that'll
make you do your job...
...more than you ever dreamed
you'd have to."
And that was how to bring love
and drive to that character.
That's the beauty of what Regina did.
There's so much love in what she does
yet she drives Jerry hard.
Riding him hard.
Now here's Jay Mohr being given
the gift of really just...
-Slam-dunking me.
-...whomping Tom!
And loving it.
Jay Mohr, Saturday Night Live
just a few seasons back.
Now you get to whomp on Tom
on the major screen!
Cut to the water glass
with the beads of sweat.
That was awesome.
I like the cut to the water and ice,
hearing the ice in the mix.
I love this scene.
"Could you get past yourself?”
-You'll lose.
-You want smaller.
-Just kicks it.
-"Get past yourself for a second.”
I love the idea of someone
being an asshole to you...
...begging you for sympathy.
Here's the fall.
We did takes where I don't fall.
Then Cameron came over and said,
"Why don't you fall on your face?"
-That's great.
- I said, "All right. Sounds like fun."”
He sort of animated
the subtext a little bit...
...of what's happening here.
It was a genius day.
Remember the talks
about this phone battle?
The war that was built up
and built up.
-The whole idea was to have a duel.
-Just stacked it.
Just bring the phone duel on.
And bring me my numbers!
He's just getting crushed.
He had a meltdown.
I've talked to Doritos about you.
They're interested. Talk to Rick.
These guys together that day.
It was insane.
-Remember?
-Insane in that room.
On another chapter of this DVD,
you'll see complete takes.
These guys are ripping, both of them,
for minutes upon minutes.
I'm gonna make this easy for you.
Just what does your heart tell you?
Sorry to hear that.
A shout out to Betsy Heimann. I love
how you're dressed. Is that crazy?
-No, I love it too.
-It is the perfect look for Dorothy.
She dressed that way, she's gonna
make a stand today. It's so great.
Perfect style, I thought.
-Drew Bledsoe.
-Drew!
Bob Sugar? He's...
He's entertaining, funny.
I don't know what it's like
to be black? I'm Mr. Black People!
Now, this is one of the (gifts,
again, the gifts of Tom...
-...to his director.
-Go ahead.
I yelled that out, to just say that.
Just, "Try this!"
You blasted it out.
We'd do takes. You'd fire dialog
at me as we ripped through it.
And we dig that about you, Cameron.
Writing on the fly. It's like playing
jazz. That's what it feels like.
-And he's riffing.
-Just going. I love that.
-Look at that, love that.
- I love that moment.
-Okay, well, this happened to me.
-This is classic.
With an actress or something?
You're kidding.
She had taken the part,
then she called me back...
...to say she couldn't do it, and she
was heartbroken. And this happened.
And it hurt like it hurts Jerry.
Think she regrets it? Actresses
you work with go on to be okay.
You're very kind, but--
Oh, there he is!
Bob Sugar says
I'm missing out by being with you.
-That's how I'm doing.
-That's why I'm calling.
No, I hear that.
But do you truly hear what I'm saying?
Sweet.
When you shot your stuff,
I had already wrapped.
That's so funny.
You were in England, right?
-This is the last two days of filming?
-It was.
Out there in Thousand Oaks.
So insane.
I am a valuable commodity!
I see a dude out to kill me,
I tell myself, "Catch the ball."
Touchdown! I make miracles happen.
Thank you, Janusz, for that shot.
And thank you, Cuba!
I went to Arizona State!
I'm a Sun Devil!
-Did you get that painting?
-No. There was a lot I was gonna get--
-The ants, I love.
-The ants.
Aries.
-Hello, brother Maguire.
-Hello, Tee Pee.
"Do not arrest this man."
Where is the Waterbed Warehouse?
- I didn't get any of that.
-That's wrong!
I was told I was gonna get it,
then it just went away.
-Somebody's got it. If you have it...
-Please, send it.
But I like you. Yes, I like you.
-This is music you found.
-Where did it come from?
In rehearsal, I played it
and Cameron said:
"Remember to bring it that day,"
and we had it.
-Where did we rehearse?
-At Sony, in the offices.
What can I do for you?
Just tell me, what can I do?
-That boy was so cute.
-Beautiful.
-You ready?
-Ready.
Making sure you are, brother.
Here it is:
Show me the money.
Right behind me!
He throws his hands up.
He's like, "That was it. That's the
line!" He's got the football going.
He's got the football going!
Yes. Well, this was all
in the script, wasn't it?
You two yelled things
off camera to me...
...while I shot my end of it.
You're on the phone, Cameron
yells to you, you yell to me.
That's so brilliant!
-Oh, God!
-Look at that--
-That line has haunted me ever since.
-For the rest of your life.
I could be at a funeral...
...you'll hear some prick go,
"Show me the money!"
-Shut up!
-"You're my motherfucker."
You know,
with all due respect, Cuba...
...I think you sort of
built that moment...
-...to such a huge, beautiful degree.
-Look at Tom!
-You know?
-Let it fly, man!
"Show me the money! You know?!"
We are so lucky
that we have tape...
...of the birth of "Show me the money,"
which will be part of this.
It's just what came from you and Tom
as you rehearsed, and it grew.
You had this music in your head.
And you were moving...
...and doing the music
and the dialog at the same time.
An amazing piece of film.
I love when you do that
"flip out" thing.
Nobody had ever seen you
act like that.
Tom's a little crazy on the set.
-You'd never let go like that before.
- I never had a character.
They saw A Few Good Men,
they saw Rain Man...
...even with Paul Newman.
Then you were like, "My balls are out...
...step on them
and pass them to the next person.”
-It's fun.
-It was awesome.
In fact, I'm starting a new company...
...and the fish will come with me.
The goldfish. Cameron was obsessed
with his goldfish.
You remember the package
that it came in?
-Even the fishes run.
-It took a few takes to get that.
-I love when you seal the bag in.
-He did it with such care.
His only friend.
That's classic.
...real and fun and inspiring...
She's so cute.
That line is from Nancy Wilson,
the great Nancy Wilson:
"Looking for truth
in this godforsaken business."
That's great.
Jann Wenner walking away.
This is embarrassing.
Damn.
-But you got your fish, honey.
-That's right.
Wendy.
How genius is that?
He's got the fish in the bag.
I mean, who thinks of that?
But not Wendy.
You don't have Wendy.
Look.
-The fish in the bag, the whole time.
-He's gotta walk out by himself.
He's got the fish.
-He's got Swim-Along.
-There we go, Dorothy.
Did she hit the coffee yet?
- I don't think that made it.
-Yeah, we had a version...
-...where she spills coffee.
-"Right now?"
Bye.
Your face, in this scene, said it
all. That's why you get paid okay.
-Really.
-Oh, look at Renee. Look at Renee.
You dream about having chemistry
with your lead actors.
Pretty awesome.
What was it like--7?
I love this, everyone goes
back to work.
"Who's got my memo?"
-Whatever, life goes on.
-Huge moment and then--
Sure, yes, medical.
Hot.
Is it harder or easier to do
a scene with a lot of extras...
...watching you act?
-It was really helpful.
-Yeah, I liked it.
It depends what you're doing.
In a funny scene,
it's like an audience.
If you're doing something
emotional and tender...
-...with people looking, that's weird.
-Show me the money--
-Oh, yeah.
I wonder what he said.
My favourite aunt is hearing-impaired.
He just said, "You complete me."
She's scared to death.
-It's been a bad day.
-Jerry's trying to grasp that concept.
-Jerry's trying to feel.
-"You complete me."
What exactly--? I kind of know
but I'm reaching...
This-- Oh, this was great stuff.
Look at that, look where it goes.
It goes from in that elevator,
that moment, to this.
-Same movie.
-I know. Shift.
-It never happens.
-This screenplay is...
When have you read
something like that?
-Hi, Mom.
-Oh, that's your mom!
These are mostly comediennes that--
There's Winnie Holzman, who wrote
My So-Called Life.
I love that line she has,
"All this chocolate-eating!"
-She wrote that, that's Winnie.
-I love it.
I...
...love this scene.
- I love Bonnie Hunt.
-Love her.
-She's awesome.
Here's another side of Renee
you meet.
Dorothy, I should say.
It's the steel in Dorothy.
And the love for the son.
It's great what you did here, Renee.
Oh, that's that day.
The first thing that I did.
Function, function.
Forward motion is everything.
Cush saves all.
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
- I was trying to sleep with you.
-Well, it worked.
And I will not let you fail.
You are Jerry Ma-fucking-guire!
Go, Kelly.
That's awesome.
-Who said anything about "loser"?
-Mistake. Wrong word! Let's leave.
The way Kelly says,
"Jerry Ma-fucking-guire."
It just sets it off, it really does.
-Puts her whole gig--
-Here we come, Beau Bridges.
-Oh, that's right, bloody beer.
-Dropping in for some love.
That's awesome.
That is awesome.
-Would you like a bloody beer?
-I'm fine.
-Beer and tomato juice.
-"Beer and tomato juice.”
That's a shout out to my buddy Kelly
Curtis, inventor of the bloody beer.
So hey, Kelly.
We decided to stay with you.
How fast can you hug him
after he says it?
Don't hesitate, as soon
as it comes out, hit him.
Watch Beau Bridges.
Watch his drink.
That's a Tom moment right there,
you just saw the real Tom Cruise.
You've done it once,
you've done it a thousand times.
Every time I see that,
I go, "That's Tom."
That's the boy.
I think there's another Tom moment
coming up in a second.
On every shoot, you get into a zone.
It takes a while sometimes...
...but when you're there,
you're there.
Anything you say or do, it's in.
-You just bring it.
-Yeah, it just comes.
Here it comes.
Janusz, lighting there.
Here we go!
There's the boy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Tom Cruise, Hollywood, California.
You driving to the studio,
today, right?
Oh, that's great.
I love when he does, "I'm free!"
-Nothing half-assed. Nothing ever.
-That's right. That's true.
Not even that.
He hadn't played hockey in years.
He scored a goal.
But he almost broke his neck.
-I was like, "That's Tom."
-Night before the shoot...
...he's on top of some guy, fighting.
I'm thinking:
"I don't want to show up
bloody and bruised.”
-That's him, man.
-Nothing half-assed.
Always balls out. It's awesome.
That's why you are where you are.
That's why friends like him.
So I hear.
Look at this.
I re-signed Cush. We're set.
-I am so happy for you.
-Happy for us.
Happy for us. Okay, happy for us.
Rod, being at the draft is good.
I should tell this story.
This scene was much simpler.
Tom said, "I'm a father.
And there's aspects of repartee
with a kid, with your son...
...that just-- I think we
can get more here."
So we dug in, and Jonathan himself--
He came to the set one day saying:
"The human head
weighs eight pounds.”
-Is that true?
-Are you serious?
So the two things came together.
Well, I wrote that--
The last one is yours, huh?
We combined the two and wrote
this scene the night before.
Did it completely fresh. It's one
of my favourite scenes.
And there's a moment here...
...where Renee watches Tom
walk off...
...and they see a life
they haven't had.
-That's Dennis Fitzgerald.
-The stand-in.
Our stand-ins.
-This shot, Renee, you watching...
- I know, I love this.
...will kill me for all time.
Look at the two of them
look at each other.
Cute. I shake your hand
and then leave.
Leave a brother out in the cold.
That's all right.
- I know he's coming home.
-Look at that.
-"I'm a Sun Devil.”
-Sun Devil.
-This is great.
-This is classic.
Are you Hootie?
And after this scene,
I really had that happen.
Some kid came up to me,
"Hey, aren't you Hootie?"
While we were filming the movie!
He hadn't seen it.
I was, like, "Oh, this is so funny."
If you see it in Spain, the kid says,
"Are you Ice-T?"
-Really?
-They change it to Ice-T.
Oh, that's great.
I love that one. The mom and son.
Why am I here? It's like I'm
five years late for the prom.
-Nobody gives a damn about me.
-Let's walk through this lobby.
I want all the media and player reps
to see you for what you are:
"Okay."
-This is good, more.
-You remember that? Bring it.
Cameron said, "Use your hands or
something. Make him keep talking."
- I love Rod Tidwell.
-See the walk. Look at the walk.
I have a tape at home of me
in my driveway practising...
...until I had the walk that I liked.
Look at this.
-I love Rod Tidwell.
-He's not listening, but he is.
The walk is just--
Cuba, the walk is--
Classic.
It's a thing of beauty.
-How are you?
-Good, hey.
"Yeah, listen to Jerry."
-Good?
-Great, baby.
-Mike Tirico, ESPN.
-Yeah, that's right.
This is, like, guy-dream come true.
-Going to the sets.
-We were having a ball.
It wasn't half bad for the girls
either, I have to say.
It might have even worked.
Yeah? Let's do that shit again.
Hey, hey. Stop.
Shooting a Reebok ad down there.
Where are my endorsements?
-Oh, Jay Mohr, "I love you."
-"I love you."
I didn't get no love from
that Energizer Bunny or Nike.
Obviously, I didn't get
love from Reebok.
-Did I tell you my Reebok story?
- I gotta get back to Cush.
Oh, your golden paycheque.
But wait, I'll boil it down for you.
Fuck Reebok!
All they do is ignore me.
Always have.
You know what was great down there?
You unloaded that large chip...
...on your shoulder.
And you let people in.
You were brilliant.
-Brilliant?
-Brilliant.
-Really?
-Take care, I'll see you tomorrow.
-You love me now?
-I'm about showing you the money!
I was just testing you,
but to hear you say that...
...makes me love you, baby.
You know?
-"You know?"
Pants were too long.
-What size are you?
-12 and a half.
Grab a couple pairs
of them new shoes by the door.
That's Light field Lewis.
I grew up with him. Didn't know he was
in the movie until after I saw it.
-You're kidding me.
-Didn't know.
This is great.
Jimmy O'Connell, playing Nirvana
on the guitar.
We lived in Seattle when rock
and sports started to be together.
They'd have a highlight reel
of a game cut to Nirvana.
I thought, "Something's happening.
These two never used to collide."
So that's why he's singing
"Something In The Way."
-This was just heartbreaking.
-Tom taking you on the big ride.
-This scene was--
-Great piece of writing.
It always got me. Now you know--
On a page until it comes to life
like this.
-Yeah, right.
-It's true.
And the camera's creeping in.
-New York City behind him.
-Oh, God.
The lights. Success is fleeting.
Look at his face.
This is life draining from a man.
Look at that!
No comment.
-He's got it wrong.
-You're on TV again.
I'm sick of me, already.
TEAM
CUSHMAN
He puts the hat on.
I'm gonna let you do it the hard way.
Let's go,
you're gonna have to go hard.
Before I go back to Denver,
we should put something on paper.
Something that says you're with me.
Not right now, Jerry.
Oh, that.
Do I know everything
there is to know here, Matt?
You're not talking
with Bob Sugar, are you?
Apparently, Denver would only
deal with him.
Said who? Sugar?
I'm learning as I go.
So you empowered him
to deal with Denver behind my back?
I'm sorry...
-I love my son.
- I love your son!
I brought Denver to 20 million.
They always deal with me.
You listened to Sugar.
Bob Sugar, Matt, is a child.
You let that snake in the door?
Listen, rookie mistake.
I'll fix this Denver thing for you.
You didn't sign anything
with Sugar, right?
Matt? Tell me you didn't sign.
Because I'm still sort of
moved by your...
...my word is stronger
than oak" thing.
-This is a little creepy.
-I know, it's "owie."
You were in the lobby
with the black fella.
Watch your mouth now.
Sorry, Jerry.
I just want to play football.
Never seen you look like that.
I've never seen him like that.
Never.
-Never seen you look like that.
-Kelly was great in this scene too.
Everything's on the run.
You and I are sales people.
We sell.
It's not "Love me"
or "Trust my handshake"...
...it's "Make the sale!
Get it signed.”
Jump right into my nightmare.
So now I can't be honest?
-I'd prefer loyalty.
-What'd we say when we got together?
Brutal truth. Remember?
I think you added the "brutal.”
There's a sensitivity thing that some
people have. I don't have it.
I don't cry at movies,
or gush over babies...
...don't do Christmas early...
...and I don't tell a man who
screwed up our lives:
She was training with Boom Boom
Mancini, am I right about that?
Kelly was preparing for this moment.
This wasn't just show up...
...and fake a punch. Kelly was ready.
It's over.
No one has ever dumped me.
I'm not trying to make history.
I climbed to the top of El Capitan...
...in 18 hours and 23 minutes.
I can make this work.
No.
Oh, Jerry.
I love a good break-up scene.
I'm a sucker.
Look at that! Look at that!
Took him down.
These are no idle moves.
He's all, "ouch."
-There's Billy's role.
-Yep. That's great.
This is great.
"You love me now?"
"Very much."
Didn't we arrive here in a limo?
No limo now, it's just, "Taxi."
Welcome back to the ghetto.
-This guy's crying.
-Roy Firestone and Dennis Rodman.
-Oh, is that right?
-And we inserted our guy.
I knew her, she's okay.
The media don't understand
the pressures $54 million comes with.
Oh, now, this is good.
Renee. She leaves
when it's your part.
She takes out the cameraman
working our camera.
We'll see you later, Renee.
We all gotta run when she's
on-screen. That would be funny.
"I'm cloaked in failure." I love that.
I love that.
Because a hockey player's kid
made me feel superficial.
I ate some bad pizza, went to bed
and grew a conscience!
Well, boo-fucking-hoo!
This is when I started to feel like you
two guys just hit a groove...
...and it would keep on going
as long as I could roll film.
And this was the last scene he filmed.
-The last thing we did together.
-That's right.
And we kept going and shooting.
Could I have another drink, please?
Anybody else would have
left you by now...
...but I'm sticking with you.
I said I would.
If I gotta ride your ass,
you gonna show me the money.
You gonna show me the money.
We together on this. You know
what I'm saying? We gonna be one.
Bopping to his music. He don't care.
-I love this.
-My cousin Keith's hand.
I love that. Your face is just like--
That was awesome.
"Did you remember the jump rope?
Just bring the jump rope."
Didn't you--? You stood
on your head in the memo scene.
That's awesome. Still got sports
going on in the background.
He's coming. He just lost his
best client. I invited the guy over.
Remember sitting outside and
watching these trucks pull out...
...and saying to each other:
"We're making a big movie.
How did this happen?"
Yeah, I do remember.
And the goal was to make it personal.
Even though it was...
...large in scope.
And that's what you're doing here.
Hi.
That's great. That's great.
Bonnie Hunt about to give you
that extra Bonnie moment.
Here comes the extra,
extra Bonnie moment.
And here's one more, checking him
out as he moves away. Yeah!
I'm telling you.
We found the ear
that day in rehearsal.
Geek. That's my favourite.
I love it, geek! Okay, look at him,
just coming apart.
-The lamp we had to lower.
-Oh, that lamp.
I love this moment coming up.
I'm so glad you're home.
That alone thing is not my speciality.
Oh, my God!
Oh, yeah. Oh, my God.
Well, I broke up with Avery.
I love that moment, Renee.
-Gosh, you know, that's too bad.
-No, it's better...
Yeah, that was a good day.
-Do you remember that day?
-Very well.
Yeah, me too.
-Taking an eyeball out.
-I remember that day.
I remember it really well.
Let's just talk about it.
-We don't have to tell all our stories.
- I was obsessed with this.
-There are some--
-Too bad.
No, you know, I'm keeping
some for just us.
-Okay.
-And that's one of them.
Unless you got a lot of money,
you can send me a cheque.
It's a really good story,
and we'll tell it in 50 years.
Exactly, then check back in.
When we have no teeth
and need assistance.
Move to DVD chapter four. It's me
alone, I'll tell you everything.
He shouldn't hear
a strange man's voice here.
I love this. That was bizarre.
Because we couldn't repeat it.
That was it, right there.
At the time it worked,
but that was the one.
Lipnicki.
Every day we saw each other,
I feel--
"The need for the speed.”
And then we'd go, "El fuego.”
That's it, he was on fire.
So cute.
Tom's his favourite actor,
his favourite movie Top Gun.
-And this was his favourite thing.
-Yeah.
-Acting.
-He did...
...a McDonald's commercial,
and became Ray Boyd.
Got to go to work
with his favourite guy.
This is the best way to spend
his day, according to Jonathan.
Hanging out with Tom.
This was when you were
writing it as you went.
"Say..."
And he would.
Yeah.
-Say, "Who is this?"
-He did the same with this scene.
Cuba, did we not call
you back after wrap?
You had wrapped. It was like:
"Get back here and in the tub."
-We got a scene to do.
-We got one more.
He was like:
"Bring it! I'm in the tub!"
Turtleneck, sensible.
V-neck, sexy. Turtleneck.
Don't say that. What are other women
my age doing right now?
They're out partying,
trying to get a man.
Trying to keep a man.
Not me, I'm trying to raise a man.
She holds on tight to it.
-I've had three lovers in four years.
-That's not bad.
All of them ran a distant second
to a good book and a warm bath.
Look at me. I'm the oldest
26-year-old in the world.
-Now, how do I look?
-Good.
Yeah? Thanks.
The beginning of the character.
James L. Brooks and I
worked hard on creating...
...the oldest 26-year-old
in the world.
Thanks for saying it so great.
Thanks for telling me how to do it.
I don't remember that.
I've lost my head!
My close-ups,
we shot Jonathan's stuff.
He'd have a break,
and I'd shoot my stuff.
That's how we shot Jonathan.
Remember?
-Because of the time.
-We had him for a few hours.
And he was really fresh.
And he was playing.
He wasn't tired yet.
-It was all play.
- It was just, maintain.
Told everyone, stay away
from Jonathan. Remember?
Because he had so many friends.
He's passing out from sleep
exhaustion here.
Another frame and his eyes are shut.
It's the sweetest thing,
that's how he's in it.
-That's a pillow I'm looking at.
-He's falling asleep.
The zoo, you know--
The fucking zoo's closed.
You said "fuck."
Yeah, I did.
-Is that--?
- won't tell.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's the foot.
"Poink" right there.
Didn't you just wanna make
a break for the parking lot?
Tuck him under there
and run away forever?
There! They got the head.
-The Charlie Brown shot.
-That's the best ever! Oh, God.
I haven't watched this--
This is a crap movie...
...Cameron, maybe next time.
-We made it work, I guess.
-We did our best, you know.
Yeah, we tried, didn't we?
- I could've done more.
-Good effort.
Just one more shot, one more take,
that's all I needed.
Here it is. This is where it started.
-Yes.
-This is great.
It's funnier than I expected,
you acting like a crazy person.
We re-shot--
-This is 5 a.m.
-Yeah, this is 5 a.m.
-Oh, you're kidding.
-We were finishing.
I am a survivor.
You're a nut!
You free-associating,
"king of the kingdom."
Yes, he's just going.
I'm the...
The fish, that's great.
-It was really early.
-I love having this fish in there.
That's great.
Now here we go.
Ready yourself, Renee.
Can you watch this scene, Renee?
All the time!
Pause, rewind, pause, rewind,
pause, rewind.
I'll be one of those old ladies:
-"Kids, I wanna show you something!"
-"When my breasts were up to here!”
"And a man could find them!"
-Funny.
-This was a day.
-Take us through it.
-No!
-Just do one of them.
-Absolutely not!
That stays in my pocket.
That's with me.
He never needs to know
what's in my head.
-Read your mind.
-Come on.
-No!
-Go!
He likes me.
He doesn't need to know.
Ladies and gentlemen,
not a bad day at the office.
Sorry about the hand.
I thought, "I love my job."
"Ladies and gentlemen,
not a bad day."
How did you feel when we chose
that as your screen scene?
-Was that true?
-I was so...
...beside myself just
to be there at all.
It wouldn't matter what you
had me saying or doing.
It was all the same.
I was so vulnerable and so...
I was--
I knew that that was
a golden moment in my life.
So I didn't give a turd how
embarrassing or-- You know?
How could you do that to me?
But the thing is,
there was a moment where...
...we were doing some
costume tests...
...and Tom was wearing some clothes.
I told you guys to stand together.
He put his arm around you.
No, you around him.
That was the moment you became
a couple for me.
And that's...
That was everything.
Speaking of everything, I loved
this scene, "I'm back," so much...
...they had to literally
pull me off the set.
I was gonna shoot all night long,
Tom saying, "I'm back."
Do you remember that?
We did the taxi.
-You fell over the bushes 20 times.
-He kept saying, "Again."”
This was a huge laugh,
Tidwell hits the post.
-That was good.
-My stuntman, Dain Turner.
-Here's Glenn Frey of The Eagles.
-T-U-R-N-E-R.
-Dain.
-That's right, Big D-dog.
Now, this was my birthday,
and I got a couple days off.
-Glenn Frey's coming up.
- I love this scene.
That's awesome.
The short-sleeved Jerry Maguire there.
I still have that shirt.
I still have that shirt, I love it.
He's like, I'm not in L.A.,
I'm gonna dress Arizona.
Did we miss "Jerry Maguire"?
Did we miss it, did he say it?
I love how he says it.
"He's a shrimp."
-Remember?
-I'll beat his ass.
Not some guy who's 5'10" and bitches.
-That's classic.
-It's harsh.
It's true, though. These players...
You gotta self-promote so much.
-Holiday cheer.
-Jerry, you're reaching.
"You're reaching."
All the stomach medicine up there.
I love that. Like, "Oh, I'm..."
-I never noticed.
-It's what they go through.
Acute observations.
I love this shot.
-Him in his underwear?
-Yes.
It's just too easy.
For two days we stood around,
a bunch of naked people.
-You loved every second.
-Not all of it. Brothers were swinging.
How can I keep up?
I like this shot too, by the way.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-I'm telling you, it was a good job.
Some dudes might have coin,
but they'll never have kwan.
What is--?
It means love, respect, community
and dollars. The entire package.
The kwan.
I love, Cuba,
when you experience kwan.
I love that.
It's like he's listening
to some good music.
It's the feeling of kwan.
But those players you mentioned
are marquee players.
How can he use the "M" word
in that way?
This is a scene we auditioned with.
Am I right?
Yeah.
"Telling me to dance."
...10 get back to the guy
who first started playing.
Way back when you were a kid, it
wasn't just about the money, was it?
Was it?
Do your job.
Don't you tell me to dance!
When you kicked the wall, I laughed.
You went crazy.
I do not dance, and I do not start
pre-season without a contract!
Another real Tom moment.
Tom missing the goal.
The hug you gave him Saturday.
Nothing half-assed.
You don't know
what it's like to be me.
I wanted to have...
...Makeup put cuts on me
to show I was tough.
But it almost didn't show.
I was so wet, everything drained down.
The blood and all, because
he took a beating.
I love this. I love this.
-Classic.
-"Help me help you."
And the audience wants to laugh here,
and you let them!
I mean, this could've been
the other thing altogether.
Genuine, beautiful,
vulnerable, angry.
And he laughed in your face!
It is genius!
Yeah! Oh, that's great.
Oh, you guys. God. God!
-Do that again.
- I thought you were gonna go frontal.
Well, we have that footage, Cuba.
-Okay, this is where I leave!
-Director's cut.
Join me on chapter five or seven.
You mean five and seven?
Five and seven, and 15 as well.
You spent a lot of time thinking
about all the airports...
...the travelling, the different...
...hours with Janusz discussing it
and music...
People passing through
from capsule to capsule.
Living their life. And that was
our plan for the airport scenes.
This is the day James L. Brooks
was laughing so hard.
You were like, "Quiet!"
He was like:
I love that scene with you guys
in the bathroom.
I couldn't wait to play it.
You gotta do that again.
I wanna watch it.
Stop the tape!
You know, the other night,
I was lonely.
I felt you understood something.
We've got a company to think about.
I'll never take advantage
of you again.
-Didn't Suzanne Somers live next door?
-Did she?
That's right, you were in Venice!
Is that where--7?
-Manhattan Beach.
-Manhattan Beach, right.
Think about what's wrong
and how to fix it.
And, you know, just be alone.
Alone.
-Alone, alone, alone.
-Alone, alone.
-You wanna go out to dinner?
-I know a great place.
I love this band, they were great.
-What do you mean by stalking?
-Coming over uninvited.
"Coming over uninvited"? So Romeo
on your balcony is a stalker?
How many days did you shoot this?
Boy, I think four days.
Him walking into it.
It's like, "Help me."
We did some takes where Tom
just came in.
Unannounced.
It was your first moment
right there, isn't it?
With the women's groups.
They'd never met you.
-They hadn't met him?
-No.
They didn't say he'd be there,
and he walked in.
-He just walked in.
-Did you use any of it?
Yeah, that front angle was one.
Todd Louiso,
who plays Chad the Nanny.
-He's genius.
-He's genius...
...and so is Renee, listening.
I love this shot of Renee listening.
-Look at that.
-Yeah, my goodness, she looks great.
We tell the audience
how we feel about--
-About every single scene.
-Hey!
-Okay, there's something that...
-Look at that, against the wall.
-Love how Bonnie take this away.
-She goes:
"For me? Wow!"
Yes, he's so--
"This is an energy bar."
That's more than a dress,
that's an Audrey Hepburn movie.
That was an interesting dress.
That dress has a story.
-That dress had some straps.
-Yes, it has straps.
-Breakaway straps.
They would not reliably
break away, however.
-They came off easily.
-Sometimes.
When they weren't supposed to.
Sometimes they didn't
when they should.
I love that look.
Let me embarrass you for a moment
here, okay?
This scene is where I felt...
...really that I wanted to direct.
It gave you a chance to do more
than just write and capture stuff.
And it's Tom with Jonathan here.
And Renee just watching them.
And I remember watching this
through the camera...
...particularly this next shot.
And I went nuts.
I just started jumping around.
And Janusz, our great DP, said:
"It's a scene in a kitchen!
Why are you so happy?"
Because that's the movie,
and that's a stolen moment.
I heard that music in my head
while you were doing it.
And I just remember thinking
from that day on...
...I want to direct too,
not just write.
I will always think of that
when I see that scene.
That's what you crave.
Remember this shot coming up you
showed me when we were rehearsing?
You were going over music.
I remember this shot.
I remember seeing it.
Look at this.
You described how you were
gonna have her run.
-That's beautiful.
-No shoes.
Look at that run. So beautiful.
-And this shot.
-That is just awesome.
This is an homage
to My So-Called Life...
...which is one of my favourite
TV shows, where...
There's our band.
I love the feeling of it.
I later met Claire Danes and said:
"Did you see Jerry Maguire? There's
an homage to My So-Called Life."
She's like, "Yeah."
Is that true?
That's me doing a bad imitation.
-Thief.
-She caught it.
And I just loved being able
to do that.
That's great. "Yeah."
-That was magical.
-Yeah, that run down, beautiful.
That night was magical.
There's no other way to--
I'll never forget that,
never forget that day.
-A song for the lovers?
-No, thank you.
Please, no.
No, really, this is like
an office meeting.
He tips them!
-You knew they were coming back!
-Office meeting.
Before...?
-Jerry?
-What?
Let's not tell our sad stories.
I'll be back in just a second, okay?
Thank you, Renee.
Yeah, it was awesome.
My wife says that too.
"Okay, calm down."
"Oh, I'm an idiot. All right."
Same look, just quiets you down.
Awesome.
This is a Cameron Crowe-ism,
this moment here.
He lives for these moments.
He thinks of these moments.
It's the big scene
the movie hinges on.
"When do we get to shoot
the mariachis?"
You couldn't wait
to shoot the mariachis.
"Listen, it's great. When do we
get to the Mexican restaurant?"
-And this moment.
-Here's Tom, graciously...
...making it through another
awkward moment.
Graciously making it through.
I don't know, I dig that song.
Okay, here we are on the porch.
-Okay.
-Hey, Renee, tell us about this.
No!
Oh, that's great.
Thoughts, comments?
I felt the kiss was
a little too long.
But really, the kiss
is about Tidwell.
-That's right.
-It's the kiss.
-He's concerned with Rod's career.
Thank you.
-Okay, the music.
-Oh, and this, the lighting.
This floored me when we saw this
on the boat in New York.
The first time I ever saw it.
When we were shooting this...
...he kept saying, "This is perfect,
this is so romantic."
He just came in, "This is so--"
Remember that, Cameron?
"Just, just, just do one again.
It's working."
-That's great.
-And it was hysterical.
We couldn't depend on our dress.
The dress kept breaking
in the wrong places.
-Is this gonna--?
-And then before--
It's gonna work,
we'll get the straps right.
I remember Tom saying, "We're on
the U-train, take us there."
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
Just take us, is it working for you?
I'm happy.
-Renee, you look great.
-That's awesome.
What you don't see
IS SO much greater.
You got that right.
Paul McCartney, solo album.
-This is just so good.
-Yeah.
I think you should not come in.
Or come in.
That's great.
"Same to you."
I live here.
Again, 5 in the morning.
This was a great night, though.
Because everyone had gone home,
you know?
-It was really basic.
-A quiet set.
A couple guys on camera,
couple guys running around.
It was very cool. Cameron's sets
are always scene-prepped.
Everybody's, you know, the set,
everybody's just into the movie...
...and help set the tone,
which comes from Cameron.
Scene-prepped. It's a great--
That kissing scene was inspired by...
...a scene in an old movie
starring Jean Arthur...
...which I thought was just a private
thing, a little private homage.
It was great when people
wrote about that...
...that we channel led Jean Arthur
in that scene. I thought:
"Thank you, Renee."
Tom was in there too, of course.
I didn't notice.
"I didn't notice."
As I say, you can feel Cuba.
Very strongly in that scene.
Oh, he's so good in this,
he's so funny.
You're sure of it. Just genius.
-Oh, God, he's so earnest and...
-Oh, that speech was just perfect.
I've read on the Net,
some jazz fans say...
...we're making fun of jazz fans.
-What?
-And it's so not the case.
It is celebrating the passion
of music fans.
In this case, a true jazz fan
of Miles and Coltrane.
-And also Dorothy Boyd.
-And Dorothy Boyd.
Dorothy a little more,
heartbroken by this...
He's the geek with the ear
and the lamp.
Yeah.
I love that part in the movie.
-Oh, terror.
-That scene was not in the script.
That scene was not in the script.
That was about...
...the chemistry of Renee and Tom.
-You just want that little piece.
-Let's just let them rip.
-And?
-Here they are.
And there it goes.
You know this is gonna
change everything.
Promise?
What is this music?
I love that.
He's just gotta hang, hang, hang.
See, that's--
That's the brilliance of Cameron.
-Not afraid--
-The pot scene?
That also, while that's going on,
to cut to the sister.
-With her to-go food.
-To allow a scene...
...that kind of room and not
be afraid, knowing that--
The intimacy and the humour,
without it being glib. I love that.
"This will be a great day!"
-That's great.
-Oh, that's great.
I meant the cut.
I did!
Oh, God. I mean, bad.
-You need a moment?
-Bad timing.
I need a moment to myself,
for myself and by myself.
Can you guys excuse me
for just a minute? Oh, God.
The cut to the mentor
saying "Good morning."
Oh, God, I have to go home.
How genius are you?
This is my favourite reaction of you,
Renee, in the whole movie...
...when you do the whole--
Your face is awesome.
-It's so funny.
- I was thinking about Rod Tidwell.
Why should I let this guy go...
It's so funny.
Take it easy.
I just wanted a few fun details.
Such a guy in the hall,
going, "Uhh!"
"What do I do now?"
You're pouring your heart out...
...and she's looking at you like
you're talking about cereal.
She's just kind of looking at you,
until this.
I love him for the man
he wants to be...
...and for the man that he almost is.
Oh, his face!
Act natural.
Busted.
Tell me he's not there.
The sister's in there.
Busted.
-Coffee?
-We bottom feeders prefer cereal first.
-Let's have Apple Jacks.
-Apple Jacks it is. Dorothy.
Good morning, darling.
Jonathan laughs like
he knows what's going on.
We've got a big fax today.
We need this commission.
No love from Apple Jacks.
Maybe they sent you
a couple of boxes?
It's an R-rated movie.
-There you go.
- It wasn't about the Apple Jacks.
-No love from Apple Jacks.
-That's cold.
Let's just root for a big offer
so we can move out of this room...
...into a real office.
Would you mind? Thanks a lot.
I thought one of the
great moments was "darling”...
...when Jerry calls Dorothy "darling"
in the kitchen...
...when he sticks up for her.
Then of course, the fax comes in.
This is the game.
I'll get back to them.
And say what? "Please remove
your dick from my ass"?
-That's great.
-Oh, she's good.
Regina King is awesome.
Just awesome. Been trying to work
with her again since this movie.
You know, putting something
else together. Awesome.
-Get me Bob Sugar on the phone.
-Marcee...
-You wanna leave me?
-A lot of agents say a lot of shit.
-You wanna leave me”?
-What do you stand for?!
How about integrity?
There's so much greed in the world...
...I don't know what to tell my son!
This guy isn't yelling,
"Show me the money!”
"Broke, broke, broke!"
"Dorothy, Dorothy."
Easy, girl.
-I'm not as good at insults as she is.
-That was pretty good.
No shit.
Let me show you something.
Yeah!
"Let me show you something."
Put that back in the box.
Let's just bury that.
Let's say that never happened.
Tell me what to do. Tell me to eat
Lima beans, I'll eat Lima beans.
You say this is the best,
all we can get--
-All we can get?
-I'm talking with my agent.
This is what you're gonna do. You're
gonna reject that shitty contract.
Play out your existing shitty contract,
and next year, you're a free agent.
Baby, this is us. You and me.
We determine our worth.
You are a strong, proud...
...surviving, splendid black man.
Marcee...
-How beautiful is that?
-"You're the shit."
Oh, baby.
Look at you winning
your Academy Award.
Rod.
For the handshake, I just pulled
you down, you go, "Okay."
-Remember?
-There it is.
You know? My man!
That's what I love
about this character...
...Is that he has it so together,
and every time...
...something gets him
off his feet, literally.
-I love it.
- I like these looks.
That's so great.
All Jerry wants to do is survive
and get back on his feet.
And he just gets bombarded by
these couples who are in love.
From the deaf couple on the elevator,
to Rod and Marcee...
...and it's, like,
"Okay, I got it.”
-Life is just hammering him.
-Exactly.
In a beautiful way.
Do you remember this camel?
Oh, my God!
Yeah, the camel chased me.
-He almost bit you, remember?
-Yeah, I remember!
That camel was no joke!
This was...
This is what it was like.
-That camel started going off.
-The camel attacked us.
-His trainer--
-One crew guy got stomped.
The trainer's trying
to keep him calm.
There's one shot in the movie
from when the camel attacked us.
I love that!
No, I guess there's not that shot.
Please join me in chapter...
What do you know
about single moms?
Oh, this is genius.
This is some writing right here.
First of all, single mothers
don't date. Watch yourself.
They've been to the circus.
You know what I mean?
They've been to the puppet show
and seen the strings.
-You love her?
-How do I know?
You know when you know.
I don't want her to go. I've been
hanging out at her place a lot.
-Mustard workout suit is--
-It's working!
It was like terrycloth or something.
She loves you. If you don't love her,
you have got to tell her.
This is great!
Women walk up to me and go, "My
boyfriend never shoplifts the pootie."
Every once in a while.
I'm like, "That's very nice.
It's very nice to hear, lady."
"I feel you, dog."
I love how he has
to say this so adamantly.
-"I didn't--"
- I didn't shoplift the pootie.
"All right.”
I love it!
We continued shooting afterwards--
"Get your ass in the car!”
Didn't we shoot about five different
angles of me shaking his hand?
We did.
Loved this goodbye scene.
I loved it too.
-How do we say goodbye?
-Look at this.
We had a whole...
Key scene with Renee and Bonnie:
"Let's shoot them shaking hands."
-"Keep them going in the back."
-"It's really funny when they..."
"Goodbye!"
All right. Goodbye.
"Hey, one more."
He said, "Don't let him go,
just keep..."
Here's that-- There it is.
"Can we shoot, please?"
"Okay, Jonathan."
Is that what he said?
He said, "Are we ready?
Are we gonna shoot?"
-I'm gonna see you this weekend.
-Go ahead and go.
"You jerk."
Sounds like a Peanuts character.
That's my Sonics shirt.
Can you do the Bridget Jones voice?
Absolutely not.
-Come on, Z.
-No way!
We spent a lot of time
discussing this moment.
Do you remember, Cameron?
The behaviour.
The glasses.
Yeah, we had to pick the glasses.
Very important.
Do a little Bridget.
Is that butterscotch?
-"Oh, Bridget!"
-She's got candy!
I was obsessed with getting
the perfect tear to be there...
...when Jerry tips down
Dorothy's sunglasses.
And she brings it.
It was our spiritual tip of the hat
to Billy Wilder.
I don't know why,
but it felt to me...
. like...
...a Billy-worthy moment if we got it.
-And there's the Cameron.
-Yeah, this is Cameron.
Turn around, walk away, turn around.
This one took a while.
This is a bizarre wedding proposal.
I'm so proud of this.
I love this.
I love this scene.
Will you marry me?
What are you thinking?
...like, "How am I doing?”
"What's going on, where am 17"
"Let me see how I'm doing."
There you are.
Last shot I filmed.
Yes, indeed, it was.
-That was your last shot in the movie?
-Yeah.
We had to get close-up footage later
because the sun was going down.
We were crying and they were like,
"Break for lunch, come back.
Can we get those tears going?"
"We have five minutes
and we're in overtime."
-This is a real moment.
-The whole crew's hungry.
This is a real moment because
Jonathan kept, yeah...
Almost.
He kept doing that.
-It was so great that we put the...
-The mariachi.
...priest dialog in later to match it.
Then Cuba couldn't wait to do this.
We had to pull him away.
He is a karaoke maniac.
I love Regina. She's like,
"That is my husband.”
"Let's go. Okay, he's drunk,
let's get out of here."
Do you remember
when we first met...
...and we were playing around
in the office?
And you put on some sunglasses
and said, "This is how I see it.
She has no idea it's
the greatest moment of her life...
...and she's walking through
her wedding day like this...
...and we all know the truth.
But she has no idea."
And you played the music,
and I walked around in sunglasses...
I'll never forget that, ever.
That was the beginning of it.
-She didn't know.
-She didn't.
Ladies and gentlemen, Bonnie Hunt.
Oh, look at them.
Nice timing, buddy.
I remember this.
Do you remember this shot?
Oh, that was the day.
This is another moment where
you as a director are going:
"Life is good."
Everybody is bringing it.
Cuba, realising
her private moment, right there.
That broke my heart.
Hey, that's my bro.
You guys really spoiled me.
See, now I'm gonna
release this to ESPN.
-You think I'm joking.
-No, it's okay. I know where you live.
You didn't have the talk, did you?
No.
Well, this definitely
was another way to go.
Hey, Dorothy, come here.
Tidwell brings them together.
Here comes the pat.
Look at this shot.
-We were just killing stunt men.
-Scott Martin.
-Scott Martin was on.
-There's Kelly.
-He's having a good game. So far.
-He is.
You're gonna miss him next year.
Loser.
She's venomous.
Catch the ball, get killed.
Come here.
-Look at Regina King do her thing.
-She's awesome.
And we'll let you live.
Now go kiss Daddy, quick.
That's one thing, whenever
I go back and see the film...
...it's always Regina now.
It's always Regina.
It's like, God. She just--
She represented the sports wife...
...holding the family together,
hoping her husband's okay.
And she's so perfectly seamless.
You just accept that--
And so were you, Renee.
Renee, easy. So were you.
So were you. Truly.
You don't see it because you...
Don't go and embarrass me
when I'm...
Give love to them all.
I love this.
This is the day we had the race?
-That's right, up those stairs.
-At 5 in the morning.
Take care of yourself on that field.
You're my entire client roster.
Don't I know this.
Now go home to your wife.
-What's that mean?
-What are you doing here?
-You could've told me on the phone.
-How about personal attention?
-You don't want to go home.
-What are you saying?
I'm just trying to talk to you.
How's your marriage?
The husband and wife thing,
how is that?
-Not everyone has what you have.
-Why did you get married?
-I'm just asking as a friend.
-You want an answer?
Loyalty.
She was loyal.
Look at you
winning your Academy Award.
It just...
I love the way Jerry--
Jerry believes loyalty is a
good enough reason to get married.
-"Grew from there."
-You're gonna laugh at me?
"Let me break something off
in your ass."
"Okay, it's that other stuff too.
You know?"
"Wait a minute, Rod,
let's talk for a minute."
And then the hit.
We used to laugh.
It was like, "Cuba...
...you're pushing Tom
out of the frame."
Every time, he pushed him
over the couch...
...pulls him through the window.
Cuba had no fear.
You just brought that character.
Beautiful.
You said most people
who auditioned...
...would see Tom and freak out.
I said, "I'll pee all over him."
You had your pants down.
I was like, "Hey, man."
I've been around certain
big stars like that, who...
...give off that presence.
But I'll give it to you, man,
you enabled me to do that.
You could have said,
"When they say cut, don't touch me."
And, "You're too hard,
can you pull back?"
And I'd have been, like, "Oh, shit."
It's like boxing with somebody...
...who pulls their punches. Not him.
That's what's fun working with
people, like you, Renee, Jay...
...everyone we had
was just bringing it.
We all felt like
we could push you around.
I felt like I could push
you guys too.
That's why you have longevity,
because you're open to people.
-That's the fun of it.
-It shows.
That's the fun of working and acting.
You have this writing
and this director, and you just...
You gotta be open to new talent,
and you are. It's awesome.
-The aeroplane.
-The Crowe theme.
-Love that. You go. Look at you.
I always thought that guy
looked like David Letterman.
You spent a lot of time
in the editing room.
-There's your AD.
-That was the first shot of the film.
-Cuba in the MRI.
-You remember your A.D.? Your guy?
-Jerry Zeesmer.
-He was my masseuse in that.
We love Jerry.
Jerry comes back in this movie.
The aeroplanes. The aeroports.
I went to see this so-called
black film the other day.
No more salt.
Your biggest game is coming up.
Oh, I love her.
-They feed each other.
-Again.
-It's just hell for Jerry.
-They're doing it again.
-It doesn't go well.
-The kids are all over.
But you just die for the character
moments and the little touches.
The way Jerry tries to
express love for Dorothy.
Now it's eating at him.
"I could do that.
I could do that."
You see his face?
"I could do that."
-Now the baby talk.
-Isn't that nice?
Way to go, Jerry.
-Give you a little hug.
-Give you a little love.
-Now?
-Baby now!
I'm trying to catch the kids.
And we were laughing
because they were running around.
-It took me two takes to catch them.
-Cameron told them to run.
-I was trying hard to catch them kids.
-That was great.
- I like this scene.
-Me too.
-Lipnicki's falling asleep.
-Oh, my God!
Jonathan comes in and he's--
I think he's drunk in this scene.
-He might have been.
-He hit the bottle.
-He's drunk on Tom Cruise.
-Hard-working gentleman...
...coming to the end of his day.
I love this scene.
I thought I just did.
This scene was like a one-scene
homage to Carnal Knowledge...
...which I'm sure nobody would catch--
Can I come and watch TV?
-In just a minute.
-For a few minutes.
-Oh, God.
-He's probably out already.
-He had that baby puppy smell.
-Look at him.
Look at him, you can't imagine.
-It's the feet.
-"Can I come in and watch TV?"
He was exhausted.
- I like this close-up here.
-"He loves my kid."
-Can we talk about something else?
- I don't think so.
I gotta tell you,
I love that they're in silhouette.
We did it in and out of silhouette,
and it was so clearly the one.
Just tells a story.
This is Nancy Wilson's
composition, "Sandy."
-A Brian Wilson-esque piece.
-Isn't she something?
I love her. Hi, hon.
And I say Meryl Lee here.
That's my mother's name.
-Yes.
-My mama.
If only agents were that accessible.
24-7.
-Mine are.
-Tell Douglass I say hello.
Damn.
He ain't afraid to hit below the belt.
That's my boy.
Look how cute he is. Look.
-Do you remember shooting this scene?
-No, not at all.
-Oh, that day. That was a day.
-Tell us about it.
Tell us about something, shit!
What'd you eat for breakfast?
Bridget, come on.
I'm working here, okay?
I'm working.
...I was in love enough
for both of us.
I pretended your proposal was real...
...when it might have been
a hypothetical.
He doesn't say anything.
"Hypothetical." Not an easy word
to just whip off and...
I stick.
-Wrong answer, buddy.
-Great face.
What do you want?
My soul or something?
-Why not? I deserve that.
-What if I'm not built that way?
- I think we made a mistake.
-What if it's true?
"Great at friendship,
bad at intimacy."
It's the theme of my bachelor film,
for God's sake.
I know, I watched it.
I sort of know it by heart.
- I don't like to give up.
-Please. Jerry.
My need to make the best of things,
and your need to be responsible...
If we don't say something about
it now, we could lose 10 years...
...being polite.
Let's just call this next road trip
what it really is:
A nice long break.
What about Ray?
Well, you'll be friends.
Didn't we do this scene earlier
than it was scheduled?
You guys sort of
had to do it last-minute.
And that really...
...really became real.
So this break is a breakup? That's--
No time to over-think it.
You just had to do it.
I've got this great guy.
And he loves my kid.
And he sure does like me a lot.
And I can't live like that.
It's not how I'm built.
I remember you doing that.
It was beautiful.
I remember that take.
I love that song.
Tom just bringing it.
We did it both ways, where the shot
moves in, and pulls out.
Dicky.
The amazing thing, well...
-This was a great moment.
-Oh, this is awesome.
Lipnicki was really asleep there.
This happens once in your life.
It happens once...
...that you get to be a part of
something like this.
-If you're real, real lucky.
-You got that right.
It's gonna happen to you
again and again, guys.
If somebody'd get off his butt
and get busy.
Oh, Bridget!
Bridget.
I love this shot with Kelly
on the escalator.
This is the exact--
That is The Graduate.
We were, I think...
We were the flip
of the same moving escalator...
...that The Graduate shot on.
The amazing thing
about that break-up scene is...
...the double-edged thing
that happened.
Some people
got married because of it...
...and some people
broke up because of it.
Including a woman that worked
in our editorial room.
Who saw it with her boyfriend.
I asked what they thought of it.
And she said:
-"We broke up!”
-Oh, my goodness.
And I go, "Wow,
that's really terrible."
And she goes, "No, it's good.
It's good!"
You know, and it was all about...
And it would go both ways.
That's hysterical.
"It's good, it's good."
Did they ever get back together?
I think they amicably separated--
They were living a lie.
Did they finish the picture,
or did they leave after that scene?
Did they see how it ended?
They saw it all,
and went out to dinner.
I'd heard this before.
People would talk afterwards...
And would go from being loving...
...to realising what they
might be lacking, or vice versa.
One of our first previews, a guy
proposed after the lights came on.
That happened a few times.
People say this is the movie
that she showed and he proposed.
-That's great.
-People left that screening at Sony...
...he got up and proposed
in the screening...
-...and they left.
- I wonder how they're doing.
They're divorced.
They came to their senses.
This guy...
...came up to me, it was interesting
that it was a guy...
-...on the set of Bridget.
-On Bridget?
And how did he say it exactly?
He said he broke up with his
girlfriend because of this film.
They watched the end, and when
he says, "You complete me"...
...he has tears in his eyes and says:
"That is-- It doesn't get any better.
That's so romantic." And he kept
going on and on about it.
And she said, "Is it?" And he said:
"Okay. Okay." And that was it.
And he knew he couldn't
be with her. Isn't that neat?
You're ruining lives
all over the world.
Cameron Crowe,
ladies and gentlemen.
-Breaking people up all over.
- I loved making this film.
-Let's talk about the commentators.
-Look at these guys.
-He was giving it up.
-Troy Aikman was still throwing.
You know, he's retired now.
But he's got a town in Texas.
-Does he really?
-It's Troy Aikman, Texas.
-Is it really?
-Right after Jerry Maguire.
We used footage
of a real Cardinals vs. Cowboys game.
We had a great time with all those
players and commentators.
-Look at you.
-Lining up with the guys.
-Look at you out there.
- I believe it.
Look at you. I believe you.
And they really
went at a brother, now.
-You have proof somewhere?
-Here comes the hit.
All the fans that we had.
Was it 17,000 or something
you recruited?
Do you remember
when we were dancing?
And we hung out between takes with
the players. Playing catch and stuff.
And Chris Mackenzie,
my trainer who built me up.
-He's actually a hockey player.
-Mackenzie.
He's out somewhere in Texas now,
playing in the Colonial League.
Y'all tried to call me
and invite me to that.
- I think so.
-You tried to call me.
-Actually, you called on my birthday.
-We always call Renee.
-Z-Dog was gone.
-You did call me.
-You passed the phone around.
- I think it's a miracle you're here.
-Because she did leave.
-Actually, this is CGI...
-...a miracle of technology.
-That's right.
It's the first
digital interview of a woman.
-Look at Regina.
-Go! Go!
-She's good.
-She's fantastic here.
Wasn't this the last take? You thought
you had it but did one more.
-Let's do one more.
-Really? Is that true?
Just stay calm. Keep the lines open,
I will call you back.
There are good doctors. Stay calm.
You have to tell me something.
I am freaking here.
-What do you think?
-She kills me.
You think about the athlete's family
and what they go through.
-Doesn't work without Rod.
- I know.
-Right on his neck.
-They show it so much.
-They show it over and over.
-It's just, you get it.
You get that love. You get it.
Right here.
Oh, God.
-Frank Gifford.
- I still have the football.
-There's Jerry.
-I'm knocked out.
Blink, baby! Wake up!
This is Jerry Zeesmer, one of
the great assistant directors.
-Bringing Rod to life.
-There he is, to the left.
Music comes in. His new life.
The beginning of his new life.
Kind of like me and this movie.
Seriously, after this movie
and the award...
I'd been acting and acting
and suddenly...
...I got knocked out, came to,
and got the big contract.
Everything came together. I had
a baby. My whole life started.
-Deserved, deserved.
-Everything came together.
He is getting up.
Well, my life went to crap.
-Listen to you.
-I was waiting for that.
You know it.
You know something bad's coming.
Oh, yeah. I love this.
Cameron almost killed me
with this dance.
"Can you do another back flip?
Okay, do everything but that."
Yes, ladies and gentlemen,
that is not a stunt man.
I just couldn't get any
enthusiasm out of you.
Barry Switzer.
Here we go,
choreographed by yours truly.
The fans had already seen this.
Cuba choreographed this whole thing.
No, I worked with Paula Abdul.
She showed me some stuff.
- I give it to her.
-We couldn't get you off the field.
-Yeah, I added the break dance.
-Yes, you did.
Okay, you know?
I don't think Paula
made that part up, did she?
-I love that.
-That answer from Regina...
This is pure joy, man.
Look at that, look at that.
I like that, he's gonna
get a flag on this.
-He's gonna get a flag.
-He's getting a flag on this one.
People said I did that dance
at the Academy Awards.
Well, if I did,
it's because I lost my mind again.
That's perfect.
That was beautiful when you
received the Academy Award.
-"Jerry Maguire."
- I almost choked on my hamburger...
...screaming and clapping for you.
-"You're gonna pay."
-You're gonna pay.
Show him the money! You know?!
Do you remember
when we were doing that?
-That's awesome.
-Oh, God, man.
Cuba, if you didn't play this
character with such joy throughout...
...we'd be dead.
It'd just be an angry guy.
Which would be great...
...but it wouldn't be Tidwell.
You know where the dance
comes from. It's part of you.
-And Tom and I doing this moment.
-Look at this.
-It was awesome.
-Talk about your great screen couples.
- I ain't doing no kissing though.
-No, baby, no way. Uh-uh.
-That was awesome, dude.
-New season, the bathroom.
Now who's this guy
in the background?
- I love this.
And he goes, let's go for it.
-Go, Jay Mohr.
-This is a real football player too.
He's awesome.
Dorothy?
What's this guy saying behind you?
He's like, "Rod, come on, man."
"Rod! Rod!"
I have to say this. We were in
Arizona, which was two hours ahead...
...it was like 3 a.m.,
or however it worked in L.A...
...Regina was asleep, you called
and got her on her phone...
...and after the first take--
She's just giving me everything.
And after the take
I asked her if she was asleep.
She said, "Yeah, but that's okay."
She was asleep and woke up for that.
- I love you.
-She's the best.
She was asleep
and she was bringing it.
-Thank you, Janusz Kaminski.
-Yeah, thank you, Janusz.
This is my mom, who is completely
unaware of the camera.
This is my mom.
She's a counsellor, still, and...
-Here's my line.
-She's a great lady.
This is great.
She's, like, bringing it on.
I gotta thank Bets
for that jacket, also.
My mom says,
"Put me more in your movies."
I say, "You have Tom outside,
staring at you through the window...
...and it's a love story with Renee.
What do you want?"
Maybe you're all correct.
Men are the enemy.
No, they're not the enemy.
But I still love the enemy.
This is classic.
Hello. Hello.
I'm looking for my wife.
Wait.
-I love that--
-"Who is this guy?"
Lorraina.
I'm not letting you get rid of me.
How about that?
Knight in shining arm our.
This used to be my speciality.
I was good in a living room.
I'd do it alone.
And now, I just...
I don't know.
But tonight...
...our little project, our company
had a very big night.
A very, very big night.
But it wasn't complete.
It wasn't nearly close to being
in the same vicinity as complete...
...because I couldn't
share it with you.
I couldn't hear your voice...
...or laugh about it with you.
I missed my-- I missed my wife.
We live in a cynical world.
A cynical world.
And we work in a business
of tough competitors.
I love you.
You...
...complete me.
-And I just--
-Shut up.
Just shut up.
You had me at "hello."
Thanks, you guys.
I was never sure about that speech.
I thought...
...you know, is it too much,
is it too...
...heart-in-hand, you know?
Tom was always "Let me do it."
-I remember him doing it.
-"Take it away, I'll kill you."
Immediately you felt that.
I remember doing it and looking
at people, and they were just...
-Destroyed.
There were three women
by the monitor.
I turned when you said,
"We live in a cynical world."
Which was an important thing
that we had talked about...
I said, "How's this working?"
They'd be, like--
And it was you
connecting to it personally.
It was more than just words.
It was a feeling, and then...
And then we get this gift from Cuba.
I always loved that speech.
On this one, you told me to hug him
and kiss him. Do you remember?
-Oh, yeah, that's right.
-"Just hug him and kiss him."
Isn't that Leigh Steinberg,
who always says he's Jerry Maguire?
There he is, in the maroon tie!
He took the picture of me
and Cuba on the set.
You remember Troy
from the Super Bowl?
We met in '93.
-That's right. I enjoyed your memo.
-Thank you.
-A little slow but you come around.
-We're out of time.
I'm forgetting somebody.
Look at this, I love this.
-Yeah, baby.
-That's Jerry Maguire.
-Look, there it is.
-Kisses.
-Awesome, dude. Awesome.
-Brother.
-Awesome!
-Remember shooting this?
I'll never forget it.
I was like,
"this can't be almost over."
-Famke came.
-Yeah, my friend. She did.
She did.
Good throw, man.
Did you see?
Oh, no. Let's go.
This is an alternate version
of Dylan's "Shelter from the Storm."
He dug into the vaults to give us.
Really?
And there's a funny thing here.
They're going off into the sunset.
But the beautiful layer
that you guys gave us was:
You don't know what'll happen.
Tidwell could be out with one injury.
He may still not be in love enough.
I love Dicky Fox here.
But Dicky gives it to you.
That's good.
You did that, that's good.
"My kind of success."
Cameron Crowe,
thank you for the experience.
-Thank you, dude!
-Thank you for the experience.
You guys, that was--
Love you, man.
I love you guys.
I've been asked to do this,
I've always said no.
I thought, I'll do it for you.
I'll sit down with Renee and Cuba.
But I really enjoyed doing it.
Also, I loved making this movie.
I loved working with you,
Renee and Cuba. It was fun.
-A beautiful experience.
-Even to the European tour.
You are a great filmmaker.
Cameron Crowe,
you are a great filmmaker.
Actors worship you.
I gotta say...
...we got to be in one
of the greatest movies ever.
Love this picture.
-And Billy Wilder saw it and dug it.
- I know.
-I remember.
-To Billy!
I remember that day. "He's on
his way." I was sweating.
"He's on his way.
He's gonna see the movie."
Then there was that gap:
"He's watching the movie."
I was saying, "Come on, I was down
by the phone, three hours later.”
It was the whole reason
for doing it, wasn't it?
The whole idea was
to just tell a story.
Tell a story the way Wilder
told a story...
...where you could turn the TV
on at night.
You meet these people that
take you on a ride for two hours.
-They leave your life, but never really.
-But it's Crowe.
It's Crowe.
Tip your hat to Wilder,
but it is Crowe.
He had his own signature.
If you look at this movie, it really
defies traditional structure.
You look at that and you go,
"That is a Crowe movie."
-That's Crowe.
-Is that too weird?
You know, James L. Brooks
is a huge...
...part of the DNA of this.
We spent years on this script.
Jim would always say:
"I want this to be something that
came from your deepest part.
And we can't stop until
it's exactly that."
And he was our greatest partner
on this...
...who's not here,
but we send our props to him.
-Props to Jim.
-Yes, props to Jim.
James L. Brooks.
I hear him, watching the movie,
I hear his voice so much, saying:
"Buddy, you're gonna get
these actors out there.
You'll have a great time. All I want
is to protect the experience.”
He did, he and Richard Sakai...
...were great producers that allowed
us the cocoon to work in.
So I just wanna say that.
But within the cocoon it was
quite an experience.
And I still...
I can feel it and smell it
every time I see the movie.
Thanks.
Cool.
And here's Nancy's theme song.
Yeah. Nice way to go out.
You know, she ain't bad, huh?
-She ain't bad.
-Thanks.
We love you, Nance!
Come over here!
-We love Nance.
-We love her.
Scott Martin, Lisa Steward.
Yeah, can't forget those guys.
Speaking of cocoons.
-Michael Doven.
-Doven!
The Dovenator.
-Shawn, Derrick.
-Shawn and Derrick.
The boys.
LeAnne.
Pushy John Caravino.
-Pat Kingsley.
-All over it.
-That's right.
And all of these musicians.
Look at this music.
You're good at that.
You kind of make me mad, in fact.
Come on, give us a little Bridget
on the credits.
It's not happening.
No, forget about it.
Come on, Renee.
Bust out something.
Just give us something.
You won't tell us what's going on.
I'm on vacation.
And we're not.
Break out just a sentence of Bridget.
Give us a sentence.
Look, it's going to Dolby.
-Another minute.
-One on Dolby.
Come on, you guys.
You ain't behind the camera.
Ain't acting. Sorry.
The Bridget Jones DVD
she'll do it for like two and a half hours.
Yeah, exactly.