Up! Up! Up! Room check!
[Lim clapping]
Convict, stand and face the wall!
Comb the area.
We'll be conducting
a mandatory sweep of the area.
You're to cooperate with all instructions.
You understand?
I understand.
[Lim] Check.
I am searching your person
to ensure you're not carrying anything
that might be harmful
to yourself or others.
Do you understand?
I understand. [Lim] Check.
Turn around.
Are we finished here?
All clear.
[exhales]
[whistles]
[driver] Oh, these mornings
are getting colder and colder.
Piece of crap can't keep up for nothing.
Where we off to, boss?
Matt shows up alive, then tells me
I'm never gonna see him again.
Only I, Foggy Nelson,
can be ghosted by a ghost.
[Marci] It's locked.
Like it was the last time you checked it.
We need to get
another dead bolt installed.
A single dead bolt and a measly chain?
Might as well be a beaded curtain.
Foggy, relax.
Relax? Are you even listening to me?
Wilson Fisk wants my scalp.
And for all we know, he wants yours, too.
It's not like you've done him any favors.
And of course Matt wants me to stick
to the sidelines while he deals with Fisk.
Only Matt Murdock is fit
for the real action.
-Just because I'm not--
-What?
Nothing. [sighs]
[exhales]
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
Foggy, breathe.
Matt was gone.
Now he's back.
Fisk is out, and I have no idea
where that leaves me.
Screw the sidelines. We go on the offense.
Offense? With Fisk?
He has the law and the FBI on his side.
And it's not like we've heard a statement
from the DA condemning his release.
No, no, nothing to jeopardize
Blake Tower's reelection.
God forbid he grow a pair.
Oh, that could work.
Blake Tower growing a pair?
Not gonna happen.
No, think about it.
The best way to protect yourself from Fisk
is to make noise,
is to be out in the open.
Oh, like a public execution.
Like a public call to action.
If Blake Tower won't
do anything to stop Fisk,
then run against him
for district attorney.
[chuckles] If you're already a target,
you might as well be
the first person to take a swing.
No, I'm serious.
The more public,
the more you're protected.
There's no way I can win.
-Well, of course not.
-Thank you for the confidence.
Anyways, we're light-years
past the deadline.
Then run as a write-in.
You base your candidacy on a single issue.
Putting Fisk back behind bars.
You'd bag a few votes.
I mean, not enough to win,
but you'd get the issue out there.
Plus, you'd make a few friends
in the NYPD, and...
that's not the worst thing
for a defense attorney.
Or you could keep checking the locks.
I won't let anything happen to you.
[sighs] Oh, baby.
[exhales] Then we better start working
on that swing.
After coffee.
-You're buying.
-[chuckles]
Have you seen my wallet?
[driver] This is good?
Yeah, here's fine.
Hey, you paying with card?
'Cause, you know, cash is better.
[Matt] Wait for me.
[chuckles] Oh, yeah. Yeah, I can do that.
[door buzzes]
Hi. Good morning.
-Purpose for your visit?
-I have an appointment with my client.
I called earlier.
I should be on the visitor list.
[guard] ID.
I can't find my wallet.
Did I leave it at home,
or drop it in the cab--
-Without picture ID, I can't--
-Just give me one second.
-Sir, please step aside while--
-This is my New York Bar number.
Now, it's not picture ID, I know,
but it did take seven years and cost me
$300,000 in student loans. [chuckles]
Does it, uh, buy me anything?
Name?
Nelson. Franklin Nelson.
[theme music playing]
[door closes]
[indistinct chatter]
-[man] How you doin'?
-Good.
-[man] You're holding up?
-Mm-hmm.
[door opens]
Matt!
I thought Foggy...
-[Matt] What's up, Michael?
-Oh, man.
-It's good to see you.
-It's good to see you, too.
-Even if it is in this shithole.
-I'm sure you're wondering--
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said shithole.
I'm trying not to curse.
What's the point of me getting out of here
in 18 months with a degree in psychology,
top of my class...
if I still swear like a goddamn sailor?
-Did it again.
-Well, sorry.
Saint Matthew.
No, come on, I'm no saint.
You and Foggy got 16 years
knocked off my sentence.
If that's not divine intervention, huh?
[chuckles]
Where is Foggy?
I've never seen you two apart.
We're not, uh...
We're not working together anymore.
-Aw, man, that sucks.
-Yeah.
Listen, I don't want anyone, even Foggy,
to know that I was here, so...
Yeah, I can do that.
-Appreciate it.
-So, what's the big mystery?
Yeah, so, look, you, um...
worked with the Albanians, right?
A long time ago.
-Low-level stuff. Mostly just running.
-Mm-hmm.
But they're offering you
protection in here?
[chuckles]
What do you want with the Albanians?
I want an introduction.
If somebody needs a defense lawyer,
I'll make sure to pass your name along.
Glowing review. But, you know,
folks in here, they're murdering bastards.
I want an introduction to Vic Jusufi.
Nobody gets in with Vic.
You can't make it happen?
[man] ...and the extra two years added?
What do you want with him, anyway?
[softly] Wilson Fisk could've turned
on any crime organization.
I want to know why the Albanians.
What did they have on Fisk?
-Just, uh... let this go.
-No, I can't do that.
-Fisk stays out, innocent people die.
-I don't know shit.
Michael, you can help me.
-[Michael] No.
-Come on.
You're gonna get me killed.
[grunts] Get this guy away from me!
I don't know him!
Get him away! Get him away!
-That's enough!
-Assault by an inmate...
I said nothing.
On my mother! My mother!
[guard 2] Sir?
It's all right.
It's just a misunderstanding.
Mr. Nelson, you need to get checked out
by the nurse.
It's fine. I'm fine.
Then you can say that
on an incident report.
Liability reasons.
Can't let you leave until you sign one.
Yeah, all right.
[guard 2] Follow me.
[door opens]
[indistinct chatter]
[man] He's right in there.
[Seema] Hi, boys.
-Hi.
-[Ray] Hey.
I brought clothes, mouthwash,
and some leftover chole.
[chuckles] Thanks.
Hey, I'm sorry.
It's gonna be like this all week.
You promise me you'll eat?
Your face looks thin.
[both chuckle]
Fine. Okay, I'll eat.
I love you.
We gotta go.
What "we"? Is Sami here?
He's in the car,
killing aliens on my phone.
I'd love to see him. Bring him up.
You're working,
and I don't want to be late.
Late? Late for what?
Late for my sister's.
Sami is gonna stay there
for a couple of days.
Sami has a bed.
One that he can't sleep in.
What do you mean? What's going on?
He stays up all night,
waiting for you to come home.
He's been watching the news.
He's... He's scared something
is going to happen to you.
Look at me. I'm fine.
Are you?
'Cause Sami isn't the only one
who's scared.
Let him stay with Nav and the kids.
Get his mind off all of this.
No.
I'll talk to him when I come home.
Look... nothing bad is gonna happen to me.
I was at the hospital.
I talked to the other spouses
waiting outside the ER.
None of those agents thought anything bad
was going to happen to them, either.
[in Hindi] I know how much
this promotion means,
-but nothing is worth--
-We can talk about this later.
[in English] Sami is going to my sister's.
Make sure you eat.
[kisses] [door opens]
[door closes]
[door buzzes]
[guard 1] Face the wall.
Let's go. Turn around.
Against the wall. Against the wall.
Now. Foreheads to the wall.
Let's go, gentlemen.
Spread your legs.
[door buzzes]
[man hisses]
[inmate whistles]
[door buzzes]
-Wait in here. Nurse should be by.
-Thanks.
[Karen] Gelsdorf...
[line ringing]
Hi. Yes.
I know you said you couldn't meet until
Friday morning, but I found something.
I don't think it can wait till then.
Yes, absolutely. Off the record.
[knock on door]
[Karen] No, only somebody who works
at the FDIC can help me.
You will?
Thank you so much. No...
Yeah, tomorrow is perfect.
Great.
I think I figured out how Fisk
has been skirting the FBI asset freeze.
When's the last time you slept?
He's been funneling his money
through Vancorp,
which is the shell corporation
that owns the hotel,
and he's keeping it in an offshore firm
named Red Lion National Bank.
-Karen--
-That's the smoking gun.
If it's not smoking,
it's at least kinda warmish.
I didn't come to talk about Fisk.
What?
It's Matt?
They found a body?
I promised I would never lie
for Matt again. Not to you.
No, you have to just...
[breathing deeply] You need
to just tell me.
Matt's alive.
Matt!
Matt, where the hell are you?
He's not here. I called.
Even asked Fran down the hall
if she saw anyone poking around.
She would know. She pokes.
Why? Why would he let us think
that he was dead?
It wasn't Matt that I saw, Karen.
I mean, not really.
It was Matt.
All five feet, ten inches of him, but...
the way that he spoke to me...
something was missing.
Well, that's nothing new.
There's always
something missing with Matt.
I used to think that it was...
it was busy lawyer, distracted Matt.
Then I thought it was weight-of-the-world-
on-his-shoulders Matt. But you know what?
It's just Matt.
[Karen sighs]
But it wasn't any of those.
I think a part of him
was buried under Midland Circle.
I don't know if he's coming back.
So much for him promising
he'd stop lying to us.
Letting us think he was dead.
A whopper.
I think Matt's made his choice.
It doesn't really leave any room
for either of us.
[Foggy] No.
I guess it doesn't.
Well, I am not going to sit here
and wait for Matt to come to his senses.
Fisk is out, and he has to be stopped.
[Foggy] Fran was wrong.
I guess she didn't poke hard enough.
[door buzzes]
Sorry again for the wait.
[sighs]
But, good news, it's not dislocated.
Great. So I can go?
[man] Almost done.
Honestly, this paper work
is a waste of time.
It just ends up in a file somewhere.
[chuckles]
I am now going to check your pupils
to make sure you're not concussed.
-Just look up for a minute.
-No, just...
Give me the paper work, please.
Okay. Let's get you out of here.
I forgot to mention...
if you come down with any headaches
the next couple of days,
make sure that you...
[both grunt]
[exclaims]
[grunts and pants]
[groans] Come on.
God damn it.
[phone ringing]
[Fisk over phone] You're not
Franklin Nelson.
[exhales] Fisk.
It's quite something to see.
For a blind man, you have
very impressive reflexes, Mr. Murdock.
What was I injected with?
[Fisk] Do you remember
the last time that we spoke?
You said that, for the cost of postage,
you could prevent my reunion
with the only person
who gives my life meaning.
The only person that I love.
And I would've let bygones be bygones.
But you didn't just threaten me...
you threatened Vanessa.
And that is something
that I cannot forgive.
Listen to me very carefully.
[dial tone]
[door buzzes]
[man] Is that him?
[man] Where'd he go?
[both grunt]
[Matt exclaims]
[all groaning and grunting]
[man yells]
[grunts]
[shouting]
[man yelling]
-[bones crack]
-[man yells]
[panting]
[inmate 1] Hey. Come here.
Come on. Let me outta here.
Where you going? Hey, come back.
Hey, come back, man.
[guard 1] On the ground!
[Matt] Hold on. I was attacked.
-Get on the ground now!
-[Matt] I was attacked. I need help. -Put your hands behind your head.
-[Matt] Okay.
[guard 2] All right, we got him.
We'll take care of him.
[grunting]
[inmates cheering]
[inmate 2] Hey, nice job, homes.
Grab his keys, quick.
[alarm blaring repeatedly]
-[over PA] Code 33, code 33...
-[inmates shouting indistinctly]
[over PA] Lockdown is now in effect.
-[over PA] Code 33, code 33...
-[panting]
Lockdown is now in effect.
[inmate 3] Light it up, Vic!
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
Lockdown is now in effect.
[grunting]
[groans]
Fisk betrays everyone!
He will turn on you.
Fisk will turn on you, too. [exclaims]
[Vic] Who are you?
And why does Fisk want you dead?
[speaking Albanian]
[Matt] Hey, wait...
What is that? Albanian?
-Are you Vic?
-[Vic] You're an idiot coming here.
Fisk still controls
half the guards and prisoners.
Yeah, but not... not the Albanians.
Not since Fisk
ratted your people out to the FBI.
[panting]
[Vic] What's it to you?
Fisk hates me
as much as he hates you people.
I helped get him locked up.
And I'm gonna do it again. [groans]
Nah, I think you're gonna die in here.
Why did Fisk flip on your people?
[Vic] It doesn't matter.
It matters enough
that you're desperate to kill him.
You missed him in here,
and then you tried again on the outside.
That is a very serious allegation.
And wrong.
We never tried to hit him... in here.
Fisk was shanked in the weight room.
-[Vic] Not by us.
-Oh, yeah? If not you, then who?
Listen, if I succeed,
Fisk ends up right back here
with you and your men.
And after that, you can do with him
whatever you please.
Fisk shanked Fisk.
He bribed some lifer to stab him.
He set the whole thing up?
The guy sliced him up
just good enough to convince the feds.
[Matt] Of course.
This guy, he's a lifer?
If he was bribed,
does that mean he's still alive?
Better than alive. Free.
Free? [chuckles]
How is he not in solitary?
Fisk got someone to cook the books
and let him out.
Okay, there are guards coming.
Give me the lifer's name.
He's the only proof we have
that Fisk set this whole thing up.
-So what?
-So if I can get to him, I can--
-You can barely get to your feet.
-Vic, please.
You took a shot at Fisk, and you missed.
I won't.
Not if you can get me out of here.
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
Lockdown is now in effect.
Drag that guard in here.
[speaking Albanian]
[panting]
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
Blood was lost
during the motorcade attack.
My baby cousin's blood.
Find the inmate who shanked Fisk.
Make good on your word.
Or we'll come find ya.
His name?
Jasper Evans.
Get him outta here.
Wait, hold on a second.
There's two guards.
Okay, now.
-This way.
-[inmate] There's an exit this way.
[Matt] There are two guards.
Trust me, please.
Lockdown is now in effect.
We need to go through
this door on the left. Here.
[inmate] It's locked.
There's a key in your top left pocket.
[guard 1] Toward the exit! The other way!
Hurry.
[guard 1] There he is!
Move! Now!
Get him! Go!
-[door buzzes]
-[guard 2 grunts]
Code 33, code 33, code 33.
[Matt] The other way. The other way.
Slow down. Thank you. Thank you.
[guard 3] Inmate! On your knees!
[clamoring]
[explosion]
[inmates shouting]
Lockdown is now in effect.
-[inmate] I can't see.
-[Matt] Left. Left.
Now take a right. Sharp right.
[inmate] I got a civilian here!
Get him out. Go.
[guard 4] Go! Go!
[indistinct shouting]
[alarm whooping]
[indistinct shouts]
[guard 5] Open the gate! Open the gate!
Open the gate!
[door buzzes]
[Matt] Drive. Drive.
Drive.
[panting]
[metal detector beeps]
[sighs] If I'm being honest, that's not
the way I thought this was gonna go.
Who eats a burger with a spork?
[door opens]
-Special Agent Poindexter.
-[Dex] Ma'am.
This is Supervisory Special Agent Winn
with OPR.
[Winn] Poindexter.
Why don't you go grab a cup of coffee?
Yes, sir. Dex.
-Don't sweat this.
-[Dex] Sweat what, exactly?
OPR wants a private interview with Fisk.
And I'm the only one
asked to leave the room.
It would be inappropriate of me
to tell you that
the Office of Professional Responsibility
has launched an internal investigation
into the motorcade attack.
It would also be inappropriate of me
to tell you that there was
a slight discrepancy
between your official report
and the forensic analysis of the shooting.
Yeah, it would be inappropriate
for you to tell me all this.
Because of you,
my wife still has her husband...
and my son still has his father.
[door opens]
-[sighs]
-[door closes] [indistinct overlapping chatter]
[exhales]
[Foggy] Detective!
The hell are you doing here?
This is a union-only function.
You know what I love about our dynamic?
We skip the pleasantries.
No hellos. No how-you-beens.
Straight to business.
I'm about to get to the business
of dragging your ass up outta here.
I wouldn't have intruded
if it wasn't important.
Let me guess. You need a favor.
See?
Do you have this kind of shorthand
with anyone else?
Wilson Fisk.
His cushy new situation
is a federally-funded slap in the face
to every officer in this room.
No shit.
Not sure what that has to do with you
crashing this party, though.
I want to say a few words,
express my solidarity.
And it would play better
if you gave me the floor.
-Just to say a few things.
-It's been a long week, Foggy, okay?
And you talking is only gonna drag it out.
Now, it's time to go.
In handcuffs or on your own.
Say no more.
Hey, Brett, how's it going?
Excuse me, esteemed constables.
Guys, could I have--
Hey, Counselor,
I personally wanna thank you
for springing my arson perp out of jail
on a technicality.
Come on. There were mitigating
circumstances, and you know it, Officer.
His building was not up to code.
Let me show you where to stick
your mitigating circumstances.
-[officers laughing]
-Hey, hey, hey, people, look, um...
Nelson's all right.
He helped the city put Fisk behind bars.
Give him a minute.
One minute.
Officers, I don't mean to disappoint.
But I'm not here to talk
only about Wilson Fisk.
With his name on everyone's lips,
he's getting far more publicity
than any cop killer deserves.
His name deserves to be buried...
buried in the same hard earth
where he put your fallen brothers.
I'm here to talk about Blake Tower...
our honorable district attorney.
Here's a man charged with ensuring
the safety of this city, just as you are.
And yet, he stands idly by
while the feds whisk that monster
out of prison
and into the warm lap of luxury.
Someone smarter than me--
[officer] That's a pretty freakin'
low bar, isn't it?
That man said, "The only thing
necessary for the triumph of evil
is for good men to do nothing."
Blake Tower is a good man doing nothing.
Which is why I'm running my own
write-in campaign for district attorney,
to oust Blake Tower and to put Wilson Fisk
into the deepest prison hole allowable
under the Eighth Amendment.
And I would love nothing more
than to do that
with the endorsement of each of you
and your illustrious union.
All right, where do I sign up?
[man 1] Hey, baby. Hey, baby.
Hey, what's up, yo?
[kissing]
Look at shorty comin'.
Hey, hey, let me get your name.
-[woman] Let's go around.
-[man 2] What we getting into?
[man 1] What's up, y'all?
Let me get your names.
[man 2] Come on!
What we getting into tonight?
[man 1] Where you going, Ma?
We got all night!
See, that ass is walking away, bro.
Yo, that's all you, bro.
That's all you, bro.
[man 2] Now, this is a real lady.
[whistles and kisses]
[man 1] Come here. You coming to say hi?
We could have some fun tonight.
Yeah, you like fun?
Get out of my way.
[man 1] You got bite.
Come on, play with us.
[Karen] Let's play a game.
What do you wanna play?
The one where I play scared little girl?
'Cause it seems you like scaring girls.
[man 1] It's all good.
We was just having fun.
Let's have fun. Huh?
Who goes first? You? Me?
Lady, we were just being friendly.
Then this is just a friendly reminder
that games like that
can get your head blown off.
Why are you still here?
[breathes deeply]
[metal detector beeps]
Trouble at home?
Um, no, I...
Actually, that's none of my business.
No, no. Um...
I could use some help, advice.
I don't know.
You've taken fire before, right?
Enough.
You have kids at the time?
Your boy having trouble with the shooting?
Yeah.
Yeah, he's, uh, not sleeping, you know...
watching the news.
Stuff like that.
I mean, I think the best thing to do
is talk to him like a man.
Tell him that the job I do
is dangerous, but I--
My advice... don't.
I tried that with my daughter.
It freaked her out so bad,
she wouldn't let me
leave the house in the morning.
She lay across the door and cried
until I called in and took the day.
Treat your son like a CI.
Make my kid my snitch?
Snitch lives in a scary world
they don't control,
and they depend on you to keep 'em safe.
Sound familiar?
Yeah, but lying to my son...
My dad was a trucker.
He mostly hauled chemical tankers.
He'd bring 'em to the house overnight
before heading out sometimes.
And I'd have nightmares,
thinking about what could happen.
But when my dad found out,
he showed me a diamond-shaped decal
on the back with the colors and numbers.
He told me the numbers tell you
how high the level of danger is.
He only hauled level four, safest stuff.
Once I knew that,
it didn't seem so scary anymore.
-Level four is the most lethal code.
-But I didn't know that.
And I didn't worry when he drove off
every morning in a rolling fire bomb.
The lies that keep us safe
are the ones worth telling.
[elevator dings]
Coming?
Ms. Page? What are you doing here?
I know we had an appointment for tomorrow,
but what we have to talk about
can't wait till then.
This is my home.
-My family is upstairs.
-I know. I'm sorry.
You're lucky I'm willing to talk to you,
period.
If my bosses at the FDIC
found out I was talking--
Red Lion National Bank.
And how the hell did you get my address?
-Did Ellison put you up--
-No. Ellison doesn't know that I'm here.
He doesn't know that I reached out to you.
I know that looks bad--
And if you did,
you wouldn't be standing here.
The sooner you tell me about Red Lion,
the sooner I go.
Wilson Fisk is laundering his money
through that bank.
We're talking millions of dollars.
-[woman] Honey, who's at the door?
-Someone from work.
The FDIC has to be monitoring
a bank involved--
We're done here.
Hey! No, I just...
I need proof.
Give me a contact at the bank.
I'll be having words
with Ellison in the morning.
Give me a name,
you will never see me again.
[woman] Honey, what's going on?
There's only one name
worth checking into, and...
good luck squeezing anything out of him.
Who?
Felix Manning.
Thank you.
Thank me by getting
the hell off my property.
Sorry.
[door opens]
I thought you were relieved for the day.
-Is everyone gone?
-Yeah.
Good. Yeah, that's good.
Why don't you go downstairs,
grab a cup of coffee?
My treat. Yeah.
That's a good idea.
I'll just...
Yeah.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Do you remember these men?
[Fisk] They were among the Albanians
who attacked the motorcade.
-[Winn] Did you see these men die?
-[Fisk] Yes, I did.
[Winn] And did you see who shot them?
There was only one FBI agent
left standing.
Special Agent Poindexter.
The moment he shot them,
can you describe, for the record,
what you saw?
They were armed.
Special Agent Poindexter
gave them a chance to surrender,
but then their weapons
came up to shoot him.
He killed them both in self-defense.
[Winn] Thank you for your time, Mr. Fisk.
[sighs]
-What's your game?
-[Fisk] Game?
I don't need any favors from you, convict.
Favors, no.
But sympathy...
Papers, protests...
the mockery.
I can carry this burden of humiliation,
but you?
You're a dedicated federal agent.
You don't know anything about me.
Neither does the Bulletin.
The press is labeling the attack
on my life as an FBI disaster.
And now they're investigating you
for doing your job.
They're questioning you
for your exceptionalism.
You saved my life!
And the lives of honorable federal agents.
Did they report that?
No.
Instead, they vilify...
and demean your act of courage.
The world is changing.
The real heroes are ridiculed
and dismissed.
And for that, I offer my sympathy.
Where are we?
Where...
Wait... Hey, hold up. Stop the car.
[man] No problem. We'll get you home.
Who are you?
Hey! Hey!
No, no, no. No.