[opening theme music playing]
[electronic chirp]
[electronic warbling]
[emcee] Lords and Ladies of the Empire,
welcome!
[dramatically] Space,
once an unreachable frontier,
is now a dazzling playground
for Earth's children.
And so, we gather here,
above the frozen skies of Jupiter...
[crowd cheering]
...to witness the sacred union
of our glorious regent,
Lord Chalon of Europa,
and the Duchess Saraka of Callisto.
[all chuckling]
Their love must be tempered
with ritual and ceremony,
shaped in the crucible of chaos...
- [woman chuckles]
- [glasses clink]
...and sanctified with blood,
blood spilled in tribute
on these sands below.
[dramatic music playing]
Tonight, you will witness
a spectacle like no other.
Behold the riders.
[crowd cheering]
[emcee] Are they not
absolutely magnificent?
[indistinct chatter]
[emcee] Years of discipline and training
have forged them into the perfect warriors
you see before you.
[grunting]
[emcee] Champions honed to a razor's edge,
each blessed with the strength
and ferocity of their totem spirit.
[woman 1 in Mandarin] My sigil
marks me as wild and untamed.
It is a secret prayer,
my longing to be free.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] To those
who are about to die,
we salute you.
[horn blares]
[woman 2 growls]
- [drums beating]
- [breathes steadily]
Now let the race begin!
- [growling]
- [action music playing]
[all grunt]
[panting]
[triceratops bellowing]
[grunts]
- [grunts]
- [clinks]
[straining]
[shouts, grunts]
[grunts]
[whirring]
- [crowd cheering]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[spacecraft whirs]
[grunts]
- [screams]
- [grunts]
[woman chuckles]
[cheering]
[dramatic music playing]
[triceratops bellows]
[panting]
[grunts]
[triceratops growling]
[energy pulses]
[in Mandarin] Everything
that does not please our overlords
has been stripped away.
In the darkness above Europa,
they take everything from us.
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[gasps, grunts]
[both grunting]
[yelps, screams]
[grunting]
[dramatic music continues]
[growling]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[groans, grunts]
[screams]
[triceratops bellows]
[dramatic music continues]
[woman] A wolf alone can be outrun,
out-fought, out-maneuvered.
[howling]
[woman] But the wolf pack
is an apex predator.
[dramatic music crescendos]
[grunting]
[grunts]
- [grapple whistles]
- [grunts]
[bellows]
[grunts]
[shouting]
[grunting]
[man groans]
[both grunt]
[spacecraft whirs]
[grunts, strains]
[triceratops growls]
[grapple whistling]
[grunts]
- [shouts]
- [bellows]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[screaming]
[triceratops groans]
- [ground rumbles]
- [crowd cheering]
[breathing heavily]
[spacecraft whirs]
[cheering continues]
[in English] Yeah!
[suspenseful music playing]
[woman in Mandarin] The aristocracy
mate for money and power.
But we who can own nothing...
[energy pulses]
...have something real,
something primal, something true.
[dramatic music builds]
[shouts]
[both grunting]
[triceratops growls]
- [grunts]
- [blade rings]
[dramatic music continues]
[grunts]
[grunt echoes]
[woman] She is magnificent.
[energy pulses]
- [grunts]
- [triceratops groans]
[woman strains]
- [music fades]
- [crowd cheering]
[in English] Whoo! Yeah.
[glasses clink]
[cheering continues]
[dramatic music playing]
Was that not glorious?
A contest of heroes
worthy of this celestial union.
But for this most special occasion,
we have something more,
a final challenge to test our champion
against nature's most
savagely primal creation.
[eerie music playing]
[metal creaks]
[breath wavering]
[roars]
[in Mandarin] Fuck!
[roaring]
- [grunts]
- [roars]
[roaring]
[shouts]
[strains]
[grunting]
[roaring]
[bellows]
- [air whooshes]
- [triceratops grumbles]
- [woman shouts]
- [roars]
[growls]
[strains]
[dinosaurs roar]
[woman grunts]
[flesh tearing]
Turn! You big bastard!
[dramatic music playing]
[roars]
- [shouts]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
[shrieks]
[strains]
[roaring]
[woman shouts]
[grunting]
[music fades]
[groans weakly]
[wailing]
[crowd cheering]
[cheering emphatically]
[ominous music playing]
[breathing weakly]
[whirring]
[emcee in English] My lords,
this carnage is no end...
- [grunts]
- [emcee] It is a beginning.
This King of the ancient world
gives us the gift
of his matchless vitality.
In his veins flows the power primordial...
as it will now flow
into those of our sovereigns,
so that they may write
our future in blood.
[in Mandarin] The Tyrannosaur
no longer screams.
He has had his fill of blood.
But you up there...
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] ...you will never have enough.
Come... let us end this our way.
[roars]
[dramatic music rises]
[crowd screams]
[Saraka shrieks]
[tyrannosaur growls]
[Saraka screams]
[screaming]
[Chalon yelps]
[music fades]
[dramatic sting]
- [grunts]
- [screams, grunts]
[woman] In the darkness above Europa...
[grunting weakly]
...they take everything from us,
even our memories.
Yet some fragments linger...
[tyrannosaur moans]
[woman] ...like the last leaves of autumn.
Among the blossoms,
I am alone with my wine.
Lifting my cup,
I ask the moon to drink with me.
Its reflection in the wine,
with mine, just we three.
[poignant music playing]
[wolves barking]
[wolf howling]
[music fades]
[electronic warbling]
[somber music playing]
[music fades]