Master Han! Master Han!
The Doctor is coming.
Stall her. Go.
Get Li!
The Doctor! Li, the Doctor!
The Doctor!
Welcome to Han Academy.
Are you looking to learn Kung Fu?
Never too late to start
even for an old woman.
We start with jacket on - jacket off.
Take off jacket, put on jacket.
I know he told you to stall me.
I did nothing of the sort.
He did ask. Sorry.
Go!
Where is my son?
Tea?
I'm not here for tea.
Where is Li?
Kung Fu is very empowering...
Uncle,
with all due respect.
I already lost one son to your "path."
I will not lose another.
I understand.
I know what Li means to you...
but I will not have him put in harm's way.
We both agree.
If you could only see
how Kung Fu helps him -
Each time life knocked me down,
Kung Fu helped me find my way back
to the proper path.
This is for you.
What's this?
I got a new position -
- at a hospital in New York.
New York?
It's a chance to restart for both of us.
Why two hats?
So you can give one to Li...
...when he finds the courage
to come out from behind your screen.
Very smart.
Your mother.
Were you even going to ask me?
I was training. Not fighting.
Hey! Can I have your gloves?
Whatever.
Oh my god!
See the run up is key.
But the balance and the jump
that's what sells it.
Now you try.
I don't think I'm going to master
this one.
You will. One day, when you need it.
See the run up is key.
How are you, Li?
Are we loving New York yet?
More missing Beijing.
The school misses you too.
Wait a minute...
Say hi!
Shifu...
I've made a new friend here,
who asked me to teach him Kung Fu.
I see.
Do you think Kung Fu can help your friend?
I think so.
Anything that helps others
and benefits yourself is a good thing.
...but downtown price is lower.
Please?
Okay okay, take it.
Thank you.
Free pizza, freshly made.