How are the pressures and saturation?
Pressures are good.
Oxygen saturation is 100%.
Feel anything?
No.
How about now?
Mm-mm.
And when he does that?
Nothing.
OK. All set, then.
Making initial incision. Hand me the Bovie.
We've entered the peritoneum.
I can't believe I couldn't do it.
I couldn't push anymore.
Don't be ridiculous. Don't apologise.
We've moved the bladder.
Here's the uterine incision.
- Oh, God...
- Hey, it's gonna be fine.
I won't tell anybody if
you want to hold my hand.
OK, we're ready now.
How are the vitals?
Still good.
You're gonna feel a little pressure now.
Uh-huh.
- Occiput is visible and...
baby is out.
Cutting the umbilical cord.
Is she OK?
What is it?
What's...?
- Say she's OK!
- Hey, hey, hey. It's OK.
Oh, God! Oh, God...
- Is she OK?
- Just relax. Hold on. OK?
Good job.
She's great.
Oh, she's beautiful.
One, two, three and open your mouth
and eat this down, OK?
One, two, three, boo.
No, no. Big "ah" and in it goes.
So, that's how it's
gonna be, huh, soldier?
I'm not a soldier.
You want me to take over?
I think your mother should know by now
that your grandfather's not a quitter.
One, two, three, and...
I want to take Sara to the park.
You want to come?
No, I'm gonna pass if you don't mind.
I'd like to get at that
painting, get it finished.
Mm, the horse?
- Yeah.
Yep. Have a good time.
Oh! No, no.
Mummy!
Here we are!
Marie?
- Hi!
- I thought it was you.
This is Mikey.
- Hello, little guy.
- Yeah.
Hey, there.
- How old is he?
- He's seven months.
- Wow. Congratulations.
- Yeah. Thank you.
Kitty!
- I'm so tired.
- Yeah.
Hopefully he'll sleep through the night
one of these days.
Yeah, well, you're past that.
How old's Sara now?
Sara is three and she's...
Sara!
Come say hi to this little boy.
Sara?
- Sara!
Sara!
Hey, it's OK. We're gonna find her.
- Stop!
- Hey, hey, lady!
- Sara!
I found her!
She was down by the track.
Fallen down the slope.
Said she... She followed a cat?
- She followed a cat.
- I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm right here.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Miss Sambrell?
- Yes.
And Sara, right? Follow me.
You have a recommendation, so Sara
will be part of our trial period.
Well, it's been tested though, right?
- Of course.
I mean, she's not, like, a guinea pig.
- It's all fully tested, perfectly safe.
This is just us fine-tuning our subscription
model before the full launch.
Look at the kids...
We're getting feedback on which features
our customers use most in the real world.
Uh-huh.
- Do you wanna go up? Yeah!
Response so far is just incredible.
The sense of security, peace of mind.
I mean, the stories we've been hearing,
they're truly inspirational.
See the screen?
- OK, then.
- There you go.
You like cartoons?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Shimmer And Shine?
Uh-huh.
- Mm-hmm. OK.
Then you watch that
and I won't be a moment. OK?
- That's it?
- Mm-hmm. That's it.
So...
Let's get you all set up.
- I'll run you through everything, OK?
- OK.
Feel free to ask any questions.
- Mm-hmm.
This is your parental hub.
I'm just pairing it with Sara's implant.
OK. We're all set.
So, this is Sara's current location,
which is here, of course.
Oh, look at that.
Now, if she ever goes missing,
all you have to do is tap here...
enter your PIN, and law enforcement
is automatically notified.
Wow, OK.
These are her vitals.
Healthy heartbeat.
Oh, I see her iron levels are a little low.
How is she eating?
Man, she's picky.
Um, she hates greens, so...
You might want to think
about nutritional supplements.
OK.
Now, tap this icon here...
to relay her optic feed.
This is what she's seeing now?
That's right.
Whoa.
That's amazing.
Mummy! It's funny.
And there are parental
controls you can apply to that.
Uh, controls?
- Content limitations.
If she witnesses something that causes
her cortisol levels to rise - like stress -
it can kind of paint out
whatever's triggering it.
Let me show you.
- OK.
Ooh...
- It's OK. Look.
See, the imagery causes a
cortisol spike, and this...
Filter on.
...is what she sees and hears.
Whoa. OK.
Yeah, I'm not sure that we'll...
It's all optional.
OK.
How much?
Nothing. It's a free trial.
Oh, free.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
And it's completely safe.
I'm sure it is, honey.
I am 2,000 years old and I remember
when we used to open up the door
and just let the kids be.
Mm. And I remember breaking my arm
because you wouldn't get a baby gate.
And how is the arm now?
Mm. Feels OK.
Are you there? Mummy!
Where are you?
Mummy?
Are you here?
Oh, what's up, sweetheart?
- I'm looking for Mummy.
You're looking for Mummy?
I got no idea where she's at.
Upstairs. Go on. Go look upstairs.
- Mummy, where are you?
- Yoo-hoo!
Mommy, I hear you!
I'm gonna find you.
I hear you, Mommy.
Ah!
Filter on.
You guys gonna be alright?
I raised you alright.
You turned out OK.
Took you a while, but you did.
Alright, sweetheart.
I'll see you later.
Terrorise your grandpa.
He can handle it.
Bye.
Orange straw.
OK, just push on my hand. OK.
- Yeah.
Relax.
Again. Is that all you got?
I think the range is getting better.
So how long till I can get back
on the bike again, you think?
I'd say two weeks
and maybe don't drive so fast.
Yeah, right.
OK. So, same time next week?
Uh, no, actually it's got to be Thursday.
I got plans Monday.
Something exciting?
Girlfriend's folks are in town, so, nope.
Oh, well, uh, Thursday it is.
Oh, I'm liking yours. That's the way.
You're not shy about using colour, are you?
That's the way a real artist...
I'm gonna try this...
Sorry, honey. Just, uh...
Grandpa's gotta sit...
Grandpa?
- Sara, bring me the phone...
Huh? Sara...
Sara...
Oh, my God!
OK, very good.
The nurse left your thing on.
Yeah, she probably forgot to take it off.
I'll get it.
- I can get it.
You good?
- Quit bugging me. Jeez.
There you go.
It's warm in here.
I don't need that.
Give me that.
Hey, Sara! One cookie!
Bad for your teeth.
Thanks.
What colour for the hair?
Mum?
Uh, whatever you want.
But I'd say brunette.
He's got his arms in the air.
He's given up.
He's got a stick out and...
He just, like, pounds on him!
Turn it off, Trick. It's gross.
What is it?
Great. The walking snitch.
- She never snitches.
- She's just weird.
I want to know what you're watching.
- What do you care, chip-head?
It's parental advisory.
You're locked out.
I want to know.
You're better off not seeing it.
Wish I never did.
What if I tell you what's in it? That work?
So, he brings it down, like, wham!
There's all this blood.
You seen much blood?
It's like juice. Thick, red juice.
And then the guy on the ground
is all, like, "Hell, no!"
And he keeps...
Oh, it's too much. I'm
fine to have my face on the flier
but on the poster, it's like, "Look at me."
Sara, what are you doing?
Sara!
What's happening in this picture?
- Are they happy or...?
- They're talking.
Just talking?
I don't know what about.
OK. Next one.
- How about that one?
- I don't know.
Is she happy?
So is this, like, an autism thing?
The spectrum is wide, but in my opinion,
she's not on it.
But what about the pencils, like, self-harm?
And these pictures are...
Has Sara ever shown
any undue anger before now?
No.
Well, then consider this part experiment,
part acting out, for your benefit.
The Arkangel never launched nationwide.
It was banned in Europe.
It'll be pulled here, too, by the fall.
I did this to her.
You can't remove the implant,
but you can get rid of the parental unit.
The screen.
Just throw it away. Problem solved.
Filter off.
Goodbye.
You're gonna be on your own today. OK?
No Arkangel.
The system isn't gonna be on.
OK? So, no fuzzy pictures.
And you won't see me?
I won't see you.
But, you do not have to be afraid.
I'm right down the street.
You won't know if something happens?
- Nothing is gonna happen.
It's important that we do this.
You're gonna be fine.
Be good, sweetie.
Watch out!
Watch it, kid.
Come on, come on, come on.
OK! OK, this is enough!
Don't touch my stuff again, Trick.
Yeah? I'll do what I want.
What do you want?
Are you OK?
Yeah, sure.
My dad's gonna see this and then bust it
all over again, cos I got in trouble.
Ever seen a bust lip before?
Mm... Not till now.
She turned the system off.
OK, this is porn. Like, people doing it.
They can't make babies that way.
They have to do it different for that.
So this one's got a hacksaw
and he's gotta cut his own foot off.
So, the terrorist guy...
OK, OK, keep an eye on the knife.
See? He's gonna take his whole head off!
Be good, sweetie.
Hey. Good boy, Petey.
You hang on in there.
You added something.
- Oh, it's like a new kind of probiotic.
It keeps your stools firm.
- Oh, Jesus, Mom.
Oh, you've got to be kidding! When
was the last time you went anywhere?
That's not dancing.
She said he was English.
- He's not English.
- He said "cup of tea" or something.
Doesn't mean anything. Susan's an idiot.
Hey, it's Trick.
Holy fuck, he's got wheels!
Yo, Trick!
Hey, guys. What's up?
Interesting hair.
- Shut up.
I'm fucking with you. It's cool.
How are you doing?
- Didn't know you cared.
Maybe I don't.
You a delivery guy now?
- Kinda, of sorts.
Shut up.
Hmm... So intriguing. I gotta go.
Hey, uh, we're headed to Lake Dalston later
if you girls want to hang.
We'll think about it.
- It'll be fun.
- Why don't you just come?
Come on!
Like my dad's gonna let me set foot
in Trick's van!
Look, we tell our folks
we're at Reilly's for movie night.
Oh, come on, it'll work!
It's worth a shot, I guess.
So, anyhow...
You and, uh, Trick, huh?
- What?
I'm not gonna do anything.
Yeah, OK. Sure.
- Oh, fuck you!
Hey! Ew!
Yay! You're home.
Not for long. I was gonna go
to Reilly's with Meryl. Movie night.
Oh, I thought movie night was on Wednesday.
Her mum's got guests over then,
so we're doing tonight.
Gonna watch some vintage thing.
The Breakfast Gang.
The Breakfast Club.
That's it.
Um, be home, like, 11:30.
Her mom will drop me back.
Well, I might be heading out, too. So...
Really?
- Yeah, really.
OK. Last one home's a rotten egg.
OK!
Hey, there. How you doing?
You look hot. Later.
I don't know...
She called me fat.
I got over it. I still remember it...
Would you like some?
- Yeah, sure.
Cold?
- Only a bit.
Come here.
Oh... It's late.
I should go.
Same time next week?
Hi, it's Sara.
Leave a message. Make it good.
Hey, it's Mum. Alright, call me.
OK? Alright, bye.
- Hey.
- Hi, Ava. I was just wondering
if the girls were done with the movie yet.
- What movie?
Breakfast Club?
- They never ended up here.
They didn't?
- No. Do you want to speak to Reilly?
I don't know.
I must have got my wires crossed.
OK, thanks.
- Alright.
- Hello?
- Hi, it's Marie.
I was wondering
if Sara and Meryl were together.
They said they were
headed down to Reilly's.
No, I haven't seen them.
- Hi, it's Marie, Sara's mom.
- Oh, hi.
Yeah, I was just...
- What's up?
Have you heard from her?
- Uh... No.
I'm sorry, I know it's late.
I was wondering, have you seen her?
- No. Everything OK?
- No, everything's fine.
Hi, it's Sara.
Leave a message. Make it good.
Um, hey, it's Mum.
Where are you? Call me.
Hi, it's Sara.
Leave a message. Make it good.
Sara?
Come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
What is that?
Fuck me harder.
Fuck me.
Oh, God, oh...
- Please.
Oh...
Here. Let me do it.
My hands are warm.
You gotta be a liar.
- What?
You said you'd never done that before.
No way you never done that before.
Swear to God.
You know, you didn't have to talk like that.
Like what?
Like the porn stuff.
I mean, like, you don't have
to talk like that... For me.
OK.
What?
Just... Just you.
What about me?
You know...
You've got muscles, but...
You're a pussy.
Yeah.
I'm busted. My mom knows I'm not at Reilly's.
Huh?
- Yeah!
We gotta go, OK?
Come on.
- Fuck.
No lights. Maybe she's still out.
Pretty sure she had a date.
Maybe she got laid.
Oh, please, that's gross!
Check out that laugh!
Yeah?
- Yeah.
Later.
Sara?
Sorry, Mum. I am a little late.
- It's OK.
How was Reilly?
She's great. I gotta go to bed.
OK.
- Night, Mum. I love you.
Mm, probiotics.
I gotta go.
I'm gonna be
a little late back from school.
Oh, yeah?
Said I'd help Meryl with a project.
She's being a dork about it, so...
OK.
- See ya!
Bye!
- Have a good afternoon.
- Thank you, dear.
Alright. What do you think?
OK, that's awesome,
but I can't put that on the van.
Why not?
- Well, A, it's not my van
and B, it's better if I'm anonymous.
For your special delivery?
Maybe, yeah.
You got any on you?
Any what?
Oh, come on, Trick. I'm not dumb.
I know what you sell.
You got any?
It's not for you.
Bet it's in your backpack.
Under the seat... With tape!
- Sara, come here.
Hey, Sara, give me that.
- Duct tape.
Give me that. No, no, no.
I bet it's in the pocket.
- Come on, give me that. No!
I'm making a little money
on the side so I can move out, OK?
It's not like I use that shit.
- Have you tried it?
Of course I've tried it but, I mean,
it's not even good coke, it's, like, average.
It's for people who like to talk about
themselves all the time. Yada yada yada.
Show me what it looks like.
- Mm-mm.
Come on. I just want to see.
Please.
Are you sure it's not sugar?
Go away.
So, one of the things people do
is they put it, like...
under their gum, bottom gum.
- OK.
So...
Oh, ew...
Gross.
Alright, let's, uh, let's put it back.
I don't think you should...
- I want to try some.
Just a little, just once.
Just once.
Whoa!
- Hi, can I help?
- I'm just looking.
Ma'am?
Excuse me? Are you Ryan Tribecky?
You stay away from my daughter.
- Uh... I don't know what...
Sara. You know exactly
what I'm talking about. You stay away.
OK, she's...
- She is 15, you junkie piece of shit.
You want the cops in on this?
I didn't do anything.
- I will show them what you did.
OK, you stay away from her,
or I will show them this. OK?
You still got that system?
Yes, I have it. So whatever she sees,
I see, and I am watching you.
OK.
- So you stay away.
OK, if she calls you, you hang up.
If she comes to see you,
you tell her to get away.
You just stay away from her.
- I'll stay away.
You stay the fuck away.
Hey, Mum.
- Hey.
The mailbox
you're attempting to reach is full.
Please try again...
Sara?
Hey, dinner's ready.
- I'm not hungry.
It's Mexican.
Please, I just...
I'm tired, and I want to sleep, OK?
OK.
So you're cutting me out?
Standard dick move.
That's what this is, right?
Look at me.
Why can't you just look at me?
- It was a mistake.
It didn't seem like a mistake
from where I was laying.
I can't be with you.
What the fuck?
I don't want to be with you.
I don't want you, OK?
You know what?
Fuck you.
Hey, Mum.
- Hey.
OK, so why is he so down?
Oedipus says things like...
"Let the storm burst, my
fixed resolve still holds," or...
"Nothing can make me
other than what I am."
He still holds himself morally responsible...
He doesn't blame fate
for what's happened to him.
Moral responsibility implies
the existence of free will, but actually...
You feeling any better?
- Uh-huh.
So, listen... I had to run some tests,
in case we had a Noro outbreak here.
Honey, it was the EC pill that made you sick.
EC?
Emergency contraception.
For terminating your pregnancy.
There's no...
There's no pregnancy.
Seriously, I'm... I'm not...
I can't... I haven't...
I understand, sweetheart.
And it will work, in spite of the vomiting.
You don't have to worry about that.
You're not pregnant anymore.
I gotta put it in your file,
but I don't have to flag it.
And I want you to know I got your back.
Please.
Sara?
You watched me.
No, I... Honey. Honey...
- You watched me with him.
I... No, I didn't mean to.
- Give it to me.
Give it...
I was trying to protect you.
I was trying to keep you safe.
- How do you turn it off?
- Filter on.
Everything I've done, I've done for you.
- On-on-on-...
Honey, I love you...
- Shut up!
Sara...
Sara! Sara!
Filter... Filter off-off-off...
Off...
Sara?
Sara!
I love you.
- Sara!
Sara!
No... No...