[low, thrumming rumbling]
[high-pitched tone]
[ethereal music plays, fades]
[ethereal music plays]
[man] Sweetheart?
If you're gonna scratch your nose,
go back to the same pose afterward.
Why do I have to be here?
It's Ricky's birthday.
And he's your brother.
Okay, we all ready to go?
Lily, you're released.
[woman chuckles]
[man] Come on, buddy.
[man grunts]
[exhales]
[grunts]
Not used to my grip yet.
Still getting accustomed to it.
[dog panting]
[grunts]
[man] Hey.
Hey.
So, um, Henry was wondering
how long till dinner.
Huh.
I guess I could start.
Is that all you do, Mr. Potts?
Invent things?
-Is that all I do?
-Oh, and what's this gadget?
That's not quite right yet, but eventually
I hope to transmit moving pictures
by wireless.
-[woman] Really?
-[man] Yes, really.
-As Marconi--
-[woman] And this?
[man] This, madam,
is a sweet-making machine.
-[woman] And is this one of the sweets?
-[man] Yes, it is.
-Is that yours too?
-Uh, excuse me.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Yeah.
Uh, I apologize for the intrusion,
but, uh, you're David Ross?
I believe I am.
-It's an honor to meet you, sir.
-Oh my God. Such an honor.
-Thank you. You're too kind.
-[chuckles]
You are so real. Uh, it's incredible.
May I?
Oh my God.
It's amazing.
So, up there,
are you, like, sleeping right now?
It's a kind of sleep.
The human experience,
the survival of the human body, of life,
that's really central to the mission--
[clears throat]
Anyway, we have to be--
-So great to meet you.
-So great.
I know they're excited, but sometimes
they are so goddamn rude.
Oh, but they don't realize, honey.
Our Lord, Heavenly Father,
bless us and these thy gifts
which we take from thy bountiful goodness
through Jesus Christ, our Lord.
Amen.
-[woman] Amen.
-[boy] Amen.
[David] I know, but you guys have to wait.
Wait a second.
I said wait for ready, set, go!
[children giggle]
Not too fast!
-It's a clear win for Lily.
-[children exclaim]
[David] A clear win.
[Lily] Mom, come on!
Coming.
[sighs]
Sleep well. I love you.
Sleep well.
["La mer" by Charles Trenet playing]
[woman exhales]
[woman moans]
[passionate gasp]
[moans]
[gasping]
[beeping]
[beeping stops]
Sorry, sweetheart. I gotta go.
[woman] Mm.
[David] You staying up?
If I don't see you…
[beeping]
[beeping stops]
Sorry.
I have to go.
[ethereal music playing]
[ethereal music continues]
[beeping]
[inhales deeply]
[ethereal music continues]
[exhales]
[inhales deeply]
[groans]
[exhales]
[grunts]
[keyboard clacking]
-[David] Hey, Cliff.
-[Cliff] David, what's up?
Some sort of minor impact.
Probably just debris.
But… [exhales] …there is a crack
in the solar coating.
Let's get to it.
[ethereal music playing]
[latch clicks]
[alarm blaring]
[whirring]
-[loud clatter]
-[air hisses]
[ethereal music playing]
[latch clicks]
[exhales]
[ethereal music fades]
I didn't ask. How's the new home?
Oh, still settling in, but it's good.
-Way out of the city, which I like.
-Henry liking the country air?
He's a little quiet,
but he'll grow into it.
And Lana?
Cape Ann gonna be
cosmopolitan enough for her?
She's doing good.
Really?
I only met her the once,
but she struck me as quite the butterfly.
I think she likes it there.
When's our next physical?
Friday.
Okay. I'll see you Friday.
-Have a good week.
-You too.
[exhales]
[device chimes]
[device beeps]
[exhales]
[groans]
[Cliff] Hey.
Still reading.
Really just looking at the words,
you know?
[Cliff] Mm.
Maybe we should have a little party.
A party?
-Who's gonna drive all the way out here?
-For the local folks.
Say hello.
Meet the neighbors.
[exhales]
[Lana] Something small. In the garden.
[Cliff] I don't know.
Be good for Henry to meet some local kids.
We'll see.
[clattering]
[muffled chatter in distance]
[door hinge squeaks]
[muffled male chatter]
[man, woman laugh]
[muffled female chatter]
[male laughs]
[laughter]
Get out of my house.
Oh, we've met the machine man.
What a trip.
I'm Kappa.
This is Sigma, Theta, and that's Epsilon.
I don't give a shit.
You're in my house.
Indeed we are.
-Do you have a cock?
-Good question.
All of you leave right now.
-Now!
-[gasps]
-You're rude not to answer me.
-I'm telling you to get out of my house.
Gonna bash your friend Kappa's brains in
in your beautiful room here?
If I have to.
That might disrupt your frequency.
If you all leave right now,
nothing has to happen.
[tense music playing]
[exclaims]
No stranger in the crowd could doubt
'twas Casey at the bat. [laughs]
[grunts]
Get him.
[grunts, groans]
[Kappa] Where even are you, man?
Get him in position. Come on.
[David groaning]
[David grunts]
-[breathes deeply]
-[David grunts]
Lay his arm out.
[David grunting]
Let's see what's inside your hand, hmm?
[David grunts] No! No, no, no, no!
[Kappa] Yeah. Yep.
No! No, no, no, no, no!
-[skin tearing]
-[David grunting]
[Kappa] That is a tough steak.
[Kappa grunting perversely]
[skin tearing]
[Sigma] Freaky.
Oh, you don't even bleed right.
You are nothing natural, my friend.
Fuck.
Sigma, give me your hammer.
Theta, get his family.
No! No!
No!
Try to work out where you are.
[silence]
[panicked breathing]
[panting]
[David] Come on! Come on!
[device chimes]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
-[woman] Please.
-[David grunts]
Please, not my children. Please!
-Please. Please, not my children.
-[grunts]
Then whose children are they, huh?
We just wanna find out
who else is a machine, Mr. Bunny.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, none of us… none of us are.
Uh, it's just… it's just him.
It's just David.
[David exhales]
[woman] We're real.
We're real. I…
Blood. Real blood,
where I got cut.
Yeah, I… I don't doubt you're real.
[relieved exhale] Yeah.
-[Kappa] And your kids are real.
-Yeah!
I'm sorry to report
that's immaterial, sugar.
Because the way the facts run,
none of what has occurred in your home,
with your full knowledge,
is right in nature.
A man sleeps in the sky
while his mechanical image
walks the earth.
[grunting]
And you…
share your bed with this abomination?
Hmm?
You know none of this is right.
How can it be?
Defying nature must have a cost,
or what will become of us all?
So, yes, you.
[grunts angrily]
-And, yes, the children.
-No…
[screams]
And the machine man will watch
with his heart screaming
a million miles above us.
-[David screaming]
-[woman] Please, no.
[whimpers] Please! Please, no!
-Epsilon, you start.
-[woman] No!
-[blade rasps]
-[woman screams] No!
[screaming]
[woman screams] No!
[scream echoes]
[tense music playing]
[tense music fades]
[phone ringing]
Hello.
Uh, what?
Wait, wait, wait.
What the hell are you saying?
[breathes deeply]
[device beeping]
[zipper unzipping]
[unsettling music playing]
David?
David, it's me.
-[David exhales]
-David.
[David] Leave me alone.
[exhales]
[Cliff] I'm so sorry.
I said get out of here!
[David sniffles]
[footsteps approaching]
[Cliff] He told me to get out.
Spoke to Ground Control.
Holland says just leave him be.
He'll be in shock.
Sons of bitches that did this walked
into a station and gave themselves up.
Some sort of hippie cult.
Board says if we feel we need protection,
we can have it,
but we are a long way from California.
I keep thinking of them.
Jessica.
Those kids.
I can't even imagine.
Bastards even destroyed his replica.
Set it on fire.
That means the whole time
that I am down here, he's just
alone up there.
Two years down on the mission,
another four to go.
Can't they make him
another replica somehow?
They made these
while we were still back down here.
Now it's just not possible.
Even if they could,
what does he have left here?
[ethereal music playing]
[both breathing heavily]
[Cliff] Soil and nutrients stable.
CO light absorption functioning.
Purity at 93%.
[both breathing heavily]
[ethereal music continues]
[man] "The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want."
"He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures."
"He leadeth me beside the still waters."
"He restoreth my soul."
"He leadeth me in the paths
of righteousness for his name's sake."
"Yea, though I walk through
the valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil."
"For thou art with me."
"Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me."
-Paying attention?
-[Henry] Yeah.
[Cliff] All right.
[gentle music playing]
[breathes deeply]
[gentle music continues]
[ethereal music playing]
[music fades]
-[grunts]
-[water splashes]
There we go.
You're up.
[beeping]
Airlock issue. I gotta run.
[zipper unzipping]
[alarm blaring]
[Cliff] Hey!
[knocking on door]
[muffled] Hey!
[alarm continues]
[keypad beeping]
-[switch clicks]
-[Cliff grunts]
[door lock clicks]
[air hisses]
Everything okay?
Sure.
Just looking things over.
[Lana] You don't know
he was gonna throw himself out.
[Cliff] I don't know.
I mean, if he were to do something,
I'm still up there.
That's a two-man ship.
It relies on the both of us.
If there was, like,
a computer malfunction,
some sort of technical issue,
that is me dead too.
Don't say that.
We have to think about this.
The man is lost.
I can't reach him,
and I don't know what to do.
What if…
what if you let him use your link?
My link?
As in…
Say, just for an hour.
Time enough to let him walk in the woods,
feel… feel the breeze on his face.
I don't know.
It'd be strange for you and Henry.
Henry doesn't need to know.
David might not even want that.
Even asking could be a kindness.
[pensive music playing]
Okay.
0800 hours, commencing routine checks.
Distance to target, 4.7 AU.
[keyboard clacking]
[sighs]
Listen, David,
I was talking with Lana, and we both feel
that you could use a break.
How would you feel
about using my link?
Just for a little while.
Breathe some… [inhales] …air.
The house, it's a long way from anywhere.
It's real private.
There's a forest out back,
a couple streams for fishing.
It's a good place.
Would you…
would you like that?
I think I'd like that very much.
So…
I'll head to the link now.
How should I speak to him?
I mean, in manner?
Quiet?
Serious, or…
I don't know, regular?
Like it didn't happen?
I mean…
You know what I mean.
Well… [sighs] …he used to be talkative,
but right now, he's not easy to read.
Just let him take in the air.
[Cliff] You ready?
[breathes deeply]
[breathing nervously]
[device chimes]
[low thrumming]
[ethereal music playing]
[device beeping]
[gentle string music playing]
Hello.
Hi.
Cliff said it might take
a little getting used to.
Would you like to see the forest?
Yes.
Thank you.
[string music intensifies]
[exhales]
[Cliff] Wow.
This is my favorite spot.
[Cliff] Mm.
[exhales]
The air is so clear.
I'd forgotten.
Hm.
Hey.
[chuckles]
He likes you.
[sobs]
[Cliff whimpers]
[whimpers]
[sobs]
[Cliff crying]
[music fades]
[Lana] What is it?
Uh…
Nothing.
Just…
You've quite the home.
[muffled chatter]
[soft clatter]
Your place…
is beautiful.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you.
Glad you enjoyed it.
Well, I best be, uh…
Of course.
I'll see you Friday.
[pats shoulder]
See you then.
-[device chimes]
-[exhales]
[device beeping]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[pen scribbling]
-[Cliff] Hey.
-[gasps]
[sighs]
You scared me.
Well, it feels like that really worked.
He seems a little
lighter now.
So,
how was it?
The poor man. He wept like a child.
In front of you?
Mm-hmm.
What did you do?
Not much. I…
He sat up by the old tree.
What… what could I even say?
Yeah.
[inhales]
[Cliff exhales]
[treadmills whirring]
Hey.
Let me show you something.
-[Cliff] You did this from memory?
-[David scoffs]
When something is vivid,
I just kind of see it.
Wait, this is quite something.
If I had this down there,
I would hang it on the wall.
You know…
if you guys could maybe
get me a canvas and some oils,
I could paint you something like this
for your home.
Like a thank-you gift.
Uh-huh.
I mean, obviously, you'd have
to let me use your replica again.
You might not want to do that.
It's just… [scoffs]
Drawing helps.
I'd love to be able to paint again.
An oil painting.
I mean, how long would a painting take?
Well, a little while, obviously.
Okay.
Look, I understand.
I shouldn't ask. It's not fair.
I'm sorry.
Let me think it over.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
[Lana] Just an hour?
One hour.
Once a week, while I'm doing the physical.
I mean, it does make sense.
He can set up his things
up in the barn there.
He had a list of what he'd need,
canvas and fancy paints and whatnot.
Clearly, it has been on his mind.
What do you say?
Okay?
[device chimes]
[David breathes deeply]
[device beeping]
[Lana] Everything you need?
Think we got your whole list.
Looks like it.
Thank you.
How you finding that? Valley of the Dolls?
Oh. [chuckles]
Can't say I'm crazy about it.
I mean, it's fun,
but my goodness, it's trashy.
A guilty pleasure.
The guiltiest.
Do you like sci-fi?
Can't say I've tried it.
There aren't many books in the house.
Cliff doesn't really read.
I'll think of a few recommendations
for you.
I'd like that.
["Quand on n'a que l'amour"
by Jacques Brel playing]
["Quand on n'a que l'amour" continues]
Sir, may I leave the table?
[Cliff] Good boy.
["Quand on n'a que l'amour" continues]
-[Cliff] Have you done much painting?
-[music ends]
-[Lana] Not since kindergarten.
-[chuckles]
Here.
Um, I can't. I'd make a mess of it.
It's fine. You make a mess,
I can paint right over it.
Here you go.
Why don't you just try to add a little
to the tree there?
[Lana] How… how do I…
Don't be afraid of it.
Just a… just a light… light stroke.
[Lana chuckles]
Okay, that's a blob.
[Cliff] It's fine.
Here, just move the brush through it.
Here.
[whispers] Like…
this.
There we go.
Perfectly good leaf.
[Henry] Mom!
-Better see what he wants.
-[Cliff] Of course.
[device chimes]
[device beeping]
[Cliff] His painting's looking good.
[sighs]
[Lana] Everything okay?
Do you have any linseed oil? I've run out.
Linseed oil?
Yeah. It, uh, thins the paint
without mussing up the color.
Uh, Wesson oil any use to you?
Nah, that won't do it.
Is there a hardware store in town?
There's Mitchell's. They'll be open.
You think Cliff would mind
if we borrow his car?
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
Got it.
[Cliff] Great.
Hey, I wanna check
the bookstore out a moment.
You wanna come?
Sure.
He wears it out.
This is a good one.
I think you'll like it.
[sighs] I'm sorry, I have to ask.
Are you Cliff Stanfield?
-Yes.
-[chuckles] I thought it was you.
Well, not you, but your, um…
What do you call it?
Replica.
[chuckles] The things they can do!
And you must be Mrs. Stanfield.
Yes.
Heard you both moved
into the old Watson place.
How you finding it?
Well, it's, uh…
-I mean, it's wonderful.
-Oh, so beautiful up that way.
Great place for a family.
Absolutely.
I was so sorry to hear about what happened
with your copilot, Mr. Ross.
His whole family…
Such a terrible thing.
Well…
Yes.
How is he doing?
He's holding up.
We really ought to be going.
Of course.
So nice to meet you.
Thanks.
[Cliff exhales]
You okay?
[device beeping]
[David inhales deeply]
[exhales]
All yours.
Thank you.
See you Friday.
[switch clicks]
[Cliff] Hey.
Take a look.
Is… is that…
You added me?
[Cliff] You don't mind, do you?
[Lana] No.
No, not at all. I'm flattered.
["La mer" by Charles Trenet playing]
[Lana chuckles softly]
[gasps]
["La mer" continues muffled]
[Cliff] Lana!
[exhales]
It's okay.
I've given you the wrong idea.
He won't know.
Stop!
Hey.
You want this.
Get away from me.
You come here. You… you confuse me.
You pick out gifts. You mess with my head.
Work your way into my home
wearing my husband like a suit.
But this is not your home,
and you are not my husband.
That man is no match for you.
You are a guest in this house.
-And you want this.
-You don't know me.
I know the way you look at me.
At you?
[breathes heavily]
[sighs]
[record static playing]
[door opens]
Henry?
You should go.
[Cliff sighs]
[device beeping]
[David breathes deeply]
Everything okay?
All fine.
[Cliff] David says
Henry wrecked his painting.
[Lana] He hit him!
He gave him a little smack
upside the head.
Which, as far as Henry knows,
was from you.
Nothing I haven't done myself
a hundred times.
You know Henry can be a terror.
Remember when he burned a hole
in the car seat? I whaled on him plenty,
right here in this room.
The boy needs keeping in line.
[exhales]
Look.
-David wants to finish the painting.
-The goddamn painting.
I know.
Let's just let him finish the painting.
Okay? That will be one,
two more visits tops.
And then… I will come up with something.
An excuse.
Okay?
Okay.
[footsteps approaching]
[grunting]
[door opens]
-Lana, listen.
-Your things are set up in the barn.
-Lana, please.
-I'm taking Henry to the pool.
[sighs]
[ominous music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[breathing heavily]
[beeping]
[beeping stops]
I got an alert.
What's up?
You gonna explain that?
[sighs]
It's ju-- It's… it's a drawing.
Just a stupid--
Like a fantasy.
Maybe I will bust your jaw.
You want a busted jaw?
I'm sorry. It's not what--
My wife!
You fucking creep!
My wife. Mine!
It's pure fantasy. I got mixed up.
Oh, you got mixed up?
She's so beautiful. It's--
[David groans]
[exhales]
-[David groans]
-Jesus Christ.
Why can't you see?
I don't have anything.
I've got nothing at all.
You have no idea what it's like to be me.
Everything I had…
Gone. Just
destroyed.
You don't know.
You have got it all,
and you don't even care.
I care plenty.
Your wife is a lonely woman.
She's all alone there.
Unappreciated.
-Unsatisfied.
-You shut your mouth.
Untouched.
I will put you through this goddamn wall!
[Cliff breathing heavily]
You don't know what you've got.
I know damn well.
Do you?
How much longer we gotta sit here?
Till your father's home.
[car engine starts]
[car door opens]
-[Cliff] Henry, go inside.
-Yes, sir.
[Cliff exhales]
[grunting]
-Cliff, what's wrong?
-Tell me what's gone on.
You and him. What's gone on?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What did you do?
I told you, nothing.
Did you pose for him?
No, I did not pose for him.
Show him your body?
Of course not.
Did he touch you?
No.
Did you touch him?
-No.
-Take him to our bed?
Absolutely not.
Tell me what happened!
Nothing. I swear.
He drew you naked.
In his quarters. Up there, onboard.
-I don't know what he drew.
-He draws from memory.
-From memory!
-He has seen nothing.
Give me the truth!
-I--
-Give me the truth!
I swear on my life, on Henry's life,
nothing happened.
But he wanted it to.
Yes.
-And you still let him come down here.
-You knew I didn't want him here anymore.
You never said that.
I told you he hit our son,
and you did not listen to me.
You didn't listen!
He said that
I don't touch you.
How did he know that?
I would never say anything like that
to anyone.
So, then, how did he know?
I don't know.
He thinks that you're lonely.
All the time you're here, I'm lonely.
We came here for you!
You brought me here, put me in this house.
Now I just walk from room to room,
and you walk from room to room,
but you're a shadow,
and I am here. I am real!
So, no, he didn't touch me,
but I wished he did. I…
For, like, a… a moment…
for a moment,
it felt like my husband was back,
and he
saw that I'm real, and I want that. I…
And I wished he did too.
[Cliff sniffles]
[breathing shakily]
[Cliff] I'm sorry.
Hey. [clears throat]
Listen.
What?
I wanted to apologize.
I overstepped the mark, and I apologize.
Nothing happened with Lana.
I know.
She wasn't interested.
Listen.
I know you don't want me
using your link anymore. It's just…
I'd like to apologize to her in person.
I owe her an apology too.
Hey. [clears throat]
Could I at least say goodbye to her?
I just wanna say goodbye.
That's not gonna happen.
You know what she told me?
That your visits offend her.
That you offend her.
The thought of you returning
makes her vomit.
She says that you're a snake.
A conman.
The worst kind.
The arrogant kind.
She won't have you anywhere near her.
She is mine.
For all time, she is mine.
Every day,
every night,
in every way.
You will not see or speak to her
ever again.
[razor clatters]
[Cliff] Who's a good boy?
[Cliff chuckles]
[beeping]
[beeping stops]
Damn it. Some kind of emergency.
What is it?
Small impact a few minutes ago.
Coolant tubing took a hit.
It's leaking pretty bad.
[ethereal music playing]
[latch clicks]
[alarm blaring]
[tense music playing]
Hey, I'm at coolant four.
[breathing heavily]
No visible signs of damage.
David, you sure it was coolant four?
David?
[tense music continues]
[breathing heavily]
David!
[muffled] David!
[tense music intensifies]
[tense music crescendos]
[latch clicks]
[breathing heavily]
Where the hell were you?
Bathroom.
The bathroom?
Coolant four was fine.
Goddamn system's
sending out false reports.
Gotta get on to McKenzie.
This is not acceptable.
Where's my tag?
My tag.
What did you do?
[breathing heavily]
Come on.
[device chimes]
[device beeping]
[unsettling music playing]
[gasps]
Lana?
No, no, no, no.
[breathing shakily] No.
Lana?
[whimpers]
[unsettling music intensifies]
[echoing scream] No!
[sobbing]
[music fades]
[sobs]
[sniffling]
["La mer" by Charles Trenet playing]
["La mer" by Charles Trenet continues]
[music ends]