Lords and Ladies of the Empire, welcome!
Space, once an unreachable frontier,
is now a dazzling playground
for Earth's children.
And so, we gather here,
above the frozen skies of Jupiter...
...to witness the sacred union
of our glorious regent,
Lord Chalon of Europa,
and the Duchess Saraka of Callisto.
Their love must be tempered
with ritual and ceremony,
shaped in the crucible of chaos...
...and sanctified with blood,
blood spilled in tribute
on these sands below.
Tonight, you will witness
a spectacle like no other.
Behold the riders.
Are they not absolutely magnificent?
Years of discipline and training
have forged them into the perfect warriors
you see before you.
Champions honed to a razor's edge,
each blessed with the strength
and ferocity of their totem spirit.
My sigil marks me as wild and untamed.
It is a secret prayer,
my longing to be free.
To those who are about to die,
we salute you.
Now let the race begin!
Everything that does not please our overlords
has been stripped away.
In the darkness above Europa,
they take everything from us.
A wolf alone can be outrun,
out-fought, out-maneuvered.
But the wolf pack is an apex predator.
Yeah!
The aristocracy mate for money and power.
But we who can own nothing...
...have something real,
something primal, something true.
She is magnificent.
Whoo! Yeah.
Was that not glorious?
A contest of heroes
worthy of this celestial union.
But for this most special occasion,
we have something more,
a final challenge to test our champion
against nature's most
savagely primal creation.
Fuck!
Turn! You big bastard!
My lords, this carnage is no end...
It is a beginning.
This King of the ancient world
gives us the gift
of his matchless vitality.
In his veins flows the power primordial...
as it will now flow
into those of our sovereigns,
so that they may write
our future in blood.
The Tyrannosaur no longer screams.
He has had his fill of blood.
But you up there...
...you will never have enough.
Come... let us end this our way.
In the darkness above Europa...
...they take everything from us,
even our memories.
Yet some fragments linger...
...like the last leaves of autumn.
Among the blossoms,
I am alone with my wine.
Lifting my cup,
I ask the moon to drink with me.
Its reflection in the wine,
with mine, just we three.