Dad.
Dad, wake up.
Wake up.
I must've drifted off.
- Where were we?
- The mad man.
Of course.
The Hatter who says,
"If I had a world of my own,
everything would be nonsense.
"Nothing would be what it is,
"because everything would be
what it isn't."
"Everything would be what it isn't"?
Even me.
Hey.
You're perfect.
You're gonna beat this.
I promise you.
Now, let's skip to something fun.
Dad.
- What is it, Charlie?
- Listen to me.
Listen.
Charlie?
Charlie!
And finally, have you ever
questioned the nature of your reality?
No.
Good.
Now, then,
I see you had a blacklisted exchange
with a guest
in the course of your narrative.
Can you tell me what happened?
He said he wanted to cut off a piece
of me to take home in his carry-on.
I told him if he wanted a trophy,
I could cut pieces of him off
and let him fish for them in the Olvido.
And did this exchange make you
question anything about your world?
No.
This world is as doomed as ever.
And just for my peace of mind...
Anything about these images
that jumps out to you?
They don't look like anything to me.
We're through 15% of the backlog.
As it stands,
we should be caught up by end of day.
Good.
And when you're done here, sir,
there's a priority request for him
from management.
Have you seen Elsie?
She was supposed to
give me a hand on something.
No. According to the system,
she started her leave today.
Is there something
I could help you with?
No, thanks.
Raise.
I'll call.
You're calling with that shit?
- Dolores, why don't you play a hand?
- You're wasting your breath.
Girl's harboring a grudge.
I don't blame you, sweetheart.
I did some ugly things to you both.
But it wasn't personal.
Confederados and the government
like to call this thing a war,
but they're fighting starving farmers
armed with rocks.
That ain't no war.
It's a slaughter.
If I had to do it all again,
I'd fuck you both over just as hard.
Well, I guess we know where you stand.
Don't pretend like you're so innocent.
Way I recollect, y'all came to me,
looking to join up with those
crooked assholes and their war effort.
Not our idea.
My friend wanted...
I guess he wanted to see
what was at the end of all this.
And yet, here you are.
Your friend didn't make it this far.
Maybe you've got more of
an appetite for this than you think.
William.
What is it?
We're in Ghost Nation territory.
Most savage tribe there is.
Those are the folks
who came calling without an invitation.
You mean
exactly what we're doing right now?
The train's the only way through.
On foot, we'll be dead in under an hour.
As soon as we're
clear of their territory,
we can stop. You can come with me.
Nothing here on out but slaughter.
The user you
are trying to access cannot be located.
Say "message" to transcribe a message.
You wanted to see me?
Is everything okay?
You left rather abruptly last night.
Was there something
you wanted to tell me?
No, I don't think so.
Hale is looking over
every department and
yours is running
behind on diagnostics.
It would be best if we presented at
least a semblance of professionalism
while the board is here.
We'll be fine.
My people know how to do their jobs.
If they applied
half as much energy to their work
as they have to second-guessing
my team's investigation--
That's all over.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Good.
You doing okay?
I'm fine. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I thought you requested a meeting.
- My mistake.
- I did. Come in.
Get back here.
Bring your friend.
What about you? What turns of fate--
I could come back later
if this isn't a good time.
This won't take long.
Theresa, you've always
been good at your job,
and the board has been impressed
with your performance so far,
which is why we were so surprised
by this woodcutter mess.
A small setback.
He slipped on a fucking rock,
then bashed his own head in
while basically on
top of a behavior tech.
Meanwhile, Ford is suddenly
using half the park's resources
to build some new narrative?
Can I bum a cigarette?
God, I see why you took these up again.
Let me remind you of something.
This place,
the people who work here are nothing.
Our interest in this place is
entirely in the intellectual property.
The code.
- The hosts' minds, the storylines--
- I don't give a rat's ass about the hosts.
It's our little research project
that Delos cares about.
That's where the real value is.
And due to a lack of foresight on
part of one of my predecessors,
35 years of information,
raw information, exists here.
Nowhere else.
Ford has always ensured that.
Now, you are a smart enough woman.
Tell me, why would we
need you to secure all of it?
Because you're going to fire him.
You don't fire someone
who created an empire.
You ask him to retire politely.
And if that person has
the ability to snap his fingers
and erase the value of that empire,
you have to make sure
you have a contingency.
So, you and I need to ensure that by
the time the rest of the board arrives,
we are on course for that transition.
Okay?
I like you.
Well, not personally,
but I like you for this job,
which is why I'm gonna give you
another chance to get a handle on
this particular bitch of a situation.
But the gods...
They require a blood sacrifice.
We need to demonstrate just how
dangerous Ford's creations can be.
No.
No, nothing so obvious.
We need someone thoroughly unexpected.
I told you never open your mouth that
wide unless someone's paying you for it.
Sorry, Maeve.
I didn't sleep much last night.
What are these
nightmares you have about?
Do you ever dream you're someone else?
I don't think so.
Why?
You ever thought about whether
this is really the life you want?
I don't intend
to make this my life's work.
No offense.
My family's got a farm. Bad soil.
Nothing grows.
I send money back to them.
They think I work in a dress shop.
What's wrong?
I'm just doing what you told me to.
A couple more years of this, and
then I can have whatever life I want.
I'm gonna get my
family out of the desert.
We're gonna go somewhere cold.
Someday.
Which one is it?
It's the one at the bar.
Go. Quick,
before the guests upstairs finish up.
Whatever she did,
it must've been serious
if they're making us
grab her in broad daylight.
We got her. Let's go.
You're supposed to be resting.
We're riding a train full of explosives
through scalping territory.
Not sleepy.
Can I ask you something?
This place you're looking for,
what makes you so sure it exists?
I'm not.
My life before,
I was so sure of the world.
But now it feels like a lie.
Only thing I know is whatever's
out there, I'm never going back.
What is it you're looking for?
Lawrence is right.
You could've stayed in Pariah,
or gone back, but you're here.
With me.
The only thing I had when I was a kid
were books.
I used to live in them.
I used to go to sleep
dreaming I'd wake up inside one of them
'cause they had meaning.
This place, this is like
I woke up inside one of those stories.
I guess
I just wanna find out what it means.
I don't wanna be in a story.
All I want is to not
look forward or back.
I just wanna be in the moment I'm in.
Dolores, back home, there's a woman.
Juliet, and her father
owns the company where I work.
She's Logan's sister.
Yeah.
And when I get home,
we're getting married.
The place you're after,
I will help you find it.
But I can't stay.
I have a life waiting for me.
I'm sorry.
Of course.
Dolores.
I've been pretending my whole life.
Pretending I don't mind,
pretending I belong.
My life's built on it.
And it's a good life.
It's a life I've always wanted.
But then I came here
and I get a glimpse for a second
of a life
in which I don't have to pretend.
A life in which I can be truly alive.
How can I go back to pretending
when I know what this feels like?
Miss Hale.
I was not aware those with your level
of insight needed any more reflection.
Dr. Ford. Always charming.
What is this?
Apparently, Miss Cullen and Miss Hale
have a presentation for us.
What about?
Following the recent reports
of host malfunction,
we asked QA
to check the last abortive update,
which featured the reveries.
- As I believe they're called?
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm sorry to report
that Miss Cullen and her team
uncovered some worrisome findings.
In the course of our code review,
we found something quite disturbing.
Wake her up.
We set Clementine Pennyfeather
back to her previous update.
When we discovered the build was buggy
due to a last-minute injection
of the Reverie code,
we quickly rolled all the infected hosts
back to their prior builds.
You're new.
Not much of a rind on you.
No!
No! No!
Please.
Help me!
Please, please, please! No!
All right, that's enough.
Freeze.
As you've no doubt gathered,
our tech is, in fact, a host.
One that has been coded for the purposes
of this simulation to read as a human.
And as you can see,
behavioral safeguards
are operating exactly
as you would expect.
Reset her. Wipe her memory.
Okay, let's do this again.
You're new.
Not much of a rind on you.
That's enough, sweetheart.
That's enough.
Freeze all motor functions.
In each case we examined,
the malfunctioning hosts
were not resetting properly.
The retention of data
that hadn't been wiped
overloaded their
decision-making apparatus,
eventually causing a system failure
that allowed for override
of their primary rule set.
The concern with the reveries
is that the hosts will remember
some of their experiences
and act on them.
You're telling us that these hosts
were responding to a grudge?
That's exactly what I'm saying,
Mr. Lowe.
And funny you should
use that particular word, "grudge,"
since what was most troubling to me
was that several techs in behavior
voiced these exact same concerns
to the head of their department.
You put this code out
without proper vetting
and without reasonable understanding
of its ramifications.
So, either you didn't write it,
or you're getting sloppy to the point
of risking the lives of our guests.
Few things surprise me anymore,
Mr. Lowe,
but this level of negligence
is fucking breathtaking.
We are way beyond rollback territory.
Within the next six months, we'll need
to rebuild the hosts from the ground up.
You want us to lobotomize them
is what you're saying.
No, not you, Mr. Lowe.
After all, this was your responsibility,
assuming that you have nothing to share
with us in terms of your culpability.
No.
Then you're fired.
Hey.
Morning, William.
I... I didn't wanna wake you.
I know last night was unexpected.
If you regret it--
I don't regret a thing.
I know you have someone
waiting for you at home.
All that feels so unreal now.
I used to think this place was all about
pandering to your baser instincts.
Now I understand.
It doesn't cater to your lowest self,
it reveals your deepest self.
It shows you who you really are.
You remember the look on Logan's face
when we left him behind?
Do you know
how long I've wanted to do that,
to let him know what I think of him?
And you, last night,
I've never felt that way before,
not with any woman.
You've unlocked something in me.
I'm not a key, William.
I'm just me.
What is that?
I don't know.
At home, I used to paint.
Landscapes mostly, but I was always
just copying the world outside me.
This morning, I woke up and I thought,
"What if I drew something new?"
I imagined something beautiful.
A place where the
mountains meet the sea.
Everyone who comes here
is longing for excitement or conflict,
and you're just
dreaming of the opposite.
Well, what about you, William?
What do you dream of?
- What is it?
- Ambush.
Is it the Ghost Nation?
Worse. The Confederados.
Fucking coward.
Vaya con Dios, motherfuckers.
They're making a run for it!
Come on, boys, get up!
Come on, stay close!
Go, boys!
Dolores!
Ghost Nation!
Let's go!
Stop, William! Stop!
It's real.
What I dreamt.
It's the place you drew.
You coming?
Once the Ghosts is done acquainting
themselves with those poor bastards,
they'll be coming after us.
My friends here
are itching to join the war effort.
Think I've had enough of war.
How about you?
You got a knack for killing.
I'm afraid this is where we part ways.
Careful.
If you're heading
west across that river,
you may be leaving
the fighting behind,
but you're gonna
be in unclaimed territories.
What's out that way?
You're gonna have to ask the dust.
Ain't nothing ever come back from there.
We're almost done here.
Why don't I close up?
You've been topside
for less than 24 hours.
You keep coming down this often,
people are going to notice.
- Where's Clem?
- I don't know. I haven't seen her.
- Why?
- Find her. Now.
What?
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
She's here. Let's go.
We can't. The brass will be there.
You don't want to fuck with me, Felix.
Take me there now.
Slow down.
Tilt your head back, please, Clem.
- Is there a problem?
- No.
Sorry.
Theresa.
May I have a word?
Sure.
I appreciate your professionalism,
but you really
don't need to bother with this,
given the change
in your employment status--
The test was a sham.
The little show you and Hale put on?
Completely transparent
from a technical perspective,
clumsy to the point
of making me embarrassed for you.
Embarrassed?
If I saw through it, I can only imagine
what Ford was thinking.
There were glaringly obvious markers
of human intervention in the code.
If your programmers were any good,
they'd be working for me.
And I know you and your team
were responsible for the stray
and its satellite transmission.
- Bernie--
- I don't care.
Forty years ago, Ford's partner wrote
half the code this place was founded on.
What you said in the lab was right.
We don't know how the hosts work,
and I think
there's something wrong with them.
Ford's explanation
only bolsters my hunch.
The ability to
deviate from program behavior
arises out of
the host's recall of past iterations.
You're thinking there's a connection
between memory and--
And improvisation, yes.
Out of repetition comes variation.
And after countless
cycles of repetition,
these hosts, they were varying.
They were on the verge
of some kind of change.
You have to know my chief concern has
always been the well-being of this park
and the people in it.
I know.
Which is why I need
to show you something.
- Talk to her.
- You first.
Look, I didn't want to retire her.
I know she's, like, your friend, or...
I guess.
But if I didn't do it,
they'd just get someone else to,
and then they'd be suspicious of me,
so, I said yes, but I did it for you.
Always doing things for other people,
aren't you?
Time to do one more thing.
What?
All my life,
I've prided myself on being a survivor.
But surviving is just another loop.
I'm getting out of here.
You two are going to help me.
No. Do...
Do you know how far these
people will go to protect their IP?
Every part of this building,
including the skin on your back,
is made to keep you here.
It'd be a suicide mission.
At first, I thought
you and the others were gods.
Then I realized you're just men.
And I know men.
You think I'm scared of death?
I've done it a million times.
I'm fucking great at it.
How many times have you died?
'Cause, if you don't help me,
I'll kill you.
If there's a problem in the park,
should we bring a security team?
Who would we trust?
Thought I could trust you, for instance.
I'm not going to
explain myself to you, Bernard.
I was charged with safeguarding
the park's intellectual property.
Why would it be in danger? You
were the only one who was stealing it.
Delos owns the hosts' minds,
the storylines, decades of work.
Ford never allowed any of it
to be backed up off-site.
All of this could've been destroyed.
In the event of what?
Ford is done, Bernard.
The board has indulged him
for long enough. He is done.
The corporation was concerned
he'd destroy all of the park's IP
on his way out the door.
You think I would've let him destroy
all of the hosts, all of our work?
There's far more at stake here
than the hosts' profiles.
Do you really think
the corporation's interest here
are tourists playing cowboy?
The longer I work here,
the more I think I understand the hosts.
It's the human beings who confuse me.
This building isn't
in any survey of the park.
That's because we use hosts
to do most of the surveys.
They're programmed to ignore this place.
They literally couldn't see it
if they were staring right at it.
And these unregistered hosts
you told me about?
I don't know. He may have moved them.
What's behind this door?
What door?
What is this place?
It's a remote diagnostic facility.
Ford and his partner used them
when the park was in beta.
I had no idea this one was here.
The cottage must've been
built on top of it.
But this equipment...
This is newer.
Slower than our
machines back at the Mesa,
but it will render a
host in a few days.
So, Ford's been making his own
hosts out here and telling no one.
What's the matter?
Have you seen these?
What is this, Bernard?
Doesn't look like anything to me.
They cannot
see the things that will hurt them.
I've spared them that.
Their lives are blissful.
In a way,
their existence is purer than ours,
freed of the burden of self-doubt.
No, no, no, no. I don't understand.
You're a fucking monster.
Am I?
Well, you were the one who would
so blithely destroy all of them,
even him, I suppose.
After everything you have shared.
What the hell are you talking about?
Is that why?
Did you tell him to--
The intimacies were your idea,
if you will recall.
I think Bernard was glad of the company.
I'm not one.
I can't be. My wife.
My son.
The burial. I was a father. My poor boy.
That's enough, Bernard.
You mustn't get yourself worked up.
I read the theory once
that the human intellect
was like peacock feathers.
Just an extravagant display
intended to attract a mate.
All of art, literature, a bit of Mozart,
William Shakespeare, Michelangelo,
and the Empire State Building.
Just an elaborate mating ritual.
Maybe it doesn't matter that
we have accomplished so much
for the basest of reasons.
But, of course,
the peacock can barely fly.
It lives in the dirt,
pecking insects out of the muck,
consoling itself with its great beauty.
I have come to think of so much
of consciousness as a burden, a weight,
and we have spared them that.
Anxiety, self-loathing, guilt.
The hosts are the ones who are free.
Free here under my control.
But he's not under your control.
He brought me here to show me this.
No. He brought you here
because I asked him to.
He's been very loyal for many years.
Your time running this place
like your insane little kingdom is over.
You've been playing God for long enough.
I simply wanted to tell my stories.
It was you people who wanted to play God
with your little undertaking.
Do you really think
the board will stand for this?
The board will do nothing.
Our arrangement is too valuable to them.
They test me every now and then.
I think they enjoy the sport of it.
This time, they sent you.
Sadly, in order to restore things,
the situation demands a blood sacrifice.
See, Arnold and I
designed every part of this place.
It was our dream.
Did you really think
I would let you take it from me?
This is what happened to Arnold?
Did you have Bernard
take him out into the woods?
No, he wasn't here in those days.
Were you, Bernard?
Like I said, I built all of this.
I'm afraid our guest has grown weary.
Perhaps you can help her, Bernard.
No.
"And in that sleep,
what dreams may come."
Bernard.
No.
No! Please! Please!
No!
We should be getting back, Bernard.
We have a great deal of work to do
on the new storylines.