- It's getting cold.
- Thanks.
That is one fine frame.
One fine frame, that is.
How much...
...does a fine frame
like that cost, do you think?
I never told you,
but you sound a little like
Dr. Seuss when you're drunk.
Anna, I'm serious.
Serious, I am, Anna.
I'd say it cost
at least a couple hundred.
I'm gonna read it for you.
Do I really sound
like Dr. Seuss?
"In recognition of his
outstanding achievement
in the field
of child psychology,
his dedication to his work
and his continuing efforts to
improve the quality of life..."
Will you concentrate?
"...his continuing efforts
to improve the quality of life
for countless children
and their families,
the city of Philadelphia
proudly bestows upon its son,
Dr. Malcolm Crowe..."
That's you.
"...the Mayor's Citation
for Professional Excellence."
They called you their son.
Wow.
We should hang it
in the bathroom.
This is an important
night for us.
Finally, someone is recognizing
the sacrifices you've made.
That you have put everything
second, including me...
...for those families
that they're talking about.
They're also saying
that my husband has a gift.
You have a gift that teaches
children how to be strong
in situations where most adults
would piss on themselves.
I believe what
they wrote is real.
Thank you.
I would like
some wine in a glass.
I would not like it in a mug.
I would not like it in a jug.
Look.
Anna, don't move.
Don't make a sound.
This is 47 Locust Street.
You've broken a window
and entered a private residence.
You don't know so many things.
There are no needles
or prescription drugs
of any kind in this house.
Do you know why you're
afraid when you're alone?
I do. I do.
What do you want?
What he promised me!
- I want what he promised me.
- Oh, my God.
Do I know you?
Don't you know me, hero?
Don't you even remember
your own patients?
D... Downtown clinic.
S... Single-parent family.
Possible mood disorder.
I was afraid!
You told me I was having trouble
coping with my parents' divorce.
You... You were wrong.
You were wrong.
Now look at me!
I don't want
to be afraid no more.
Please, just give me
a minute to think.
I waited ten years for you!
I'm not giving you nothing!
Ben Friedkin?
Some people,
they call me "freak".
Ronald Sumner?
I am. I am a freak.
Look at...
Vincent.
Vincent Grey.
Don't. Don't.
I do remember you.
- No.
- Quiet, very smart.
Compassionate.
Unusually compassionate.
You forgot "cursed".
You failed me.
You failed me!
Vincent, I'm sorry if I
wasn't... if I didn't help you.
But if you just...
let me try.
You just
give me a chance...
- Oh, God. Oh, God, honey.
- Did Vincent...
- Now, don't talk. Shh.
De profundis
clamo ad te, Domine.
It's okay, Cole.
My name is Dr. Malcolm Crowe.
We were supposed to meet today,
but I missed our appointment.
I'm sorry.
You know,
in the olden days in Europe,
people used to
hide out in churches.
They would claim sanctuary.
What were they hiding from?
Bad people, mostly.
People that wanted to put
them in jail... hurt them.
Noticed your eyeglasses. They
don't have any lenses in them.
They're my dad's.
The lenses hurt my eyes.
What were you talking
about with your soldiers
when I came in?
- De...
- De profundis clamo ad te, Domine.
It's called "Latin".
All your soldiers
speak Latin?
No.
Just one.
A-Are you a good doctor?
Well...
I used to be.
I won an award once
from the mayor.
Had an
expensive frame.
I'm gonna see you again, right?
If that's okay with you.
It's me.
Pennsylvania Turnpike westbound
slow to Valley Forge 24.
On the Blue Ridge both directions,
generally slow between number three...
- Hey, good morning.
Cole?
Hey, your Cocoa Puffs
are getting soggy.
Let me see you.
Aw, honey, you got a spot.
Okay, here it comes.
Something you were
looking for, baby?
Pop-Tarts?
They're right here.
Oh.
What are you
thinking, Mama?
Lots of things.
Anything bad about me?
Hey, look at my face.
I was not thinking
something bad about you.
Got it?
Got it.
- Get up.
- Th-That's Tommy, Mom.
- Okay, you tuck it in.
Hey, Cole?
You want this?
Hey, freak, how'd you like that
arm-around-the-shoulder bit?
I just made that up. I went
with it as great actors do.
It's called "improv".
Hey, baby.
How was your day?
Hmm?
You know, you can
tell me things if you need to.
Oh, you know what I did today?
I, uh... I won the Pennsylvania
Lottery in the morning.
I quit my jobs.
And I ate a big
picnic in the park
with lots of
chocolate mousse pie.
And then I swam
in the fountain all afternoon.
What'd you do?
I was picked first for
kickball teams at recess.
I hit a grand slam
to win the game.
Everybody lifted me up
and carried me around, cheering.
In that case, I am gonna
make you some triangle pancakes.
You got an hour.
Hi.
Want to sit?
Don't feel like
talking today?
Wanna play a game?
It's
a mind-reading game.
Here's how it works:
I read your mind.
If what I say is right, you
take one step towards the chair.
If what
I say is wrong,
you take one step back
towards the doorway.
If you reach the chair,
you sit down.
If you reach the door,
you can go.
Wanna play?
Okay.
When your mother and father
were first divorced,
your mom went to see a doctor
like me, and he didn't help her,
so you think I'm not
going to be able to help you.
You're worried that
she said she told him things,
things she couldn't
tell anyone else.
Secrets.
You have a secret,
but you don't want to tell me.
Your dad gave you
that watch as a present
just before he went away.
He forgot it in a drawer.
Doesn't work.
You keep pretty quiet
in school, but...
...you're a good student.
You've never really been
in any serious trouble.
We were supposed
to draw a picture.
Anything we wanted.
I drew a man...
...got hurt in the neck by
another man with a screwdriver.
You saw that on TV, Cole?
Everyone got upset.
They had a meeting.
Mom started crying.
I don't draw
like that anymore.
How do you draw now?
Draw... people smiling...
...dogs running...
...rainbows.
They don't have
meetings about rainbows.
No.
I guess they don't.
What am I thinking now?
I don't know
what you're thinking now.
I was thinking,
you're nice...
...but you can't help me.
I thought you meant
the other Italian restaurant
I asked you
to marry me in.
I'm so sorry, Anna.
I just can't seem
to keep track of time.
And I didn't have
a very good session today. I...
They're both so similar.
Same mannerisms,
same expressions, same...
...things hanging
over their head.
I think it might
be some kind of abuse.
Cole has...
scratches on his arm.
I think they might
be fingernail cuts.
Defensive cuts, maybe.
I don't know, Anna.
Maybe a teacher or a neighbor.
I don't think it's the mother.
I've seen her with him, and...
...doesn't seem to fit.
Or I could just be wrong.
Maybe he's just a kid who
likes to climb trees a lot.
Anna...
I know that I've been
a little distant. I...
I know that it makes
you mad. I just...
...feel like I'm being
given a second chance
and I don't want
it to slip away.
Anna.
Happy anniversary.
Stop looking at me.
I don't like when people
look at me like that.
Okay.
I walk this way to school
with Tommy Tammisimo.
He your best buddy?
He hates me.
Do you hate him?
No.
Did your mom set that up?
Yes.
Did you ever talk to your mom
about how things are with Tommy?
- I don't tell her things.
- Why not?
She doesn't look at me like everybody else
and I don't want her to.
- I don't want her to know.
- Know what?
That I'm a freak.
Hey.
You are not a freak.
Okay?
Don't you believe anybody that
tries to convince you of that.
That's bullshit!
You don't have to go through
your life believing that.
Okay?
Come on.
You said the "S" word.
Yeah, I know.
Sorry.
So, your Dad lives in Pittsburg
with a lady that works in a tollbooth?
What if she has
to pee when she's working?
Think she just holds it?
I don't know. I was just
thinking about that myself.
You asked a lot of questions
about Dad today. How come?
Well... sometimes we do
things to draw attention,
to express our feelings
about certain issues, uh,
divorce, whatever.
For example, a person might
leave something on a desk
for someone else to find.
Do you know what free-
association writing is, Cole?
No.
Free-association writing
is when you take
a pencil in your hand and...
...you put the pencil
to a piece of paper and you start writing.
And you don't look at what you're writing
or think about what you're writing.
You just...
keep your hand moving.
And after a while,
if you keep your hand moving
long enough, words and thoughts
start coming out that you didn't even
know you had in you.
Could be... something
you heard somewhere else, or...
...feelings you had
deep inside of you.
Have you ever done any
free-association writing, Cole?
Yes.
What did you write?
Upset words.
Did you ever write any upset
words before your father left?
I don't remember.
Can you do
something for me?
I want you to...
...think about what you want
to get out of our time together,
what our goals should be.
Something I want?
If you could change something
in your life, anything at all,
what would it be?
Instead of something I want,
can it be something
I don't want?
Okay.
I don't want
to be scared anymore.
You gonna get that?
Are you gonna get that?
-  Hey.
-  Hi.
Don't you see
enough of me at the store?
I'm on my way out to the flea market
in the Amish country, and I thought...
you'd wanna come along and show me
how to buy at one of these things.
I don't know if I can
deal with the Amish today.
You can't curse or spit
or anything around them.
I just figured maybe
you just wanted to get some air,
because you'd seemed
kind of down lately.
Um... I'm okay.
All right. Do you think that
I should stop by on my way back
and show you what
I got? 'Cause that wouldn't be a problem.
No. I... You know,
I can see 'em on Monday.
Sure. Yeah, that's fine. Understood.
Okay, so I guess
I'm gonna get going then,
- and I'll speak to you later.
- Okay.
- Don't step in horse manure.
- Well, thank you very much.
Keep moving, cheese-dick.
Can anybody guess what city
was capital of
the United States of America
from 1790 to 1800?
I'll give you a hint:
It's the city you live in.
-  Philadelphia.
- Right, right.
Philadelphia's one of the
oldest cities in this country.
A lot of generations have
lived here and died here.
Almost any place
you go in this city
has a history
and a story behind it.
Even this school
and the grounds it sits on.
Can anyone guess what
this building was used for
a hundred years ago,
before you went to school here,
before I went
to this school, even?
Yes. Cole.
They used to hang people here.
No. Uh, that...
Mm-mmm. That's not correct.
Uh, where'd you hear that?
They'd pull the people in,
crying and kissing
their families bye.
People watching...
spit at them.
U-Uh, Cole, this-this building
was a legal courthouse.
Laws were passed here,
some of the very first
laws of this country.
This whole building was
full of lawyers, lawmakers.
They were the ones
that hanged everybody.
Um...
I don't... I don't know which
one of these guys told you that,
but, um... they were
just trying to scare you.
I don't like people
looking at me like that.
Like what?
Stop it!
I, uh... I-I-I don't
know how else to look.
You're Stuttering Stanley!
Excuse me?
You talked funny when you
went to school here.
You talked funny all the way
to high school.
What?
You shouldn't look at people.
It makes them feel bad.
- How did you...
- Stop looking at me!
Who have you...
b-b-been speaking-ing to?
Stuttering Stanley!
- Stop it.
- Stuttering Stanley!
- S-S-Stop... Stop that!
- S-S-Stop it.
Stuttering Stanley!
Shut up, you f-f-f-freak!
Hey, big guy.
How's it going?
I don't wanna talk
about anything right now.
Okay.
You like magic?
Hmm?
the magic penny.
Looks like
an ordinary penny.
But I do my little
magic shake, and...
...now it's in my right hand.
But that's not the end
of the magic trick.
I do another
little shake, and...
...right there
in the vest pocket.
But that's not the end
of the magic trick.
I do another little shake...
and...
...right back in
the left hand where it started.
That isn't magic.
What are you talking about?
Of course it's magic.
You just kept the penny
in that hand the whole time.
Think so?
I didn't know you were funny.
Malcolm, sit your
cute butt down and listen up.
No doubt about it.
Anna is like my sister.
And you better make her happy.
And I'm not talking about no...
..."Mmm! This taste like
real butter" kind of happy.
I'm talking about...
What's up, girl?
"Julie Andrews,
mm-hmm, twirling around
like a mental patient on
a mountaintop" kind of happy.
Now, that's the kind
of happy I'm talking about.
Shh. Come here.
Shh. Don't tell her I told you,
but she said
she knew she love you...
from the first time
she met you on the street.
She'd do anything for you.
I love you guys.
My nose is running.
Turn it...
And then you do
the magic shake.
The penny has moved
from my pocket...
...all the way back
to the hand it started in.
That's stupid.
It's supposed to be funny.
It's stupid.
I want my penny back.
He doesn't
get invited places, so...
It's our pleasure.
Last time was a Chuck E. Cheese
party a year ago.
He hid in
one of those purple,
plastic tunnels
and didn't come out.
- Chucky who?
- Cheese. It's a kids place.
-  Excuse me.
-  Sorry.
Sir.
Madam?
Is someone
out there?
Open this door, please.
Come on.
I can't breathe.
If you can hear me,
open this door.
I swear on my life I didn't
take the master's horse.
Open this door, or I'll break
through it and grab you!
The star of the commercial
always gets his own trailer.
For what?
He needs a place to think
about his character, alone.
You only had one line.
Darren, check it out.
Oh, yeah.
My dad made me invite him.
Happy birthday, Darren.
Is there something
you wanna see in there?
No.
We're gonna
put on a pretend play.
Wanna be in it?
Okay.
It's called
Locked in the Dungeon.
Yeah, Cole, and... you get to be
the one locked in the dungeon.
Don't! Don't!
No! Don't!
-  No! No! No! No! No! No!
- Let me out!
Help! Help! Help!
- Cole?
- Oh, no!
- Help! Help!
- Cole!
- Oh, my God. Is there a key for this door?
- Help me!
Cole? Honey, honey,
can you hear me?
- Open the door!
- God!
- No!
- Oh, my God, Cole!
- Oh, my God! Help me!
- Help! Help!
The tests would indicate
he did not have a seizure.
He's doing fine.
After some rest,
he can go home tonight.
There's some cuts
and bruises on your son
- that are concerning me.
- Oh, man.
Yeah, those are from sports.
You think I hurt my child?
You think I'm a bad mother?
Mrs. Sloan over there,
she's a social worker
with the hospital,
and she's gonna ask you
a couple procedural questions.
What happened
to my child today?
Something was happening to him,
physically happening.
Something
was very wrong!
Hey.
Did your father used to
tell you bedtime stories?
Once upon a time,
there was this young prince,
and he decided that
he wanted to go for a drive.
And he got
his driver,
and they
started driving.
Driving, driving.
Driving a lot,
and, uh... um...
...they drove so much
that he fell asleep.
And...
Then he woke up, and he realized
they were still driving.
- This was a very long trip.
- Dr. Crowe?
You haven't told
bedtime stories before.
Uh, not too many, no.
Well, you have to add
some twists and stuff.
Okay. Some twists.
Like what kind of twists?
Give me an example.
Maybe they run out of gas.
They run
out of gas?
That's good, 'cause
they're driving, right?
- Okay...
- Tell me the story about why you're sad.
You think I'm sad?
What makes you think that?
Your eyes told me.
I'm not supposed to talk
about stuff like that.
Once upon a time, there was
this person named Malcolm.
He worked with children.
He loved it.
He loved it more
than anything else.
And then one night,
he found out that he made a...
...mistake with one of them.
He couldn't
help that one.
And he can't stop thinking
about it. He... can't forget.
Ever since then,
things have been different.
He's not the same person
that he used to be.
And his wife... doesn't like
the person that he's become.
They barely speak anymore.
They're like strangers.
And then one day, Malcolm
meets this wonderful little boy.
A really cool
little boy.
Reminds him a lot
of the other one.
And Malcolm decides
to try and help this new boy...
...'cause he feels that
if he can help this new boy,
be like...
helping that other one too.
How does the story end?
I don't know.
I want to tell you
my secret now.
Okay.
I see dead people.
In your dreams?
While you're awake?
Dead people, like,
in graves and coffins?
Walking around
like regular people.
They don't
see each other.
They only see
what they want to see.
They don't know they're dead.
How often do you see them?
All the time.
They're
everywhere.
You won't tell anyone
my secret, right?
No. I promise.
Will you stay here
until I fall asleep?
Of course.
Cole... has pathologies more
severe than initially assessed.
He's suffering from
visual hallucinations,
- paranoia...
...some kind of...
school-age schizophrenia.
Medication, hospitalization
may be required.
And I'm not helping him.
Hi. This is Lynn Sear,
Cole's mom.
Yeah. Uh, yeah, I-I'd like
to talk to you about your boy
and his friends keeping
their goddamn hands off my son.
Mama?
No.
Dinner is not ready!
What are
you gonna do?
Y-You can't hurt me anymore!
Neddy, you're
a terrible husband, Neddy!
Look what you
made me do! Neddy!
I'm okay. Okay. Okay.
Once there was a boy,
very different from
all the other boys.
He lived in the jungle...
...and he could speak
to the animals.
Did you think
the play sucked big time?
Heh. What?
Tommy Tammisimo acted
in a cough syrup commercial.
He said everyone was
self-conscious and unrealistic.
He said the play
sucked big time.
This Tommy kid
sounds like a real punk.
I thought the play was
excellent. Better than Cats.
- Cats?
- Never mind.
Cole, I was really interested
in what you told me
at the hospital.
I'd like to hear
more about it.
Cole?
What?
Something up there?
Cole?
I don't see anything.
Be real still.
Sometimes you feel it inside,
like you're falling
down real fast,
but you're really
just standing still.
Do you ever feel the prickly
things on the back of your neck?
Yes.
And the tiny hairs on your arm,
you know, when they stand up?
Yes.
That's them.
When they get mad...
...it gets cold.
I don't see anything.
Are you sure they're there?
Cole?
Please make them leave.
I'm workin' on it.
Come on.
Aah!
Mommy, Daddy?
My throat hurts.
Run! Run!
Pedia Ease cough suppressant.
Gentle, fast, eff...
Cole.
Oh, I don't care what they say.
This thing is broken.
Take 'em off.
I don't want them
on my table.
I saw what was in your bureau
drawer when I was cleaning.
Got something
you want to confess?
Hmm?
The bumblebee pendant?
Why do you keep taking it?
It was Grandma's.
You know, what if it broke?
You know how sad I'd be.
You'd cry 'cause you
miss Grandma so much.
That's right.
Sometimes people think
they lose things...
...and they really didn't
lose them, it just gets moved.
So, did you move
the bumblebee pendant?
Don't get mad.
So, who moved
it this time?
Maybe someone came in our house,
took the bumblebee pendant
out of my closet and placed
it nicely in your drawer.
- Maybe.
- God, I am so tired, Cole.
I'm tired in my body,
I'm tired in my mind,
I'm... tired in my heart.
I need some help. You know,
I don't know if you noticed,
but our little family
isn't doing so good.
I mean, I've been praying,
but I must not be praying right.
Looks like we're just gonna have
to answer each other's prayers.
If we can't talk to each other,
we're not gonna make it.
Now, tell me, baby.
I-I... I won't get mad, honey.
Did you take
the bumblebee pendant?
- No.
You've had enough roast beef.
You need to leave the table.
Go!
Hey, come on.
I'll show you where
my dad keeps his gun. Come on.
Sebastian, come on.
Mama?
If you're not very mad,
can I sleep
in your bed tonight?
Look at my face.
I'm not very mad.
Baby, why are you shaking?
Cole, what's wrong?
Oh, God,
please tell me!
Oh, please.
Oh.
It's Edwardian,
beautifully worked
with mine-cut diamonds
and an actual color
Burmese sapphire.
It's timeless.
Oh.
You, uh...
...got anything
a little plainer?
Plainer?
You want a plain ring to go with your
plain fiancé? Is that how it is?
No! Baby, don't...
don't get in a tizzy.
Uh...
You're so beautiful.
Y-You're like a Burmese
sapphire all by yourself.
- You don't need all that.
- Uh-huh.
Why don't you try it on and see
how you both feel about it?
There.
How does that feel?
I think this piece, um,
communicates a longing.
I imagine that
the woman who owned it
loved a man that
she couldn't be with.
Did he have wavy hair
and chestnut eyes?
- What?
- Um, I-I don't know, but...
...a lot of the pieces
in this store communicate,
and I think you should choose
a piece that speaks to you.
I think maybe when people own
things and then they pass away,
a part of themselves gets
printed on those things,
like...
like fingerprints.
I'll just wrap it up.
You don't need a guy
with a master's.
You need a wrestler with
a neck larger than his head.
No, I need
a wrestler with a master's.
- What's this?
- Happy birthday.
- From you?
- Mm-hmm.
It's a...
...first edition.
- Wow.
Oh, this is too much.
No. Took it out of
your Christmas bonus.
It's perfect, Anna.
Thanks.
What do you want
more than anything?
I don't know.
I told you what I want.
I know what I want.
I want to be able
to talk to my wife again...
...the way we used
to talk to each other...
...like there was no one
else in the world except us.
How are you gonna do that?
I can't be
your doctor anymore.
I haven't paid enough
attention to my family.
Bad things happen
when you do that.
Do you understand?
I'm going to transfer you.
I know two psychol...
Don't fail me.
Don't give up. You're the only
one who can help me. I know it.
I can't help you.
You...
Someone else can help you.
You believe me, right?
Dr. Crowe,
you believe my secret, right?
I don't know how
to answer that, Cole.
How can you help me...
...if you don't believe me?
Some magic's real.
Do you know why
you're afraid when you're alone?
I do. I do.
I'm sorry about that, Vincent.
I hope I didn't
leave you alone too long.
- Whew. It's cold in here.
Vincent, why are you crying?
You won't believe.
- I'm sorry about that, Vincent.
I hope I didn't
leave you alone too long.
- Whew. It's cold in here.
- Vincent...
No, you know what?
I never liked 'em either.
When I was a kid,
I had this blood test done,
and I threw up chili cheese
fries all over this male nurse.
Excuse me.
Dr. Reed is on line two.
Vincent, will you excuse me?
I have to take this.
- Just give me a minute, okay?
- Okay.
No entiendes.
Yo no quiero morir.
Yo no quiero morir...
- Oh, my God.
- Yo no quiero morir!
You been
running around?
Make you feel better?
I like to run around.
It's good exercise.
Do you wanna
ask me questions now?
Wanna be a lance corporal in Company M,
Third Battalion, Seventh Marines?
We're being dispatched
into the Quang Nam province.
Maybe later.
Something happened,
didn't it?
You wiggin' out?
Yes.
I think I am.
Do you know what
"yo no quiero morir" means?
It's Spanish. It means
"I don't want to die."
What do you think these ghosts
want when they talk to you?
I want you
to think about it, Cole.
I want you to think
about it really carefully.
What do you think they want?
Just help.
That's right.
That's what I think too.
They just want help,
even the scary ones.
And I think I might know
a way to make them go away.
How?
Listen to them.
What if they
don't want help?
What if they're just angry and
they just want to hurt somebody?
I don't think
that's the way it works.
How do you
know for sure?
I don't.
Hey.
Hey! Hey!
What's happening?
What's...
Cole!
What's happening to you?
Is someone hurting you?
I'll... I will kick their ass.
Cole, if they're
hurting you...
Mama, you sleep now.
Aah!
I'm feeling much better now.
D-Do you want
to tell me something?
She came a long way
to visit me, didn't she?
I guess she did.
Can you get some water?
That's her sister.
...you know, and I went through
this with my father's cancer, but...
I just can't imagine a child
being in bed for two years.
How many...
How many doctors?
- I think it was six.
- Six different doctors?
- I think so, yes.
- Oh.
I just heard the, uh... the
little one is falling ill now.
God help them.
Don't go home, okay?
I definitely won't.
Aah!
Mister?
Excuse me, mister.
Are you Kyra's daddy?
It's for you.
Sh-She wanted
to tell you something.
Oh, no! Here he comes!
Look, he's coming my way. Psst.
Would you like to dance?
Um, well, actually,
I just came with my friends.
Oh. Well, how about this?
We can dance for a little bit,
and if you don't
like the way I dance,
y-you can kick me.
Oh. Okay then.
It's time for lunch, Kyra.
- I'm feeling much better now.
- That's so great, honey.
It's time for your food.
Can I go outside
if I eat this?
I don't know. You know how
you get sick in the afternoons.
We'll see.
Don't say that
it tastes funny.
You know I don't
like to hear that.
Sammie's
mom called.
You were keeping her sick.
You liked it, she said.
She looked
out for you.
Is Kyra coming back?
Not anymore.
-  All right.
-  I think that's enough.
- That's enough makeup.
- Okay.
They're calling
for the stable boy.
Oh, we have to hurry!
Who, uh...
Who were you talking to?
Just practicing my lines.
Thanks for giving me
this part, Mr. Cunningham.
You know, when I went to school here,
there was a terrible fire in the theater.
They rebuilt the whole thing.
Yeah, I know.
Aw.
Only he who is
pure of heart
can take the sword
from the stone.
Let the boy try.
But he is a stable boy.
He cleans up after the horses.
Silence, village idiot.
Let the boy
step forward.
Hail King Arthur!
Yea!
- Hoorah!
I thought you were really
great in the play, Cole.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You know what else?
- What?
I thought Tommy Tammisimo
sucked big time.
Ha-ha-ha.
I got an idea how you
can talk to your wife.
Wait till she's asleep.
Then she'll listen to you
and she won't even know it.
I'm not gonna
see you anymore, am I?
I think we said
everything we needed to say.
Maybe it's time to say things
to someone closer to you.
Maybe we can pretend like we're
gonna see each other tomorrow.
Just for pretend.
Okay.
I'm gonna go now.
I'll see you tomorrow, Cole.
I-I'm okay, officer.
I-I'm okay.
I don't know
what happened.
Hmm.
Jeez, I hope
nobody got hurt.
You're very quiet.
You're mad I missed
the play, aren't you?
I have two jobs, baby.
You know how important
they are for us.
I'd give anything
to have been there.
I'm ready
to communicate with you now.
Communicate?
Tell you my secrets.
What is it?
You know
the accident up there?
Yeah?
Someone got hurt.
They did?
A lady.
She died.
Oh, my God.
What, you can see her?
Yes.
Where is she?
Standing
next to my window.
Cole, you're scaring me.
They scare me too sometimes.
They?
Ghosts.
You see ghosts, Cole?
They want me
to do things for them.
They...
They talk to you?
They tell you
to do things?
They're the ones
that used to hurt me.
What are you
thinking, Mama?
You think I'm a freak?
Look at my face.
I would never think
that about you. Ever.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Just let me think
for a minute.
Grandma says hi.
She says she's sorry for
taking the bumblebee pendant.
She just
likes it a lot.
What?
Grandma comes
to visit me sometimes.
Cole, that's very wrong.
- Grandma's gone, you know that.
- I know.
- She wanted me to tell you...
- Cole, please stop.
She wanted me to tell you
she saw you dance.
She said...
when you were little,
you and her
had a fight
right before
your dance recital.
You thought she didn't
come to see you dance.
She did.
She hid in the back
so you wouldn't see.
She said you
were like an angel.
She said...
...you came to the place
where they buried her...
...asked her a question.
She said the answer is...
..."Every day."
What did
you ask?
Do...
Do I make her proud?
Mama.
Hi, everybody.
As most of you know,
I'm not used to doing this,
and, uh, I promised Anna that
I'd try not to embarrass her.
I'll leave that
to her mother.
But we do want to thank
all of you for coming
and for sharing this
wonderful day with us.
It's, uh... bittersweet,
almost, for me,
because I hate
giving her up...
Anna?
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Why, Malcolm?
What?
- What is it? What?
- Why did you leave me?
I didn't leave you.
I see people.
They don't know they're dead.
How often do you see them?
All the time.
They're everywhere.
They only see
what they want to see.
Okay, Mikey.
Come on.
Give me a minute.
- Oh, God. Oh, God, honey.
- Did Vincent...
- Let me see.
It doesn't even hurt.
- Let me see. Take your hand...
Oh, God.
Okay. Okay.
Anna, I think I'm okay.
Really, I think it just went...
...went in and out. I...
It doesn't
even hurt anymore.
I think I can go now.
Just needed
to do a couple things.
I needed
to help someone.
I think I did.
And I needed
to tell you something.
You were never second.
Ever.
I love you.
You sleep now.
Everything will be
different in the morning.
Good night, Malcolm.
Good night, sweetheart.