[grunting]
[both grunting]
Stop!
[whimpers]
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Harcourt, hand me my gun.
She knows?
She was walking around with Peacemaker's
X-ray vision helmet on.
He's not gonna like that.
He's touchy about his helmets.
What the fuck?
We need to talk.
I figured it out
when a bomb exploded in Murn's face
and he barely took any damage.
I already knew he had
way more butterfly knowledge
than what was possible
from our current investigations.
I confronted him. He came clean.
My people came to Earth
because our planet was dying.
Your people? The butterflies?
- The one in Goff, she's our leader.
- "She"?
- Yes.
- Why "she"?
Well, she had a vagina.
Aliens got vaginas?
What was her real name?
Unlike humans,
we don't name our genitalia.
No, the one in Goff.
What was her real name?
You're interrogating me?
I guess.
You can't pronounce it
with a human tongue.
I suppose it'd be something like
"Eek Stack Ik Ik."
- "Eek Stack Ik Ik"?
- Yes.
This shit is getting goofy.
We liked it here.
We were gonna live out our lives.
But then Goff and the others
started planning.
- For what?
- How to dominate your world.
I was the sole dissenter.
They said I was oversensitive.
You're over sensitive?
That's when they started leeching.
Using humans in positions of power
as hosts.
- You took over someone!
- Yes.
Yeah, you killed someone,
whoever Murn really was.
I needed to stop them!
So I inhabited
the worst person I could find.
This man, Leota, he's...
He's a murderer.
But still I know his thoughts. He's...
Even he could have changed.
I know that.
I took that from him.
I took his freedom and his face.
And every day,
I dread waking up to his memories.
Does Economos know?
He knows.
But he sticks his fingers in his ears
every time it comes up.
He doesn't want Waller knowing
he's keeping something from her.
She doesn't know?
- No. And you can't tell her.
- Why?
I told you a long time ago,
you can't trust Waller.
We can't risk anything going wrong.
We have to stop them.
Now that we attacked
the bottling company,
they'll know we're on their trail.
We need to be sure they don't move
the cow before we find it.
- The cow?
- Yes.
What cow?
You forgot to tell her about the cow?
[theme song playing]
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
There's a...
- Get it on
- Get it on top
Make a move extreme
- Make a pose
- Shortcut to your dreams
Float straight to the stars
On that flying thing
- Getting high
- Getting brave
- Getting snowblind, game
- Set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon
In a world beyond
Get a beat, got a heat
On a phony string
Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
[Eagly screeching]
[Peacemaker] Yeah? What?
You got something to say?
[kids laughing]
Okay. Good.
All right, kids,
and that's how I defeated Kite Man,
one of the world's
most dangerous villains,
with only my two fists, my Desert Eagle,
and two rocket launchers.
Any questions?
Yeah, kid with the sad eyes.
You said the Blackheart Ruby
weighed 30 pounds.
Yes.
And Kite Man was riding a kite?
That's right.
Wouldn't he have crashed anyway
due to gravity?
No.
Yeah, chubster.
- Do you have a coterie of supervillains?
- No!
Any more questions?
Yeah. Gender-swapped Alfred E. Neuman.
Have you ever met the Flash?
Yeah, I met the Flash.
Like everybody else who's ever met him,
I thought was an unbearable d-bag.
What about Wonder Woman?
What about raising your hand?
Urkel.
Have you met Wonder Woman?
I've never met her,
but she did spend an entire party
eye-effing me from across the room.
- Sick.
- Dude!
Dude, I said "effing."
Any more questions?
Yeah, Canadian tuxedo.
Do you have a pet?
I do have a pet.
That's a great question.
I have a pet named Eagly. He's an eagle.
Yeah, Rubik's Cube World Champion 2025.
Why is your pet's name so unoriginal?
Why are you my least favorite kid
in this class?
Because I can see right through you,
and I think you're a loser.
[kids laughing]
[kid 1] Loser!
- [kid 2] Loser!
- Whatever.
Anybody else?
Jamil's kid.
Do you have an origin story?
You dumb fuck, you killed him.
[sobbing]
Not in the traditional sense.
Any, uh...
Any more questions?
Pasketti Arms.
Do you know Becky Coolidge?
Becky Coolidge?
That's my mom. She used to bartend
at the Starlight Lounge.
Becky Coolidge. Yeah, that's right.
I haven't seen her in, like, ten years.
I think you might be my real dad.
What?
Okay, guys, I think
Mr. Peacemaker has to go. [chuckles]
What a great show and tell, huh?
Thank you, Adiva,
for bringing your Uncle Peacemaker.
Yay! [laughing] All right.
[continues cheering]
- I appreciate you doing this, man.
- No problem.
This little Garcia kid last week
brings her uncle.
Guy's a veterinarian.
He's got, like, a sick coati.
A coyote.
A coati. It's like a South American
raccoon. They're adorable.
Motherfucking kids couldn't get enough.
My kid comes home,
she's crying her eyes out
because we've got
no relatives worth shit,
definitely none with dying coati.
I said, "Baby, don't you worry.
- Daddy knows a superhero."
- [both laugh]
"And this superhero,
before he left the hospital,
he promised he'd always be there for me
no matter what I needed."
I never said anything like that,
but okay.
As long as we make those other kids
feel like shit, right?
That's all that matters.
Sure.
There you go.
See you soon, bitch.
Or as they say in your language,
"Ching chong chikety chopsticks."
[laughs]
I think
your Google translation's off, Auggie.
That means "my haircut looks like
a donkey took a shit on my head."
See ya.
Wouldn't wanna be ya.
"Wouldn't wanna be ya"?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I pretty much nailed him there.
Not sure you needed to add...
I know, I fucked it up.
Detective Song!
What in the Sam Hill is happening here?
Captain, last night
I took all the evidence to a judge.
You took what to what?
And I was issued an arrest warrant
for Christopher Smith,
our new key suspect
in the murder of Annie Sturphausen.
We couldn't rightly have
two people in jail for the same crime.
You have got no idea
what you're fucking with here.
There's something wrong with that guy.
Get the troops together.
Let's go get Peacemaker.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
No, it's over.
Where to, boss?
I wanna go home, get a shower,
maybe have a broad over to suck my dick.
And then I'm gonna do something
I should've done a long time ago.
What's that?
Kill my fucking son.
- [engine revs]
- Damn right.
Good boy. Yeah. Good boy.
Oh, you're such a good, handsome boy.
Getting hungry there, Goff?
Yeah. Quit complaining, you goofus.
I could've fed you to Eagly.
Man, you really go through
this stuff, huh?
I'll try to swipe some more.
You cool?
How do you know you can trust him?
I don't. It's an educated guess.
Something in your gut?
I don't trust my or anyone else's gut.
I trust logic.
And Murn's helped us way too much
to be lying.
Adebayo knows Murn's a butterfly.
La, la, la, la. No, no, no, no!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I can't hear a thing.
I don't hear you. I don't hear you.
So he literally
puts his fingers in his ears.
Yeah.
- Oh.
- You have something?
Yeah. Security camera footage
from the bottling plant.
Every three days, there was a delivery
of one of these giant tanks.
It's gotta be the raw amber fluid
that they're processing, right?
Yeah, but we've gotta figure out
where it's coming from
for it to help us.
Let me check something out.
We're gonna approach with caution,
surround the trailer, and enter easy.
Peacemaker is a trained killer.
Do not hesitate to shoot him
if he shows resistance.
[knock on door]
Come in, Adrian.
How did you know it was me?
You knock in a very annoying way.
Oh. Sorry.
- Dude, you still have that thing?
- Yeah.
He tried to kill us,
and he cut off half my toe.
Yeah. Sometimes I just think
I'm insecure in my masculinity,
so I'm making up for it
by having a dangerous pet.
You know, like one of those
knuckle-dicks in Georgia
with a tiger on a leash.
Dude, my advice,
cut it out with the introspection.
The mind is a den of scorpions
better left running from, not towards.
What is Goff doing?
What the fuck?
Let's go! Move out!
[vibrating]
- What?
- I think we've got a problem.
Okay, Goff.
One tap is "yes."
Two taps is "no."
Do you understand?
Okay, Goff.
Is that a peace sign?
Oh, Goff, what's your favorite color?
Dude, it's yes or no questions.
I just said it.
Right. Okay. Yeah.
Uh, Goff, is your favorite color teal?
Bro, what the fuck?
What?
I'm gonna go through all the colors
and then eventually
we'll find out which one he likes best.
And why would you give a fuck
what his favorite color is?
And why are you starting with teal?
You don't think it's interesting
that a praying mantis-thing
has a favorite color,
and it might, unexpectedly, be teal?
That is mildly interesting, but he just
drew a peace sign on the jar.
- Don't we wanna see what's up with that?
- Yes, we do.
Goff, why did you put a peace sign
on the jar?
Yes or no. It's yes or no.
It's only fucking yes or no questions!
That's a lot of rules!
Two fucking rules! Two!
One: Yes or no.
Two: Don't be a fucking moron.
How am I supposed to follow
that second rule?
Maybe by shutting the fuck up.
- Oh, okay, I see. I see how you are.
- [vibrating]
Your preferred conversation partners
are Eagly and Goff,
neither of who are capable of speech.
Try introspection on that, motherfucker.
Sorry.
No, you're right.
I do surround myself with things
that don't talk back and maybe I just...
- You shouldn't blame yourself...
- Dude, fucking... I'm talking! Listen!
Listen!
I'm getting this weird feeling
that you're angry.
[screams]
Goff,
are the butterflies here
to eat our flesh
- like the aliens from Pitch Black?
- [Goff taps twice]
Goff, are you here to put babies in us
like in Alien?
- [Goff taps twice]
- [sighs]
Dude, you're upset about that?
Well, how else am I gonna
experience motherhood?
Mm, I don't know.
Goff, are you here so we can help you
get back home like in E. T.?
[taps twice]
Are you here so you can play us
a shitty song like in Close Encounters?
[taps twice]
[dog barking]
God damn it! Answer, man.
- I'll go over there.
- You'll never make it in time.
Have you tried Vigilante?
Quick. What are some other movies?
Uh, the Three Amigos!
Un Chien Andalou.
Porky's. Porky's Il...
With aliens. Why would I want
a list of random movies?
Well, in case we wanted
to watch a movie later.
[cell phone playing "Barbie Girl"]
Who is this?
Vigilante, have you seen Peacemaker?
"Vigilante"?
I don't know that person. That's, um...
Is that even a name? I'm...
It sounds Italian.
I'm American, so that can't even...
- What's so urgent, Murn?
- If you're at home, get the fuck out.
The police are gonna be there any second
with an arrest warrant.
Grab Goff.
Sorry, buddy.
- [Peacemaker grunts]
- [screeches]
This is the Evergreen Police Department.
Open the door and come out
with your hands up, now.
This is the Evergreen Police Department!
Open the door and come out
with your hands up, now!
Listen up.
This is the Evergreen Police Department.
Come out now, peacefully.
We have an arrest warrant
for Christopher Smith.
I repeat, come out now
with your hands up.
I'm taping Goff to me
so I have both hands free.
Clear.
God damn it.
- Toss the place.
- 10-4.
All units, suspect is gone.
Spread out
and search the surrounding area.
Knock on all trailers
and speak to the occupants
regarding suspect's possible location.
What the hell?
[exhales sharply]
Okay. Double-check that side.
Psst.
Eagly.
Eagly. Eagly.
Eagly!
Eagly?
Fitzgibbon, doesn't Smith have
a pet eagle?
That's the rumor.
I think I just saw one
jump off the roof.
What?
[mouthing] She's a cop.
She's a cock?
[whispering] She's a cop.
Gotta get the fuck out of here.
Fitz, dispatch half our guys
back into the woods.
- I think there's someone back here.
- You got it.
All right, listen up!
All right, where's your car?
I uber-ed.
Why'd you uber?
Day off. I thought we'd get wasted.
Get what?
Shit.
Stay where you are! Don't move...
[choking]
[straining]
They're here!
There they are!
Sophie!
[indistinct shouting]
Hey! Here. Hey, I'm here. Hey!
What the hell happened?
Peggy, get an ambulance!
Shit.
Freeze!
[gunshots]
[both grunting]
I told you not to do that.
Look, at worst, he's paralyzed.
Oh, shit!
Stop or I'll...
Hey. Stop right there.
Stop right there or I'll shoot!
Get it off!
[screaming]
Shit. Eagly's hardcore, man.
Stop!
There's a car for you over that hill.
Take it and get out here.
Who are you?
Do you wanna ask stupid questions
or do you wanna live?
Which one do you wanna do?
- No, please. Don't.
- No, please.
- Don't! Don't!
- Please.
[muffled gunshot]
[Eagly screeching]
[car honks]
- Why are you honking?
- Shut up.
Hey, Soph. Soph!
Jesus Christ!
You scared the shit out of me.
I think you had a seizure or something.
Fitzgibbon?
Yeah. Yeah, it's me. You all right?
Where are Peacemaker and the buffoon?
Hey, you need to sit still
until we get an ambulance here.
Soph. Hey! Soph!
Soph!
What are you doing?
- I'm calling Harcourt.
- No!
What the fuck, dude? No, no, fuck, no!
- Fuck! No biting. No biting.
- They can track these things.
No, don't... No, shit!
[screaming] Fuck!
"You're welcome, Vigilante,
for saving my life."
It was a secure phone!
They can't fucking track it.
Oh!
My bad, then. Sorry, dude.
That was a pretty big fuck-up
on my part.
Fuck, man!
I had a fuck-ton of super-cute pictures
of Eagly on there, man.
- They're irreplaceable.
- Fuck. Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry, Eagly.
[screeches]
Wait. What about the cloud?
I don't know what the cloud is!
The fucking cloud happened
when I was in prison, okay?
Everybody talks
about this fucking cloud!
They might as well be talking about
neuropsychology
or fucking cricket or Blackpink songs.
You're a little intense right now.
Like, I don't wanna be uncool,
but your face looks really weird
when it goes into
all those various angry positions.
It's like I'm looking at a Dracula.
Ah, fuck. What the fuck
are we caught up in, man?
- That guy just executed those dudes.
- [chuckles]
I know. How fucking cool was that?
Wasn't cool at all.
Well, that's a little judgmental.
One of them
was fucking unconscious, man.
Dude, we're saving the world
from a fucking alien invasion.
It's everything we've ever wanted.
It's not what I wanted!
The bigger question is,
what's going on with you?
- Me?
- We used to go out, kill bad guys.
Boom, boom, boom. No problem.
We accidentally kill the wrong person,
"Oh, shoot. Bummer. That stinks."
Then we move on.
Now suddenly you've got this weird
new-age belief that all life is sacred?
Dude, what are you doing?
- Give me your phone.
- They could be here any minute.
You smashed mine. I'm using yours.
- Mine isn't secure.
- I don't give a fuck.
- How do you know my password?
- I know my own birthday, dude.
- "Taylor Swift's sexy butt"?
- What?
Your last search.
Oh, no. That's, um,
just because I wanted
to see some pictures of her sexy butt.
I was... I was too late.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
I got here just as the...
just as the shooter was running away.
Peacemaker.
No, no, no.
No, it was a Caucasian man
about five-and-a-half feet tall.
Red hair, striped shirt
with a red tie...
Had a black mask and, uh...
I think it was...
a fedora.
He just ran off saying...
"Robble, robble."
Soph!
Hey!
Robble, robble.
Hey. Hey, Soph!
Hey, this is gonna sound weird,
but I think Locke was just describing
the fucking Hamburglar.
Striped shirt, red tie,
fedora, black mask.
That's the Hamburglar.
McDonald's mascot?
Yeah.
- It wasn't him.
- Yeah, I know it wasn't the Hamburglar,
but it's like either
that guy's so fucking stupid
and can't think of a better lie,
or he's fucking with us.
I think Locke's working with them.
"Them"? Who?
Hey, Soph, you need to lie down.
You had a concussion.
I'm fine, human.
What?
Hey. Hey, where you going?
I need to call some friends.
Friends? Hey, what friends?
- Soph?
- [engine starts]
Captain. Hey.
Found a shitload of weapons in there.
And this.
I just glanced at it.
There's some real crazy shit in there.
All right, Officer Johnson.
I'll put that into evidence.
See what else you can find.
Look around the periphery
of the trailer.
Uh...
Periphery of the trailer. Periphery.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh-huh. Okay. All right.
Okay, I got it.
They're gonna be here any minute.
Does anyone know about
Peacemaker having a diary?
What?
[whispering] Fuck.
Nothing.
My man on the inside has it.
So hopefully
that's the last we hear of it.
- Hey, you have a diary?
- No.
They found one in your trailer.
Bullshit. I got a notepad,
but I barely ever use it.
Fuck that. We've got a bit of an issue.
- We know. You're a wanted man.
- Not that. Goff got out.
- Goff?
- Yeah, we kept Goff.
You kept Goff?
Because Peacemaker
has masculinity issues.
It's like a knuckle-dick's tiger.
I didn't trust you guys,
and I kept him because I wanted answers.
And I knew he wasn't gonna get out.
But then he got out
and took over an oriental woman.
Asian.
Pretty sure she was oriental.
You're not supposed to
say "oriental" anymore. It's "Asian."
Why?
Nobody knows why. It's just bad.
They do know why, asshat.
"Oriental" insinuates "other,"
so some people consider it derogatory.
It's kind of like I need a fucking
snowflake scorecard, but fine.
Oh, the agony the straight,
white dude goes through
imprisoned in a world
where they suffer the unspeakable horror
of occasionally having to substitute
one word for another.
I said, "Fine!"
And you know what?
Maybe I find "asshat" derogatory.
Can you stop?
Now the Asian cop is Goff.
Insofar as how much
he likes teal, though, we're clueless.
God damn it, Peacemaker.
Dude, don't you talk to me
after you send
Pennywise the fucking clown out
to help us.
- Locke?
- That psychopath murdered three cops,
and one was unconscious when he did it.
Hey, I, uh, found something.
I think I know where the raw amber fluid
is coming from.
Soph, what's going on?
Nothing.
I've got paramedics coming
to check you out. They're on their way.
There's no need and no time for that.
Soph, those aren't even words!
- You've had a brain injury...
- I'm fine.
Uh...
I do feel that she was fond of you.
- Who?
- Sophie.
You?
Sure.
But in the end,
this is better for everyone.
What is?
Just enjoy the moment.
People don't realize that smiling
is different on every single head.
Every time you have to relearn it.
This is the truck that Adebayo found
visiting every three days.
[Murn] Right.
I was able to access
all the security-camera footage,
and highway-cam footage in the area,
and by stepping backwards...
find out the route of the truck.
It's consistent.
Same truck, same path, every few days.
And I was able to follow it back
all the way to the start.
It's listed as "Coverdale Ranch."
A ranch?
I'm guessing this barn is where
all the amber fluid's coming from.
That barn is not big enough to produce
enough to fill those vats every day.
Butterflies burrow.
You saw it below the Goff residence.
And at Glan Tai where I kicked that
gorilla's ass and saved all your lives.
You are really stretching out
your 15 minutes.
The source is underground.
We destroy their food source,
we destroy the butterflies.
What? How do we know that?
What the fuck is going on?
There's something weird going on
and you think me and Vigilante
are too stupid to notice.
Hey, everyone, look!
Which one's me and which one's Eagly?
Okay, you're half right.
But you score 50% on a test at school,
what do you get?
- A "D."
- An "F."
"F," all right.
School wasn't my bag. It's for dorks.
We have reason to believe that
the butterflies have a cow.
A cow?
A large animal
that they milk for amber goo,
and there's only one on the planet.
And without it, they'll die.
When were you gonna give me
that bit of information?
What is going on?
And I'm the asshole here for actually
believing we're a fucking team.
Everyone, get done
what you need to get done.
We leave at the break of dawn
for Coverdale Ranch to kill the cow.
Monster
Come on pretty monster gimme
Hunky babe with her plastic boobs
And the poison in her skin
Bleeding stitches
on the fresh cut wounds
I can feel her needle sting
Confident in her riding boots
- And behind the evil grin
- [snarls]
Beautiful like a bad tattoo
Looking like a mortal sin
- A lady unnatural and shady
- [screeches]
And I think she's like
A demon afrodisiac
I wanna she her shaking that
Shake that thing
Monster
She's my favorite monster
She's my beautiful monster
She's a monster, yeah
Come on in my bed
Come on pretty monster gimme
Real eyes cannot realize
Real lies in perfect form
Forgery by a surgery
She is more than flesh on bone
Synthesized like a Frankenstein
With a lot of silicone
Superwoman and a dirty freak
Yeah that's what turns me on
A beauty
A different kinda cutie
And I like her sexy
Artificial body parts
I wanna lick her beauty scars
She's a thing
Monster
She's my favorite monster
She's my beautiful monster
She's a monster, yeah
Come on in my bed
Come on pretty monster gimme
[all grunting]
[butterflies screeching]
[groans]
Monster
She's my favorite monster
She's my beautiful monster
She's a monster, yeah
Come on in my bed
Come on pretty monster gimme
Monster
She's my favorite monster
She's my beautiful monster
She's a monster, yeah
Come on in my bed
Come on pretty monster gimme
Monster
She's my favorite monster
She's my beautiful monster
She's a monster, yeah
Come on in my bed
Come on pretty monster gimme
Monster
She's my favorite monster
She's my beautiful monster
She's a monster, yeah
Come on in my bed
Come on pretty monster gimme
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry, Lee.
You were right.
I just got too wrapped up
in some dumb shit.
And I just wanna be home,
and be with you.
Oh, baby.
And I don't know
what's right or wrong anymore.
My mom, she made me do this thing.
What thing?
I can't say.
But I betrayed this big goof
who trusts me.
And I feel so bad.
And it's killing me.
And I think it's been stopped,
but I can't believe what I did.
And I know stuff
that my mom doesn't know.
And if I tell her, then I betray them.
And if I don't tell her,
then I betray her.
And I'm just not made for this shit.
So just... leave.
You don't owe those people.
And you don't owe your mother either.
If that's not where you belong,
then it's not where you belong.
- But the bills?
- We'll figure out some other way.
I'll borrow some from my sister.
[kisses]
Let's go back to Gotham.
It's okay.
[whirring]
Hey, did Adebayo leave?
I think she went home, yeah.
- Is she avoiding me or something?
- Why would she be avoiding you?
I don't know.
- Here.
- What is it?
It's a P90.
I put a dove of peace on it for you.
It's facing the wrong way.
Tail should be on the right.
It's super-nice, though. Thank you.
Sure.
I don't think I really care
about the dove of peace.
I just think I said that
'cause I don't wanna
kill people anymore.
No offense, but we could be taking on
dozens of those things tomorrow.
I'm not sure right now is the best time
for you to go all Mahatma on us.
No, I'm fine killing aliens.
Especially the bug ones.
Listen, I know when we first met,
I said I thought you were
a total piece of shit.
But I don't think that anymore.
No?
85% a piece of shit, maybe.
But the rest of you is...
Night, Chris.
Good night... um...
Emilia.
Good night, Emilia.
[pleasant music playing]
Dude, I thought you said
you didn't write a diary.
Among many items found in the search
of Christopher Smith's home
was a diary
written by the suspect.
Now, the diary maintains that
the world is inhabited by aliens
posing as human beings,
and it is the suspect's job
to find and kill them.
The diary links Smith not only to
the murder of Annie Sturphausen,
but directly to the murders
of Senator Royland Goff and his family,
and potentially 33 victims
at the Glan Tai Bottling Plant massacre.
But rest assured that
every police station across the country
has one mandate this morning:
Find and stop the Peacemaker
by whatever means necessary.
What the fuck?
Kiss me once
Kiss me twice
C'mon, pretty baby
Kiss me deadly
Kiss me once
Kiss me twice
C'mon, pretty baby
Kiss me deadly
Kiss me once
Kiss me twice
C'mon, pretty baby
Kiss me deadly
Kiss me once
Kiss me twice
C'mon, pretty baby
Kiss me
Kiss me deadly
Sad. Look sad. Look sad.
You fucking ass. Come on. Look sad.
[mumbling sadly]
Does this look sad?
Hey.
[laughs]
[clears throat]
Okay. Sorry, sorry. [shushes]
[sobbing]
[laughs]
Ah, look at you.