Saturday
November 12, 1955
10:03 PM
Doc!
Doc! Doc! Doc!
- Doc! Doc!
-What?
Okay, relax, Doc. It's
me. It's me! It's Marty.
No, it can't be.
I just sent you back to the future.
Yeah. No, I know. You did send me
back to the future, but I'm back.
I'm back from the future.
Great Scott!
Hey, kids, what time is it?
Howdy Doody time!
Great Scott!
It's Howdy Doody Time
Bob Smith and Howdy Do
Say Howdy Do to you
Howdy Doody time?
Date. Sunday, November 13, 1955. 7:01 a.m.
Last night's time travel experiment
was apparently a complete success.
Lightning struck the clock tower
at precisely 10:04 p.m.
sending the necessary 1.21 gigawatts
into the time vehicle,
which vanished in a brilliant flash of
light leaving a pair of fire trails behind.
I, therefore, assume
that Marty and the time vehicle
were transported forward through time
into the year 1985.
After that...
After that, I can't recall what happened.
In fact, I don't even remember
how I got home.
Perhaps the gigawatt discharge coupled
with the temporal displacement field
generated by the time vehicle caused
a disruption of my own brain waves
resulting in a condition
of momentary amnesia.
Indeed, I now recall that moments
after the time vehicle disappeared
into the future,
I saw a vision of Marty saying
he had come back from the future.
Hey, Doc!
Undoubtedly, this was some sort
of residual image...
Doc.
Doc, calm down, okay. Just calm down.
It's me. It's Marty.
No, it can't be you!
I sent you back to the future!
That's right, Doc. That's right,
but I came back again.
I came back from the future.
Don't you remember last night?
You fainted. I brought you home.
This can't be happening! You can't be here!
It doesn't make sense for you to be here!
I refuse to even believe that you are here!
Doc, I am here, and it does make sense.
Look, I came back to 1955 again with you,
the you from 1985,
'cause we had to get a book from Biff!
So once I got the book back,
you, that is the you from 1985,
were in the DeLorean,
and it got struck by lightning,
and you got sent back to 1885!
1885?
It's a very interesting story, future boy,
but there's just one little thing
that doesn't make sense.
If the me of the future is now in the past,
how could you possibly know about it?
You sent me a letter.
"Dear Marty, if my
calculations are correct,
"you will receive
this letter immediately
after you saw the
DeLorean struck by lightning.
"First, let me assure you
that I'm alive and well.
"I've been living happily
these past eight months in the year 1885.
"The lightning bolt that hit the DeLorean
caused a gigawatt overload
"which scrambled the time circuits,
activated the Flux Capacitor,
"and sent me back to 1885.
"The overload shorted out the time circuits
and destroyed the flying circuits.
"Unfortunately, the
car will never fly again."
It actually flew?
Yeah, we had a hover conversion done
in the early 21st century.
Incredible!
"I set myself up as a blacksmith as a front
"while I attempted to repair the damage
to the time circuits.
"Unfortunately, this proved impossible,
"because suitable replacement parts
will not be invented until 1947.
"However, I've gotten quite adept
at shoeing horses and fixing wagons."
1885! Amazing!
I actually end up as a blacksmith
in the Old West.
Pretty heavy, huh?
"I have buried the DeLorean
in the abandoned Delgado Mine
"adjacent to the old Boot Hill Cemetery
as shown on the enclosed map.
"Hopefully, it should remain undisturbed
and preserved until you uncover it in 1955.
"Inside, you will find repair instructions.
"My 1955 counterpart..." That's me.
"...should have no problem repairing it so
that you can drive it back to the future.
"Once you have returned to 1985,
destroy the time machine."
- Destroy it?
-Yeah. Well, it's a long story, Doc.
"Do not, I repeat, do not attempt
to come back here to get me.
"I am perfectly happy living in
the fresh air and wide-open spaces.
"And I fear that unnecessary time travel
"only risks further disruption
of the space-time continuum.
"And please take care of Einstein for me."
Einstein?
He's your dog, Doc. Einstein is
what you call your dog in 1985.
"I know you will give him a good home.
"Remember to walk him twice a day
and that he only likes canned dog food.
"These are my wishes.
Please respect them and follow them.
"And so, Marty, I now say farewell
and wish you Godspeed.
"You've been a good, kind,
and loyal friend to me,
"and you made a real difference in my life.
"I will always treasure our relationship
and think on you with fond memories,
"warm feelings,
and a special place in my heart.
"Your friend in time, Doc Emmett L. Brown.
"September 1st, 1885."
I never knew I could write
anything so touching.
I know. I know, Doc. It's beautiful.
It's all right, Copernicus.
Everything is gonna be fine.
I'm sorry, Doc.
It's all my fault you're stuck back there.
I never should've let Biff get to me.
There are plenty worse places to be
than the Old West.
I could have ended up in the Dark Ages.
They probably would have burned me
at the stake as a heretic or something.
Let's look at the map.
All right, according to this, the time
vehicle is sealed off in a side tunnel.
We may have to blast.
Whoa!
I think you woke up
the dead with that blast.
Take this camera.
I want to document everything!
This reminds me of the time I
attempted to reach the center of the Earth.
I'd been reading my favorite author,
Jules Verne.
I spent weeks preparing that expedition.
I didn't even get this far.
Of course, I was only 12 at the time.
You know, it was
the writings of Jules
Verne that had a
profound effect on my life.
It was when I was 11 that I first read
Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea.
It was then that I realized
that I must devote my life to science.
Doc, check it out. Look at this.
My initials!
Just like in
Journey to the Center of the Earth!
That means the time machine
must be right through this wall!
It's been buried in here for
70 years, two months, and 13 days.
Astounding!
"As you can see, the lightning bolt
"shorted out the time circuit
control microchip.
- "The attached..."
-Schematic.
"Schematic diagram will allow you
to build a replacement unit
"with 1955 components, thus restoring
the time machine to perfect working order."
Unbelievable that this little piece of junk
could be such a big problem.
No wonder this circuit failed.
It says, "Made in Japan."
What do you mean, Doc?
All the best stuff is made in Japan.
Unbelievable!
You know, when I was a kid,
I always wanted to be a cowboy.
And now, knowing I'm gonna spend
my future in the past,
it sounds like a wonderful way
to spend my retirement years.
It just occurred to me, Marty,
since I end up in 1885,
perhaps I'm now in the history books.
I wonder.
Could I go to the library and look
myself up in the old newspaper archives?
I don't know, Doc. You're the one
that's always saying, you know,
it's not good to know too much
about your own destiny.
You're right, Marty.
I know too much already.
Better that I not attempt to uncover
the circumstances of my own future.
Copernicus. Come on, boy!
I'll get him, Doc. Copernicus!
Copernicus, come on. Let's go home, boy.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Copernicus? Come on.
Come on, let's go home. Come on. Come on.
Doc! Doc! Come here!
Quick!
What's wrong, Marty?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
You're not far off, Doc.
Great Scott!
Check this out.
"Died September 7th, 1885." That's
one week after you wrote the letter!
"Erected in eternal memory
by his beloved Clara."
Who the hell is Clara?
Marty, please don't stand there!
Oh! Right. Sorry.
I gotta get another picture.
"Shot in the back
by Buford Tannen over a matter of $80"?
What kind of a future do you call that?
"Buford Tannen
was a notorious gunman
"whose short temper
and a tendency to drool
"earned him the nickname Mad Dog.
"He was quick on the trigger
and bragged that he had killed 12 men
"not including Indians or Chinamen."
- Does it mention me? Am I one of the 12?
-Just a minute.
"However this claim
cannot be substantiated,
"since precise records were not kept
after Tannen shot a newspaper editor
"who printed an unfavorable story
about him in 1884."
- That's why we can't find anything.
- Look.
William McFly and family. Your relatives?
My great-grandfather's name
was William. That's him. Good-looking guy.
McFlys, but no Browns.
Well, maybe it was a mistake, Doc.
Maybe that grave wasn't yours.
There could've been
another Emmett Brown back in 1885.
- No.
-I don't know.
Did you have any relatives here back then?
The Browns didn't come
to Hill Valley until 1908.
And then they were the von Brauns.
My father changed our name
during the First World War.
Doc, look.
Great Scott, it's me!
Then it is true, all of it.
It is me who goes back there and gets shot.
It's not gonna happen, Doc.
After you fix the time circuits
and put new tires on the DeLorean,
I'm going back to 1885,
and I'm bringing you home.
The clothes fit?
Yeah, everything except
the boots, Doc. They're kind of tight.
I don't know.
Are you sure this stuff is authentic?
Of course. Haven't you ever seen a Western?
Yeah, I have, Doc.
Clint Eastwood
never wore anything like this.
Clint who?
That's right. You
haven't heard of him yet.
Marty, you have to wear the boots.
You can't wear those futuristic things
back in 1885.
You shouldn't even be wearing them
here in 1955.
All right, Doc. Look, as soon as I
get there, I'll put them on. I promise.
Okay. I think we're about ready.
I put gas in the tank.
Your future clothes are packed.
Just in case,
fresh batteries for your walkie-talkies.
Oh! What about that floating device?
- Hoverboard.
-All right.
You know, Doc, it's gonna be a hell of
a long walk back to Hill Valley from here.
It's still the safest plan.
After all, we can't risk sending you back
into a populated area
or to a spot that's geographically unknown.
You don't want to crash into some tree
that once existed in the past.
This was all completely open country,
so you'll have plenty of run out space
when you arrive.
Remember, where you're going,
there are no roads.
There's a small cave
over there which will
be a perfect place to
hide the time vehicle.
Well, the new time circuit control tubes
are warmed up.
Time circuits on.
I wrote the letter on September 1st,
so we'll send you back the very next day,
September 2nd. That's a Wednesday.
September 2nd, 1885, 8:00 a.m.
I get shot on Monday the 7th,
so you have five days to locate me.
According to my letter, I'm a blacksmith,
so I probably have a shop somewhere.
All you have to do is
drive the time vehicle
directly toward that screen,
accelerating to 88 miles an hour.
Wait a minute. Doc, if I drive
straight towards the screen,
I'm gonna crash into those Indians.
Marty, you're not thinking
fourth-dimensionally.
You'll instantly be transported to 1885,
and those Indians won't even be there.
- Right.
-Well.
Good luck for both of our sakes.
See you in the future.
- You mean the past.
-Exactly.
Happy trails, Marty!
Ready, Marty?
Ready!
- Set!
-Hi-ho, Silver.
Indians!
The cave!
Charge!
Shit! The cavalry!
Damn, I ripped the fuel line.
Maggie!
Fetch some water! We got a hurt man here.
- Mom! Mom, is that you?
- -There, there now.
You've been asleep
for nearly six hours now.
I had this horrible nightmare.
I dreamed... I dreamed I was in a Western.
I was being chased by all these Indians
and a bear.
Well, you're safe and sound
here now at the McFly farm.
McFly farm?
Well, you're
my... You're my, my...
Who are you?
The name is McFly. Maggie McFly.
McFly. Maggie?
And that's Mrs. McFly,
and don't you be forgetting the Mrs.
- And what might your name be, sir?
-Well, it's...
Eastwood.
Clint Eastwood.
Well, you hit your head, Mr. Eastwood.
Not too serious, but lucky for you,
Seamus found you when he did.
Seamus.
Me husband.
You'll be excusing me, Mr. Eastwood,
while I tend to William.
William.
Oh, that's okay, Will. It's okay.
- That's William?
-Aye.
William Sean McFly, the first of
our family to be born in America.
It's okay, Will.
This here is Mr. Clint
Eastwood here visiting.
He surely likes you, Mr. Eastwood.
Maggie.
I've got supper.
I'm not one to pry
into a man's personal affairs,
but exactly how is it that
you came to be way out here
without a horse, or boots, or a hat?
Well, my car... Horse broke down,
and a bear ate my boots,
and I guess I just forgot my hat.
How could you forget a thing like your hat?
- Would you like some water?
-Yeah.
I'll tell you what I'll do, Mr. Eastwood.
I'll help you find your blacksmith friend.
You can stay the night in the barn,
and tomorrow I'll take you
as far as the railroad tracks.
You can follow them straight on into town.
I'll even give you a hat.
That's great. Thanks.
Ah...
That's my William.
Oh.
Yes.
I think you'll find the barn comfortable.
Never had any complaints about it
from the pigs.
- Mmm.
- Seamus!
- A word with you.
-Aye.
Will you hold him for a minute?
Are you sure you're not after
bringing a curse on this house
taking him in like that?
He's such a strange young man.
Aye. But I've just got a feeling
about him, Maggie,
that looking after him is the right thing
to do. That it's important.
Hey, buddy.
Look how the baby takes to him.
Little Will never takes to strangers.
It's almost as if he's connected to us.
Hey, Will.
So you're my great-grandfather.
The first McFly born in America.
And you peed on me.
- Give us some soap.
-Here you go.
Take a look and see
what just breezed in the door.
Why, I didn't know the circus was in town.
Must have got that
shirt off a dead Chinese.
What will it be, stranger?
I'll have ice water.
Ice water?
Water?
You want water, you better go dunk
your head in the horse trough out there.
In here, we pour whiskey.
- Excuse me.
-For what?
I'm trying to find the blacksmith.
Hey, McFly!
Thought I done told you never to come in...
You ain't Seamus McFly.
You look like him, though,
especially with that dog-ugly hat.
You kin to that hay barber?
What's your name, dude?
Marty...
Eastwood.
Clint Eastwood.
- What kind of stupid name is that?
-I'd say he's the runt of the litter.
Hey, now, boys, would you take a look-see
at these pearly whites?
Hell, I ain't seen teeth look that straight
that weren't store-bought.
Take a gander at them moccasins.
What kind of skins is them?
What's that writing mean?
"Nike"? What is that?
Some sort of Injun talk or something?
Bartender, I'm looking
for that no-good, cheating blacksmith.
- You seen him?
-No, sir, Mr. Tannen. I have not.
Tannen.
You're "Mad Dog" Tannen.
"Mad Dog"?
I hate that name.
I hate it, you hear?
Nobody calls me "Mad Dog"!
Especially not some duded-up,
egg-sucking gutter trash.
Dance!
Come on!
Come on, runt!
You can dance better than that!
Shit.
Whoo!
You better run, squirrel.
Get him!
Whoa!
We got ourselves a new courthouse.
High time we had a hanging!
Look at him swing.
Yeah, haven't had
a hanging in a long time!
It'll shoot the fleas off a dog's back
at 500 yards, Tannen,
and it's pointed straight at your head!
- You owe me money, blacksmith.
-How do you figure?
My horse threw a shoe.
And seeing as you was the one
that done the shoeing,
I say that makes you responsible.
Well, since you never paid me for the job,
I say that makes us even.
Wrong! See I was on my horse when it
threw the shoe, and I got throwed off!
And that caused me to bust a perfectly
good bottle of fine Kentucky red eye.
So the way I figure it, blacksmith,
you owe me $5 for the whiskey
and $75 for the horse!
That's the $80.
Look, if your horse threw a shoe,
bring him back, and I'll reshoe him.
I done shot that horse!
Well, that's your problem, Tannen.
Wrong. That's yours.
So from now on, you better be looking
behind you when you walk.
Because one day you're gonna get
a bullet in your back.
Doc!
Marty, I gave you explicit instructions
not to come here
but to go directly back to 1985.
I know, Doc, but I had to come.
But it's good to see you, Marty.
Marty, you're gonna have to do something
about those clothes.
You walk around town dressed like that,
you're liable to get shot.
Or hanged.
What idiot dressed you in that outfit?
You did.
"Shot in the back
by Buford Tannen
"over a matter of $80,
"September 7"?
That's this Monday!
Now I wish I'd paid him off.
And who's this beloved Clara?
I don't know anyone named Clara.
I don't know, Doc.
I thought maybe
she was a girlfriend of yours.
Marty, my involvement in such
a social relationship here in 1885
could result in a disruption
of the space-time continuum.
As a scientist, I can never take that risk.
Certainly not after what
we've already been through.
Emmett!
- Hello, Emmett.
- Hubert.
- It's the mayor.
-Excuse me, Emmett.
Do you remember last week
at the town meeting when you volunteered
to meet the new schoolteacher
at the station when she came in?
Oh, yes, quite so.
Well, we just got word
she's coming in tomorrow.
Here are the details for you.
- Thanks for all your help.
-Anytime, Hubert.
Oh! Her name's Miss Clayton. Clara Clayton.
Well, Doc, now we know who Clara is.
Marty, it's impossible.
The idea that I could fall in love
at first sight is romantic nonsense.
There's no scientific rationale
for that concept.
Come on, Doc. It's not science.
You meet the right girl,
it just hits you. It's like lightning.
Marty, please don't say that.
That's the way it was for me and Jennifer.
I mean,
we couldn't keep our eyes off each other.
God, Jennifer, damn.
I hope she's all right, Doc.
I can't believe
we just left her there on the porch.
Don't worry, Marty. She'll be fine.
When you burned the almanac in 1955,
the normal timeline was restored.
That means once we're back in 1985,
you just have to go over to her house
to wake her up.
Oh, Marty, turn that valve over there
all the way to the right.
Yeah, pull it all the way around.
Okay. Let's go!
- Iced tea?
-No, thanks.
It's a refrigerator.
Well, I guess Miss Clayton
will have to find other transportation.
If I never meet the
woman, there's no
possibility of a romantic
infatuation, right?
- You're the doc, Doc.
-All right.
We'll get the DeLorean
and get ourselves back to the future.
Oh, listen, Doc, I tore a hole in
the gas tank when I was landing,
so we're gonna have to patch it up
and get some gas.
You mean we're out of gas?
Yeah, it's no big deal.
We've got Mr. Fusion, right?
Mr. Fusion powers the time circuits
and the Flux Capacitor,
but the internal combustion engine
runs on ordinary gasoline.
It always has.
There's not gonna be
a gas station around here
until sometime in the next century.
Without gasoline, we can't get
the DeLorean up to 88 miles per hour.
So what do we do?
- Twenty-four!
-It's no use, Marty!
Even the fastest horse in the world
won't run more than 35, 40 miles an hour!
Bartender said
that's the strongest stuff they got.
Try it, Marty.
Give it more gas!
Damn!
It blew the fuel injection manifold.
Strong stuff, all right.
It will take me a month to rebuild it.
A month?
Doc, you're gonna get shot on Monday!
I know! I know! I know! I wish...
Wait. I've got it!
We can simply roll it down a steep hill!
Oh! We'd never find
a smooth enough surface. Unless...
Of course! Ice!
We'll wait until winter
when the lake freezes over.
Winter? Doc, what are you talking about?
Monday! It's three days away!
All right, all right, all right. Just
let's think this thing through logically.
We know it won't run under its own power.
We know we can't pull it.
But if we could figure out a way
to push it up to 88 miles an hour.
Huh?
That's it.
How fast can she go?
Why, I've had her up to 55 myself.
I heard that Fearless Frank Fargo
got one of these up to near 70
out past Verde Junction.
Do you think it's
possible to get it up to 90?
Ninety? Tarnation, son,
who'd ever need to be in such a hurry?
It's just a little bet he
and I have, that's all.
Theoretically speaking, could it be done?
Well, I suppose, if you had a straight
stretch of track with a level grade,
and you weren't hauling no cars behind you,
and if you could get the fire hot enough.
And I'm talking about hotter than
the blazes of hell and damnation itself.
Then yes, sir, it might be possible
to get her up that fast.
Tell me, when does the next train
come through here?
Monday morning at 8:00.
Here. This spur that runs off the main line
three miles out to Clayton Ravine.
It's a long stretch of level track
that will still exist in 1985.
This is where we'll push the DeLorean
with the locomotive.
Funny. This map calls Clayton Ravine
Shonash Ravine.
That must be the old Indian name for it.
It's perfect.
A nice long run that goes
clear across the bridge over the ravine,
you know, over near that
Hilldale housing development.
Right, Doc, but according to this map,
there is no bridge.
Well, Doc, we can scratch that idea.
I mean, we can't wait a year and a half
for this thing to get finished.
Marty, it's perfect.
You're just not thinking
fourth-dimensionally.
Right. Right. I have a
real problem with that.
Don't you see? The
bridge will exist in 1985.
It's safe and still in use.
Therefore, as long as we get the DeLorean
up to 88 miles an hour
before we hit the edge of the ravine,
we'll instantaneously arrive at a point
in time where the bridge is completed.
We'll have track under us
and coast safely across the ravine.
- What about the locomotive?
-It will be a spectacular wreck.
Too bad no one will be around to see it.
Help me! Help!
Great Scott!
Hurry!
Jump!
Whoa.
Oh...
Thank you, sir. You saved my...
...life.
Emmett Brown at your service, Miss...
Clayton.
Clara Clayton.
Clara!
What a beautiful name.
May I help you inside with these?
Oh, no, that won't be necessary.
I can take care of it.
- You've done more than enough already.
-But it's really no trouble.
Doc, she says it's fine,
and we got to get going.
Ma'am, good luck with your school teaching
and everything.
Clara, I'll straighten everything out
with Mr. Statler for the buckboard rental.
Don't worry about that.
I feel somewhat responsible
for what happened.
Oh.
That would be very gentlemanly of you,
Mr. Brown. Emmett.
You know, I'm almost glad
that snake spooked those horses.
Otherwise, we might never have met.
I suppose it was destiny.
Well, thank you for everything.
You're quite welcome.
I will see you again, won't I?
Of course. You'll see lots of me. I'm sure.
I have a shop in town.
I'm the local scientist,
blacksmith.
Science? What sort of science?
Astronomy? Chemistry?
Actually, I'm a student of all sciences.
Hey, Doc, we got to get going.
Oh, yes. Well, excuse us, Clara.
We have to get going.
Toodle-oo.
What do you mean,
you're gonna be seeing lots of her, Doc?
Well, I might see her
again just in passing.
Come on, Doc. Did you see the way
she was looking at you?
She did have quite a scare, right?
After all, Miss Clayton almost ended up
at the bottom of Clayton Ravine.
Clayton Ravine.
Holy shit. Hey, Doc, Clayton Ravine
was named after a teacher.
- They say she fell in there 100 years ago.
-100 years ago! That's this year!
Every kid in school knows that story,
'cause we all have teachers
we'd like to see fall into the ravine.
Great Scott!
Then she was supposed to go over
in that wagon.
Now I may have seriously altered history.
Look, Doc, what's the worst
that can happen, huh?
So they don't name the ravine after her.
Let's just get the DeLorean ready
and get the hell out of here.
I wish I'd never invented
that infernal time machine.
It's caused nothing but disaster.
Doc, Doc, this is Marty.
Do you read me? Over.
Check, Marty.
Great, Doc. These things still work.
All right, Marty. Once more,
let's go over the entire plan and layout.
I apologize for the crudity of this model,
but I just...
Yeah, I know, Doc.
It's not to scale. It's okay, Doc.
All right. Tomorrow night, Sunday,
we'll load the DeLorean
onto the tracks here, on the spur
right by the old abandoned silver mine.
The switch track is where
the spur runs off the main line
three miles out to Clayton...
Shonash Ravine.
The train leaves the station
at 8:00 Monday morning.
We'll stop it here,
uncouple the cars from the tender,
throw the switch track,
and then we'll hijack...
Borrow the locomotive and use it
to push the time machine.
According to my calculations,
we'll reach 88 miles per hour
just before we hit the edge of the ravine,
at which point we'll be instantaneously
transported back to 1985
and coast safely
across the completed bridge.
What does this mean? "Point of no return."
That's our fail-safe point. Up until there,
we have still have enough time
to stop the locomotive
before it plunges into the ravine.
But once we pass this windmill,
it's the future or bust.
Here you go, Marty.
Connect that to the positive terminal.
- All right, Marty, you all set?
-Yeah. Yeah. Go!
Train pulling out of the station!
Coming up to the switch track!
Stop at the switch track!
Throw the switch!
Pull up to the DeLorean!
Pushing the DeLorean up
to 88 miles per hour!
It couldn't be simpler.
Hello?
Emmett?
It's Clara.
Quick, cover the DeLorean!
- Hello.
-Why, hello.
This is quite a surprise.
Well, I hope I'm not disturbing anything.
Oh, no, no, we were just doing
a little model railroading.
Oh.
Emmett, when my bags
were thrown from the wagon,
my telescope was damaged.
And since you mentioned
an interest in science,
I thought you might be able
to repair it for me.
I would pay you, of course.
Oh, no, no, no.
I wouldn't think of charging you for this.
Well, let's have a look at it.
I think a lens
may be out of alignment,
because if you move it this way,
the image turns fuzzy. See?
But if you turn it the other way then...
Everything becomes...
...clear.
I could repair it right away
and have it for you tonight.
Oh, tonight is the town festival.
I wouldn't dream of having
you work on my telescope
during such an important occasion.
You are planning on attending, aren't you?
- Well, actually, ma'am, I don't think...
-Yes, of course, the festival.
Well, in that case, I'll see you
this evening at the festival, Emmett.
- Mr. Eastwood.
-Ma'am.
Thank you for taking care of my telescope.
You're quite welcome.
It's a nice telescope.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as mayor of Hill Valley,
it gives me great pleasure
to dedicate this clock
to the people of Hill County!
May it stand for all time!
Tell me when, gentlemen.
Three! Two! One!
Now!
Let the festivities begin!
You know, Marty, in a way, it's fitting
that you and I are here to witness this.
It's too bad I didn't bring my camera.
Ready, gentlemen?
The only problem is
we'll never be able to show it to anybody.
Smile, Doc.
Yee-ha!
What great music!
Yeah, it's got a beat,
and you can dance to it.
Step right up gentlemen and test
your mettle with the latest products
from Colonel Samuel Colt's Patent
Firearms Manufacturing Company
of Hartford, Connecticut.
Now, take this model, for example.
The new, improved and refined
Colt Peacemaker
selling to you tonight
for the low, low price of $12.
- Good evening.
-Evening.
You look very nice.
Thank you.
Would you like...
- Would you care to...
-I'd love to.
Young man, how about you?
You want to give it a try?
No, no. No, thanks. Hey, Doc, this...
Son!
- Sonny boy!
-The Doc can dance?
Son. Son. Son!
Hey, I just told you that even a baby
could handle this weapon.
Surely you're not afraid to try something
that a baby could do.
Hey, I'm not afraid of nothing.
Come on, then.
Let's just step up here like a man.
Now, then what you do
is you just ease that hammer back there
and squeeze off a round.
No, no, no!
Right on out there and be real smooth.
That's the way you do it.
- Listen, can I try that again?
-Yeah, go ahead.
Hey, just tell me one thing.
Where did you learn to shoot like that?
7-Eleven.
Buford, you sure that blacksmith
is gonna be at this here shindig?
Sure he's here. Everybody's here tonight.
You gentlemen will have
to check your firearms
if you want to join in on the festivities.
Who's gonna make us, tenderfoot? You?
I am.
Marshal Strickland.
I didn't know you was back in town.
If you can't read the sign, Tannen,
I presume you can read this.
Pretty tough hombre when you're pointing
a scatter gun at a man's back.
Just like you, Tannen,
I take every advantage I can get.
Now you gonna check your iron?
I was just joking with your deputy.
Of course, I'm gonna check my iron.
- We all were. Weren't we, boys?
- Yeah, right.
Tannen.
Your knife, too.
Smile, Marshal. After all, this is a party.
Only party I'll be smiling at is the
one that sees you at the end of a rope.
Have fun!
See, that's how you handle them, Son.
Never give them an inch
and maintain discipline at all times.
Remember that word, discipline.
I will, Pa.
Swing that partner
With a right big swing
Over to the side
It's the same old thing
Thank you very much.
Why, Mr. Eastwood, nice to see you.
I see you got yourself some
respectable clothes, lad, and a fine hat.
Yeah, well, a couple people didn't like
the way the other one looked on me.
Sure, and that one suits you, Mr. Eastwood.
- It's very becoming.
-Oh, thanks.
Hey, "Frisbie." Far out.
What was the meaning of that?
- It was right in front of him.
-Aye.
Swing that partner halfway round
Sashay back to the head of the set
All the way up to the head of the set
Now, bow to the partner
You're through
- Hey, that's mine!
-Not anymore.
- Give me that.
-There he is, Buford.
- Where?
-There.
Dancing with that piece of calico.
What are you gonna do, boss?
I figure if I bury this muzzle deep enough
in his back, nobody will hear the shot.
Careful, Buford.
You ain't got but one bullet with that.
I only need one.
I told you to watch your back, smithy.
Tannen, you're early.
It's a Derringer, smithy.
Small but effective.
The last time I used it,
fellow took two whole days to die.
Bled to death inside.
It was real, real painful.
That means you'll be dead
by about supper time Monday.
Excuse me. I don't know who you think
you are, but we're dancing.
Well, look at what we have here.
Ain't you gonna introduce me to the lady?
I'd like a dance.
I wouldn't give you the pleasure.
You'll just have to go ahead and shoot.
- All right.
-No, no. Emmett, I'll dance with him.
Boys, keep the blacksmith company
while I get acquainted with the filly!
I don't dance very well
when my partner has a gun in his hand.
You'll learn. You'll learn.
You know, smithy, maybe I'll just take
my $80 worth out of her!
Tannen, leave her alone!
Whoo!
Yeah, I bet there's something you can do
that's worth $80.
I believe you've underestimated me, mister.
Have I?
Ow!
Stop it! Damn you, Tannen!
No, I damn you!
I damn you to hell!
You.
Hey, lighten up, jerk!
Mighty strong words, runt!
You man enough to back them up
with more than just a pie plate?
Look, just leave my friends alone.
What's wrong, dude? You yellow?
That's what I thought. A yellow belly.
Nobody calls me yellow.
Then let's finish it right now.
Not now, Buford. Marshal's got our guns.
Like I said, we'll finish this tomorrow!
Tomorrow we're robbing the Pine City stage.
What about Monday?
We doing anything Monday?
No, Monday would be fine.
You can kill him on Monday.
I'll be back this way on Monday.
We'll settle this then.
Right there out in the street
in front of the Palace Saloon.
Yeah, right. When?
- High noon?
-Noon?
I do my killing before breakfast. 7:00!
8:00. I do my killing after breakfast.
Marty!
All right, now. Break it up.
What's all this about?
You causing trouble here, Tannen?
No trouble, Marshal.
Just a little personal matter
between me and Eastwood.
This don't concern the law.
Tonight, everything concerns the law.
Now break it up.
Any brawling, it's 15
days in the county jail.
All right, folks. Come on, this is a party.
Come on! Let's have some fun!
8:00 Monday, runt.
If you ain't here, I'll hunt you
and shoot you down like a duck.
It's "dog," Buford.
Shoot him down like a dog.
Let's go, boys!
Let these sissies have their party!
Marty, what are you doing,
saying you're gonna meet Tannen?
Hey, Doc, Doc, don't worry about it.
Monday morning 8:00 a.m.
We're gonna be gone, right?
Theoretically, yes,
but what if the train's late?
- Late?
-We'll discuss this later.
No, we'll discuss it now. Late?
What do you mean?
Thank you for your
gallantry, Mr. Eastwood.
Hey, ma'am.
Had you not interceded,
Emmett might have been shot.
Marty... Clint, I'm gonna take Clara home.
Right. Good night,
Doc. Good night, Clara.
You sure set him
straight, Mr. Eastwood.
I'm glad somebody finally got the gumption
to stand up to that son of a bitch.
You're all right in my book, Mr. Eastwood.
I'd like to buy you a drink.
Hey, listen, I don't want a drink.
- You don't have to buy me anything.
-Young man. Young man.
- It was no big deal.
-I'd like for you to have this brand-new
Colt Peacemaker and gun belt
free of charge.
- Free?
-I want everybody to know
that the gun that shot Buford Tannen
was a Colt Peacemaker!
Hey, no problem. Thanks a lot.
Of course you understand that if you lose,
I'm taking it back.
Thanks again.
You had him, Mr. Eastwood.
You could have just walked away,
and nobody would have thought
the less of you for it.
All it would have been was words,
hot air from a buffoon.
Instead, you let him rile you.
Rile you into playing his game,
his way, by his rules.
Seamus, relax. I know what I'm doing.
- He reminds me of poor Martin.
-Aye.
- Who?
-Me brother.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You have a brother named Martin McFly?
Had a brother.
Martin used to let men provoke him
into fighting.
He was concerned that people
would think him a coward if he refused.
That's how he got a Bowie knife
shoved through his belly
in a saloon in Virginia City.
Never considered the future, poor Martin.
God rest his soul.
Sure, and I hope you're considering
the future, Mr. Eastwood.
I think about it all the time.
And that crater
in the middle north west,
the one that's out there
all by itself like a starburst...
Uh-huh.
...that one's called Copernicus.
Listen to me. I feel
like I'm teaching school.
Please, continue the lesson.
I never found lunar geography
so fascinating.
You're quite knowledgeable.
When I was 11, I had diphtheria.
I was quarantined for three months.
So my father brought this telescope,
and he put it next to my bed
so I could see everything out the window.
Emmett, do you think we'll ever be able
to travel to the moon
the way we travel across the country
on trains?
Definitely. Although not for 84 years
and not on trains.
We'll have space vehicles,
capsules sent aloft with rockets.
Devices that create giant explosions.
Explosions so powerful that they just...
That they break the pull
of the Earth's gravity
and send the projectile
through outer space.
Emmett, I read that book, too!
You're quoting Jules Verne
From the Earth to the Moon.
You've read Jules Verne?
I adore Jules Verne.
So do I.
Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea.
My absolute favorite.
The first time I read that
when I was a little boy,
why, I wanted to meet Captain Nemo.
Don't tease, Emmett. You couldn't have
read that when you were a boy.
It was only first published 10 years ago.
Oh, yes. Well, I meant it made me
feel like a boy.
I never met a woman
who liked Jules Verne before.
I never ever met a man like you before.
Doc?
Hope you know what you're doing.
You talking to me?
You talking to me, Tannen?
Well, I'm the only one here.
Go ahead, make my day.
- Say good morning, Mr. Eastwood.
-Morning.
Have a cigar, Mr. Eastwood.
Anything I can do for you today,
Mr. Eastwood?
- No, that's fine.
-Good luck tomorrow, Mr. Eastwood.
- We'll be praying for you.
-Thanks.
Good morning, Mr. Eastwood.
Interest you in a new suit for tomorrow?
I'm fine. Thanks.
- Doc, what are you doing?
-Oh, nothing.
I was just out enjoying the morning air.
It's really lovely here in the morning.
Don't you think?
Yeah, it's lovely, Doc.
So listen, we've got to load the DeLorean
up and get ready to roll, all right?
Hey, look at that, the tombstone.
Marty, let me see that photograph again.
My name, it's vanished.
Hey, that's great, Doc. Don't you get it?
We're going back to the future tomorrow,
so everything's being erased.
But only my name is erased.
The tombstone itself
and the date still remain.
That doesn't make sense.
We know that this photograph represents
what will happen
if the events of today continue
to run their course into tomorrow.
- Right. So?
-Excuse me, Mr. Eastwood.
I just need to take
your measurements.
Oh, look, pal, I don't
want to buy a suit.
- No, this is for your coffin.
-My coffin?
Well, the odds are running
two to one against you.
Might as well be prepared.
So it may not be my name that's
supposed to end up on this tombstone.
It may be yours.
- Great Scott.
-I know. This is heavy.
Marty, why are you wearing that gun?
You're not considering going up
against Tannen tomorrow?
Doc, tomorrow morning
I'm going back to the future with you.
But if Buford Tannen comes looking
for trouble, I'm gonna be ready for him.
You heard what
that son of a bitch called me last night.
Marty, you can't go losing your judgment
every time someone calls you a name.
That's exactly what causes you
to get into that accident in the future.
What? What about my future?
I can't tell you. It might
make things worse.
Wait a minute.
Doc, what is wrong with my future?
Marty, we all have to make decisions
that affect the course of our lives.
You've got to do what you've got to do,
and I've got to do what I've got to do.
- Marty.
-Yeah.
- I've made a decision.
-Uh-huh.
I'm not going with you tomorrow.
I'm staying here.
What are you talking about, Doc?
There's no point in denying it.
- I'm in love with Clara.
-Oh, man.
Doc, we don't belong here.
Neither one of us.
You know, it could still be you
that gets shot tomorrow.
This tombstone could
still be in your future.
Marty, the future isn't written.
It can be changed. You know that.
Anyone can make their future
whatever they want it to be.
I can't let this one little photograph
determine my entire destiny.
I have to live my life according
to what I believe is right in my heart.
Doc, you're a scientist.
So you tell me.
What's the right thing to do up here?
You're right, Marty.
- Wow, that worked great.
-I've at least got to tell her goodbye.
Come on, Doc. Think about it.
What are you gonna say to her?
"I've got to go back to the future?"
I mean,
she's not gonna understand that, Doc.
Hell, I'm in it with you,
and I don't even understand it.
Doc, listen.
Maybe we...
I don't know,
maybe we can just take Clara with us.
To the future?
As you reminded me, Marty, I'm a scientist,
so I must be scientific about this.
I cautioned you
about disrupting the continuum
for your own personal benefit.
Therefore, I must do no less.
We shall proceed as planned,
and as soon as we return to 1985,
we'll destroy this infernal machine.
Traveling through time
has become much too painful.
It's Emmett, Clara.
Emmett, won't you come in?
No, I better not. I...
What's wrong?
I've come to say goodbye.
Goodbye? Well, where are you going?
I'm going away. And well, I'm
afraid I'll never see you again.
Emmett!
Clara, I want you to know
that I care about you deeply.
But I've realized that I don't belong here,
and I have to go back where I came from.
And where might that be?
I can't tell you.
Well, wherever you're going,
take me with you.
I can't, Clara.
I wish it didn't have to be this way,
but just believe me when I tell you
that I'll never forget
you and that I love you.
I don't understand
what you're trying to say.
Clara, I don't think there's any way
that you can understand it.
Please, Emmett. Please, I have to know.
If you sincerely do love me,
then tell me the truth.
All right then.
I'm from the future.
I came here in a time machine
that I invented,
and tomorrow I have to go back
to the year 1985.
Yes, Emmett.
I do understand.
I understand that because you know
I'm partial to the writings of Jules Verne,
you concocted those mendacities
in order to take advantage of me.
Oh! I've heard some whoppers in my day,
but the fact that you'd expect me
to entertain a notion like that
is so insulting and degrading!
All you had to say is, "I don't love you,
and I don't want to see you anymore."
That, at least, would have been respectful!
But that's not the truth.
Good to see you, too.
Emmett. What can I get you? The usual?
No, Chester, I'm gonna need something
a lot stronger than that tonight.
- Sarsaparilla.
-Whiskey, Chester.
Whiskey? Emmett, are you sure?
You know what happened to you
on the Fourth of July.
Whiskey.
Okay, I ain't your papa.
Just don't want to see you
do the wrong thing.
You can leave the bottle.
It's a woman, right?
I knew it.
I have seen that look on a man's face
a thousand times all across the country.
All I can tell you, friend,
is you'll get over her.
Oh... Clara was one in a million.
One in a billion. One in a googolplex.
The woman of my dreams,
and I've lost her for all time.
I can assure you, sir,
there are other women.
Why, if peddling this barbed wire
all across the country
has taught me one thing for certain,
is that you never know
what the future might bring.
The future.
Oh, I can tell you about the future.
Oh, man, did I sleep.
What time is it, Doc?
Doc?
Wake up!
Get up! Let's go!
I got me a runt to kill.
It's still early, boss. What's your hurry?
I'm hungry.
And in the future, we don't need horses.
We have motorized carriages
called automobiles.
If everybody's got
one of these auto whatsits,
does anybody walk or run anymore?
Of course we run,
but for recreation, for fun.
Run for fun?
What the hell kind of fun is that?
Doc! Doc!
How much has he had?
None. That's the first one,
and he hasn't touched it yet.
He just likes to hold it.
Doc! Doc! What are you doing?
I've lost her, Marty.
There's nothing left for me here.
All right, that's why you gotta come back
with me.
- Where?
-Back to the future!
- Right! Let's get going!
-Great.
Gentlemen, excuse me,
but my friend and I have to catch a train.
Here's to you, blacksmith.
- And to the future.
-Amen.
- Amen.
-Emmett, no!
Doc! Doc! Doc!
Come on, Doc. Wake up. Wake up, Doc!
- How many did he have?
-Just the one.
Just the one? Come on, Doc.
There's a fellow that
can't hold his liquor.
- Get me some coffee. Black!
-Joey, coffee!
Ma'am?
- How far does the 8:00 train go?
-San Francisco is the end of the line.
I'll take a one-way ticket.
You want to sober him up in a hurry, son,
you're gonna have to use something
a lot stronger than coffee.
Yeah, what do you suggest?
Joey, let's make some wake-up juice.
Come on, Doc, swallow. Here we go.
In about 10 minutes, he's gonna be
as sober as a priest on Sunday.
Ten minutes!
Why do we have to cut these things
so damn close?
Here, stick this clothespin on his nose.
When he opens up his mouth,
go ahead and pour it on down his gullet.
Oh, and stand back.
- He's still out!
-Oh, that? That was just a reflex action.
It's gonna take a few more minutes
for the stuff to really clear up his head.
Perfect.
Come on, Doc.
Come on, wake up, buddy.
Wake up, Doc! Come on. Come on.
Seamus, wouldn't expect
to see you here this morning.
Aye. Something inside me told me
I should be here
as if my future had
something to do with it.
He'll come around in a minute. Come on.
Come on, Doc. Let's go, Doc!
Let's wake up now, buddy. Come on.
Are you in there, Eastwood?
It's 8:00, and I'm calling you out.
It's not 8:00 yet!
It is by my watch!
Let's settle this once and for all, runt!
Or ain't you got the gumption?
Listen.
I'm not really feeling up to this today.
So I'm gonna have to forfeit.
Forfeit?
What's that mean?
- It means that you win without a fight.
-Without shooting? He can't do that.
Hey, you can't do that!
You know what I think?
I think you ain't nothing
but a gutless, yellow turd!
And I'm giving you to the count of 10
to come out here and prove I'm wrong!
One!
Doc, come on, sober up, buddy.
Let's go. Come on.
- Two!
- You better get out there, son.
I got $20 gold bet on you,
so don't let me down.
Three!
I got $30 gold bet against you,
so don't let me down.
Four!
You better face up to it, son,
because if you don't go out there...
- What?
-Five!
- What if I don't go out there?
-You're a coward.
Six!
And you'll be branded a coward
for the rest of your days!
Everybody everywhere
will say Clint Eastwood
is the biggest yellow belly in the West!
Seven!
Here!
Eight!
I already got a gun.
Nine!
Ten!
Do you hear me, runt?
I said that's 10, you gutless,
yellow pie-slinger!
He's an asshole!
I don't care what Tannen says!
And I don't care
what anybody else says either.
- Doc! Doc, you okay?
-I think so.
What a headache!
Listen, you got a
back door to this place?
Yeah, it's in the back.
Let's go, Doc.
Are you coming out here,
or do I have to come in after you?
The thing I really miss here is Tylenol.
Hey!
Reach, blacksmith!
Yes, sir, that poor fellow last night
had the worst case of broken heart
I have ever seen.
When he said he didn't know
how he could live the rest of his life
knowing how much hurt
he'd caused that little girl.
Well, I really felt for
him. I did. Right here.
Listen up, Eastwood!
I aim to shoot somebody today,
and I prefer it'd be you.
But if you're just too damn yellow,
I guess it'll just have to be
your blacksmith friend.
Forget about me, Marty, and save yourself!
You got one minute to decide.
You hear me, runt? One minute!
I've never seen a man so broken up
over a woman.
What did he say her name was? Cara? Sara?
- Clara.
-Clara.
- Excuse me.
-Ma'am?
But was this man tall
with great big, brown puppy-dog eyes
and long silvery, flowing hair?
You know him.
Emmett!
Time's up, runt!
Prepare to meet your maker, blacksmith.
Right here, Tannen!
Draw!
No!
I thought we could settle this like men.
You thought wrong, dude.
Thank you.
That was good.
- You know what I think?
-No.
- I think Buford's going to jail.
-Yeah.
Get him out of that shit.
Get them!
Buford Tannen, you're under arrest
for robbing the Pine City stage.
You got anything to say?
I hate manure.
Look!
Yes!
- The train!
-Can we make it?
We'll have to cut them off at Coyote Pass.
Hey! Hey, mister. Mr. Eastwood.
- Here's your gun, mister.
-Thanks, kid.
Seamus!
It's worth $12. Never been used.
- Maybe I'll trade it for a new hat.
-Right, and take care of that baby!
I will!
Emmett!
"Time machine."
Come on, Marty!
- Go, Doc.
-Come on. Give me your hand!
Come on, Marty.
Come on. Let's go!
Masks on.
- Reach!
-Is this a holdup?
It's a science experiment.
Stop the train just before you hit
the switch track up ahead.
- Doc!
-Uncouple the cars from the tender!
I've wanted to do that all my life.
What are these things, anyway?
My own version of Pres-to-Logs.
Compressed wood
with anthracite dust
chemically treated to
burn hotter and longer.
I use them in my forge
so I don't have to stoke it.
These three in the furnace
will ignite sequentially,
make the fire burn hotter,
kick up the boiler pressure,
and make the train go faster.
Ready to roll!
Emmett!
Marty, are the time circuits on?
Check, Doc!
Input the destination time.
October 27, 1985, 11:00 a.m.
Check. Okay, we're cruising
at a steady 25 miles an hour, Doc.
I'm throwing in the Pres-to-Logs.
Marty, the new gauge on the dashboard
will tell us the boiler temperature.
It's color-coded to indicate
when each log will fire.
Green, yellow and red.
Each detonation will be accompanied
by a sudden burst of acceleration.
Hopefully, we'll hit 88 miles per hour
before the needle gets much past 2,000.
Why? What happens after it hits 2,000?
The whole boiler explodes!
Perfect!
- Hey, Doc! We just hit 35!
-Okay, Marty. I'm coming aboard!
Emmett!
Come on. Come on.
You better hold onto something, Doc!
The yellow log is about to blow!
Golly.
We just passed 40, Doc!
Emmett!
We just passed 45, Doc! Go for it!
Fifty.
- Emmett!
-Clara!
I love you!
- Doc! Doc! What's happening?
-It's Clara! She's on the train!
Clara? Perfect.
She's in the cab! I'm going back for her!
The windmill!
Doc! The windmill! We're going past 50!
You'll never make it!
Then we'll have to take her back with us!
Keep calling out the speed!
Clara, climb out here to me!
- I don't know if I can!
-You can do it!
Just don't look down!
That's it!
Sixty miles an hour, Doc!
You're doing fine! Nice and steady!
Come on!
Just a little further!
I can't, Emmett! I'm scared!
Seventy!
Keep coming, Clara!
Come on! Come on! You're doing fine!
Come on! Nice and easy!
Don't look down! That's it!
You're doing fine!
Doc! The red log is about to blow!
Clara!
Emmett!
I'm trying to reach you!
- Clara, hold on!
-I can't!
Oh!
Doc, I'm gonna slip you the Hoverboard!
Marty, watch out!
Emmett, help!
Hold on, Clara!
Doc, ready, Doc?
Catch it!
Yes! Yes!
Emmett!
Hold on!
Yes!
Well, Doc,
it's destroyed.
Just like you wanted.
- Hey, butthead, get away...
-Watch it, Biff!
Marty, I didn't mean to scare you.
I didn't recognize you in those clothes.
- What the hell are you doing?
-Just putting on the second coat now.
You going cowboy, huh?
Come on, guys.
We're gonna be late for brunch.
Coming, Dave.
Come on, Dad, we're not gonna hold
your reservations all day.
I can't find my glasses.
- Lorraine, have you seen my glasses?
-They're in your suede jacket, honey.
Marty, what's wrong?
We thought you went to the lake.
You wore that to the lake?
Thank God you guys
are all back to normal.
Marty, who are you supposed to be?
Clint Eastwood?
Right. I gotta go get Jennifer.
I really like that hat, Marty.
Thanks, Biff.
Jennifer.
Jen.
Marty.
I had the worst nightmare.
Marty, that dream I had is so real.
It was about the future.
About us.
And you got fired.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean I got fired?
"Hilldale."
Hilldale! This is where we live.
I mean, this is where we're going to live.
Someday.
Marty, it was a dream, wasn't it?
Hey.
The big M.
- How's it hanging, McFly?
-Hey, Needles.
Nice set of wheels.
Let's see what she can do.
- Next green light.
-No, thanks.
What's the matter? Chicken?
Chicken McFly.
Whoo!
- Marty, don't.
-Grab hold of something.
Come on! Get on!
Yeah, go! Go, go, go!
Did you do that on purpose?
Yeah, you think I'm stupid enough
to race that asshole?
Jeez! I would have hit that Rolls-Royce.
It erased.
You're right. There's not much left.
Doc's never coming back.
I'm sure gonna miss him, Jen.
What the hell?
Doc!
Marty!
Doc! Doc!
Marty, it runs on steam!
Meet the family. Clara, you know.
- Hi, Marty!
-Ma'am!
These are our boys.
Jules and Verne.
Boys, this is Marty and Jennifer.
Doc, I thought I'd never see you again.
You can't keep a good scientist down.
After all, I had to come back for Einstein,
and, well, I didn't want you
to be worried about me.
Oh!
I brought you a little souvenir.
It's great, Doc. Thanks.
Dr. Brown, I brought this note
back from the future,
and now it's erased.
Of course it's erased.
But what does that mean?
It means your future
hasn't been written yet.
No one's has.
Your future is whatever you make it.
So make it a good one, both of you.
We will, Doc!
Stand back!
All right, boys, buckle up!
Hey, Doc, where are you going now?
Back to the future?
No, already been there.
THE END