Guardian, this is Omaha 4-4
on heading 158 to Laredo.
Copy, Omaha 4-4.
I'm picking up movement
on the FLIR.
Coming in for a closer look. Stand by.
This is
the United States Border Patrol.
Get on your knees and put your hands up.
Hey! Get down!
Get down! Stay down!
Get down!
This is
the United States Border Patrol.
Get on your knees
and put your hands on your head.
This is the United States Border Patrol.
Get down on your knees. Put your hands up.
Let me see your hands!
Show me your hands! Show me your hands!
Show me...
Be advised. There's been an explosion.
Officers are down.
Hey! Over here!
What do you got?
Prayer rugs.
Hey, honey. Yeah.
Stay here with me.
Just stay here. It's okay.
Just come with me slowly and quietly.
Stay here with me. Stay... Oh, God.
You don't have to do this.
You don't have to do this, please.
The scene in Kansas City tonight
is one of horror, confusion and grief.
Fifteen people, among them two children,
are so far confirmed dead
- with many more injured...
- The victim's families remain...
Haunting images of the attackers
- are coming to light from surveillance...
- Secretary of Defense James Riley
is expected
to make a statement on the attacks.
Our intense focus on recovery
and assisting the injured
and the families of those
who have been killed
is matched only by our determination
to prevent more attacks.
A message to our attackers.
Your bombs do not terrify us.
They empower us.
They empower us to send you
something that is truly terrifying:
the full weight
of the United States military.
Down, down, down on the ground!
No! Here for what?
I'm not the fighter!
Fighter...
How you doing?
You think I'm gonna
waterboard you, Bashiir?
Waterboarding is when we can't torture.
This is Africa.
I can do whatever the fuck I want here.
You're gonna answer
every question I ask you
without me harming a hair on your head.
Do you wanna know why?
Because if you don't...
I'm gonna call in
an air strike on your house.
Nice pool, by the way.
Whoever said crime doesn't pay
wasn't stealing oil tankers, were they?
Those men are Yemeni.
We have nothing to do with that.
Your fight is with ISIS, not me.
All my fights are on water.
They sure are, Bashiir.
And Yemen?
Just across the Gulf.
What a coincidence.
It's kind of tricky
for Yemeni nationalists to book
an international flight these days.
So, if their passports were fake,
they'd fly straight to Kansas City
instead of going to Mexico
and hiring coyotes to truck them
a hundred miles through the desert, right?
So, the big question is...
how'd they get to Mexico?
'Cause they sure as hell didn't fly.
No, they... traveled by ship.
A ship you didn't try and steal.
So that means someone paid you not to.
So, here's my only question, Bashiir.
Who paid you to let the ship through?
Is that your brother?
'Cause I don't want to kill the pool guy.
- Every ship smuggles people.
- Mm-hmm.
And they don't need my permission.
Yes, they fucking do.
Last chance.
- This is a bluff.
- No.
You American.
You have too many rules.
No rules today, sport, just orders.
- Go ahead, sir.
- You're green.
Roger that.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I want you to watch this.
I want you to watch it. Watch.
You have a big family, Bashiir.
Lots of brothers.
You should've chosen another line of work.
I could do this all day.
But sooner or later,
I'll get the brother
you can't live without.
I promise.
It's one more thing
pointing to the cartels.
Now, the money came
from Qasim al-Raymi's camp,
which isn't a surprise.
The ship, on the other hand,
is a Panamanian freighter, La Victorina,
registered to the Mexican
holding company Grupo Duro.
It docked at Port of Veracruz on the 18th.
Carlos Reyes' company.
The one and only.
If you need Matt home,
I can get him out at 0600 tomorrow.
I'll have a plane to Washington
ready for you in an hour.
See you tomorrow, Matt.
Smuggling terrorists seems
pretty short-sighted to me.
Border's gonna tighten like a vice now.
What happened to the price
of cocaine after 9/11, Ken?
Tight borders are good for business.
Let's go.
- Will you be home by 3:00?
- I have to stay late for the science fair.
- Do you want me to pick you up?
- I'll take the bus. Love you.
Let's go.
It's pretty good.
How much do they make?
For lookout?
Twenty, thirty a day.
Man, but that's all they're worth.
But you...
Well, shit, you know
both sides of the river.
You got a passport.
Come and go as you please.
Rafa!
Introduce me to your cousin, dumbass!
No way fucker!
You know him?
Eh.
His cousin has a big ass.
Fat ass.
What's going on?
Hide the beer.
You can name your own price, you know.
Hmm?
This is the border.
The Matamoros Cartel
pay people well to work it.
You can, uh...
start making your earn with me, cousin.
Take it.
It's yours.
So, what would I have to do?
You really ought to invest
in a little sunscreen, Matt.
If you guys would start wars
someplace cloudy, I wouldn't have to.
DOJ get an ID
on those other suicide bombers?
- Not yet.
- Uh, might want to get on that.
There's proof Reyes Cartel helped
one of them get to the border, so...
we know enough to move forward.
Mr. Secretary...
Matt Graver.
Have a seat.
What do you think
is the most valuable commodity
that cartels move across our borders?
Twenty years ago, cocaine.
Uh, today I'd have to say it'd be people.
It's a resource
they don't have to cultivate or process
and if they don't make it across,
they can pay to cross again
at three times the price of a kilo.
How would you define terrorism,
Mr. Graver?
I think that's your job, sir.
"Any individual or group
that uses violence
to achieve a political goal."
The administration believes that
the drug cartels now fit that definition.
Next week,
the President's adding drug cartels
to the list of terrorist organizations.
You can understand how that
will expand our ability to combat them.
The cartel territories
are fairly stable at the moment,
but as we learned in Iraq,
striking your enemy
is a whole hell of a lot easier
if they're fighting each other.
I'll do whatever you need.
Just point the way.
Do you have any thoughts?
I mean, I wouldn't take out
a cartel leader. Turn one cartel into 50.
Besides, killing kings
doesn't start wars, it ends them.
- That's our concern.
- Mm-hmm.
You have a location on Reyes?
- No, but the family's under surveillance.
- Is he in contact with them?
Not to our knowledge, but we assume, yes.
- Any kids?
- Two.
- What's the age of the youngest?
- Sixteen.
Sixteen?
Yeah, if you wanna start a war...
kidnap a prince.
King will start it for you.
You did this sort of thing
in the Middle East.
- Hmm.
- You think those tactics will work here?
If you want it to, sir.
Boots on the ground,
you're gonna hire on the outside.
And the same goes for your supply train
and for air support.
And I don't need to remind you
what happens
if they figure out that it's us.
Just to be clear,
you wanna see this thing through,
I'm gonna have to get... dirty.
Dirty is exactly why you're here.
What do you need?
Everything.
Drones with attack capability...
- You have Blackhawks, right?
- Mm-hmm.
I want two of those. I need logistics,
communications equipment
compatible with a SOCOM JCU.
First phase, I need a strike team,
- two snipers, I need a demolition team...
- Are you going to Ukraine?
I got Russians on the payroll, brother.
Don't put me in that position.
Where's the coup?
It's an extraction... for starters.
How much can I know?
Brother, you don't want to know.
Well, I don't need specifics,
but I have to know where they're going.
Mexico.
- You gotta be fucking kidding me.
- It's not the government.
It's cartel.
Treasury cutting the checks?
Eh, under a company in Brazil
called Rio Verde.
If it's constant action, I'm ten mil
a month in payroll and supplies.
At least.
I want 150 over cost and immunity.
Done.
Congratulations, you can afford
your own hockey team now.
You'll be easy to shop for at Christmas.
I don't celebrate Christmas.
Well, I bet you will this year.
What'd they do?
Doesn't matter.
No rules this time.
I'm turning you loose.
How loose?
Carlos Reyes.
How's that for loose?
It's your chance
to get even for your family.
You're gonna help us start a war.
With who?
Everyone.
Aah! Aah...
Aah!
Put them on.
Adiós.
Diaz was the top lawyer
for the Matamoros Cartel...
Officials suspect he was killed by a rival Cartel.
They fear further retaliation attacks...
...and a new Cartel war.
This would have been a lot easier
taking her in the house.
Could get real sloppy on the street.
Sloppy's good. Sloppy makes it look
like the cartel did it.
All right, let's go.
I'll fucking kill you!
Fucking shit!
Fucking bitch!
What are you looking at?
She started it.
Miss Reyes?
She called me a narco whore
and slapped me, so I hit her.
What would you do?
You.
- Go to the nurse.
- Mm.
No, you're not going anywhere. Sit.
Now what am I going to do with you?
- She deserved what she got.
- It's not your place to do it.
Fine.
You beat the shit out of her.
I should expel you.
Do it.
That's what I thought.
How we looking?
Got eyes on the prize?
Roger. Prize is in the tail vehicle.
Shit...
...the connection's gone.
Check your cell signals.
No signal.
Step on it!
Go back, go back! Move!
Go back, go back!
No!
No! No! No!
Muévase.
Tell your boss Carlos Reyes...
...this is what you get for fucking with the
Matamoros Cartel.
- Where we going?
- Go straight to the plane.
And don't worry about the vehicle.
- We'll take care of it.
- All right.
All right, you're gonna drive that
to the mall. Keys are in the gas flap.
You just leave them there.
- All right.
- Then you go see what's waiting for you.
- Where you got us?
- Building 5, sir.
- You're gonna take a left...
- I know where it is.
Now walk me through
what I'm watching here.
This is a map of Mexico on 100-mile grids.
And you took the subject here.
Speculation is
Reyes has a family residence
somewhere near Monterrey.
Has the Mexican police responded yet?
Yeah, local, state,
and federal police are all there now.
Satellite cannot
pick up cell chatter.
- Okay.
- Yeah, we can lock coordinates
to the cell and snag the phone number,
but we can't hear the call.
Give me a satellite feed
of the house in Mexico City.
Yeah, you got it.
What we're hoping for is a call
from this location to start a trail.
- Any family members in the house?
- No, just staff.
A teenage girl
with her own 30-room mansion.
I wish I was a teenage girl.
Pull up the incident site.
- Looks like you popped them all.
- No, we only engaged one.
One died in the crash,
and the other two we tied and left.
- That's a pretty big risk. Why do that?
- Just to see what they'd do.
Back it up.
Show me earlier.
A minute just after we left.
Yeah.
Keep going.
All right, there, good.
Call is not coming from the house,
it's coming from that fucker right there.
- Give me a live feed and find him.
- On it.
Phone! Lock in on it.
All right, locking now.
- Data link up.
- There's the king.
There it is. Start tracking.
- Come on.
- Tracking on two.
Standby. We got three.
Please don't hurt me.
Por favor.
What do you want from me?
If you let me go...
I won't tell anyone, I swear!
Use the sink if you're thirsty.
I swear... please!
- Get down!
- Police! Get down!
- Hands where I can see 'em!
- Move! Move!
Clear!
We got another one here!
Are you okay?
Are we clear?
All clear!
It's okay.
Let's go.
Am I in Texas?
Yeah, we are.
What do you want us to call you?
Isabel.
I need to ask you a question.
Did they hurt you?
What happened here?
I got in a fight at school.
So when do I get to go back home?
Well, we still need to work through
some things
to make sure we understand
all the circumstances
surrounding your abduction, okay?
But you're safe.
So hang in there,
we're gonna get you home very soon.
Alicia will look after you.
And if you need anything, just ask her.
We put the girl in the middle
of Matamoros territory,
and Reyes will start the fireworks.
What's a good spot where we can leave her?
We'll hold her
in a federal police depot in Méndez.
We're deep enough in Matamoros land
that they'll have to fight their way out
if they come looking for her.
Where do I say you found her?
Oh, say we raided a safe house
in Brownsville and found her there.
Matamoros Cartel
is very strong in this area.
Reyes will have trouble
getting his men through.
Ah, they'll let his men through.
Getting back out will be their problem.
When would you bring her across?
Well, now that we've got the cartels
at each other's throats,
the sooner the better.
Secret won't keep long.
Uh, there's no secrets in Mexico.
Why do you think I'm driving armor?
Can you get me cleared for that?
Will do.
Federal police will meet you
at the border with an escort.
- Thanks.
- Suerte.
Any excuse to fuck with
Carlos Reyes is a good thing.
Good luck, brother.
Still amazes me.
The appetite of this place.
Yeah, well, welcome to America.
- You all right?
- What the fuck?
Hey! Why don't you keep
your fucking eyes peeled?
Ah, you can't even tell
they're gangbangers anymore.
I've got a problem.
Either be home before dawn
or my dad will get mad.
Oh, get the fuck out, dude, no.
No, no, no. You got a new daddy now.
All right?
When you meet him, act like a fucking man.
You ready to be a man, right?
All right, yes, dude. Shit.
Just wait here
till I come get you, all right?
Come on.
I'm telling you to find him.
Get it together you moron.
Gallo
So this is your American cousin.
Welcome.
Come on, don't be afraid. Sit down.
- How are you?
- Good.
- What's your name?
- Miguel.
I need someone trustworthy.
I don't give a shit. Find him!
You deal with this idiot.
I need more migrants in bus thirty-three.
Fuck.
You ever heard of koi fish?
- No.
- No?
I have a pond at home with
a shitload of koi fish in it.
They're huge, all different colors.
But my favorite is a fish this fucking big.
I call him Santa Claus, because he's so fucking fat.
When I find the mother of
that guy who fucked up...
I'm going to cut her to pieces...
...and feed her to Santa Claus.
So no fuck-ups, right?
- No. No.
- No?
You'll make the border crossing, right?
I can see you're someone I can trust.
You'll make more money
than your dad does in a year.
It's a deal then.
Sí.
How you feeling?
I'd feel better if someone
actually told me what was going on.
We're turning you over
to the Mexican army.
They'll arrange
to take you back to your father.
Let's go.
I'm gonna need you to put this on.
Load up!
Loading up!
Heads up!
I have seven Mexican police vehicles
located at the border checkpoint waiting.
They're moving and forming up
in your configuration at this time.
It's a nice day for a drive, huh?
Ah, beautiful day.
Blue skies, large-caliber weapons...
I love getting out of the office.
Air, how are we looking?
Clear on both sides.
You see no vehicles?
Nothing but desert. You're clear.
What's your field of view?
Ten miles in every direction.
Mexico Feds said
that the road would be clear.
- Looks like they're keeping their word.
- All right, copy that.
Why weren't we stopped at the border?
'Cause I'm special.
I thought you were policemen.
You're soldiers.
You know, we saved you. Why don't you
just sit back and be grateful?
Oscar-One,
paved road ends half a mile ahead.
Wait, what?
Paved road ends in half a klick.
Road isn't paved ahead.
You got your thermal?
Yeah, in my bag in the back.
You gotta take the wheel.
All right.
Got it.
Oh, shit.
Nothing's ever easy.
I got it.
Shit.
I got no vis.
This fucker's speeding up.
Well, he's not stupid.
Stay on his ass.
Dirt roads make me nervous.
Air, I'm blind here.
Road's clear.
No vehicles, no movement, left or right.
All right, anything?
Shit. Oscar-One,
incoming on your right.
- Air, I see nothing.
- Contact right.
I don't see anything.
All down! Down!
Stuck! I'm stuck!
Aw, come on!
Left side, hundred meters!
Take him out!
Roger that. Heads down!
Heads down!
We're stuck. We're stuck.
Go! Go! Go!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Clear!
Federal Police! Help!
Clear.
- Drop your weapon.
- Them, over there.
Sir!
Spread out!
Lower your weapons!
Please don't shoot!
Put 'em down, guys! Easy, easy.
- ¡Abajo!
- Ayuda.
Easy, guys, easy.
- Down, down.
- ¡Ayuda!
Help, please, we need help!
We're Federal Police!
Fuck!
- Shit.
- Fuckin' Mexican police shot me?
You all right?
Oh, shit.
- I'm good. It caught the plate.
- All right. We clear?
Sir! We have police vehicles
approaching from the south.
Five klicks out.
All right, load up!
Come on. Load up!
Where is she?
New mission! Gather round! New mission!
Uh-uh, no time for that.
Head north. I'll find her.
Okay. Go.
All right, we got company
three klicks out, coming from the south.
Grab that Humvee, pull this thing out.
Go! Now! Now!
Come on, guys! Now!
Go, go! Let's go!
Let's go! Move it!
Take this.
All right?
Send me a signal when you get
to the border, we'll come and get you.
All right?
Let's go, let's go! Let's move it!
All right, everyone in their vehicles!
Air, we need a medevac
from rally point alpha.
Contact 47th Med at Laughlin.
Roger that, Oscar-One.
Be advised, you have police vehicles
approaching your six in a Code 3.
Oh, that's great.
Police approaching our six fast.
Air, we need a lane clear at the border.
No bullshit.
Anybody gets in our way,
we drive right through them.
Border coming up fast. Border.
¡Oye!
Isabel?
No...
No!
Get in.
Nothing's going to happen to you.
Who kidnapped me?
Your father has a lot of enemies.
And you're one of them?
Yes, I am.
You're gonna need stitches.
Yeah. Lucky for me,
I'll still need them tomorrow.
Miss Sunshine on your six.
Hey. Fuckin' Mondays, huh?
Can we go somewhere that's private?
All right.
- Can you give me a sec?
- Ma'am.
My source is with her right now.
She'll be back in an hour.
- That's not what I'm talking about.
- It was a green on blue, Cynthia.
There was no other option.
You wanted Afghanistan, now you got it.
This isn't Afghanistan,
this is our fucking neighbor!
There are 54 million Americans
with relatives there...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...and they're all sitting around
watching footage
of dead Mexican police on Fox News.
The police were the ambush.
- Oh, yeah, okay.
- We had no choice.
- All...
- They attacked us.
Doesn't matter. POTUS doesn't have
the stomach for this.
- He shut us down.
- What did you say?
We're shut down.
I did my fuckin' job, you do yours.
You sit that fuckin' coward down,
and you explain to him...
This is how we win.
He's not worried about winning.
He's worried about
being fucking impeached,
because you killed
two dozen Mexican police.
Who worked for Reyes.
Spin it. Do your job.
This only strengthens our position.
We don't have a position, Matt.
Because we're not
supposed to fucking be there.
Your objective was to start a war
with Mexican cartels,
not with the Mexican government.
You know what?
This... This is why nothing ever changes.
You think change is the goal? Really?
You've been doing this
too long to believe that.
Hello, sir, sorry to bother you.
We're lost.
No need to be afraid.
I'm not a Mafioso.
My name is A-L-E-J-A - N-D-R-O.
What's your name?
Sí.
A-N-G-E-L.
Angel...
We need food and water...
And a place to rest.
If you help us...
I can pay you.
She's the girl on TV,
the one they kidnapped.
Help me... help her.
How do you know how to sign?
My daughter.
She's deaf?
She was.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you hold her
someplace in Mexico?
We don't have the infrastructure
for that, sir.
Mission security
would be almost impossible.
- Was this your mission?
- No, sir.
Then why are you answering?
Mr. Graver?
We don't have
the infrastructure for that, sir.
Mission security
would be almost impossible.
And this girl was witness
to all aspects of the mission, correct?
No, she was shielded from the kidnapping.
What about the 25 Mexican police officers
that were killed, on foreign soil,
all of which she witnessed?
The ones who attacked us? Yes, sir.
Where is she?
I have a source
bringing her to the border.
Do we have an exact location?
That question is for you, Mr. Forsing.
We don't know her whereabouts, sir,
but he has a beacon.
He'll activate it
as soon as he gets close to the border.
If they can make it to the border.
Which is a chance we cannot take.
Cynthia.
Yes, sir?
You handle it from here.
We can't risk her falling
into the wrong hands.
When the beacon's activated,
your team takes them. You understand?
Clean the scene.
When I say clean, gentlemen,
I mean spotless.
Your operative included.
Do you know
how hard he was to make?
I could throw a stick across the river
and hit 50 grieving fathers.
Make another one.
Can't do that.
Well, look who doesn't have
the stomach for it now.
Oh, who are you to question me after
all the shit that I've eaten for you?
We ID'd the other bombers, Matt.
They're US citizens.
- They're from New Jersey.
- Doesn't change anything.
It changes the fucking narrative!
Is the baby deaf?
No.
Different worlds?
Different worlds.
I understand.
Hey.
You got the girl?
She's with me now, yeah.
They want me to cut ties.
You've got to get rid of her.
I can't do that.
What are you telling me?
Not this one.
Help me get her across,
and we can decide what to do with her.
Uh-uh. Don't put me in that situation.
If they're cutting ties,
you're already in that situation.
If she stays here, she'll be killed.
Help me get her across.
I can't help you do that.
You gotta do what you gotta do.
I'll figure it out.
Good luck.
I gotta get you north.
See, the flashing light is you. All right?
That red line, that's your path.
- Okay.
- Don't get that wet.
Everybody off.
Keep it safe for a bit.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
They're sheep.
Treat them like it.
Siganme.
¡Rápido!
Help!
Leave her!
Follow me!
We're here.
Move it!
Follow the trail to the road.
Your ride's waiting.
It's okay.
Come on.
Show me a job that pays better
and I'll do it.
Where are you headed, baby?
Get me to the grocery store on Trenton.
I can walk from there.
Why does a soldier know sign language?
My daughter was deaf.
I know who you are.
You're the attorney
whose family they killed.
Not "they."
My father.
A man who worked for him.
Why?
To send a message.
Now you hunt them...
so you won't be a message.
I will always be a message.
Only now, the message is different.
Is the border hard to cross?
It could be...
for Isabel Reyes.
From now on,
your name is Carina.
My name is Carina.
You come from Oaxaca.
Now if anyone asks who I am...
...say you're paying me
to pretend to be your father.
Why not just say you're my father?
Because your lies will be
different from mine.
Now we have the same lie.
Give me your shoe.
What's that?
A GPS transmitter.
In case we get separated.
Put on your shoe.
Signal was activated at 1939,
heading northeast of Reynosa.
- I'm sending another team to finish this.
- No. I'll do it.
'Cause if I don't,
he'll probably come and kill you.
So many.
That's how it is.
Who should I talk to?
He'll be here soon.
Good morning, future Americans, how are we?
Has everyone paid?
You?
No.
Do you know how much it is?
A thousand for the both of us.
Each.
I still need something for the other side.
You don't get to discuss it.
Children go in a different bus.
Oh...
We travel together.
Here's a thousand.
Here's another.
OK, fine.
Very good.
Everyone on the blue bus.
You two, travelling together.
With your kid, go on.
The rest of you, wait here.
There's interference on the road.
- Are the vehicles unmarked or police?
- Unmarked.
ETA to target?
Twenty-five minutes.
Almost there, friends, paradise is coming.
Manos arriba.
You have a gun?
Yes.
Get up.
Búscalo.
Siéntate.
What do you have in the bag?
Drugs?
No.
Everyone out!
Move it, move it.
Look what I found.
Migrants don't carry guns.
Is it him?
Yes.
Were you in Texas a couple of days ago?
No, I wasn't.
No?
My people don't lie, especially not to me.
Take Isabel Reyes to my truck.
So what exactly are you up to?
Taking a holiday at the border?
No.
We're escaping a bad situation.
Our only option was to cross the border.
I'm taking the girl back to her mother.
You guys have come across someone
with a lot of value...
...but also very dangerous...
...for all of you and your loved ones.
If you harm the girl, you guys will be
starting a new war...
...that you can't back out of.
Or we can make a phone call
and ensure the safety of everyone.
That way, everyone stays clean
and we can avoid any trouble.
You work for Carlos Reyes or what?
It's as simple as that, brother.
Don't be afraid. We're here to protect you.
Who is that you're travelling with?
Don't know.
I hired him...
...to pretend to be my father.
Your friend says he works for Carlos Reyes.
So does he work for your dad?
Huh?
Yes.
So how do we do this?
We call my guy and he
connects us to the boss.
Then call him.
No! No! No! No!
No!
That's him. ETA?
Fifteen minutes.
Get us there in ten...
I can't have the girl talk.
Hang on back there.
Gonna get bumpy.
End of the road, friend.
You're going to die like an animal...
...at the hands of a child.
José.
No!
This is what you gotta do to be a hitman.
Shoot him.
Take it so you can be a soldier.
Let me do it. He's just a kid.
He can do it.
Be brave, no fear.
Glad we didn't have to do that.
What about the girl?
Two minutes out.
Matt?
Base, what's subject's
exact location inside the car?
Subject is back seat, right side
behind the passenger.
Prize is passenger side,
second seat, green Expedition.
Rules of engagement?
Fuck it all.
Wipe it clean.
Javi, don't shoot! Just be ready!
Stand up! Stand up!
What are you doing?
Matt!
You're fucking us!
- She said spotless.
- Fuck 'em all.
She'll go into witness protection.
Sit down.
So you wanna be a sicario.
Let's talk about your future.