Introduce me to your cousin, dumbass!
No way fucker!
You know him?
His cousin has a big ass.
Put them on.
Diaz was the top lawyer
for the Matamoros Cartel...
Officials suspect he was killed by a rival Cartel.
They fear further retaliation attacks...
...and a new Cartel war.
I'll fucking kill you!
Fucking bitch!
What are you looking at?
Shit...
...the connection's gone.
Check your cell signals.
No signal.
Step on it!
Tell your boss Carlos Reyes...
...this is what you get for fucking with the
Matamoros Cartel.
Please don't hurt me.
What do you want from me?
If you let me go...
I won't tell anyone, I swear!
Use the sink if you're thirsty.
I swear... please!
Any excuse to fuck with
Carlos Reyes is a good thing.
Good luck, brother.
I'm telling you to find him.
Get it together you moron.
- Gallo
So this is your American cousin.
Come on, don't be afraid. Sit down.
How are you?
- Good.
What's your name?
- Miguel.
I need someone trustworthy.
I don't give a shit. Find him!
You deal with this idiot.
I need more migrants in bus thirty-three.
Fuck.
You ever heard of koi fish?
I have a pond at home with
a shitload of koi fish in it.
They're huge, all different colors.
But my favorite is a fish this fucking big.
I call him Santa Claus, because he's so fucking fat.
When I find the mother of
that guy who fucked up...
I'm going to cut her to pieces...
...and feed her to Santa Claus.
So no fuck-ups, right?
You'll make the border crossing, right?
I can see you're someone I can trust.
You'll make more money
than your dad does in a year.
It's a deal then.
Federal Police! Help!
- Lower your weapons!
- Please don't shoot!
Help, please, we need help!
- We're Federal Police!
Nothing's going to happen to you.
Hello, sir, sorry to bother you.
We're lost.
No need to be afraid.
I'm not a Mafioso.
My name is A-L-E-J-A-N-D-R-O.
What's your name?
A-N-G-E-L.
Angel...
We need food and water...
And a place to rest.
If you help us...
I can pay you.
She's the girl on TV,
the one they kidnapped.
Help me... help her.
How do you know how to sign?
My daughter.
She's deaf?
She was.
I'm sorry.
Is the baby deaf?
No.
Different worlds?
Different worlds.
I understand.
Everybody off.
Help!
Leave her!
Follow me!
We're here.
Move it!
My name is Carina.
You come from Oaxaca.
Now if anyone asks who I am...
...say you're paying me
to pretend to be your father.
Why not just say you're my father?
Because your lies will be
different from mine.
Now we have the same lie.
Give me your shoe.
What's that?
A GPS transmitter.
In case we get separated.
So many.
That's how it is.
Who should I talk to?
He'll be here soon.
Good morning, future Americans, how are we?
Has everyone paid?
You?
No.
Do you know how much it is?
A thousand for the both of us.
Each.
I still need something for the other side.
You don't get to discuss it.
Children go in a different bus.
We travel together.
Here's a thousand.
Here's another.
OK, fine.
Very good.
Everyone on the blue bus.
You two, travelling together.
With your kid, go on.
The rest of you, wait here.
Almost there, friends, paradise is coming.
You have a gun?
Yes.
Get up.
What do you have in the bag?
Drugs?
Everyone out!
Move it, move it.
Look what I found.
Migrants don't carry guns.
Is it him?
Yes.
Were you in Texas a couple of days ago?
No, I wasn't.
My people don't lie, especially not to me.
Take Isabel Reyes to my truck.
So what exactly are you up to?
Taking a holiday at the border?
We're escaping a bad situation.
Our only option was to cross the border.
I'm taking the girl back to her mother.
You guys have come across someone
with a lot of value...
...but also very dangerous...
...for all of you and your loved ones.
If you harm the girl, you guys will be
starting a new war...
...that you can't back out of.
Or we can make a phone call and ensure the safety of everyone.
That way, everyone stays clean
and we can avoid any trouble.
You work for Carlos Reyes or what?
It's as simple as that, brother.
Don't be afraid. We're here to protect you.
Who is that you're travelling with?
Don't know.
I hired him...
...to pretend to be my father.
Your friend says he works for Carlos Reyes.
So does he work for your dad?
Yes.
So how do we do this?
We call my guy and he
connects us to the boss.
Then call him.
End of the road, friend.
You're going to die like an animal...
...at the hands of a child.
This is what you gotta do to be a hitman.
Shoot him.
Take it so you can be a soldier.
Let me do it. He's just a kid.
He can do it.
Be brave, no fear.
Jawi, don't shoot! Just be ready!