When was the last time
you spoke with Cassian Andor?
(GRUNTS)
MAARVA: Ferrix has been
hiding long enough.
CASSIAN: So now
you're taking on the Empire?
What's left to keep you here?
The Rebellion.
Did he tell you?
He's writin' a manifesto.
You're my ideal reader.
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
He said to give this to you.
So, searching for a more
fluid banking situation, are we?
What will it cost?
I have a 14-year-old son.
I'd like to bring him with me.
-I'm not asking for betrothal.
-Then what are we talking about?
DAVO: An introduction.
Your daughter's 13.
She'll soon come of age.
Don't tell me you're taking proposals.
I'm in so much trouble, Vel.
ISB knows Kreegyr's plan.
They'll be waiting for him.
-You think it's worth losing Kreegyr?
-I did.
SERGEANT MOSK: (OVER SPEAKER)
Calling about Andor.
You wanted news if I had it.
Yes. Please, go on.
The mother.
She's passed away.
He might show up at the funeral.
-OFFICER: They just moved the body.
-What happens now?
TIGO: As a prominent citizen of Ferrix,
she rates a big send-off.
They'll want to close Rix Road.
You're going to give them a permit.
XANWAN: Cass, I'm sorry.
Your mother's dead.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIZZLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(WARBLING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SHUDDERS)
(WHIRRING)
You're here.
Welcome. And just in time for dinner.
I'll eat later.
I want to get changed,
take a walk around the town.
I'll pull an escort.
No need.
Corv will take me.
Keep it small.
As you wish.
(CRACKLING)
(WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
-BRASSO: Xan.
-Hey.
Looked like you were wrapping up,
so I thought I'd wait.
-How long you been here?
-I spoke to Cassian.
-What?
-He called the shop.
How?
Picked up the old box line
and there he was.
-(WHISPERS) Where?
-I don't know. I...
-Where is he?
-He wouldn't say.
Does he know about Maarva?
Yeah, he does now.
It was a very short conversation.
-He asked about the funeral.
-Let's walk.
-Who else knows this?
-No one.
Keep it that way.
Can't be too careful.
They're watching Maarva's.
Could be anywhere.
He'd be insane to come back now.
I hope you told him that.
Like I said, it was a very short call.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(METAL SCRAPING)
(CREAKS)
NURCHI: I can't stop thinkin' about
this whole Maarva situation.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Imagine losing you mother like this.
I couldn't stand it.
Not being there for your mom.
Have Brasso place her stone,
just breaks your heart, right?
You gotta feel for Cassian.
I'd be losing my mind.
Want another?
XANWAN: Maybe just one.
NURCHI: Why worry it though? (CHUCKLES)
It's not like he knows about it.
Guarantee you,
he's got no idea what's going on.
Bank on that.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Hey.
You know something I don't?
Do me a favor, keep it that way.
Hey.
We'll have another round.
(SIGHS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(METAL CLICKS)
(CLICKING)
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(EXHALES)
(PERRIN SIGHS)
I thought you left without me.
-Crossed my mind.
-Mmm.
-I looked for you but, uh...
-I'm sure.
Kloris, we'd like privacy, please.
KLORIS: Ma'am.
PERRIN: (SIGHS) What now?
(SIGHS)
You're gambling again.
-Nonsense.
-And here, in Coruscant.
PERRIN: That's ridiculous.
Do you have any idea
how tired of this I am?
-(BEEPS)
-PERRIN: (OVER SPEAKER) It's a lie.
It's total fantasy.
Who's telling you this?
-Please.
-PERRIN: No, I'm serious.
Perrin, please.
-Who is saying this?
-MON: Just don't.
We'll go back there, right now.
We'll put it to an end.
We will not.
I've been shamed enough for one night.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
You can't live without a casino? Fine.
You go to Canto Bight
and do whatever it is you need to do.
But not here.
You promised.
-I've kept my promise!
-Keep your voice down.
PERRIN: (OVER SPEAKER) He can't hear me.
This is wrong, Mon.
This is people trying to take you down
by coming after me.
You tell me who's saying this
and I'll tell you why.
Oh, please.
Where would I get the money?
That's the question
that scares me the most.
Someone's lying to you.
On that, we can agree.
(SIGHS)
(CINTA GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS) You're here.
I couldn't remember
if I'd locked the door,
if you'd even remember how to get here.
-And here I am.
-CINTA: I was on my way to pick you up.
This guy I've been watching, he's ISB.
(WHIRRING)
CINTA: He's their guy in town.
His boss showed up tonight.
Good to see you too.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
An ISB supervisor came in tonight.
A woman.
Here. Now.
I was on my way to pick you up
when they left the hotel
dressed like locals.
-(BEEPS)
-I had to follow.
They're getting ready, Vel.
They must know Andor's coming.
You did the right thing.
CINTA: We have to get there first.
-I know.
-Everything depends on it.
I said I know.
Come away from the window.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
CLEM: Here's the thing, Cassian.
The man who sees everything
is more blessed than cursed.
-(METAL CLATTERS)
-CLEM: Look at that. Here we go.
Stand back, let it drip.
-(SIGHS)
-(MUSIC PLAYING)
Look how quickly that's cleaned up.
Hard to believe, right?
Two minutes.
No longer, no shorter.
You know why
they don't make these anymore?
'Cause they'd rather sell you
a brand new system at ten times the price.
I mean, how many we got?
60? 70 of them?
Just sittin' there.
Five hundred credits each.
People don't look down
to where they should.
They don't look down,
they don't look past the rust.
Not us though, eh?
Eyes open, possibilities everywhere.
Just need to get this cleaned up
before Maarva find us
doing this in the house.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(PANTING)
(HOUNDS GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(BARKING)
MAN: Who's there?
(PANTING)
-MAN: Cass?
-CASSIAN: Pegla?
PEGLA: Down, now!
(HOUNDS GRUNT)
Huh. (PANTING)
PEGLA: I don't believe it. (EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
Hey.
I'm just...
I'm so sorry.
I loved your mom, I really did.
I know.
It's good to see ya.
What are you doing here?
Just keepin' an eye
on the place till we sell it.
CASSIAN: Sell it?
-Where's Bix?
-(GRUNTS)
Where is she?
Cass... (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SHUDDERS)
(SOLEMN MUSIC PLAYING)
NEMIK: "There will be times
when the struggle seems impossible.
"I know this already.
"Alone, unsure,
-"dwarfed by the scale of the enemy.
-(SHUDDERS)
NEMIK: "Remember this.
Freedom is a pure idea.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
NEMIK: "It occurs spontaneously
and without instruction.
"Random acts of insurrection are occurring
constantly throughout the galaxy.
"There are whole armies,
battalions that have no idea
"that they've already
enlisted in the cause.
"Remember that the frontier
of the Rebellion is everywhere.
"And even the smallest act of insurrection
pushes our lines forward.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
NEMIK: "And then remember this.
"The Imperial need
for control is so desperate
"because it is so unnatural.
"Tyranny requires constant effort.
"It breaks, it leaks.
"Authority is brittle.
"Oppression is the mask of fear.
"Remember that.
"And know this,
"the day will come
when all these skirmishes and battles,
"these moments of defiance
"will have flooded the banks
of the Empire's authority
"and then there will be one too many.
"One single thing will break the siege.
(RAIN PATTERING)
NEMIK: "Remember this.
"Try."
TIGO: We've loosened air traffic
as you requested.
Pulled back our uniform patrols,
relaxed our curfew.
We've baited the trap and opened the door.
We've got recon units
prepped and positioned.
I know you've got
your own sources out there.
What time is the funeral?
They asked for midday.
We pushed it back two hours.
They slow down a bit after lunch.
DEDRA: And the funeral area?
KEYSAX: Right there. That's her box.
We're allowing them
half of Rix Road for one block.
TIGO: We gave them a max of 30 people.
The Daughters pushed back,
so we've upped it to 40.
"Daughters"?
The Daughters of Ferrix.
It's a social club.
Andor's mother was a past president.
A local annoyance.
KEYSAX: The control position's here,
here, and here.
We'll have snipers
and a containment unit there.
Containment, yes. Snipers, no.
I want him taken alive.
I want that message passed along the line.
And clearly.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING)
BLEVIN: "Where would I get the money?"
"That's what scares me the most."
KLORIS: That's right. Word for word.
BLEVIN: Was she more angry about him lying
or the possibility of gambling debts?
KLORIS: Hard to say.
Mon Mothma is of great interest here.
Having her husband dig a hole
for himself could be helpful in many ways.
KLORIS: Well, it sounded like
Perrin had done this before.
BLEVIN: They've made some
odd banking moves recently.
This would certainly explain it.
Kreegyr. You're missing it.
Keep listening.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You can close out your Anto Kreegyr files.
BLEVIN: How many attacked?
JUNG: They're still counting the bodies.
BLEVIN: It's over?
They walked right into it.
It was over before they started.
Prisoners?
Not today.
Take a guess who's not happy about that.
She called in.
He's been talking her down.
DEDRA: (OVER SPEAKER) I just wish
I had been part of the conversation, sir.
PARTAGAZ: This wasn't a dialogue, Dedra.
We get nothing from a dead body.
Someone needs to be
in the room saying that.
PARTAGAZ: You're missing the point.
Today was about wiping the taste
of Aldhani from the Emperor's mouth.
You want to start a conversation?
Find Axis.
(BEEPS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(DOORS HISSING)
(WHIRRING)
(REVVING)
(WHOOSHES)
-(SLURPS)
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SIGHS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
That's not him.
GUARD: (OVER COMMS) Sir?
CORV: The big man.
We've been played.
Where is he?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS) Okay.
Make it quick.
(GASPS)
I wanted her to leave with me.
-BRASSO: I know.
-I came to get her.
BRASSO: She told me.
I couldn't get back.
You shouldn't be here now, Cass.
-But the last time I saw her, we argued.
-Don't.
-CASSIAN: I told her I was coming back.
-Stop.
-I never should have left that morning.
-BRASSO: Stop.
She told me you'd say all this.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
"Tell him, none of this is his fault.
"It was already burning.
He's just the first spark of the fire.
"Tell him,
he knows everything he needs to know
"and feels everything he needs to feel.
"And when the day comes,
and those two pull together,
"he will be
an unstoppable force for good.
"Tell him...
"I love him more than anything
he could ever do wrong."
-PEGLA: Hey. (SHUSHES)
-Who's that?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIO)
GUARD: There's different shifts
that they're taking.
Street's clear. Hurry up.
-Bix?
-Still got friends in the hotel.
-She was alive three days ago.
-Why are they keeping her?
She must know something.
-(CLICKS)
-We can't just leave her there.
You're gonna take on a full garrison?
I'll take care of Maarva.
You take care of yourself.
It's too late for that.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER PA SYSTEM)
(WHIRRING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LUTHEN: Any luck?
Was getting worried.
What's the verdict?
Has he come home or not?
They seem to think so.
They're everywhere.
-There's an ISB supervisor in town.
-A woman?
You know her?
Not yet.
This is good.
How is this possibly good?
LUTHEN: They'll do the hunting for us.
They'll want him alive.
They'll find him, we'll kill him.
Where will they take him?
The hotel.
So that's our target.
We just need him dead
before they start asking questions.
How long do we have
before the festivities start?
Few hours. You'll hear the anvil.
-Where's Cinta?
-Watching the mother's house.
LUTHEN: Oh, forget that.
Get her up to the hotel.
I'll have a look around.
(ANVIL CLANGS)
LUTHEN: What's going on?
(CLANGS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ANVIL CLANGS)
(CLANGS)
Get Cinta. I'll be at the hotel.
(ANVIL CLANGS)
(CLANGS)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER SPEAKER)
(ANVIL CLANGS)
(MARCHING BAND WARMING UP)
What's going on?
I'm not sure.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER SPEAKER)
(ANVIL CLANGS)
GUARD: (OVER COMMS) I can hear music, sir.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER ON COMMS)
(ANVIL CLANGS)
(WHIRRING)
(CLANGS)
(MOURNFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
KEYSAX: Of course I hear it.
I'm just not seeing it.
They've started.
They're coming from all over town.
I want everything out here.
Show of force immediately.
Stand to!
Double time, form up.
Let's move!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
TIGO: You call this a perimeter?
Square this away!
Get these people off the streets.
GUARD 1: Team one here.
GUARD 2: Team two here.
GUARD 3: Go, go, go!
GUARD 4: Team three...
TIGO: Restrict them!
-(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
-GUARD 5: Move! Move! Move!
GUARD 3: Go, go, go!
GUARD 4: Move! Move! Move!
GUARD 5: Take a unit down there.
You, Captain, take them that way.
(MOURNFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
-Double the reward.
-You found him?
I want twice as much
and a ride out of here when it's over.
-Where is he?
-Pretend you're arresting me.
-Hey!
-What do you think you're doing?
Hey. Move it. Move!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
GUARD: Right,
we need to assume the positions.
Secure the perimeter.
(NURCHI GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER SPEAKER)
Back!
-TIGO: Which building?
-Across the street.
DEDRA: I need two men.
TIGO: He's seen him?
-No, but he's sure he's there.
-We're wasting time.
I've got a recon unit
on the terrace up there now...
No. I need him alive.
Don't make me say it again.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
(HUMMING)
Sir.
SYRIL: She's here.
It's her.
(BEEPS)
(MOURNFUL MUSIC STOPS)
(WIND BLOWS)
(WHIRS)
(SPIRITED MUSIC BEGINS)
-What are we doing?
-We're wasting time.
(WHIRS)
(WATER SPLASHING)
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
ALL: (CHANTING)
Stone and sky. Stone and sky.
Stone and sky. Stone and sky...
-(CHANTING CONTINUES)
-(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Stone and sky.
(GASPS)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
-Tenek.
-Cassian.
-(SIGHS) Where's Bix?
-(ANVIL CLANGS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
I'm sorry about your mother.
(WHIRRING)
(WARBLES)
(CRACKLING)
My name is Maarva Carassi Andor.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I'm honored to stand before you.
MAARVA: I'm honored
to be a Daughter of Ferrix,
and honored to be worthy of the stone.
Strange, I...
feel as if I can see it.
I was six, I think,
first time I touched a funerary stone.
Heard our music, felt our history.
Holding my sister's hand as we walked
all the way from Fountain Square.
Where you stand now,
I've been more times than I can remember.
I always wanted to be lifted.
I was always eager,
always waiting to be inspired.
I remember every time it happened,
every time the dead lifted me...
(WHEEZES)
With their truth.
(LABORED BREATHING)
And now I'm dead.
And I yearn to lift you.
Not because I want to shine
or even be remembered.
It's because I want you to go on.
I want Ferrix to continue.
In my waning hours,
that's what comforts me most.
But I fear for you.
We've been sleeping.
We've had each other,
and Ferrix, our work, our days.
We had each other, and they left us alone.
We kept the trade lanes open,
and they left us alone.
We took their money and ignored them,
we kept their engines churning,
and the moment they pulled away,
we forgot them.
(SIGHS) Because we had each other.
We had Ferrix.
But we were sleeping.
I've been sleeping.
And I've been turning away from the truth
I wanted not to face.
There is a wound that won't heal
at the center of the galaxy.
There is a darkness reaching like rust
(GLITCHES) into everything around us.
We let it grow, and now it's here.
It's here, and it's not visiting anymore.
It wants to stay.
The Empire is a disease
that thrives in darkness,
it is never more alive than when we sleep.
(WHEEZING)
It's easy for the dead
to tell you to fight,
and maybe it's true,
maybe fighting is useless.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Perhaps it's too late.
But I'll tell you this...
If I could do it again,
I'd wake up early
and be fighting these bastards...
Move!
MAARVA: (WHEEZING) ...from the start.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Fight the Empire!
Enough!
(ALL YELLING)
No!
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
Placement!
(CROWD YELLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BLASTER FIRED)
(CROWD YELLING)
Let him through!
Hold the line!
-(PANTING)
-KEYSAX: Let him through!
-Let him through!
-(GRUNTS)
KEYSAX: Let him through.
Hold the line!
-(GRUNTS)
-(CLANGS)
You! Bell tower, make it stop now!
-Go!
-(PANTING)
KEYSAX: Hold the line!
I dreamt you came back.
Bix?
You climbed over a wall.
Hey, listen, we gotta get outta here.
Maarva was here.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Wasn't she great?
(SIGHS)
(ALL YELLING)
(BUZZING)
KEYSAX: Get him up!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
-GUARD: Move, move!
-(CROWD SHOUTING)
There's no one out there. Come on.
They'll get angry.
No.
(ALL YELLING)
(CLANGS)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(BEEPING)
(YELLS)
-(EXPLOSION)
-(MAN 1 SCREAMS)
NURCHI: Ah!
(CRASHING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GROANS)
MAN: Oh, my God...
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Come. Come.
-There you go.
-(BIX GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
MAN 1: Come on, let's get moving. Come on.
MAN 2: Keep moving!
There! That's him!
Get him!
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
-KEYSAX: Hold the line!
-Open fire!
(BLASTERS FIRING)
Fire at will!
(MAN GRUNTS)
(STORMTROOPER GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(BRASSO GRUNTS)
(STORMTROOPER SCREAMS)
(MAN GROANS)
BRASSO: (PANTS) Come on!
-Move!
-KEYSAX: Get him!
-(BLASTERS FIRING)
-WOMAN: Ah!
(XANWAN GRUNTING)
Ah!
-(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
-(BLASTERS FIRING)
(B2EMO WHIMPERS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
-CORV: You.
-(GASPS)
What are you doing here?
(CINTA SHUDDERS)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CINTA BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIRRING, BEEPS)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN SCREAMING)
-(GRUNTS)
-Okay.
(BIX GRUNTS)
(BLASTER FIRES)
(GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(MAN YELLING)
(YELPS)
-(GRUNTING)
-(CLANGS)
(BIX BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(EXPLOSION)
-(BIX WHIMPERS)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(CLANGS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(STORMTROOPER SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(DEDRA SCREAMING)
SYRIL: Do as I say. Move!
Straight ahead. Through the door.
Quickly!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(DEDRA PANTING)
You?
How?
You were in trouble.
(PANTING)
Syril.
I knew that.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I should...
I should say thank you.
You don't have to.
(DEDRA PANTING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(BIX PANTING)
(DISTANT BLASTERS FIRING)
VEL: What about this?
Everything goes.
-VEL: Closet?
-Empty.
-You're bleeding.
-It's fine.
That's blood.
It's nothing.
It's not mine.
JEZZI: Come on, guys.
The fuel gauge says zero.
-I've got nothing.
-(GRUNTS)
It's topped out. It's reading full.
JEZZI: Do you wanna come up here and see?
Bang the gauge, Jezz.
Just give it a whack.
(SIGHS) It's got a few kinks,
but it's a good old ship.
I'd have more confidence
if you were coming.
(HISSES)
It flies.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Pull it! Pull it!
PEGLA: We're full!
PEGLA: Give me those.
(PANTING) Now, go.
You go now or forget it.
No.
(WHIRS)
(BARKING)
B2EMO: C-C-Cassian.
-PEGLA: Get it going!
-Almost there.
-(BIX WHIMPERING)
-Hey.
-Help her up.
-BIX: Brasso.
She's coming around. Come on.
Let's get moving!
BRASSO: Come. Come with me.
-(BIX BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(WHIRS)
-Hey, Jezz.
-Hey, Cass.
Can they make it to Gangi Moon?
If they ever make it out of here.
You're not coming?
Stay low all the way to Farside Sea.
The moment you get over the water,
you climb.
Straight home, full pump,
hand throttle, no comms.
All in. You understand?
Yeah.
B2EMO: You're n-n-not coming?
Not today, Bee.
B2EMO: I n-n-never got to see you.
You take care of Bix until I get there.
I'm counting on you.
B2EMO: You always say that.
(SCOFFS)
And you always come through.
Get them out of here! (CLAPS)
He'll find us.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Cassian will find us.
-I will.
-(SIGHS)
I'll find you.
Now, go! Go, go!
(WHIRS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
-(METAL RATTLING)
-(GROANS)
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
(EXHALES)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
(SERGEANT MOSK EXHALES)
(WHOOSHES)
LUTHEN: Prepare for evac.
Full stealth.
(BEEPING)
(BEEPS, WHIRS)
You came here to kill me, didn't you?
You don't make it easy.
(SIGHS)
I will now.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
What game is this?
No game.
Kill me.
Or take me in.
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(TIE-FIGHTER WHOOSHES)
(MUSIC STOPS)