[Peacemaker] I'm gonna be honest
about something here.
Homunculi freak me the fuck out!
- Homunculi?
- Yeah.
It's plural for homunculus.
It's a tiny miniature person.
Yeah, I don't like what they're up to.
I don't like what they fucking do.
Hey, Doll Man. You ever meet him?
- Doll Man?
- He turns small.
- He calls himself Doll Man?
- Yeah.
- Barrett M82?
- Yep.
Nice. Have you ever seen
a one-millimeter finger?
Gives me the heebie-jeebies.
Nobody told me
I had to deal with fucking homunculi.
[Leota] Who's saying you gotta deal
with them now?
You kidding me?
I found a miniature spaceship
in the apartment
of the chick I had sex with.
You guys know, the one who was
really into having sex with me
she came, like, four times.
We know who she is.
We don't need to know
how much she enjoyed
having sex with you.
- What if it's a clue?
- It's not.
Fair. I was just trying to slip it
into the conversation
hoping nobody notices. My bad.
Still, fucking hate homunculi.
Where's this tiny spaceship now?
- Adebayo's desk, under my lunch.
- John.
Fuck.
Hey, I want it back
when you're done with it, Dye-Beard.
Oh, shit. Is Project Butterfly homunculi
that team-up with hardbody sluts
that wanna control us?
No, but who's the guy
that's peeking out behind the trash can?
Fuck, it's... it's Vigilante.
He's trying to be helpful.
Hey, get out of here!
[Vigilante] What? I'm just looking
from behind a trash can.
It's a normal thing to do.
The hell it is!
- [Vigilante] Are you a psychiatrist?
- What?
[Vigilante]
Then don't tell me what's normal.
Maybe my secret identity
is a psychiatrist,
and I know what's normal.
If you're a psychiatrist,
we're all screwed.
Get the fuck out of here.
[Vigilante] I was about to go,
and then you had to say that.
Now if I acquiesce,
I'll look and feel small.
Vij, bro, come on be cool.
[Vigilante] I just wanna make sure
you're okay. I don't trust these people.
I'm fine.
[Vigilante] Just remember, even if
they end up being okay to "work with,"
they're still not gonna be good friends.
And none of them
is the type to be a best friend.
[Peacemaker] Okay.
[Vigilante chuckles] I'm just chuckling
even thinking about it.
Okay, bro.
[Vigilante] If one of them does become
a friend, it should be her.
Because there's a bunch of rumors
going around about you being racist,
and, you know, frankly,
it's a little embarrassing for me,
as if I become a racist by osmosis,
even though I mostly kill white people.
So, catch you guys later.
Isn't that guy wanted
on multiple counts of murder?
We have bigger fish to fry.
We have a United States Senator
to assassinate by the end of the day.
[theme song playing]
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
- Get it on
- Get it on top
Make a move extreme
- Make a pose
- Shortcut to your dreams
Float straight to the stars
On that flying thing
- Getting high
- Getting brave
- Getting snowblind, game
- Set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon
In a world beyond
Get a beat, got a heat
On a phony string
Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
[screeches]
[rock music playing]
I'm a powertrain
Can't stop silence
Working night and day
Can't stop trying
I'm a powertrain
Can't stop silence...
[Murn] Our target
is Senator Royland Goff.
He's mostly known for being
a radical proponent of climate change.
Okay, so we're gonna kill him
'cause climate change is a hoax?
Why do all people
that think pro-wrestling is real
think climate change is a hoax?
It's not a hoax.
[scoffs] Yeah, okay. Facebook's lying
to me every day for no reason.
Senator Goff is a butterfly,
and we need to take him out.
Next photo.
[laughs]
- Fuck!
- [Murn] What is it?
- [Peacemaker] Look at this!
- Oh, my God!
Shit. I'm so sorry.
- My wife sent it to me.
- Your wife?
- Yes. It's my wife.
- Holy shit!
- I'm so sorry.
- I had no idea Adebayo here was playing
for the Washington Lickatoapusses,
did you, Murn?
I didn't know that you was playing
for the, I don't know,
the fucking Milwaukee
Roided-Up Toilet Bowl Hats!
I'm not from Milwaukee.
I'm so sorry, sir.
She just moved to a different hotel
because Harcourt said that
it would be dangerous
- if we stayed in the same suite.
- Shit! She just threw you under the bus.
- Okay. So, this is my fault now?
- No.
It's just now Keeya thinks
I chose this job over her,
and we're experimenting
with new forms of intimacy,
and I didn't know that WhatsApp
would just automatically
put this on to the device.
WhatsApp will do that
if you don't change the settings.
- Nobody told me!
- Yeah, no shit.
- [continues laughing]
- It's not that fucking funny, you dick.
- Just continue, Leota.
- Yes, sir.
[Peacemaker] Whoo!
Goff may be traveling with his family.
That is a weird segue.
We don't know yet whether or not
his wife and children are butterflies.
If so, you'll have to kill all of them.
What?
I thought you loved peace
with all your heart,
no matter how many
men, women and children
you needed to kill to get it.
Yes, I said that.
I say that, and I mean it,
that's the vow I took, but...
kids?
Well, we aren't sure yet
if they're butterflies.
Okay. Easy. This is the part where you
tell me what the fuck a butterfly is?
We're not here
to answer your questions, Smith.
So what is it,
"Just trust us and shoot kids?"
Come on, man.
Look how adorable that one is.
The other one not so much.
He's got, like, a Children of the Corn
vibe going on.
Are you sure those two kids
came out of those parents?
That's an attractive couple.
That one looks like it came out of them,
- the other one looks like a butt baby.
- A butt baby?
Yeah, my older brother told me
there's two types of babies:
one that comes out
of a woman's vagina, normal,
and then butt babies,
worse in every way,
they come out a woman's butt.
You know, I believed I was a butt baby
until I was 14.
That explains a lot.
What does this have to do with anything?
Just because
that's an unattractive child,
doesn't mean I wanna kill it.
Your feelings are noted.
This is Goff's bodyguard,
goes by the name of Judomaster.
What's the fuck's
that guy gonna protect him from,
- pink hearts and green clovers?
- We understand he's dangerous.
He's two feet tall!
We'll be on site in about ten minutes.
Peacemaker and Harcourt
will take out Goff
while Leota, John and I work remotely.
Don't terminate the kids or the wife
until we tell you it's okay.
- Any questions?
- Yes.
Is scissoring real?
I keep getting contradictory reports.
I suspected you were a butt baby
from the beginning.
I'm all for it.
One thing I'm in favor of
is two chicks going at it.
- Jeez.
- What? I'm a fucking ally.
Having a lesbian haircut
doesn't make you an ally.
You haven't seen my porn folder.
Four hundred gigs of alliance.
- Hey, where's the dove of peace?
- The what?
The dove of peace. My trademark.
It's engraved on all my weapons.
My tomahawk, my sword,
my blow darts, my pistol.
You wanted us to stop
and take the sniper rifle to an engraver
and put a dove of peace on it?
Uh, yeah, this is fucked-up.
How then kill someone with something
that doesn't have a dove of peace on it?
Fuck. Every time I draw a dove of peace
it looks like a ghost.
Fuck!
So why don't you just tell him
what butterflies are?
I don't trust him. Do you?
I guess not.
We need Peacemaker
to stop questioning us.
He's stubborn,
but he also has a deep need to belong.
We can use that to our advantage.
- Cool.
- Toss me a screw.
So...
They say you've done,
like, some real hardcore shit.
I'm trying to do what I can
to make up for my past.
[motor whirring]
Things I've done make me... sad.
There.
That's a feeling of mine
I just shared with you.
Cool.
It is cool,
'cause I've never done it before.
Never done what before?
Shared a feeling.
[laughing] Come on.
You've never shared any feeling?
No.
You've never even said,
"Oh, my God, I'm hungry."
No.
You've never said,
uh, "It's chilly in here"?
Is chilly a feeling?
- Yeah, I think so.
- No.
Come on.
You've never said you felt chilly?
Why?
You think I'm some weak-ass girly-man
who needs a poofy jacket
or a little blanky?
You gonna bring me a baby pacifier
for that wittle blanky, John?
No.
That's how I thought of it in the past.
But now I'm becoming a deeper,
more well-rounded individual.
In fact, I'm a little chilly right now.
- You are?
- No.
But I saw it as an opportunity
for growth to say I was.
Uh, okay. Looks like we're good to go.
[Peacemaker grunts]
Those ones are empty calories.
Here they come. Here they come.
We got the Berenstein Bears
in the Mercedes.
Papa bear, Mama bear, Brother bear
and Sister bear all accounted for.
We've got a bodyguard and Cobra Kai
in the Cadillac Escalade.
Copy.
It's Berenstain Bears.
- What?
- The children's books.
It's Berenstain Bears
not Berenstein Bears.
[chuckles] Dude, I grew up
on those books. It's Berenstein Bears.
Um, absolutely not. It's actually named
after the creators, Stan and Jan Beren...
- Does this fucking matter?
- No, sir.
It's Berenstein.
- I don't mean to correct you, sir, but...
- Shut up.
Mercedes and Escalade have landed.
- [bodyguard] Sir.
- [Royland] Oh, little rugrats are here.
[imperceptible chatter]
There she is.
Kid's not as ugly in person.
Still looks weird, though.
Is your target in sight?
He's playing with the kids.
- Is Goff in sight?
- Nope.
- Now?
- No.
Take your shot when he's clear.
Yeah, I know, dude.
Shut the fuck up, okay?
They're about to enter the house.
I know what he's about to do,
I still don't have a goddamn shot.
If you don't get him now, Smith,
we'll probably have to wait
till morning.
Yeah, that's not helping me
make the big motherfucker
in front of him disappear, okay?
Want me to take him out too?
No.
Fuck.
All right. Hook a brother up.
- No.
- Okay.
- I don't need the carbs anyway.
- I noticed.
Look, they're in the window.
What the fuck?
I think the whole family
- is butterflies.
- Why?
The second they were
out of the bodyguards' sight,
their demeanor changed.
They dropped the pretense
of being a playful family.
They're politicians, right?
Maybe the whole "happy family" thing
is just what they do in public.
Yeah, I don't think that's what it was.
Did you see them?
I don't know. Maybe they're just weird.
I'm not cool
with any of this shit anyway.
I don't know why we're fucking killing
these people, okay?
A Sharpie dove of peace
isn't a legitimate dove.
- What?
- This fucking thing!
I'm not a fucking drawer, okay.
[Murn] Calm down, Peacemaker.
We're not killing anyone
who doesn't deserve it.
I'm not Amanda Waller.
I guess we'll just have to wait
until morning.
[Harcourt sighs]
["Would you love a creature" playing]
Memories and beliefs
Means nothing more to me
Than a ball and a chain
Inside of my brain
Holding me back from living a life
I just can't stretch my wings to fly
I am what I am
Nothing more than a man
Nothing heavenly
Within my command
With everything to lose
I reach out to you
Would you love a creature like me?
[Peacemaker] So...
How'd you get into this line of work?
How did you get into this line of work?
My old man, I guess.
Dads.
[scoffs]
Mine got me my first Glock
when I was 12.
- Which one?
- The 20.
That's a lot of gun for a little girl.
I was a lot of little girl for a gun.
- How'd you end up working for Waller?
- What is this, 20 questions?
After high school, I joined the CIA,
spent a couple of years
in the DEO, then ARGUS,
that's where Waller found me.
And now, here I am, living the dream,
about to assassinate
a couple of children.
[clears throat]
Would you love a creature like me?
[stutters]
Um...
Hey, can you, uh, can you watch
for a second? I got to go...
Sure. Yeah. Totally. Yeah.
[Vigilante] Psst.
Psst.
Hey. Hey, dude.
That was a really interesting
conversation that you guys had.
What the fuck you doing here, man?
[Vigilante] I followed you guys
in my Vigilante-mobile.
- When'd you get a Vigilante-mobile?
- [Vigilante] You've been in it.
The Sebring.
- Can you believe this motherfucker?
- [Vigilante] Oh, my God.
- Is that the fucking trash can guy?
- [Vigilante] What do you want me to do?
Paint it purple
and put a big red "V" on the hood?
- I'd get instantly pulled over.
- [Peacemaker] No.
Just don't call it a fucking
Vigilante-mobile. It's a Sebring.
[Vigilante] What? Fuck!
[Murn] We know he's there, Peacemaker.
Dude, they know you're here.
Get out of the bushes.
[Vigilante] I don't know
what you're talking about.
What is he supposed to be,
a talking bush?
I don't even understand
what he's trying to do.
[Vigilante] Ugh, fuck.
Vigilante needs to stay there with you.
I don't want him going out
and fucking this up.
- Dude.
- [Vigilante] What?
You're a fucking clown.
[laughs]
All right.
That's definitely photoshopped.
No it's not.
It says it right... "Berenstain."
A-I. Like, "Ain."
"Berenstain."
[Vigilante] Why don't we just take out
the bodyguards and storm inside?
The bodyguards are probably
just innocents hired to protect them.
[Vigilante] Right, okay.
Is that the answer?
Shit.
[Harcourt] The Berenstain Bears
are in the dining room.
Copy that. I don't have eyes.
Peacemaker, do you have a shot
on Papa Bear?
Not quite yet.
What the fuck?
They're pouring some sort of
honey-colored goo into bowls.
- They're butterflies!
- How do you know?
What the fuck?
There's some sort of purple things
growing out of their mouths.
Peacemaker, take them out!
- Even the kids?
- [Murn] Yes, all four bears, now!
If you have a shot
terminate them immediately.
Peacemaker, God damn it, take the shot!
- I don't know if I can hit...
- They're clear. Take the shot.
[breath trembling]
Should have put a dove on the gun. Fuck!
Take a breath, Smith. Steady yourself.
God damn it!
Waller gave us a killer who can't kill.
[exhales]
[Vigilante] Hey, dude.
Move over for a sec.
[Vigilante humming]
[gasps]
Mama Bear out.
[continues humming]
Billy Bear out.
Susie Bear out.
[Vigilante] And now, Papa Bear...
[grunting, groaning]
Kiai!
What's "kiai"?
It's a martial arts term.
It means "convergence of energy."
Judomaster. Harcourt, do you copy?
[grunting]
[groans]
[Murn] Harcourt, Peacemaker,
do you copy?
[Vigilante] Oh, shit.
[both groaning]
Do you copy?
Fuck.
Adebayo.
John, watch the front gate,
make sure no one leaves.
- How am I supposed to stop them?
- Any way you can!
If anyone lets them know
what we're up to here, we're fucked!
Obviously he feels anger.
[both grunting]
[Vigilante groans]
- Shit.
- [Vigilante] Fuck, dude.
[grunting]
[Vigilante] Uh, no. Fuck this. No way.
It's over. You won. Fair fight.
I... I got to go. Fuck it.
No!
[screams]
Let's get them inside.
[gun cocking]
Stay right there.
[groans]
Shit.
- Who are you?
- [Harcourt] Jesus.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Just stay there.
- [gun cocking]
- [Leota] Drop your weapon.
Hands in the air.
All right, I'm cool.
- You work for Royland Goff?
- Yes.
You one of them?
One of what?
Adebayo, what are you doing?
Take care of it.
Take care of what?
I'm not one of anything.
- I'm former Secret Service and...
- I don't think he's one of them.
It doesn't matter. He's seen us.
And Peacemaker needs our help now.
Listen, I haven't seen anything, okay?
My wife's name is Marianne.
- Why are you prolonging this?
- We've been married 16 years.
- We have three kids.
- People are depending on us.
- We don't have a goddamn choice!
- Mason, Declan and Jaden.
- Adebayo, what the fuck!
- I love them
more than anything in the world.
Don't do this.
[Leota yells]
[pants]
I'm sorry.
[Harcourt groans]
I've never killed anyone.
Well, your streak's still going.
Make sure he's clean.
Murn will want a sample if he's not.
God.
[breath trembling]
Hey.
Good. Harcourt.
Peacemaker isn't here.
Can you track him?
Yeah.
He's in the house.
His heart's still beating.
[heart beating]
[paper crackling]
[groans softly]
Try the side door.
- The bodyguard wasn't a butterfly.
- [Harcourt] Great.
You're fucking adorable.
I want to put you in my pocket.
I want to take you home,
play with you with my G.I. Joes.
Just don't fuck Chewbacca.
Here's a little known fact.
Wookiees have teeth on their asshole.
That's canon.
And remember to wave
when I put you away in my special box
'cause if you get stuck in there,
you'll suffocate.
Fuck you.
You remind me of a shit I took
last night, only Asian.
Oh!
Big man.
Hey, nice costume, bro. Little tight.
I can count the veins in your dick.
Big swoll man, so tough.
I'm gonna keep you around
in case I snap my Achilles tendon.
I'll replace it
with your whole fucking body.
That way you can help me flex my toes
for the rest of my life. Thank you.
Remember when I fucked you up?
What you eating there,
Flamin' Hot Cheetos?
Yes.
- Want some?
- Yeah.
[groans]
[groans] Fuck. All right.
Fuck, I get it.
Ow! Fuck, man!
What the fuck do they put in Cheetos?
[groans] Seriously, stop!
["Six feet under" playing]
It feels good here, six feet under
And I still wait and wonder
How could I stay there all the time
In my grave it's warm and cozy
It's safe, no one disturbs me
I feel fine until the end of time
I've got some sad girls
Some bitches crying
Some poor souls more that are whining
Six shots in the back
Thanks for the attack
It feels good
Six feet, six feet under
[Vigilante] What the fuck?
- This place is mine
- Six feet, six feet under
- This place is what I find it's all mine
- Six feet under
- It's my home
- Six feet, six feet under
- I'm alone
- No one controls
- Six feet...
Take the tunnel to the forest.
From there, get to Glan Tai,
let them know what's occurred here.
Yes.
In some nights I think of lifetime
Sunlight and how that star shine
Bit by bit I forget 'bout it
But I guess I'm feeling happy
Unstressed and sometimes sappy
On my own...
Oh, shit, we're over them.
There's a basement.
Where the hell's the door?
I've got some sad girls
Some bitches crying
Some poor souls more that are whining
Six shots in the back
Thanks for the attack
- It feels good
- Six feet, six feet under
- It feels fine
- This place is mine
- Six feet, six feet under
- This place is what I find it's all mine
- Six feet under
- It's my home
- Six feet, six feet under
- I'm alone
- No one controls
- Six feet, six feet under...
This place is six feet under
Fuck.
Six feet under
[Vigilante] No!
What are you doing?
If I keep changing
my facial expressions,
he won't be able to recognize me
in a lineup.
You need to tell me what you know,
how you know it, and who sent you.
Otherwise you will know pain
unlike ever before.
I'm not telling you shit.
[screams]
Fuck!
Does that change your mind?
Sorry, pal, not for sale.
- What?
- Give it all you got?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
[screaming]
- How do you like that?
- I like it.
I like it a lot. I don't give a fuck.
You're not gonna break me, motherfucker.
Good God, no! No... [screaming]
Fuck!
[thudding]
[grunting] God damn it!
Peel off the back
and put it on the door.
[beeps]
Fuck!
What is it?
Experimental ARGUS device
An adhesive explosive.
Just have to link it up
to this program.
[retches]
Why are you licking it?
I thought it was an adhesive,
like an envelope.
You just have to peel off the back
and stick it on there.
I'm sorry, I just...
[shuddering, panting]
[groans]
Hey.
Aren't you Gut Chase's younger brother?
The one who was playing D&D
all the time?
[Vigilante] Since then I've turned
my body into an instrument of vengeance.
Dude, that's admirable.
Your body is way more toned
than it used to be.
- Thanks.
- You were always wiry.
- Solid frame, good foundation, I guess.
- Yeah.
Hey, hey, don't worry.
I'm not giving this guy anything.
Uh, maybe
you should just give him a little.
[beeping]
Oh, you fucking fucker.
Fuck!
No, not the fucking car,
you little fucker!
So...
Pure pain couldn't get you to talk.
What about the fear of losing
something more permanent,
like a toe?
I'll start with his pinky.
What? My pinky? Why me again?
This one's obviously the alpha,
more likely to have knowledge.
And humans are, above all,
creatures of empathy.
The best way to get them to talk
is to hurt the ones they love most.
- What?
- Fuck it.
Cut off all his toes, I don't care.
Dude, if someone doesn't have
their pinky toe, they'll fall over.
It's the most important toe
on the human body.
I don't think that's true.
It is. [screaming] I read it
on the Internet!
[buzzes, beeps]
[screaming in pain]
[Vigilante] Oh, God! No!
Fuck!
It worked in the lab, damn it.
Why is it not coming off?
Because your blades
are dull as fuck, man.
Why don't you maintain
your torture shit?
[Vigilante] Jesus fucking Christ!
Guess it's not working.
Love can be an invisible illusion
Love should all be laid bare
Loving means engraving
it onto your heart
[yells]
[both grunting]
Fuck!
[grunting]
No!
- Peace out, motherfucker.
- [snarls]
[pants]
[John] Oh. Holy shit.
Oh, my God.
Fuck. [grunts]
Shit.
[shudders]
[groaning]
Stop where you are.
I said stop!
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[straining]
Oh, come on. Really?
[yells]
[whimpers]
[laughs]
Economos, motherfucker.
Yeah.
Kiai!
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. [grunts]
[continues grunting]
[Leota coughs]
Are you all right?
[Leota] We're coming, Smith!
We're trying!
Smith?
- Smith!
- We're okay. We're down here.
I think he only cut off
about half my toe.
Hey, what you say your name was, again?
Adrian. I need to put my mask back on
in case they come down.
What the...
["Push Push" playing]
[screeches]
Yeah!
Come on
I wanna take you higher
Oh. Project Butterfly.
Push, push, Lady Lightning
Push, push
Come on
I want to take you higher
Let's make electric fire
Push, push, Lady Lightning
Push, push
- Dude.
- [Vigilante] What?
If you fuck up this mission,
I will kill your fucking family.
[Vigilante laughing] Okay, good luck.
A little late for that.
[Vigilante] You guys got beer?