[Fisk] The painting that's intended
for this wall
is something I am specially attached to.
[Lee] Of course. Rabbit in a Snowstorm.
Yes, the agreement.
It said I was to get
all my belongings restored to me.
Precisely. And we might be able
to use this violation of terms
to lobby the feds for something else.
The painting!
That's what I'm interested in.
I can assure you we're doing
everything in our power, but...
there's a challenge
to your ownership claim.
It comes home.
Do you understand?
Lawyer's out! Cameras back on!
[agent over radio] Wellers,
we have a situation. Report to the CP.
[Wellers] Shit.
Inside. Shut the door.
[Fisk] Show them to me.
[typing]
[woman over radio] All units
on the citywide, NYPD...
[radio chatter continues indistinctly]
[Doyle] Shit. Are you hearing this?
What happened at the Bulletin?
We should be there,
not stuck here with this asshole.
He go to bed?
[Doyle] Turned in early.
Nice and cozy, while the world explodes.
And now the news, Mrs. Shelby.
...rushed to nearby hospitals
in critical condition.
But what we do know is that,
according to several eyewitnesses,
the brutal attack on the Bulletin staff
has been carried out
by none other than Daredevil.
The word from the witnesses
we've spoken with is that Daredevil,
Hell's Kitchen's renowned vigilante,
is the perpetrator.
...they don't know the whereabouts
of Daredevil or whether...
This brutal act hits Hell's Kitchen after
a period of relative calm in the city,
with the FBI arresting
many of New York's...
[theme music playing]
You're missing the point. He didn't
just find someone to wear my suit.
Someone as fast and skilled as I've
ever seen, and I couldn't take him.
-He found someone to kill me.
-Matthew...
I was stupid enough to think
that I had Fisk cornered.
He knew I'd find the witness,
and I just brought the sheep to slaughter.
Jasper Evans is dead.
He's dead and he leaves a son behind,
and that's on me!
I was so sure that I finally
was out in front of this bastard.
And Fisk, he knew I thought that.
-He was waiting for me.
-Matthew--
Foggy and Karen both could've been killed.
And there would have been nothing
I could have done to stop it. Nothing.
You're losing blood.
I need to stitch you up.
I listened to you.
I listened to you, and they almost died.
God damn it. I'm such an idiot.
No.
I'm the idiot.
I told you to involve your friends,
and I made things worse.
I'm used to putting on a brave face when
people bring their troubles to the church.
And I find that they
don't just bring their troubles,
they bring their answers, too,
if you let them talk enough.
But...
what you're dealing with
is so far beyond my experience that...
Well...
all I can hope to do is help keep
your wounds stitched and your head clear,
so you can be safe.
And I'll be more careful
about giving advice to the Devil.
And, occasionally, possibly,
I'll try to keep my mouth shut.
Could I get that in writing?
Look, I know you were just trying to help.
Now, can I please see to those wounds?
[exhales]
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
[breathes heavily]
What if you stopped this fight,
took time to heal...
and let other people like you
go after Fisk?
This isn't their fight.
Fisk is my problem.
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
The problem is,
he's always five steps ahead of me.
I don't know if I can beat him.
And I don't know if I can beat
the man he sent to kill me.
You won't know for certain
till you find him.
I thought you were gonna keep
your thoughts to yourself.
-You really want me to do that?
-[chuckles softly] No.
If he was wearing
a copy of your Devil suit...
Well, he didn't get it at Sears.
How good a copy was it?
It was perfect.
-[Karen panting on TV]
-[gunshot on TV]
[Dex] Hello, Karen.
It's nice to see you again.
Was there anyone else
in the room named Karen?
Or on the whole Bulletin staff?
I'm advising my client
not to answer any questions
that treat her like an asshole.
[Ray] There was not.
He was talking to you.
-Why don't we watch it again? See--
-No.
-He was talking to me. That's true.
-[Ray] Okay.
-Good.
-[Karen] But I've never met him before.
Well, according to your own newspaper,
you've met Daredevil at least twice.
That psycho's not Daredevil.
I got a pretty good look at him, too.
Could have fooled me.
Do you think every fat guy with
a white beard and red suit is Santa Claus?
If he comes down my chimney
and leaves presents under the tree.
Exactly. If he acted like Santa.
This guy doesn't act like Daredevil.
Based on your two encounters?
Dig a little deeper.
Why don't you read everything?
He doesn't kill people, ever.
It's not Daredevil.
So you keep saying.
Did you ever look into Felix Manning?
Red Lion Bank?
Any of the leads
that I dropped in your lap?
They're on my to-do list.
This is bullshit.
He dropped your name, Ms. Page.
Used your gun to murder someone.
And in this entire shitshow,
you're the one person
he didn't lay a finger on.
So I'm sorry that you think
that this is bullshit,
but something doesn't add up.
So we're gonna keep
going over this until it does.
It's not gonna add up until you start
asking the right questions.
How about this one? Where's Matt Murdock?
Yet another fine example of a question
that's besides the friggin' point!
You were supposed to deliver him,
Mr. Nelson.
But there are zero Matt Murdocks
in my custody.
Zero Jasper Evans left alive.
Think that's random?
He kills the one guy with dirt on Fisk.
You know that already?
Is that why you don't wanna go there?
-Karen--
-What?
That psycho in a suit
did Agent Nadeem a huge favor.
Now there's no one left to tell the world
what a fool Fisk is making of the FBI.
Did you know Daredevil
was gonna attack the Bulletin?
Is that why you brought
your gun last night?
Okay. We're done here.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Are you okay?
No, I'm definitely not okay.
[cell phone ringing]
[cell phones ringing and chiming]
None of the people who own those phones
are okay, either.
-Come on. Let's go.
-No...
I don't get it. You... You almost died.
That doesn't leave a mark?
I don't have time to think about that.
Right now,
Agent Nadeem's got all my attention.
If he digs into Jasper Evans, he'll know
we're telling the truth about Fisk.
Then he'll dig into the rest of it.
I hope.
I did this.
[Foggy] Wilson Fisk did this.
Evans wouldn't have come to the Bulletin
if I hadn't threatened his son.
This isn't on you.
And this isn't the time
to give up the fight.
-We need to find Matt--
- No. Um...
-I'm gonna go to the hospital.
-[cell phone vibrating]
Are you hurt?
I'm the only one who wasn't.
Marci. I should take this. She's worried.
Hey, babe.
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm fine.
I know. I'm sorry, it's just been crazy.
The time has--
Seema, I'm fine.
Really, I--
Seems, I wasn't even there.
I got there after it was all over.
That's right.
I'll be home tonight, okay?
[knock at door]
Oh, shit. That's tonight?
No. No, no. Don't cancel. Um...
It'll be good to see the family.
And good for Sami, you know?
And let him know
everything really is all right.
I love you, too.
Where is he?
-[Betsy] Damn, it's cold out here.
-[Melvin] You got your hat?
I could get your hat.
[Betsy] No, Melvin, it's okay.
I'm in the office today.
[Melvin] Okay.
I made you cheese and pickles.
Thanks, love.
-[Melvin] You got your gun?
-[Betsy] Of course. Right here.
What's going on?
You've been acting strange all morning.
[Melvin] I...
worry about you.
Because I hang out
with paroled cons like you?
[Melvin] 'Cause they're not like me. [Betsy] I can take care of myself,
big man.
You be good today.
I'll make asopao for dinner.
[Melvin] Okay.
Love you.
[Matt] Betsy's your parole officer.
Please don't tell anyone.
It's against the rules.
I don't care
what you do with Betsy, Melvin.
You know why I'm here.
Fisk made me make the suit.
Did that man hurt you?
I'm sorry.
Who was he?
He didn't tell me his name.
But I can make you a new one...
to protect you against him.
-It'd be a fair fight.
-I don't want the suit anymore.
You don't like it?
I've outgrown what it stood for.
When you made my suit,
there were molds, measurements.
At the workshop, maybe there's something.
I've been to the workshop.
It's been burned down.
Yeah, I burned it down,
because I didn't want to help Fisk, but...
he made me a new shop
and he threatened Betsy.
People died
because you helped him, Melvin.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Where is your new shop?
[Marci] Foggy Bear?
Oh, my God! Are you all right?
When did you get here?
I tried to stay awake.
I've been watching the news all night.
Are you hurt?
Babe, talk to me.
I'm okay.
I'm just tired.
Let's get you to bed.
Babe?
[Ray] Jasper Evans.
Locked up in '91
on a couple of murder two counts.
Seems he walked into a convenience store,
got talked to the wrong way,
ended up shooting an honest cashier
and a sweet old granny
picking up her Sunday Powerball ticket.
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
Warden, this lifer
was supposed to be serving
a year in the hole
for shanking Wilson Fisk.
Is that a question?
How could he be in the hole and get killed
in a newspaper office at the same time?
Some pencil-pusher must've checked
the wrong box and let him out by mistake.
Look. I'm not trying to jam you up.
I'm just trying to nail down
how he got out.
And who might have wanted him dead.
I need answers, Warden.
You got nothing? Seriously?
I want my lawyer.
I talked to the Bulletin reporter.
Jasper Evans was going to say
that Fisk staged his own shanking.
He had him released
from prison as payback.
Jesus.
Tell me the warden disputes that.
He's more concerned
with covering his own ass.
-He's lawyered up.
-Oh, shit.
It's all hearsay.
I mean, Evans might have been lying.
And maybe he was telling the truth. We gotta kick this up the chain.
-Who are you calling?
-The ADIC.
And tell him what?
We don't know all the facts.
Except there's a damn good chance
that Fisk is manipulating us.
If it's true,
every asshole we put away with Fisk's help
will be back on the street by morning.
Everything we've done,
the people we've lost,
it will all be for nothing.
You can't unring that bell.
Just give me a chance
to figure out if it's true.
How?
I need two days.
You want a pony, too?
Just let me get the facts.
If Fisk really did play us, we'll bury that son of a bitch together.
Wow.
I don't know what got into me.
It's okay.
I mean, it was way, way better than okay.
Like, way better.
[chuckles] I mean, I get it.
After what you went through last night.
I was convinced I was gonna die.
The last thing I remember thinking was,
"Not yet."
Oh, you must've been so scared.
More than I've ever been
in my entire life.
But there was something else beneath it.
This feeling of being unsettled.
[stammers] Important things left undone.
Marry me.
-Stop.
-I'm serious.
-Let's go to the courthouse right now.
-Foggy Bear, slow down.
I love you, Marci, and I'm pretty sure
that you love me, too.
I do love you.
But when you propose,
I want it to be from your heart.
Not from this.
[kisses] Shit.
I'm gonna be late for my deposition.
Go. Shower. I'll pick this up.
What the hell?
[Ellison] Think about what Amber
would have wanted. You know?
[Carla] They want to take her off
of life support.
I'll let you know what we decide.
[Ellison] Okay. I'm so sorry.
I'm...
[woman over PA]
All surgical residents to pre-op.
Chief ortho resident to ER.
-[Ellison] Oh, hey.
-[Karen] Hey.
How are you feeling?
[clicks tongue]
I'm full of Percocet.
Jell-O.
-Rage.
-[Karen chuckles]
Uh...
Amber?
Oh, she's on...
She's brain-dead.
Just, uh, machines keeping her alive.
-It wasn't worth it.
-Karen...
Look, three people died.
Why? Because I had to pick a fight?
I'm pretty sure
that's what we're supposed to do. Sometimes, we get our asses kicked.
Could you get me the water?
It's over there.
Don't think you have some proprietary
claim over sticking it to Fisk.
You know, this fight belongs
to every person in Hell's Kitchen.
And I'm one of them,
so I intend to keep fighting.
We're gonna go to print today, tomorrow,
and the next day and the next day.
Here. I want you to write down
everything you know about Daredevil.
His connection to Fisk.
The man who attacked us last night,
it wasn't Daredevil.
Who was it, then?
[exhales]
I don't know.
But you know it wasn't Daredevil.
Karen, do you know who Daredevil is?
Don't ask me that. Please.
Why not?
Karen, if you know something,
you've gotta tell me right now.
[stammers] I can't.
Some piece of shit attacked my people,
in my house!
And if you know anything,
anything that will get me closer
to finding out who he is,
then, God damn it,
you are going to tell me!
Or you can go clean out your desk.
[keypad beeping]
[gate buzzes]
[Matt] Why is the suit here?
[Melvin] That's not the one he wore.
Fisk made me make two.
Why?
-Ask him yourself.
-What are you doing?
I have to go now. He said.
-Don't do this.
-I don't have a choice.
He'll come for Betsy.
Why'd he ask you to trap me here?
Is he coming? Tell me who wore the suit!
I will find him.
I will put an end to this.
I can't. Fisk will know.
And he'll hurt Betsy.
If you really loved her,
you'd cut her loose.
This life doesn't work with Betsys.
[grunting]
[Melvin] I can't let you leave!
[Matt groaning]
-Someone's coming.
-I'm not supposed to be here.
It's the FBI, Melvin.
Why would Fisk send...
They're supposed to find you
with the suit.
Oh, God.
He's framing me for being Daredevil.
Melvin, come on, he's tricking you.
Please. Betsy's all I have.
Once Fisk has me, he will kill you both.
-Oh, man.
-You gotta help me, or Betsy's dead.
Who did you make the suit for?
He never told me his name...
but he was an FBI agent.
How do you know that?
He was talking about it
with the man who brought him.
[agent 1] Breach. Breach. Breach.
[agent 2] FBI! Don't move!
Go! Go! Go!
[agent 2] Stop fighting, or we'll shoot!
[agent 3] Hands behind your head.
-[Melvin] Please! I gotta get to her!
-[agent 3] On your knees.
On your knees!
[Melvin] Betsy!
He'll hurt Betsy!
-He asleep?
-Been in bed all night.
[Ray] I need to talk to him.
-You want company?
-No. I got it.
[Manning] Potter's in custody.
Should we alter his situation
or his girlfriend's?
No.
He's irrelevant now.
Where is Poindexter?
Laying low, as ordered.
Although, I'm concerned
about his mental stability.
Yeah.
I've demanded a lot from him.
You keep an eye on him.
But let him be for now.
We need to talk.
You're working late.
Shouldn't you be with your family?
Seema, isn't it?
Say her name again and see what happens.
What can I help you with?
[scoffs] Help me.
You know, you remind me of someone
I knew growing up.
Jack Kem.
Yeah, but everyone knew him as Jiggy.
You know, Jiggy lived
in a two-family house all by himself.
It was practically a mansion to me.
But Jiggy was a helper, too.
He was always
helping out folks on the block.
Annie the single mom needs a new car.
Jiggy's got it.
The Hoffmans are desperate for rent.
No problem.
Ten-year-old me
thought this guy was a hero.
But it turned out
Jiggy had hidden ten kilos of heroin
in the trunk of Annie's sedan.
Another five in the Hoffman baby's room.
Guess who the cops arrested
when they tracked down that powder?
[Ray scoffs]
I've seen your kind of help before.
Have a little faith in me,
Special Agent Nadeem.
I'm a better man than Jiggy.
This...
All of this...
This was my price,
which I was plain about
at the start of our relationship.
And you have paid it.
I need to know.
Right now.
You let Jasper Evans out of prison
to pay him back for shanking you?
Your desperation diminishes you,
Special Agent.
Good night.
[Fisk] "The Hero of Hell's Kitchen
Feeds a Simpleton to the Feds."
Won't that make a hell of a headline
for tomorrow's Bulletin?
Melvin made his choice.
Yet you did hesitate before you left. Were you waiting for a messenger
from the Lord to stop you,
like he stopped Abraham
from killing his son?
Were you disappointed
no messenger arrived...
or relieved that you didn't have to risk
your life for a weak-minded criminal?
You're not strong enough
to beat the man I sent for you.
You're not smart enough to beat me.
You couldn't do it alone.
You couldn't do it with your friends.
Your father never knew when to lay down.
He was too proud.
You will die the same way.
Please, Betsy, don't do me like this.
I wasn't the one who violated parole.
You did this to yourself.
-[Matt] Betsy.
-[gasps]
Don't. I'm not here to hurt you.
I'm here about Melvin.
Melvin Potter?
[Matt] He's been arrested.
Bullshit.
He's not gonna tell anyone
about your relationship,
but that's not
what you need to worry about.
You need to worry about Wilson Fisk.
Oh, shit. Damn it, Melvin.
Fisk doesn't leave loose ends.
He will kill you.
Don't go home. Don't go back to work.
Leave town.
[Betsy] What about Melvin? Is he okay?
You can't help Melvin.
He made his bed
when he went back to work for Fisk.
You're a cold piece of work, aren't you?
Melvin told me
about the Devil of Hell's Kitchen.
He thought you were a hero.
I told him assholes like you and Fisk
are cut from the same cloth
and both of you
would take advantage of Melvin
because he has a good heart
and a trusting way!
You've been warned, Betsy.
You want to live?
Run. [Marci] Foggy?
Foggy, baby, are you okay?
Because I don't think you're okay.
Oh.
I'm-- I'm fine.
I think I know what Fisk is up to.
[crying and sniffling]
[line ringing]
[man] Hello?
-Hi, Dad. It's me.
-Karen? Good Lord.
I heard something on the news.
That wasn't where you work, was it?
Yeah. Yeah, it was. I'm okay, though.
I was thinking that maybe
I could come home for a little while.
I don't know.
I'm afraid the timing is not great.
Yeah. Of course. I get it.
But you can call anytime, all right?
Dad...
I was just trying to do the right thing.
It just...
It went all wrong.
That's what you do, Karen.
Good night.
[sobbing]
[Ray] I'm not asking for prisoner files.
All I want is footage
from the security cameras. Copies.
I'll even pay for them.
We're supposed to be
on the same side here.
All I want to do is see exactly
what happened when Fisk got shanked.
Well, you have him call me
as soon as he gets in. Understand?
I'll--
Asshole.
[all] Surprise!
[Seema laughing]
Wow. [chuckles]
[Seema] Congratulations
on your promotion, nuuri.
Thanks, everyone.
Hey, bud. Come here.
Sorry I'm late.
[clinking glass]
Ray, you make every single person
in this room so proud.
Proud of the man you are
and who you strive to be.
For the example you set for our son.
For the husband and friend we adore.
And for being the man
who hogs more blankets at night
-than is humanly possible.
-[all chuckle]
But even with that, you've always been
the person to warm my heart.
Congratulations
on your well-deserved promotion.
-[man] Cheers.
-[woman] Congratulations.
-I love you.
Eww.
Way to kill the moment, buddy.
-[chuckles]
-Mom, we're out of soda.
[Seema] There's plenty
in the fridge downstairs.
I'll get it.
I need a moment with you first.
What?
-I told you, everything is fine.
-You lied to me.
I called you, afraid for your life,
and you lied.
I have to hear from Annie Wellers
what really happened?
That that murderer attacked you
and that you shot him?
-Seems--
-I have to hear it from her?
-I didn't want you to worry.
-Well, I am worried.
I'm worried what this job
is doing to you, to us.
What's that supposed to mean?
I will always have your back.
To them. To everyone.
But I'm not an idiot.
-I didn't say you are.
-When you lie to my face, you do.
You're right.
I'm just trying
to keep everything together.
I don't want to screw any of this up.
I worked so hard for this, for us.
How-- How can I fix this?
You can start with telling me the truth.
And by getting more drinks.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
-[Ray grunting]
-I didn't come here to fight.
[panting]
Who are you?
I'm Daredevil.
The real one.
-You don't look like--
-I buried the red suit.
The man who attacked the Bulletin,
he resurrected it.
You do, however, match the description
of a guy who's been tuning up FBI agents.
Which is the last thing I ever wanted,
but you people haven't left me any choice.
If you'd just wake the hell up instead
of playing right into Fisk's hands.
He's using you, and I think you know it.
Now, I heard you confront
that psycho at the Bulletin.
I heard you try to stop him,
and he almost killed you, too.
So let me ask you this, Agent Nadeem...
Who do you think is the danger here?
Me... or him?
-[shushes]
-[door opens]
[Sami] Dad, Mom wants to know
where you are.
Don't come down, Sami.
I dropped a beer, there's glass.
Tell your mom I need
a couple of minutes to clean it up.
[Sami] Okay.
[door closes]
Let's say I believe the guy
that just broke into my house.
Let's just say that.
What do you got?
The man who attacked the Bulletin
dressed as Daredevil...
he's in the FBI.
Keep talking.