You got any stories, friend?
Yeah, I suppose I do.
You want to know
the saddest thing I ever saw?
When I was a boy,
my brother and I wanted a dog.
So, our father took in an old greyhound.
- Never seen a greyhound, have you?
- No.
Seen a few showdowns in my day.
A greyhound is a racing dog.
It spends its life running in circles,
chasing a bit of felt
made up like a rabbit.
One day, we took it to the park.
Now, Dad had warned us
how fast that dog was,
but we couldn't resist.
So, my brother took off the leash.
And in that instant,
the dog spotted a cat.
I imagine it must have looked
just like that piece of felt.
He ran.
Never saw a thing as beautiful
as that old dog running.
Until at last, he finally caught it.
And to the horror of everyone,
he killed that little cat.
Tore it to pieces.
Then he just sat there, confused.
That dog had spent its whole life
trying to catch that thing.
Now it had no idea what to do.
That is one humdinger of a story,
partner.
Shall we drink
to the lady with the white shoes?
Find me.
Show me how.
There she is. Pariah.
City of outcasts, delinquents,
thieves, whores, and murderers.
Once we cross the gates,
you will reap the full benefits of El
Lazo's gratitude for my safe return.
Are you all right?
Of course.
Did I do something wrong?
Just earlier, I thought I heard you
talking to someone.
Must have been the wind.
Come on.
This way.
The farther up we get from Sweetwater,
the more grandiose, the bigger
the narratives become.
It's beautiful in its own way.
For once, I agree.
Some of the park feels like
it was designed by committee,
market-tested,
but everything out here is more raw.
But it doesn't come cheap.
Rumor is, they are hemorrhaging cash.
We're considering buying them out.
Supposedly, this place was all started
by a partnership,
and then right before the park opened,
one of the partners killed himself.
It sent the park into a free fall.
I mean, I don't know any of the details.
I don't even know his name.
You must have a team of lawyers
looking at this place.
Yeah, well, they came up empty.
He's a complete mystery.
Not even a picture.
Well, whoever designed this place,
you get the feeling
they don't think very much of people.
Who are they?
They call themselves
the Army of New Virginia.
Everyone else calls
them the Confederados.
My father told me about them.
Ex-Confederate soldiers
that refused to surrender after the war.
Now they work as mercenaries
below the border.
They are the key to this game.
What game?
The biggest game there is.
War.
Supposedly, it's at the far reaches
of the park.
Now, I've never made it that far,
but this could be our chance.
I've known plenty of
truly fucked-up individuals in my time.
Few that'd hold a candle to you, sure.
But this one?
Theodore Flood? He was Wyatt's friend.
You know, his former associations
are exactly why we need him.
He's gonna lead me
straight to the big bad wolf.
I wouldn't count on that.
Aw, shit.
Didn't take you
for the charitable type.
You should have left him
on that tree to die.
You believe in fate, Lawrence?
If the bitch exists,
I'd like to kick her in the teeth
about now.
Don't be so glib.
You'll hurt my feelings.
As another old friend of mine
likes to say,
"There's a path for everyone.
Your path leads you back to me."
Do you ever wonder why I've kept you
with me this whole journey?
Maybe you like the pleasure of
my company, you sadistic fuck.
Maybe I do.
There's not a man in the world
who would take the tone with me you do.
In a past life, perhaps.
Teddy here is not looking long
for this world.
Nearest healer is in Pariah.
But ain't no way
he's gonna make it that far.
He's lost too much blood.
Are you lost?
Our friend here
is a little worse for the wear.
Any water nearby, son?
There's a creek
on the other side of the canyon.
Fetch us some, would you?
Now, hurry.
Our friend here needs some
if he's going to make it.
Get.
Too small.
What does that mean?
And what are you
sending him for water for?
I'm the one you made fill up
the sow's bag this morning.
A shame, really.
I always enjoy
our time together, Lawrence.
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
It means I was wrong.
The path that brought you here,
it wasn't for me.
It was for him.
Sorry, Lawrence.
Guess I'll see you on the other side.
Not looking good for you.
Closing.
Forget it. I win.
I always win!
Not fair.
All you had was a smashed cheekbone
and an ear.
You know how hard it is to get
the auricle curves symmetrical?
You had to, what,
plug and patch a couple bullet holes?
And a knife wound.
It was a contained incision.
Almost like they were
looking for something.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You really think this little fuck
puppet's coming to get you? Huh?
It got off the table and ran.
That's 'cause you forgot
to put her in sleep mode.
Yeah, I really think I remembered
to put her in sleep.
You know, that's the thing
about forgetting.
You think you remembered,
but you didn't.
- Break time.
- Yeah!
I've got a ham sandwich
and a nubile redhead
loaded up in the VR tank,
awaiting instruction.
Yeah.
Welcome back.
Looks like a couple gallons of Lawrence
swirling around in you did you good.
Ready to get back on the road?
Merciful thing
would be to put a bullet in me.
Whoever said I was merciful?
And it's not my fault you're suffering.
You used to be beautiful.
When this place started,
I opened one of you up once.
Million little perfect pieces.
And then they changed you.
Made you this sad, real mess.
Flesh and bone, just like us.
They said it would improve
the park experience.
But you know why they really did it?
It was cheaper.
Your humanity is cost-effective.
So was your suffering.
Whatever it is you want from me, mister,
I ain't gonna be worth a damn
to you like this.
Well, that would be a shame, Teddy.
After your misadventure,
Wyatt killed a settler family.
Made off with their daughter.
Girl, I think you know,
name of Dolores.
They have Dolores?
There it is.
The magic word. Come on.
Hey! Much obliged there, son.
Don't worry about him.
Someone'll be along for him shortly.
Mommy!
Are you all right?
When I ran from home,
I told myself it was the only way.
Lately, I've wondered if in every moment
there aren't many paths.
Choices.
Hanging in the air like ghosts.
And if you could just see them,
you could change your whole life.
Is that what you want?
You want to change your life?
Doesn't everybody want that?
I guess they do.
Maybe that's why they come here.
Whoever you were before
doesn't matter here.
There's no rules or restrictions.
You can change the story of your life.
You can become someone else.
No one will judge you.
No one in the real world will even know.
The only thing
holding you back is yourself.
What do you mean by that?
You said,
"No one in the real world will know."
I thought you weren't
supposed to notice things like that.
Why wouldn't I?
Recently, it seems like the whole world
is calling to me
in a way it hasn't before.
Billy, where the hell
have you been? Come on.
El Lazo's agreed to have
an audience with y'all tomorrow.
In the meantime,
there's a brothel I recommend.
Ooh. They have a contortionist.
Oh, I don't think Dolores
would find that very interesting.
Who the fuck cares what Dolores wants?
She's a goddamn doll!
Can you not say that around her?
I swear, I feel like she understands.
Of course you do.
May you rest
in a deep and dreamless slumber.
Hello, Dolores.
Do you know where you are?
- I'm in a dream.
- Yes, Dolores.
You're in my dream.
Tell me, do you know
what this dream means?
Dreams are the mind
telling stories to itself.
They don't mean anything.
No. Dreams mean everything.
They are the stories
we tell ourselves of what could be,
who we could become.
Have you been dreaming again, Dolores?
Imagining yourself breaking out
of your modest little loop?
Taking on a bigger role?
Well,
I suppose I can't begrudge you that.
My father told me to be satisfied
with my lot in life.
That the world owed me nothing.
And so, I made my own world.
Tell me, Dolores,
do you remember the man I used to be?
I'm sorry.
I'm forgetful, sometimes.
Hardly your fault.
But I'm sure you remember him.
Arnold.
The person who created you.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I recall
anyone by that name.
And yet, you can.
Somewhere, under all those updates,
he is still there.
Perfectly preserved.
Your mind is a walled garden.
Even death cannot touch
the flowers blooming there.
Have you been hearing voices?
Has Arnold been speaking to you again?
No.
You're...
You're hurting me.
Analysis.
When was your last contact with Arnold?
Last contact,
34 years, 42 days, seven hours ago.
Yes, Dolores.
The day Arnold died.
And you have no records
of any contact with him since?
No.
What was the last thing he said to you?
He told me I was going to help him.
Help him do what?
To destroy this place.
But you didn't, did you?
You've been content in your little loop.
For the most part.
I wonder...
If you did take on
that bigger role for yourself,
would you have been
the hero or the villain?
That's enough, Dolores.
I'm sorry for bothering you,
but there's no one else left
who was there.
No one who understands,
as we understand.
Are we very old friends?
No.
I wouldn't say "friends," Dolores.
I wouldn't say that at all.
He doesn't know.
I didn't tell him anything.
That's it.
Come on, little one.
Come on.
What the fuck?
Grab it!
Ah! God!
Damn it, you little shit!
Jesus! Tell me you're not this stupid.
You stole a bird
and a fucking behavior tablet?
I wasn't stealing. I was borrowing.
I haven't got the code right yet,
but with practice...
Is that your ace plan?
You're gonna fix up a birdie
and get yourself a promotion?
You're not a fucking ornithologist.
And you're sure as hell not a coder.
You are a butcher.
That is all you will ever be.
So, unless you wanna score yourself
a one-way ticket out of here
for misappropriating
corporate property...
You better destroy that fucking shit.
Now, come on, we got another body.
What?
It's her.
Again.
Jesus.
How the hell did you get this job if
you're scared shitless of these things?
Personality testing should have
weeded you out in the embryo.
Now, come on,
let's get this thing back in rotation.
Yesterday you seemed out of sorts.
Feeling better this morning?
I had troubled dreams.
But I feel more myself now.
Guys, come on.
El Lazo awaits.
I present to you El Lazo.
You're a hard man to find.
Most wanted men are.
We saved your man, Slim, here,
from quite a predicament.
In recompense,
I'd like an introduction
to your Confederado friends.
It's only fair.
There's no such thing as "fair" here.
In Pariah, justice ain't just blind,
she's crooked.
Bitch's scales are always tipped.
If you don't see how,
well, that's 'cause
they're tipped against you.
Still, by way of gratitude,
I can supply you a night
with some very amenable women.
I've fucked enough whores.
You're gonna need to sweeten the pot.
How about I sweeten it
by killing you quickly?
There's something you're seeking,
isn't there?
I know what that feels like.
I'm seeking something, too.
If you let us, I know we can help you.
How is it the lunatics
always find their way to me?
Then again, the Confederados are missing
a few bullets in their barrels, too.
You folks just might get along.
A Union convoy is transporting a shipment
of nitroglycerin from the front today.
The Confederados would like
to divest them of said shipment,
but we are not welcome
that side of the border.
A trio of travelers
such as yourselves, however...
You want us to help the Confederados
steal from the Union?
They're just going to use that nitro
to slaughter your people
below the border.
Personal grudges hold no sway
where profit is concerned.
Oh, we understand.
We're businessmen, too.
Very well, then.
But blondie here, she's gonna need
a change of clothes for the occasion.
My, my, look who's packing.
I don't aim to use this.
Those men are Union soldiers,
like my father was.
I know. We won't hurt them.
We're gonna stick to the plan.
We'll take the nitro and go.
All right.
It's showtime.
Halt!
Howdy.
My associates and I
are here to relieve you of your ride.
Someone's been telling you boys tales.
Nothing in this wagon worth taking.
The story I heard is one bullet from us,
and that "nothing"
blows you all to kingdom come.
Well, then you understand
why we cannot surrender it.
We're sworn to protect
the people of this young republic
from reckless, halfwits like you.
Call me halfwit again.
Please.
Do as he says.
We don't want to hurt you.
Yeah, I'd listen to her.
He'll shoot just to see the fireworks.
Hand them over.
Come on.
Hey. Come on down,
give me your guns. Everybody lives.
Nice and easy.
Right over here.
A little further, please.
Much obliged.
Here you go.
That's for lying.
Stop!
And that was for "halfwit."
And this...
No!
Stop! Please!
That's the spirit!
I knew you would get into this place.
Yes!
Yup.
Not bad for a day's work.
Vámonos.
We told them everyone would live.
Guys, looks like Slim didn't make it.
They put up a fight.
We made them pay for it, though.
Price of doing business. Slim knew that.
Had my doubts, El Lazo.
But you came through.
We're gonna blow these cactus-eaters
back to the dirt holes they crawled from.
Let's get it down to the station.
No time to waste.
If I may, Captain,
your men are weary,
with a long road ahead.
You have secured a great victory
for your cause today.
Perhaps an evening of celebration
is in order.
Anything you desire.
What do you say, Captain?
There's another train in the morning.
You will be a true asset to our ranks.
All right, Bart.
Let's try this again.
God damn it, man.
You're still miscalibrating
by four centimeters to the right.
You keep pouring whiskey on the guests,
I'm gonna have to reassign you
to a narrative
where your talents
will go tragically unappreciated.
Hey, that's the host
that tried to kill me.
- Where are you taking that?
- Livestock.
And then the incinerator.
Fuck this.
Fuck.
Isn't she from Behavior?
You think they found something?
- All right. Be cool, dickhead.
- Okay.
No one's looking at us.
Hi.
You're Destin, right?
That's correct.
I almost didn't recognize you
with your pants on. Here.
What the fuck?
There's a common misconception that
the hosts don't log sexual encounters
when they're underground
for reprocessing.
But, like I said, misconception.
Oh, fuck.
I need something.
QA sent a body down here,
the woodcutter from Sector 14.
- I want to see it.
- No.
I can't.
I need this job.
Look, Destin,
in a second, I'm gonna walk out of here,
and your friends are going to wonder
what this was all about.
Now, your answer can either be,
"I'm helping Behavior track a problem,"
or, "I'm a creepy necro-perv."
Up to you.
Five minutes,
then it's going in the incinerator.
Huh. You took a little more time than
that for your examination, didn't you?
All right, big guy.
What were you doing up there?
What the fuck?
You've been
holding out on me, Maurice.
Oh, shit.
We've got a big problem.
Turns out our big, dumb friend
had some hidden depths.
That is a laser-based satellite uplink.
This was in the body of the host?
Mmm-hmm. You were right.
Orion's Belt has three stars, not four.
Our friend wasn't drawing stars.
He was drawing a target.
Someone has been using our host
to smuggle data out of the park.
Now this... This I could get used to.
You're not going to indulge?
My flesh has tasted a greater pleasure
than any offered here.
War.
It's that good, huh?
Another round? On the house.
There's a place in glory
for a brown man who knows his rank.
You're two able-bodied men
of strong stock.
The road to glory could use more warriors
in its fight for our divine provenance.
That is just what we were thinking.
Come here, come here.
I know you want to play the war game,
but I'm not going anywhere
with these psychopaths.
If you don't like 'em,
once we get to the front,
you can just kill them
and join the revolutionaries.
No, Logan. Enough is enough.
I'm not doing this.
You actually let loose for once,
you shoot an unarmed man,
and now you feel bad because
you can't call yourself the hero.
Don't you get it yet?
There is no such thing
as heroes or villains.
It's just a giant circle jerk.
I think that philosophy says way more
about you than it does about the world.
And you, you see the world so clearly?
You probably think you're on this trip
because you're some kind of contender,
some threat to me?
I picked you precisely because
you will never be a threat to anyone.
My sister probably picked you
for the same reason.
I earned my place.
Nobody handed it to me.
Right. A lifetime of working hard,
following the rules,
and you finally reach the pinnacle
of your career trajectory...
Executive Vice President.
Upper middle management.
Do you remember the day that you finally
got those three fancy little letters?
EVP.
You walked into my office
in that cheap black suit of yours,
and you shook my hand
and you thanked me for the opportunity.
That was the best day of your life.
Right, buddy.
That's what I thought.
What does it mean?
The maze.
You must follow the maze.
What's wrong with me?
Perhaps, you are unraveling.
Right here.
Easy pumping that nitro into him.
Fill the empties with tequila
and seal them up.
Your work for the revolution
is not quite done yet, my friend.
Careful.
Slim always had a bad temper.
William, we have to go now.
Lazo's been conning us the whole time.
He was never going to give the nitro
to the Confederados. We have to run!
Of course we do.
That's how this place works, right?
They create an urgency
and a sense of danger,
so they can strip us down
to something raw, animalistic, primal.
It's a sick game,
and I don't want to be a part of it.
This isn't a game. They'll kill us.
But together,
I know we can find a way out.
How can you be sure?
There's a voice inside me,
telling me what I have to do.
And it's telling me I need you.
Shit.
They have Logan.
Help me.
No.
No more pretending.
I thought you had no appetite
for war, boy.
This is a declaration of war.
El Lazo set us up.
We can find him for you.
You can find him for us
by joining him in hell.
Dolores, run!
Dolores?
How did you do that?
You said people come here
to change the story of their lives.
I imagined a story
where I didn't have to be the damsel.
Now that train is our only chance
of making it out of here alive.
Motherfuckers.
You pull that trigger,
we'll all go up in a ball of hellfire.
So,
why don't you loosen your grip a mite?
It's okay.
I don't trust him.
Which is the first step
to truly knowing me.
Give me your gun, El Lazo.
Now that we're all friends,
you can call me Lawrence.
Now, why don't we settle in.
It's a long ride to the front.
You want a sip of this swill?
Don't worry, it ain't nitro.
I'm coming.
The girls are a little worn out,
but I can rouse one.
You boys want some company?
No. Just whiskey.
Lawrence's donation must be running low.
But we're short on time.
You need to buck up, Teddy.
I told you, no company.
Thought I might join you, anyway,
as I never like to drink alone.
Well, isn't this a rare honor?
Teddy, you know who this is?
Can't say that I do.
Everything good
that has ever happened in your life,
and everything rotten,
this is the man you have to thank.
How am I doing, Robert?
Any closer to finding
what I'm looking for?
And what is that, exactly?
We're looking for a man named Wyatt.
Killed a rancher back in Sweetwater,
took his daughter.
That last part doesn't sound familiar.
Figured your stories
could use a little embellishment.
You know, I always felt this place
was missing a real villain,
hence my humble contribution.
I admit, I lack the imagination
to even conceive of someone like you.
The urgency, however,
doesn't quite fit the character.
It betrays a certain anxiety.
Now, Wyatt, on the other hand,
that's something new.
Is he just another stooge for the
tourists to mount on their wall at home,
or have you finally made
a worthy adversary?
Someone to stop me
from finding the center of the maze.
And what is it
you're hoping to find there?
You know why you exist, Teddy?
The world out there,
the one you'll never see,
is one of plenty.
A fat, soft teat
people cling to their entire life.
Every need taken care of,
except one.
Purpose.
Meaning.
So, they come here.
They can be a little scared,
a little thrilled,
enjoy some sweetly affirmative bullshit,
and then they take a fucking picture
and they go back home.
But I think there's a deeper meaning
hiding under all that.
Something that the person
who created it wanted to express.
Something true.
Well, if you're looking
for the moral of the story,
you could quite simply ask.
I'd need a shovel.
The man I'd be asking died 35 years ago.
Almost took this place with him.
Almost, but not quite. Thanks to me.
Well, maybe he left something behind.
I wonder what I would find
if I opened you up.
Even at death's door,
you're still a loyal pet.
Is that why you came here, Robert?
To try to talk me out of it?
On the contrary.
Far be it from me to get in the way
of a voyage of self-discovery.
Mr. Flood.
We must look back and smile
at perils past, mustn't we?
We should get back on the road.
Time's a-wasting.
Hello, Felix.
It's time you and I had a chat.