♪ Wonderful electric ♪
♪ Cover me in you ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love with a strict machine... ♪
Fuck yes! I'm up!
♪ I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love with a strict machine... ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love with a strict machine ♪
♪ I'm in love with a sick machine ♪
♪ I'm in love. ♪
I didn't see him, Mia.
Fuck.
Fucking hell, man.
Rob, we've gotta go and look.
Oh my God, Rob.
- Hey, it's all right, baby.
Oh my god.
- Fuck.
- Oh my god.
Fuck.
- We've gotta... Gotta call someone.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Fucking hell, Mia. Think, OK, hey?
You need to think, baby.
We... We've been fucking caning it,
yeah?
I... I... I... I...
This is prison, yeah?
A fucking instant prison.
I've... Fuck...
I've got fuck knows how much drink in me.
I fucking hit a guy.
They would put me in the cell.
I'm the driver, they'll...
They'll put me in a cell.
They'll fucking keep me there.
- That's what they'll fucking do.
- We can't just leave him here.
Shut the fuck up, Mia, right.
Shut...
- What, just leave him here in the road?
- I need to fucking think, OK?
I need to think. Fuck!
Fuck. Fuck.
OK, there's a... There's a...
There's a lake over there.
And there's a sleeping bag
in the boot.
You keep an eye on the road.
Keep an eye on the road.
No!
- Mia.
- Don't.
Mia, come on.
- No!
- Baby, come on.
- Come on.
Mia, you get the fucking rocks.
I'll stack them, OK?
I need loads of fucking rocks.
Just put a fucking pile...
Put the fucking pile there...
Put the pile...
Close it up. Close it up.
Close his head. Close his head.
Three...
Two...
One...
Um, it's an honour
to be speaking here today
amongst such impressive company.
Uh, I'm thrilled to have been shared...
I'm thrilled to have been asked
to share my vision of the future
such as it is.
Looking around
at a world of injustice, intolerance
and huge environmental challenges
it's hard to imagine a bright future,
but we can and we must.
It's the only way
that we can build a better tomorrow.
Um, so...
I'll start with a funny story.
Right. I'm off.
Bye-bye.
- See you late on.
- See you tomorrow.
OK.
- Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Bye, mum.
- There we go.
Hiya, puppy.
One moment.
Coming.
Just a second.
- Mrs Carmichael?
- Yes.
I'm here on behalf of Realm Insurance.
Just need to log
your recollections about the accident.
- Am I alright to come in?
- Uh, OK then.
Someone who has risen to become
one of the most innovative architects
of her generation.
Not just an architect of buildings
but communities.
But enough of me, telling you about her,
please welcome Mia Nolan.
Thank you, Martin. Thanks.
It's an honour to be speaking here
amongst such impressive company.
Good evening. Welcome to Fences Pizza.
Your pizza is ready for collection.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Hey. Hey.
- Did your chin catch Dutch fur disease?
- Mia, fuck you.
Well, I didn't say I didn't like it.
Come in.
What's it been?
It's been like two years now, hasn't it?
Uh, three.
Dropping in on my hotel room.
It must be important.
Shall we find somewhere to eat?
- Yeah, well I...
Uh, I got in touch
cos I saw that you were in town for...
What is it?
Some... Some architecture thing?
It's a forum they call it.
People actually pay
to come and listen to me talk.
Imagine that.
Almost does my head in.
And you're looking good.
Is that the gym?
- Well, you look...
- I look like dog shite, me.
Uh, I'll save you the bother.
Dried up dog shite.
- Do you want a drink?
- Uh, knocked it on the head.
What, you quit? Like, fully quit?
Nine months, three weeks, two days.
Well done. Well, that's great.
You go ahead.
- Really, go on.
- You sure?
- Absolutely.
- OK.
Well, you picked
a terrible place to come see me cos...
It reeks of hops
all the way down the street outside here.
- Did you notice that?
- No.
It's like a full-on beer smell.
Can't help your sobriety that.
But I probably shouldn't be talking
about booze, should I?
Rob, I hope you're not here
to talk about what I...
It's about that, yeah.
I've been... I've been thinking
about it again, that night.
- Rob.
- I can't not think...
We said that we'd put it out of our minds.
Weren't we just gonna try and keep it out?
I can't. I'm sorry.
It was a long time ago.
Well, in here, it's now.
Yeah, I know.
Why today?
Why is it preying on your mind today?
- There's a news story.
- A news story?
A... A featured article,
well, whatever you call it.
I... I... I printed it for you.
Mia? That... That's her.
It's his wife.
- You don't know that's his wife.
There is a photo of him at the bottom.
It's him.
And the poor cunt,
they never found him...
so she never remarried.
She... She never fucking moved house.
She stayed where she is,
in case he came back.
All this time, Mia.
She's still waiting for him.
That's dreadful.
But what can we do?
I'm gonna write her a letter.
- No.
- Anonymous.
I am not gonna mention you.
- Rob, no.
You'll open up God knows what.
You'll just rake it all up.
- I... I can't live with it, Mia.
- There's things that they can do now
cos they can trace it back.
They can trace it back.
- They'll find the body and they'll find us.
- They won't find us.
Yes, they will and then we're fucked.
Look, when... when...
when I quit alcohol
they told me to make amends
with anyone I've ever hurt.
Who have I hurt more than her?
Yeah. They also say
you're not supposed to hurt anyone else
so what about me?
- What about her?
No, no, no.
No.
Fuck!
It was your idea.
It was your fucking idea.
I know.
I know and that... I... I'm sorry.
Fifteen years, 15 years,
the fucking shame, the fucking guilt.
I've got somewhere. I've got a life.
You don't know. You don't understand Rob.
- That's not the point...
- You don't understand.
You don't understand.
You're not married.
I've got a son. He's nine years old.
You've seen photos of him.
Think of him, please.
I'm sorry.
I sat on this for you.
- I fucking sat on this for you.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey, look at me.
- Look at me.
- I've made up my mind.
And... And that's how it is.
- Please, please, please.
Please, please, please, Rob.
Hey, listen, I understand.
I understand.
Do you?
Yeah. Come on, let's talk about this.
No, no, I can't stay here.
- No, no, no, no.
- What... What are you doing? Let go.
Mia, I'm fucking leaving.
What are you doing?
Mia, let the... Mia, let the fuck...
Let the fucking go.
Fuck.
Jesus!
Shit!
Huh?
Codger.
That's his name, Codger.
What?
- Ah, you don't like him.
- Well, it's not that...
It's so hard
to get presents for you.
No, I like him. He's... fluffy.
Exactly.
No, Ali's gonna love him.
It's just we've got
a lot going on, what with Ali and...
I'll take him back.
The pet shop guy was OK.
It won't be a problem at all.
- No, no, no. You're right.
It'll be good for Ali.
Codger stays.
He's Codger the Lodger.
Changing time. Uh...
Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
The fucking van...
Room service.
Lovely. Thank you.
Hi, love.
Yeah, it was...
No, the speech went great...
Yeah, I'm back in the morning.
No, I'm just tired. That's all.
Um, did he?
Oh, that's great.
No, don't put him on.
Hi. Hey.
Hey, dad said you were great
in your rehearsal for your play
you had a rehearsal.
Yeah, I'm proud of you.
Yeah.
I love you.
So that's one night.
You've had room service
and a 9.99 charge for the movie.
For a movie?
Mm. You watched a film last night, no?
- Yeah.
I was in last night, yeah.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
I'm from Realm Insurance,
about the pizza van accident.
Oh, come in.
I mean, it'll cover you
for up to four months
but that is quite a substantial claim.
Well, I was heading off on tour
with the Philharmonic next week
Europe, Middle East, Australia.
Not now.
Well, as I'm you appreciate
with a pay-out of this size
we will need to investigate
the circumstances of the accident.
Yeah, of course.
Now, that stretch of the street
has a security camera
vandalised, by some kids, I'm guessing,
paint-balled right in the wrong place.
But the, um, delivery van thing
must've had a camera.
Not working.
Oh, for God's sake.
No, that's actually good for your claim.
Fences Pizza's a big company.
They've been in the press claiming
their driverless fleet has a good record.
The malfunctioning camera,
that's a step toward negligence.
So if we can prove full liability
you could also consider filing
a substantial civil case
under our litigation wing?
Could be a lot of money.
Yeah. OK. I'm sold.
Great.
Now, I'll just hook you up
to the recaller here.
That's one of those, um,
memory dredgers?
We prefer corroborators.
- Police things, aren't they?
- Mm, not since last year.
We all have them now.
- OK. May I?
- Yeah.
I feel like a specimen.
So, this accesses engrams,
your memories of what happened.
Now, they're subjective.
They may not be totally accurate
and they're often emotional
but by collecting a range of recollections
from yourself and any witnesses
we can help build a corroborative
picture of the whole.
I don't remember anything.
It's a total blank.
Uh,
I've got something that might help.
What? Getting drunk?
The accident happened a few hundred metres
from the Castle Port Brewery.
The whole area smells like a pub.
No sipping. Just take a sniff.
Aroma's a great memory boost.
Helps anchor you to where you were.
- Mm, that's familiar.
- OK.
Now, hold that smell in your mind.
Close your eyes and picture the street.
Getting something now?
Yeah, I went to a sort of...
comic shop.
Culty stuff.
Um...
I think it started snowing
when I came out
heavy snow.
Um, there was music from a car.
I like that song.
There was a woman
in a yellow coat coming towards me.
Could you recall on her face?
She had this weird lipstick on,
stood out.
And she's pretty.
Yeah, yeah, and that too.
Well, the more emotional your response
the more vivid your memory of it is.
So there was the music and a girl,
and then what happened?
Well, I went to cross the road.
Wasn't really thinking about anything,
and uh...
And that's just when it just goes. Um...
Uh... that's OK
- What you've given me is already useful.
- Really?
Well, I've got someone
to look for:
Little Miss Yellow Coat.
- Hey!
- Our wanderer returns.
Yeah.
You don't know
how to fix this, do you?
Um, yeah, I'll have a look at it later.
- Hi, mum.
- Hey, you.
Tonight's the big night.
♪ We could've been anything
that we wanted to be... ♪
It's the school musical, Bugsy Malone.
You alright?
Yeah. Yeah.
They've got this, um, sound system
for the backing tracks
that they can't work out
and I said that I'd help them out.
So, I'm gonna be there all day.
You're not gonna die of loneliness
here on your own, are you?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Well, we'll see you later, 7:30.
Mm-hm.
- Don't forget.
I won't.
See ya.
- See you later.
- Bye.
It was only yesterday.
You're efficient.
The fresher the memory,
the stronger it is
and the stronger the memory,
the stronger the case.
I'll also just get you
to take a sniff of this.
God knows what they think
we're doing in here.
OK. If you close your eyes,
I'm also gonna play a piece of music.
God. Yeah, yeah, that... That was on.
How weird.
Hold those things in your mind
and picture what you saw.
♪ Anyone ♪
♪ You can blame me... ♪
I was on Stanhope Road,
near the hotel place
looking at flats and stuff, you know,
window shopping.
I saw this guy walking towards me.
I remember thinking
he looked sort of sweet.
♪ You can run around... ♪
The music was coming from the car,
which pulled off.
Actually, that was when
the delivery thing drove past.
Fences Pizza?
What sort of speed was it going?
You mean, was it going too fast?
- Um...
- Try and focus on the vehicle.
Uh, maybe.
Um...
Um, I don't know. I couldn't really say.
What about the impact itself?
Well, I didn't really see it.
I just saw the aftermath really.
A moment earlier
you saw a bright light?
Yeah.
Like a camera flash just before.
Just outside the dentist place.
And I'm assuming
your window glazing's soundproof?
Yes. We get the odd screamer.
Oh, well, I won't bother
with the music then.
Look, to be honest.
The memory's a bit embarrassing as in...
Oh, don't worry. I've seen it all.
Do you have to use that thing?
Look, your memories
will be sealed and private
unless they indicate
you're harming yourself or another person.
Go on then.
I'd had a patient.
Hm, so I see.
She left around six I think.
I stayed to clear up.
You saw something from the window?
There was a guy in the hotel window.
Well, what can I say?
He was picturesque.
Did you take a photo?
Well, I tried to.
I left the flash on by mistake
so, all I got was the reflection.
- And then?
- I was going to take another one.
I saw some woman staring at something.
So I looked down.
It was just a load of commotion.
There was a woman in a sort of lime coat.
Mm. Yellow, actually.
Well, I knew it was vivid.
Well, memories can be subjective.
What we do is build up an overall average,
a crowd-sourced picture of reality.
Did you see the vehicle
that hit the pedestrian?
Any sense of its speed?
I didn't see the actual crash.
Sorry.
OK.
You won't tell anyone... about the photo?
Don't need to put that in my report.
Safe with me.
That'd be room 304.
Can you tell me who stayed there?
You're not the police.
- No, but...
Then you'd have to lodge
for an information request for that.
Oh, but that could take
up to a week to process.
Sorry, management's an arse about it
ever since that thing with, uh...
What's his name? The judge of Hot Shots.
Anyway he got caught
with a rent boy and, um...
a tabloid got his name
by hacking our booking system
and yeah, they're tight as anything
by the rule now.
Hm, the woman I'm after
hasn't done anything.
I just think
she might have seen something
outside yesterday evening about 6.30.
Oh I can...
I can tell you that she wasn't outside.
And I know what she was looking at.
- How so?
I can't tell you who she is, but, um...
She's into interesting films.
We logged the in-house movies
that people watch and, um...
Her choice stood out.
Oh.
How nice for her.
Thanks.
Aw, bless you.
- How's your pizza accident going?
- Mm.
A pain in the arse.
Can't pinpoint liability cos no one agrees
on the speed of the bloody thing
and I can't find anyone
who actually saw the impact.
Well, not yet.
Except maybe smudge face here,
whoever she is.
Oh, bingo.
Mia Nolan, you might be the one,
if you'll talk.
What, if she'll talk?
She was doing something embarrassing
in the hotel room
watching a porn film.
She might not want me poking around
in her head.
She's like 50 miles out of town.
Do you mind if I head there now?
It's a bit late.
Well, if I sort this out in 24 hours,
I get two times bonus.
Well...
Go. Go.
♪ I know I won't ever let you go ♪
♪ Oh, it's more ♪
♪ Than I could ever stand ♪
♪ Oh, but anyone ♪
♪ Who knows what love is ♪
♪ Will understand. ♪
Hi, I'm Shazia. I'm from Realm Insurance.
- Yeah, I've already got insurance...
- I'm not selling anything.
I'm following up on an incident
you might've seen, a road accident.
I don't know anything
about an accident.
This was only yesterday.
An accident?
On Stanhope Road.
Medina Plaza Hotel
a pedestrian was hit
by a delivery vehicle
Fences Pizza, driverless.
Um, right, yeah.
I'm sorry, actually, I did.
When you first mentioned it,
I just didn't think of it.
But, um, yeah, I did.
So, you saw what happened?
Uh, yeah there was
a guy crossing the street
and this little van thing
sort of just clipped him. It was quick.
Do you mind if I ask you
a few questions about it?
It won't take long.
- I'm sorry. I'm really busy.
I've got... I've got...
I don't wanna sound heavy,
but it is a legal requirement
since last year.
It's a legal requirement?
Aye, if you've witnessed
an incident, yes.
Look, I have to notify the police
when people refuse
and when they get involved,
it just drags everything out, so...
Come in.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Just that way.
OK.
What does that do?
The recaller?
Just helps me get a record
of what happened.
May I?
I mean, I can just tell you what happened.
I can remember.
Um, the... The van hit the guy
and he fell over
and then people came to help.
How fast was it going though,
the delivery vehicle?
Um...
See? I just need a sense of that.
It's sometimes hard to articulate
exactly what your mind's eye seen
but capturing your impression
of what you saw is really useful.
- OK, but I've got...
- That's all I'm interested in.
Look, you can read the terms here,
if you like.
All the legal stuff is in there.
Look, I don't care
what you might've been doing
in the hotel room in your own time.
Not gonna ask you anything about that.
Won't go there.
- OK.
- Private stuff is private stuff.
- So it's just the accident?
- Just that.
Ah, it's a bit of a long read,
isn't it?
Do you... Do you want a tea or a coffee?
Oh, coffee'd be great.
- Yeah, OK. Espresso?
- Perfect.
Do you mind if I just go and,
uh, have a pee
if I'm gonna be sat down a while?
- Yeah, sure.
- OK.
I ate hotel food, had room service.
I ate room service.
I was in the hotel room on my own.
I watched porn.
Saw the accident.
Come on. Focus.
I was on my own.
There you go.
Take a sniff.
- What's that for?
- It'll just help your recall.
That's it.
The music will help jog your memory too.
OK, close your eyes.
OK.
Let's start with you in your hotel room.
♪ You can blame me ♪
♪ Try to shame me... ♪
I was in my room.
And I ordered room service.
All I need is the accident.
Uh, try to picture the moments
leading up to the impact.
...the fucking shame, the fucking guilt.
No!
- I sat on this...
- Shut the fuck up...
...the fucking go.
Rob?
No!
♪ Anyone! ♪
♪ No, they don't know
what happiness and love is... ♪
Well, that's great.
Got what I needed on the van, so...
I'll be off.
- OK.
That's it.
- So, you've got everything you needed?
- Yeah.
Doesn't take that long.
It was just a simple thing
with the speed, so...
- Right, yeah.
- Yeah.
Sorry about being short.
It's been a long day.
- No, it's fine...
- A lot of work on.
Did you...
So you got everything you needed?
Yeah, yeah, got it all.
Don't worry. Thank you so much.
I know this sounds silly, but, um...
You know, sometimes,
I just think mad things
and it doesn't mean anything.
Do you know what I man?
When you have...
When you have strange thoughts?
No it's, it's fine.
Like I said, I...
I got what I needed, so thank you.
Yeah, but do you know what I mean?
It's not like, um... It's just my head.
Come on!
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry, um...
Um...
I fucked up and I panicked.
Does your head hurt?
OK.
What am I gonna do with you?
I mean, I can let you go...
but you're gonna tell someone,
aren't you?
No.
I know, but even if you say you won't
your recollections are all recorded.
- I won't.
- They're not?
No.
If I take that off your mouth,
will you promise not to scream?
Do you promise?
Get the recaller, I'll delete...
I'll delete them. It won't go anywhere.
That I know, cos I tried to delete it
and I couldn't figure it out.
I won't say anything to anyone, I promise.
I'll forget the whole thing.
No one will know. I won't say anything.
I wish I believed you.
I mean it.
I mean it. I've... I've seen things.
I've seen things on the recaller:
secrets, personal things,
I've never spilled any of it.
I'm not allowed to. It's the law.
It's like confessions...
It's like Catholic confession.
It'd be illegal for me to say anything,
totally illegal, even if I wanted to.
None of that's true, is it?
- It is, I swear.
- It's not.
Did you tell anyone
that you were coming here today?
No.
- You're lying.
- I'm not. I swear, I'm not lying.
No, I swear.
I swear.
No!
No.
What did you do
before you came here today?
♪...understand
♪ Oh, but anyone... ♪
♪ who knows what love is... ♪
I like that song.
♪ will understand... ♪
Who did you speak to?
- Bingo. Mia Nolan, if she'll talk.
- If she'll talk?
No!
No.
- Is that your husband?
- No!
No.
I'm really sorry.
No!
Will you please
close your eyes for me?
Everyone's in their costumes already.
Mia, please, you know,
make sure you're on time.
Yeah, I know, love.
Are you far off?
Remember it starts at 7:30.
I'm gonna make it, 7:30.
- 7:30.
- Yeah.
- Alright.
- I'll see you outside.
- See you in a bit, sweetheart.
- OK.
Cutting it a bit fine.
Yeah.
It was just work stuff, you know.
Jesus Christ. What'd you eat,
a vineyard?
No, I just finished a design,
so I had a glass of wine.
Fuck off, a glass.
- Let's just go in, alright?
- Alright. Fine.
"You give a little love" from Bugsy Malone
♪ We could've been anything
that we wanted to be ♪
♪ And it's not too late to change ♪
♪ It's been decided
to give it some thought ♪
♪ Maybe you'll agree we really ought ♪
♪ Two, three, four ♪
♪ We could've been anything
that we wanted to be ♪
♪ Yes, that decision was ours ♪
♪ It's been decided,
We're weaker divided ♪
♪ Let friendship double up our powers... ♪
Yeah.
Just confirming a double homicide.
One adult male and one male infant.
Yeah, yeah.
Who kills a baby?
I don't know. Probably someone worried
about leaving a witness.
Blood bath upstairs and this downstairs.
But it couldn't see.
Poor fucker was born blind, apparently.
I have to say.
I have absolutely no idea
who I'm looking for.
So it's a good job you're not asking me.
Come on. Let's clear out there.
Let's let the recall team
do their job. Come on.
Yeah.
♪ You give a little love
and it all comes back to you ♪
♪ La, la, la, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ You know you're gonna be remembered
for the things that you say and do ♪
Put your hands together
for this year's fantastic school choir.
What a lovely evening.
Thank you so much for coming.
Put your hands together
for Mrs Hendricks...
That went above and beyond
with the costumes...
They look fantastic...
"You Give a Little Love" from Bugsy Malone