with these sacks of coal.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I didn't know who they were going to send.
I didn't know
they were going to send eggplants.
It's an Italian's job. Disgraceful!
-Mr Big Shot. Spend, spend, spend.
-Enough, Pop.
The floor was mouldy. We had to change it.
He who arrives late has no bed!
-Everything okay?
-Yes. Everything is fine.
Good. We'll meet you
at the hotel in Pittsburgh.
Make a reservation for dinner.
We'll rehearse immediately after.
-Who's the eggplant?
-I'm working for him.
What happened? You lose a bet?
What the hell ya doing?
You need work, you come to me!
I'll find you work.
Matter of fact, I can use you this week.
-You'll make some real money.
-A sack of money.
-I'm already making money.
-I'll double it.
This isn't the right place
to talk about it.
Meet me in the bar at eight o'clock sharp.
Understand?
-Okay, I'll see you later.
-Forget this guy.
With you friend Dominic?
Before accepting his offer,
we need to talk.