[eerie music playing]
[eerie music intensifies]
[silence]
["Bright Eyes" by Art Garfunkel playing]
♪ Is it a kind of dream? ♪
♪ Floating out on the tide ♪
[moans]
♪ Following the river of death
Downstream ♪
♪ Oh, is it a dream? ♪
♪ There's a fog along the horizon ♪
♪ A strange glow in the sky ♪
♪ And nobody seems to know where you go ♪
♪ And what does it mean? ♪
♪ Oh, is it a dream? ♪
♪ Bright eyes ♪
♪ Burning like fire ♪
♪ How can you close and fail? ♪
♪ How can the light
That burned so brightly ♪
♪ Suddenly burn so pale? ♪
♪ Bright eyes ♪
♪ Is it a kind of shadow ♪
♪ Reaching into the night? ♪
♪ And nobody ever knows when you go ♪
♪ And where do you start? ♪
♪ Oh, into the dark ♪
♪ Bright eyes ♪
♪ Burning like fire ♪
♪ How can you close and fail? ♪
♪ How can the light
That burned so brightly ♪
♪ Suddenly burn so pale? ♪
♪ Bright eyes ♪
[music fades]
Got a customer.
-I'm on my lunch.
-Yeah, I can smell that.
Mine's in five minutes,
so if I start with a customer now,
it cuts into my break.
[muzak softly playing]
That's Keith Holligan.
So?
So he murdered his wife.
Oh, it were manslaughter.
Judge said she drove him to it.
Don't seem like the strangling type to me.
-Puffy hands.
-Surely, we don't have to serve him.
Everyone needs shoes, Nida.
How about doing your job?
[sighs]
[sniffing]
[sighs in disgust]
[Keith groans]
[Keith] I think I'm going to need the 11.
I'm large.
For my height.
-Sure you can't do a discount?
-I'm so sorry. No, we can't.
I'm just a bit strapped
till the end of the month.
I can put them aside for you.
Go on, then.
If you fancy writing down your number,
I won't mind.
[chilling music playing]
[Keith gasping]
[muzak softly playing]
Reckon he's into your sort.
[man 1] Time and time and time again!
And so we've been treated
to this rather pathetic display
of a flailing government
holding on for dear life.
And it is thanks
to Mr. Callaghan's government limping on
that our nation has suffered
through a winter of discontent.
Now, they promise us a brighter future,
yet the fact remains
that Labour isn't working.
-He's a bit bloody young, in't he?
-He's good though.
They haven't just failed nationally,
but right here in Tipley.
You only have to look around to see it.
Rubbish in the streets. Crime on the rise.
The character of your neighborhood
under threat.
[murmurs of agreement]
[man 2] Bloody right!
We don't wanna end up like Cheetham.
[man 1 laughing]
You hear what he said? He said,
"We don't wanna end up like Cheetham."
[crowd laughs]
[man 1] Of course, we all want change,
but the right kind.
So don't just hope for a better future.
Vote for one!
[crowd clapping]
Thank you. Thank you very much.
[indistinct chatter]
[keys jingling]
[TV reporter] As the election nears,
polls show
Mrs. Thatcher's Conservative Party
retains a commanding lead.
Violence erupts as the far-right
National Front march through Southall,
causing thousands in damage
with over 100 arrests
and five police officers hospitalized.
US and Soviet
nuclear non-proliferation talks hit--
[man on TV] Down two places to number six,
"Does Your Mother Know" by ABBA.
A new entry at five for Paul McCartney
and Wings with "Good Night Tonight."
And at number four right now here
in the studio with their hit "Rasputin,"
it's Boney M.
♪ There lived a certain man
In Russia long ago ♪
♪ He was big and strong
In his eyes, a flaming glow ♪
♪ Most people looked at him
With terror and with fear ♪
♪ But to Moscow chicks
He was such a lovely dear ♪
♪ Ra ra Rasputin
Lover of the Russian queen ♪
♪ There was a cat that really was gone ♪
♪ Ra ra Rasputin
Russia's greatest love machine ♪
♪ It was a shame how he carried on ♪
[music stops]
[car engine starts]
[muzak softly playing]
[ethereal music playing]
[music stops]
You're dreaming
if you think you can pull that off.
Mr. Duncan wants a word.
[man] So, Nida, it's nothing major,
but I understand you're in the habit
of eating your lunch in the stockroom.
-Oh--
-It's fine.
Everybody does it.
We don't mind. But it's…
it's what you're eating.
You see, most people's food,
um, normal food,
it doesn't tend to linger afterwards.
It's not really fair on your coworkers,
and there is a chance it could…
well, it could get into the shoe leather.
So, if you must eat in there,
maybe just bring in a sandwich.
Like a cheese and ham sandwich.
Or just a cheese sandwich, if you're
one of those that doesn't do ham.
-Of course, I'm sorry to have to ask--
-I'll do sandwiches from now on.
You know, I think Vicky will be
very appreciative.
But as… as will we all.
The thing is,
I did bring a biryani in today.
I see.
[inhales]
Well, um, it's-- How about the basement?
-Yes! Yes, you could use the basement.
-The basement?
Mr. Possett himself used to work
down there in the early days.
He didn't like to be disturbed.
It couldn't be further from civilization.
[chuckles]
Thank you, Mr. Duncan.
Very good. Very good. Thank you, Nida.
What?
-[chilling music playing]
-[Nida grunting]
[chilling music intensifies]
[gasping]
[chilling music stops]
Hello, what do you want?
Just taking my lunch break.
[unsettling music playing]
Hmm.
Hmm?
[menacing music playing]
[gasps]
[groans]
[menacing music intensifies]
-[music stops]
-[clatter in distance]
[ethereal music playing]
[ethereal music playing on TV]
[male on TV] Transuranic heavy elements
may not be used where there is life.
Medium atomic weights are available.
Gold, Lead, Copper.
Jet, Diamond, Radium,
Sapphire, Silver, and Steel.
Sapphire and steel have been assigned.
-[male voice echoes] Hello.
-[gasps]
[boy on TV] So, where are they?
Mum and Dad?
-[girl] Gone.
-[boy] Gone? Gone where?
Out of the door, downstairs?
Well, where, then?
Here in the room?
You mean they disappeared, Helen?
[male voice] Uh, yeah, hi.
So, my name's Gaap. I'm a demon.
You anointed this talisman
with your blood,
so now we're bound together and-- [grunts]
[muffled] Bloody hell.
Look, I… I've got
a whole introductory speech here.
We… we gotta work together.
-Can you pick me up?
-[Nida whimpers]
Come on, pick me up.
Just… just pick me up.
Please?
That's it. Come on. Come on.
I… I… I won't bite.
I promise. Come on.
[clearly] Right. So, as I was saying,
you anointed the talisman,
and the rules are you've gotta carry out
three human sacrifices
over the next three days
or else the world's gonna end.
What?
If you want me to help you,
you need to permit me entry.
Uh…
Dost thou permit me entry? Yes or no?
This isn't real.
You have to say "yes."
Just say the word "yes." Say it.
If you say "yes," I'll… I'll stop, okay?
I'll go away.
You'll never hear from me again, like this
didn't happen. Just say "yes." Say it.
Say it. Come on, say it. Say it.
Say it! Say it! Say it!
Yes!
[electrical buzzing]
[whimpers]
-[unnatural deep breathing]
-[whimpers]
[Nida breathing anxiously]
[snarling]
-[breathes heavily]
-[yelping]
[Gaap] Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on. What's the matter?
[Nida whimpering]
[Gaap] All right, I gotta be honest.
I lied about going away.
Uh, hang on. Is it… is it these?
Yeah, yeah, sorry. My regular appearance
is probably a bit much for this realm.
-[breathing heavily]
-Uh, just a sec. [demonic echoing]
[breathes shakily]
[Gaap in normal voice]
This any better for ya?
I peered into your soul,
and apparently, this is a physical look
you find appealing, so…
Maybe you saw this recently and liked it?
I don't know. Let me have a look.
[snaps fingers]
Wow.
-Uh…
-[breathes shakily]
Okay. Am I, like, a clown?
[whimpers]
This how clowns dress in your realm?
I mean…
I mean, I can… I can work with it, but…
[chuckles] Uh…
[gasping]
You have got to get over the shock
and just talk to me.
You know, we have got to work together.
I'm dreaming.
Dream-- You're really not, you know.
You're not real.
You're not real. You're not real.
[sniffles]
[panting]
[whimpers]
Hiya. Like I said,
we have got to work together.
It's blood and bone. You marked
the talisman. I don't make the rules.
I mean, basically, we need to deliver
three sacrifices by Maymass--
Uh, that's May Day to you. Or else it's…
Well, it's burning skies time.
[breathing heavily]
I sense you need some convincing.
Uh… [sighs]
Let me show you
how this will play out, all right?
What'll happen if we don't succeed.
You ready?
Ready?
Three, two, one.
[high-pitched tone]
[gasps]
[siren blaring]
[Nida screaming]
-[siren stops]
-[gasping, coughing]
So, basically, this is the sort of thing
we're dealing with.
-[siren blaring]
-[Nida coughing]
-[siren stops]
-Scorching wall of flame.
It's agonizing death for all, and so on.
[siren blaring]
-[siren stops]
-[Nida whimpering]
[siren blaring]
[whimpers in pain]
[people screaming]
-[siren stops]
-[Nida whimpering]
-[siren blaring]
-[screams]
-[siren stops]
-[Nida whimpering]
[whimpering]
[silence]
See, burning people, they do smell
like you'd expect, don't they?
Like a… a burger on a griddle.
It's quite nice
if you disassociate from it.
Mind you, the charred hair
really gets stuck in your throat.
To be honest, I don't want the apocalypse
to come about any more than you do.
So let's stop it happening, you and me.
All we have to do
is deliver three sacrifices in three days.
It's only three killings.
Like I said, animals don't count.
You have to do humans.
And there's gotta be a cadence to it.
One a day.
[chuckles] It's one kill a day. It… it's…
Wha… what?
[panting]
That is fewer people than die falling off
ladders in the same time period.
You'd be less lethal than a ladder.
If I talk to you, you're real,
so I'm not gonna talk to you.
Well, we started conversing already,
so that ship has sailed.
-No, it hasn't.
-Oh, oh, yes, it has.
-[Nida grunts]
-Uh, don't worry. We're a team.
I'm on your side here, you know?
Let's just get kill number one
under your belt. Start racking 'em up.
You can stop it
because I am not killing anyone.
[Nida continues indistinctly]
…so I don't know
why you keep talking to me!
That's what I'm here for.
All right? Moral support.
So just hold on to that brick.
Let's go thwack someone.
-What brick?
-The one in your hand, love.
[Nida gasps]
I'm not doing what you say.
What's that, love?
[Gaap] Oh yeah.
Yeah, he's perfect.
There's no witnesses.
-Talk about beginner's luck.
-[Nida] No.
One quick pop to the head and you're done.
Please, make him stop.
Make who stop?
Love? Are you all right?
-I need a doctor.
-You want me to go and call one?
Would it help if I told you
I can see into this man's soul,
and he absolutely deserves to die?
-Shut up!
-[Gaap] He's got a daughter.
Her name's Laura. She's eight years old.
Do you wanna know what he does to her?
To Laura?
-No, I don't wanna know.
-Sorry, love. I don't follow.
He pays Laura a little nighttime visit--
[Nida] Shut up!
[man] Is everything okay?
Do you wanna know how the bastard
makes her feel? Get a load of this.
[unsettling music playing]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
She kills herself, aged 28,
exhausted by the pain and the shame of it.
[gasps]
Maybe put that down.
[man grunts]
[dog barking]
[gasps]
[dog sniffing, whimpers]
[retching]
[retching, coughing]
[groans]
Yeah, it does take some getting used to,
I'll grant you that.
But a couple more of those
and I'll be out of your hair. [chuckles]
Look, hang on.
Uh… Yeah, yeah. Look, see? One line gone.
That's one sacrifice registered.
Two to go.
You've got a whole day
to pick the next one.
Oh, come on. You--
You forgot to flush.
Oof. Fuck me.
[indistinct chattering]
Sorry to disturb you, sir.
-[man] What is it, Suz?
-A missing person.
[man] Boy or girl?
A 39-year-old man.
A Tim Simons.
No, don't know him.
[Suzie] His wife said
he didn't come home last night.
Yeah, because he's on the piss.
It's not even 24 hours yet.
I know, but, sir, the thing is,
she says his dog came home without him.
[dog whimpering]
I suppose we stopped taking pictures
of each other.
Here.
That's him.
He… he never stays out. He…
Something's happened. I know it.
We don't know anything's happened at all.
Hello.
Who's this?
It's okay.
It's okay, Laura.
This man and this lady
are going to help find Daddy.
Worried sick, aren't you, love?
[Gaap] How long are you
just gonna sit there for?
You're late for work. You have to go in.
You can't have people getting suspicious.
[chuckles] I mean it.
If you don't turn up--
Fucking shut up!
I killed a man.
-I've killed someone.
-Yeah, that was hours ago.
I keep feeling the crack of his skull
on the brick.
I did that.
It's your fault.
You're not even-- [inhales deeply]
[whimpers]
I'm crazy.
I'm a crazy person.
They said Mum was mad.
They'll say it about me.
But this time, they'll be right.
They'll be totally bloody right.
Hey, look, look. You're not crazy.
I'm a murderer.
Yeah, but you're not a crazy one.
Why is this happening?
Look.
This is actually my first assignment.
It's more of an initiation, really.
Sort of earning my wings.
I mean, I'm new to this too.
I'm not a bad person.
Oh no. No. It wouldn't work if you were.
It has to be someone corruptible.
So, I mean, if you think about it,
what's happening here,
it actually reflects really well
on your character.
Huh?
Yeah.
What… what are you doing?
-Calling the police.
-What? Why?
[tense music playing]
-Why?
-So they'll arrest me.
[chuckles] But then you won't be able
to do the other sacrifices.
Good!
Then the apocalypse will happen,
and billions will die.
I mean, I know. I get it.
You don't want the blood
of three victims on your hands,
but if it saves billions…
[phone line ringing]
[man] Hello, emergency services.
What service do you require?
Hello?
Hello? Is anyone there--
[exhales in relief]
See? You… you are a good person.
What do I do?
Just carry on as usual
so the normals don't get spooked,
which means going to work.
And while you're there,
we can decide who to kill next.
[muzak softly playing]
Hello.
What's this?
You were supposed to be in at 9:00.
I threw up this morning.
I thought I might be ill.
Oh, don't come near me.
I don't want your germs.
You look awful.
Well, she's nice.
Front-runner for the old…
[mimics throat slitting] I think.
Uh, she does steal from the till,
you know.
-Gotta pick someone!
-Sh!
God, I… I do love a little old lady. Hey…
[inhales deeply]
Oh, isn't she sweet?
She can't stop thinking
about the end though.
They can't wait for it to come.
You'd be doing her a favor.
Shut up.
-[woman] What was that, love?
-Nothing.
-She dreams of death. Even now--
-How are those for you?
I think they're good.
I'll just go and have a little look.
Just do it. No one will miss her.
No, shut up.
She's nearly dead already.
Very nice.
Sir?
-Sir?
-[man] Yeah?
They said you're in here.
That was nice of 'em.
-Can it wait?
-[Suzie] It's Tim Simons.
[man] Oh aye. Turned up, has he?
[Suzie] He has, sir, but he's dead.
Someone's clobbered him, sir.
So they have.
[man] So, come on.
What time do you finish?
Depends what time you wanna start.
[Vicky chuckles]
Maybe I won't wanna stop.
[Vicky] And maybe I won't wanna stop you.
[Vicky laughs]
How about this handsome fucker, eh?
God's gift till he loses his hair at 32
and spends the next 29 years
taking it out on his missus.
[tense music playing]
[woman whimpers]
[gasps]
-Stop showing me this stuff.
-His missus won't be her.
She never marries. Very sad.
Well, well, look. It's half-five already.
You gotta get the next one in by midnight.
You have to pick someone.
On your last trip, did you discover
what the Earth people eat?
They eat a great many of these.
They peel them with their metal knives.
Boil them for 20 of their minutes.
For fuck's sake.
-Do you want the apocalypse to happen?
-You're in the way.
[robot on TV] They are clearly
a most primitive people.
[Gaap snaps fingers]
[man on TV] Nuclear tensions rise
as talks break down
and US and Soviet jets…
I was watching that.
Both superpowers possess
a growing arsenal of atomic weaponry,
yet given the horrific devastation
any nuclear exchange would cause,
it's assumed the policy…
You see that?
It's manifesting.
Do you understand? This is the form
it's taking. This is real.
You don't have much time.
You're the only one who can stop it.
[Gaap] No. No.
Don't take the piss, Nida.
[sighs uncertainly]
No, you're not… you're not a knife person.
-Way too grabby. Cut your hands all up.
-Yeah.
Oh, I know. I know. Down there.
Yes.
That's you. You're a basher.
Come on, you've had the practice now.
It'll be way easier this time.
Dutch courage, eh? That's what you need.
Where do you keep your booze?
I don't drink.
Yeah, shit, yeah.
Uh…
Well, do you want a drink?
["I Don't Like Mondays"
by the Boomtown Rats playing]
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I don't like Mondays ♪
♪ I wanna shoot ♪
♪ The whole day down… ♪
She totally blanked you, huh?
-What about her? [mimics throat slitting]
-[clears throat]
-You know?
-[bartender] You waiting, love?
[Nida] I'll have…
Triple scotch, please.
Easy, you still got work to do.
You want ice with that?
Do people have it with ice?
Generally.
Okay, then.
Actually, make it two triple scotches.
Thank you.
-You don't have to get one for me.
-I didn't.
♪ Tell me why ♪
-♪ I don't like Mondays ♪
-♪ Tell me why ♪
[coin clatters]
["Hit Me With Your Rhythm Stick"
by Ian Dury and the Blockheads playing]
Right, let's get cracking.
You see anyone tasty?
[man cheering]
Oh, oh, all right.
You see him? He's perfect.
Piece of work, that one.
String of burglaries.
Mostly targets the elderly.
[ethereal music playing]
[Gaap] What do you reckon?
-No?
-Mm-mm.
Okay. Uh…
Ah! You see… you see her with the pints?
She went on holiday
when she was 12 years old
and saw her sister drown
in a swimming pool.
[girl screaming]
She could've pulled her out,
but she just stood there and watched.
Fucking hell.
You could be making this up.
["Hit Me With Your Rhythm Stick"
continues playing]
Ah! Okay, you see him?
About three years ago, he thought
his wife was cheating on him. So, he--
Strangled her in the bath.
Are you familiar with his work?
Keith Holligan.
It's funny. It wasn't premeditated,
but he did have a hard-on
when he did it, so…
♪ Hit me with your rhythm stick ♪
♪ Hit me, hit me ♪
♪ Das ist gut, c'est fantastique ♪
♪ Hit me, hit me, hit me! ♪
♪ Hit me with your rhythm stick ♪
♪ It's nice to be a lunatic ♪
♪ Hit me, hit me… ♪
[shudders]
[gasps]
[Gaap] I think we have a contender.
Well, he can't have got far. Come on.
♪ Hit me, hit me, hit me! ♪
[music ends]
[urine splashing]
Perfect location. Ain't no witnesses.
You should rush him.
Now, come on!
Did you just follow me from the pub?
[chuckles]
You're a dark horse, aren't you?
-I've read about girls like you.
-[zipper zips]
-I'm just around the corner.
-You know what? Home turf. Even better.
Come on.
Not much sense in being shy now.
Looks like he wipes his arse
with his house.
Um…
Do you want to do it here or…
May… maybe bedroom's better?
-I think the bedroom.
-Bedroom, right.
[Nida chuckles softly]
[Keith] Come on.
Don't be frightened.
It's almost midnight.
You're cutting it fine.
-[whispers] Shut the fuck up, you.
-What was that?
Can't wait to fuck you.
[chuckles]
[Gaap] Fucking hell.
[breathing heavily]
[splutters] Sorry, it's a bit…
Sorry.
What are you doing? Just fucking do it.
[cassette clatters]
♪ It's only a heartbeat away ♪
♪ When I need love ♪
♪ I hold out my hands ♪
♪ And I touch love ♪
♪ I never knew there was so much love ♪
♪ Keeping me warm night and day… ♪
-[Nida whimpers]
-[Keith sighs]
Tell you what. You get comfy.
I'll just go have a wash down there first.
Mm-hmm.
♪ A telephone can't take the place
Of your smile ♪
♪ But you know
I won't be traveling forever ♪
♪ It's cold out, but hold out… ♪
[Keith] Won't be a minute.
♪ When I need you ♪
♪ I just close my eyes ♪
♪ And I'm with you ♪
Not actually gonna shag him, are you?
I was… I was just checking.
I was just checking…
Uh, it is 11:54, six minutes left,
since you asked, so…
Just fucking come on!
♪ It's not easy
When the road is your driver ♪
♪ Honey, that's a heavy load
That we bear ♪
♪ But you know
I won't be traveling a lifetime ♪
♪ It's cold out, but hold out ♪
♪ And do like I do ♪
♪ Oh, I need you… ♪
You're gonna hit me with that.
[whimpers]
Okay, then.
I always knew something would happen.
Ever since I did it,
I've had
dreams.
This is what I deserve.
[breathes shakily]
I honestly did love her.
[Keith whimpers]
I think.
[sobs]
I wasn't a bad husband. I just--
[Nida grunts]
-[Nida grunts]
-[blood squelches]
-[Nida whimpers]
-[Keith gurgling]
[Gaap grunts]
[Nida sobs]
[whimpers]
Yes!
Ah, even with four minutes to spare.
[sobbing]
Well, you can't have that lying around.
[panting]
[whimpers]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Gaap] Get out before he sees ya.
Sh.
-[floorboard creaks]
-[man] Keith?
Who are you?
No, no witnesses. He's gotta go.
[Nida gasps]
-Get out!
-I can't kill another one.
-[man] Stay there.
-He's seen you. You have to.
Get out of my house!
-[dishes clattering]
-Get away!
[Gaap] Do it! It's him or you.
Please, please, please.
Just get out of here.
Please, please
[Nida gasps, grunts]
[Nida grunts]
[both grunting]
-[man grunts]
-[Nida whimpers]
[breathing heavily, grunts]
[man gasping]
[groaning]
[Nida whimpers]
-I'm so sorry.
-[man groans]
[straining]
I'm so sorry.
[Nida whimpering]
[man gasps]
Come on, let's go.
[clock chimes midnight]
[Nida] Who was he?
[Gaap] That'd be Keith's brother, Chris.
What was he like?
You know stuff.
Was he a good person or a bad person?
He was…
ordinary.
I know. I know. I know.
It's not what you wanna hear,
but, you know…
[exhales] …what's done is done.
And on the plus side,
you scored two tonight.
That one a day is just a minimum,
but two does get you over the line.
You done it.
Hey, look.
See, it, um…
It…
Just… just two secs.
Hi there. Gaap of Misophaes.
Yeah.
Yeah, so, uh,
I've got a talisman circa 1926,
but the rune face just failed to register
one of the sacrifices.
Yeah, two kills,
but only one's been recorded.
Right.
Um, I mean, yeah, but…
What? We… we--
What, we can't just--
[Gaap sighs]
No.
Yeah, yeah. I get it. I get it.
[phone clatters]
-Keith didn't count.
-What?
-Why?
-He's a murderer.
Makes him ineligible.
That's what they're saying.
But we've been picking people
who deserve it.
You're not strictly
supposed to do it that way. I just…
I thought you'd find it easier.
I mean, the first bloke,
the one by the canal,
they're giving us that one 'cause
he's never actually killed anybody, but…
What about what he did to his daughter?
You said she kills herself at 28,
thanks to him.
Yeah, but that's in the future.
I'm sorry.
Look, basically, anyone
who's already been directly responsible
for the death of another human being,
they're off-limits.
Once that's happened,
as far as my boss is concerned,
they're playing for the home team.
You know, we're actually lucky
that Keith's brother
turned up just before midnight.
It would've been Armageddon otherwise.
Look, you did well.
Oh, absolutely go fuck yourself!
Right up a tree!
-This is all right for you.
-It isn't.
No blood on your hands.
You're just watching.
Light entertainment.
If the apocalypse does come,
you'll have a big fun finale.
-That'd be upending the whole place--
-It's frowned upon. You get told off.
-If I fail my initiation…
-[Nida laughs]
Kicked out of demon school? Boo-hoo.
-More like cast out.
-Whatever.
Cast out into a boundless, cosmic void.
And doomed to spend eternity
in a vacuum of infinite nothingness.
Absence of matter, of time,
of space, light, and sound.
I would endure a profound, palpable,
and ever-present lack of existence,
alone in perpetuity,
forever more.
Sounds like my life.
To be honest, I'm scared.
So one more victim, then.
Yeah, only thing for it.
-I can't be doing a total innocent.
-It's just murderers we have to avoid.
You mean people like me.
My whole life,
I never wished harm on anyone.
[Gaap scoffs]
I didn't.
Uh…
You couldn't have summoned me
for my trial if you hadn't.
Well, you had to be corruptible,
not beyond corruption.
You know what? You must have had
some dark force inside you
when you touched the talisman.
There's no shame in it.
No, go on. Who pissed you off?
[eerie music playing]
[chilling music playing]
[chilling music continues]
[chilling music intensifies]
So I'm thinking just lure her
down to the basement on some pretense,
clock her on the stairwell,
and say she lost her step and fell.
[Vicky] Snap out of it.
You can deal with the kid out there.
Needs black shoes for a funeral.
They pulled her dad out of the canal.
I'd do it myself,
but she gives me the willies.
[muzak softly playing]
[Gaap] Well, she… she…
she's not in mourning.
Well, she's… she's not not mourning.
Happy it's finished. Sad he's dead. It…
But… it has finished.
You… you spared her
another five years of it.
A lifetime of therapy,
but a lifetime, nonetheless.
She's a mum at 29. A nan at 57.
Eh?
I just thought you'd like to know.
It's a good fit.
[man 1] And, of course, the final touch.
-[man 2] Colin, really? You--
-No, no, no, no, no.
-I insist. Too late.
-[man 2] Very well.
[man 1] Here we are in footwear.
This is Mr. Michael Smart.
You probably recognize him.
He's all set to be our next MP.
Well, with a little luck
and a following wind.
[both laughing]
-His father and I were at school together.
-Fuck me.
[man 1] He's been using my weekend cottage
as a base of operations.
-You can tell he's ex-military.
-[laughs]
Michael's got a big speech tonight
at the town hall.
I promised him a new suit and new shoes.
The finest that Possetts has to offer.
[whispers] On the house.
I've told him
he'll go out of business at this rate.
[both laughing]
Fuck me some more.
Well, I said I'd leave you in the hands
of our finest assistant, so, um…
Vicky, if you could take care of Michael.
Michael, enjoy Vicky's
more than capable hands.
-Hey, steady on there. Steady on.
-[Vicky] Won't you walk this way?
[Michael] I'll walk
however you want. [laughs]
For Christ's sake,
there's boxes all over the floor.
Would you pick up your bloody mess?
I'm thinking car park later.
Wait till he comes out. Reverse into him.
Pin him up against the wall.
Keep the pedal down
till you hear the stomach pop.
Eh? What do you think?
[Michael laughs]
-[Michael] I won't tell if you don't.
-What?
[Vicky, Michael laugh]
[Michael] I hope
I have your vote this week.
Afraid not. National Front for me.
Oh!
Why is that?
Don't like how things
are changing around here.
Mm.
My aunt, she's been in Cheetham 20 years.
Now she's got them living either side.
That's what's next.
We've not got a pot to piss in,
so why should we share with them
who don't belong?
You think voting National Front will help?
I think they'll stand up for us.
Says so
right on the front of their leaflet.
But they won't get elected.
-They might.
-They're too overt.
People feel it's, um,
bad manners.
[inhales]
You know why I don't print
"stop immigration"
in gigantic letters
on my campaign literature?
Because look at me.
Look at me!
[unsettling music playing]
You know what I stand for.
So,
do I have your vote?
Yes, sir.
Good girl.
[Gaap] So, who are you gonna kill,
your boss or Vicky? You haven't got long.
What's his future? Michael Smart?
-Uh, it--
-Can you show me his future?
-Yeah, but let's not--
-Then show me right now.
Or I'll run out there,
confess to everything,
and then it's over,
and then you're fucked.
[sighs]
Show me.
-[male announcer] 16,472 votes.
-[audience clapping]
[Michael] Not just different,
they're inferior.
[man] …expelled from the Tories,
Michael Smart launched
his new Britannia party.
The rivers of blood are here!
Reclaim your power.
The land is ours.
[male announcer] In a shock victory,
Britain has a new prime minister.
[Michael] Fifth columnist traitors.
I've seen what's coming.
Rising seas, burning sky.
We are at war.
[crowd cheering]
[gasping]
He's fucking Satan.
[Gaap] No, he's not one of ours,
not literally.
I mean, they do like him.
They're fans of his work, you might say.
He's got to go.
-He's next.
-Oh, uh, they are not gonna like that.
Just avoid murderers.
You said that was the one rule.
Right, but he's responsible
for an impressive number of juicy deaths--
Not yet he isn't.
Right, but he… he… he beats his wife.
-Hasn't killed her, though, has he?
-I mean…
[splutters] I mean, he killed a dog
with a rock when he was 12.
Animals don't count.
That was one of the first things you said.
[breathes deeply]
-Does Michael Smart qualify or not?
-Well, technically, yeah, but--
Then I choose Michael Smart.
He's the one. That's that.
Honestly, they are not gonna like it.
But it's within the rules,
so they can lump it.
It's him
or no one.
I mean it.
[Gaap scoffs]
Do you want to fail your initiation, hm?
He wants to try an 11.
Hurry up. It's gone closing time.
Stool's there. Do it yourself.
Uh…
♪ Freeze, I'm Ma Baker ♪
♪ Put your hands in the air
Gimme all your money ♪
["Ma Baker" by Boney M playing]
♪ This is the story of Ma Baker ♪
♪ The meanest cat from old Chicago town ♪
♪ She was the meanest cat ♪
♪ Oh, she was really tough ♪
♪ She left her husband flat ♪
♪ He wasn't tough enough ♪
♪ She took her boys along ♪
♪ 'Cause they were mean and strong ♪
♪ Ma, Ma, Ma, Ma ♪
♪ Ma Baker, she taught her four sons ♪
♪ Ma Baker, to handle their guns ♪
♪ Ma, Ma, Ma, Ma ♪
♪ Ma Baker, she never could cry ♪
♪ Ma Baker, but she knew how to die ♪
[music stops]
You've changed.
["Ma Baker" resumes playing]
[music stops]
-[dog barking]
-[indistinct police radio chatter]
[tense music playing]
[Suzie] No sign of forced entry.
-Could've been a fight between 'em.
-Well, one hell of a fight.
[Suzie] Well, we know
Keith was no angel, for sure.
Hmm.
Did any of our lot turn that on?
I don't think so.
[scoffs]
Keith Holligan?
Aye, he were in last night.
He's in most nights.
Anything unusual about him?
Well, he killed his wife.
I mean, last night.
Was he behaving differently?
[bartender] Just his usual self,
such as he is.
Sat on his perch dragging his pints out.
Left around closing time.
-Anyone follow him out?
-[bartender] Not that I saw.
Well, thanks for your time, Bob.
[Bob] There were one thing last night.
I mean, she didn't speak to Keith.
-Who didn't speak to Keith?
-This Indian lass. Never been in before.
Drank two triple scotches by herself.
We don't get many of 'em in here,
let alone ordering whiskey.
-Can you describe her?
-Yeah, Indian.
You mentioned that.
That's all that stood out.
Bit shorter than you, maybe.
Julie, did you see her?
Sat over there.
-Saw her talking to herself.
-Talking to herself?
Sort of muttering.
Seen her in town.
Works in shoes at Possetts.
Cheers, Bob.
[Nida] After Smart's finished his speech
at the Town Hall,
he's got to head for the cottage,
which is here.
So whichever way he goes,
he's out in the country.
So I'm thinking I wait outside the hall
in the car. I follow him along the--
-What if he's not alone?
-Is he gonna be alone? You tell me.
-Well, yeah, but--
-Well, then all I have to do is--
[doorbell ringing]
Some people, eh?
I'm gonna paint over it.
Nida Huq?
Len Fisher, Tipley Police.
I'm just making some routine inquiries.
Do you mind if I have a word?
Yeah, sure.
I mean, yes.
[chuckles] Inside?
Invite him in, and then kill him.
[splutters]
Yeah. [laughs]
-Would you like a cup of tea?
-Oh, no need. I won't keep you.
Well, like I say, it's just routine.
[Nida] Okay.
Were you in the pub last night?
The Three Crowns?
Yeah, I was.
Regular, are you?
-I wouldn't say that.
-How often are you in there?
To be honest,
last night was the first time.
[Len chuckles] First time.
God, it's just…
it's just around the corner, isn't it?
Well, I don't drink. Not usually.
But you did last night.
Yesterday was Mum's birthday.
She's not with us anymore.
You know, it's not…
Not easy.
No.
And I'm not meant to drink.
I don't have it in the house
or anything, but…
I'm not proud of myself.
I'm not here to judge.
We all need to let off steam
every now and then.
Thank you.
What's all this about anyway?
Well, you've probably heard
about Keith and Chris Holligan.
-Who?
-The Holligans. Keith and Chris.
I've not heard of them, I'm afraid.
Well, Keith was actually
in the Three Crowns last night.
Did you see him?
Maybe.
I wouldn't know him.
Well, I only ask because…
Looks like you served him at work
a few days ago.
Did I?
[Len] Those are your initials,
aren't they?
Must have served him, then.
We get so many in the door.
To be honest, by the end of the day,
I hardly recognize myself.
[both chuckle]
So, you didn't see him?
I certainly didn't notice him.
So sorry I wasn't more help.
Well, if anything does come to you,
please let us know.
Well, you're a total fucking liar,
in't ya?
I'm impressed.
-He didn't buy it though.
-Best hurry, then.
Smart will be finishing his speech.
[engine starting]
That cop is following us.
It really would be an easy kill.
He was gonna have a heart attack
next year anyway.
It's not like he has any family.
No one's gonna miss him.
["One Step Beyond" by Madness playing]
And together with the threat to freedom,
there is a sense of helplessness.
A sense that our once great nation
has fallen behind, lost its way,
lost its identity.
But it is not too late,
and we are not helpless.
This election may decide our fate.
Well, that fate is ours to decide.
So don't just hope for a better future.
Vote for one!
Fantastic. Fantastic.
Great night. Thank you.
Oh, thank Karen for the quiche.
-Hey, great speech. Good luck.
-Oh. Thank you.
-I've got a good feeling about this.
-I… I do hope so.
Well, uh, off for my beauty sleep.
-Oh, of course, yeah.
-[laughs]
[tense music playing]
The bloody hell you up to, love?
[classical music playing]
[humming]
[crossing bell ringing]
[engine revving]
[tires squeal]
[groans]
Bollocks.
-It's not too late to find someone else.
-Oh, shut up!
I'm just saying it'd be much easier
for me if you found someone else--
If you're not gonna help, then piss off.
I mean it.
Fine.
["Lucky Number" by Lene Lovich playing]
♪ I never used to cry
'Cause I was all alone ♪
♪ For me, myself, and I
Is all I've ever known ♪
[classical music playing]
♪ In everything I do
I take complete control ♪
♪ That's where I'm coming from ♪
[humming]
♪ Everything I need to keep me satisfied ♪
♪ There's nothing you can do
To make me change my mind ♪
[classical music playing]
[tires squeal]
God's teeth!
["Lucky Number" resumes playing]
[grunts]
[classical music playing]
[car horn blaring]
[chilling music playing]
Shit.
[tense choral music playing]
[Michael] What the bloody hell
are you doing?
[groans] Come on. Help me, then.
[whimpers, screaming]
[screaming]
Please.
[tense music swells]
[car horn honks]
[Len] Police!
-Stop!
-[Michael panting]
[Len] I said stop!
[grunts] Bloody animal.
She's trying to bloody kill me.
[panting]
Put it down.
I have to do it.
It's not right.
You know it's not.
[whimpers]
Are you a good man?
I don't know, love.
I hope so.
Put it down.
Love…
[Nida] If I don't do this by midnight,
there'll be war.
Fire…
Fire everywhere.
[sniffles]
Well…
we'll deal with that if it comes to it.
[whimpers]
Put it down.
I can't.
Gaap, I'm sorry.
Gaap!
-Come here.
-[Nida cries] I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
[Nida sobs] I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
-[Len panting]
-[Nida crying]
[clock ticking]
[Suzie] Nida?
Nida?
You're saying you were only targeting
people who've done something wrong?
Mm-hmm.
Um…
except that man, um, Chris.
He just turned up.
And each time you sacrificed someone,
it got registered on the talisman?
Is that right?
But they said Keith didn't count.
Which wasn't fair.
This was in your jacket pocket.
This is a talisman, yeah?
It's gone normal now.
Before, it…
before, it had shapes on it that sort of
changed when you looked at it.
And the demon who told you to do all this,
he first spoke to you
through that talisman?
Just for a moment.
I could only hear him to start with.
-Then he was actually in the room.
-What did he look like?
Like a monster at first.
Then he turned into the man from Boney M.
The man from Boney M?
Who does the dancing?
Okay.
-So, the man from Boney M tells you--
-His name's Gaap.
Sorry, Gaap tells you
there'll be a nuclear war
if you don't kill three people
before May Day.
He didn't just tell me.
He showed me what it'd be like.
I felt the flames.
I smelled people burning.
Not long now.
I tried to stop it.
Honest, I did.
[sniffling]
[whimpers]
[clock ticking intensifies]
[sobs]
[clock ticking stops]
[Len] Her mind's gone, that's for sure.
Certainly what the lawyer will say.
Am I mad to feel sorry for her?
[sighs] Suz, there's three men dead.
So, no matter how much sympathy you might
muster for her personal situation,
there's families mourning.
You hear that?
[siren blaring in distance]
[Gaap] Nida?
[gasps]
Evening, all.
[laughs]
I failed.
Yeah, well, me too, so that's that.
Just got word.
They are casting me out. Eternal oblivion.
I'm so sorry.
Do you wanna come with me?
What?
That's where I've been,
checking the small print.
The rules don't cover it.
There's another loophole, apparently.
They don't say anything
about a human companion.
So, I mean, you could come with.
Into eternal oblivion?
Oh no, it's much worse than that.
It's with me.
I'll give it a go.
["Bright Eyes" by Art Garfunkel playing]
♪ Is it a kind of dream? ♪
♪ Floating out on the tide ♪
♪ Following the river of death
Downstream ♪
♪ Oh, is it a dream? ♪
Jesus Christ, they've done it.
♪ There's a fog along the horizon ♪
♪ A strange glow in the sky ♪
♪ And nobody seems to know where you go ♪
♪ And what does it mean? ♪
♪ Oh, is it a dream? ♪
♪ Bright eyes ♪
♪ Burning like fire ♪
♪ How can you close and fail? ♪
♪ How can the light
That burned so brightly ♪
♪ Suddenly burn so pale? ♪
♪ Bright eyes ♪
♪ Burning like fire ♪
♪ How can you close and fail? ♪
♪ How can the light
That burned so brightly ♪
♪ Suddenly burn so pale? ♪
♪ Bright eyes ♪
[music fades]