Still got it.
What's that?
An old friend.
I was rummaging through a closet...
...and it was sitting there.
It's nice, Paul.
It's got character.
When I wrote my first book,
I carried it...
...in this while I looked
for a publisher.
- I was a writer then.
- You're still a writer.
I haven't been one since I got
in the Misery business.
Not a bad business.
And it would still be growing too.
The first printing for Misery's Child
was the most ever.
Over a million.
Marcia, please.
Misery Chastain put braces on your
daughter and put her through college.
Bought you two houses
and seats to the Knicks.
What thanks does she get?
You go and kill her.
I never meant for it to become my life.
If I hadn't gotten rid of her now...
...I would be
writing her forever.
I'm leaving for Colorado to
try to finish the new book.
If I can make this work...
...I might just have something
I want on my tombstone.
I'm your number one fan.
There's nothing to worry about.
You're gonna be just fine.
I'll take good care of you.
I'm your number one fan.
Where am I?
We're just outside Silver Creek.
How long?
You've been here two days.
It's gonna be okay.
My name is Annie Wilkes.
My number one fan.
Yes. That's right.
I'm also a nurse.
Here.
Take these.
What are they?
They're called Novril.
They're for your pain.
Thank you.
How come I'm not in hospital?
The blizzard was too strong.
I couldn't risk getting you there.
I tried calling,
but the phone lines are down.
You mustn't tire yourself.
You've gotta rest.
You almost died.
Open wide.
Your legs just sing grand opera
when you move, don't they?
It's not gonna hurt forever, Paul.
I promise you.
Will I be able to walk?
Of course you will.
And your arm will be fine too.
Your shoulder was pretty badly dislocated.
It was a little stubborn,
but I finally popped it back in.
What I'm proud of
is the work on those legs.
Considering what I had in the house,
a doctor couldn't have done better.
It's not nearly as bad as it looks.
You have a compound fracture
of the tibia in both legs...
...and the fibula in the right leg
is fractured too.
I could hear the bones moving...
...so it's best your legs
remain immobile.
As soon as the roads open...
...I'll take you to a hospital.
In the meantime, you've got a lot of
recovering to do...
...and I consider it an honor
that you'll do it in my home.
This is Marcia Sindell.
I'm calling from New York.
I'd like to speak to the
chief of police or sheriff.
- Which one do you want?
- Whichever one is not busy.
I'm pretty sure they're both not busy,
Ms. Sindell, since they're both me.
I also happen to be president of the
Policeman's Benefit Association...
...chairman of the Patrolman's
Retirement Fund...
...and if you need a fishing
guide, you could do a lot worse.
Call me Buster, everybody does.
What can I do for you?
I'm a literary agent, and I...
I feel like a fool calling you...
...but I think one of my clients,
Paul Sheldon, might be in trouble.
You mean Paul Sheldon the writer?
- He's your client, huh?
- Yes, he is.
Everybody sure likes those Misery books.
Yeah.
I'm sure you know Paul's been
coming to Silver Creek Lodge...
...for years to finish his books.
I understand he's been up here
the last six weeks.
Well, not quite.
I just called there and they...
...said he checked out
last Tuesday.
Isn't that a little strange?
I don't know. Does he usually phone
you before he checks out of a hotel?
No. No, of course not.
His daughter hasn't heard from him...
...and when he has a book coming out,
he keeps in touch.
So when there wasn't any word
from him, I...
You think he might be missing, huh?
I hate that I made this call.
Tell me I'm being silly.
Oh, a little over-protective maybe.
Tell you what I'll do.
Nothing's been reported out here...
...but I'll put his name
through our system.
If anything turns up,
I'll call you right back.
Oh, I'd appreciate that.
Thanks a lot.
Goodbye, Ms. Sindell.
We got a phone call?
Busy morning.
Yeah. Work, work, work.
Virginia, when was that blizzard?
Last Tuesday. Why?
No reason.
I guess it was kind of a miracle,
you finding me.
No, it wasn't a miracle at all.
In a way, I was following you.
Following me?
It wasn't any secret to me you
were at the Silver Creek...
...seeing as how I'm your
number one fan and all.
Some nights I'd just tool on
down there and sit outside...
...and look up at the light
in your cabin...
...and imagine what was going on
in the room of the greatest writer.
Say it again.
I didn't hear you.
Don't move now.
I wouldn't want to hurt this neck.
Well, the other afternoon...
...I was on my way home...
...and there you were,
leaving the lodge.
I wondered why a literary genius would
go out when there was a storm coming.
I didn't know there was
a big storm coming.
Lucky for you I did.
Lucky for me too.
Because now you're alive...
...and you can write more books.
Oh, Paul, I've read everything of yours.
The Misery novels.
I know them all by heart.
All eight of them.
I love them so.
You're very kind.
And you're very brilliant.
Like a baby.
- All done.
- Thank you.
When do you think
the phone lines will be up?
I have to call my daughter
and agent in New York...
...to let her know I'm alive.
It shouldn't be much longer.
Once the roads open, the phone
lines will be up in no time.
If you give me their numbers,
I'll keep trying them.
Could I ask you a favor?
I noticed in your case there is
a new Paul Sheldon book...
...and I wondered if maybe...
You want to read it?
If you wouldn't mind.
I have a hard and fast rule...
...as to who reads my stuff
at this early stage.
Only my editor, my agent...
...and anybody who saves me from
freezing to death in a car wreck.
You'll never realize
what a rare treat you've given me.
Boy, it's like clockwork,
the way your pain comes.
I'll get your Novril.
Forgive me for prattling...
...and making you feel all oogy.
What's your new book called?
I don't have a title yet.
What's it about?
I don't know.
I know it sounds crazy, but I haven't...
...written anything but Misery
for so long.
Why don't you read it...
...and tell me what it's about.
Maybe you can come up with a title.
Like I could do that.
Nothing unusual about
Mr. Sheldon's leaving, Buster.
- You can tell by the champagne.
- Maybe you can, Libby.
He always orders a bottle of
Dom Perignon when he's ready to go.
Then he pays up and he's out.
No long-distance phone calls...
...or Federal Express packages?
Anything out of the ordinary?
I don't think Mr. Sheldon likes for
things to be out of the ordinary.
Considering who he is,
and all famous and all...
...he doesn't put on airs.
Drives up from New York
in the same car each time.
A '65 Mustang.
Says it helps him to think.
Always been a good guest.
Never makes a noise.
Never bothers a soul.
- I hope nothing's happened to him.
- So do I.
I bet that old Mustang's pulling into
New York right now.
I'm sure you're right.
Thanks, Libby.
My pleasure.
I know I'm only 40 pages
into your book, but...
But what?
Nothing.
No, no.
What is it?
What's ridiculous...
Who am I to make a criticism
to someone like you?
It's all right, I can take it.
It's brilliantly written.
But then everything you write
is brilliant.
Pretty rough stuff, huh?
The swearing, Paul.
There, I said it.
Yeah. The profanity bothers you.
It has no nobility.
These are slum kids.
I was a slum kid.
Everybody talks like that.
They do not!
What do you think I say at the feed store?
"Now Wally, give a bag of that
effing pig feed and...
...ten pounds of that
bitchly cow corn!"
And the bank.
Do I tell Mrs. Bollinger:
"Here's one big bastard of a check...
...give me your Christing money!"
There! Look there!
See what you made me do?!
Oh, Paul, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Sometimes I get so worked up.
Can you ever forgive me?
It's fine.
I love you, Paul.
Your mind.
Your creativity.
That's all I meant.
Well, this sure is fun.
Virginia...
...when you're in this car,
you're not my wife, you're my deputy.
This deputy would rather be home
under the covers with the sheriff.
- Stop.
- What?
- Stop!
See that broken limb?
Could be the weight of the snow.
Could have been a rotten branch,
could have been the wind.
Could have been a lot of things.
Need some help?
No, I'm enjoying myself!
Thank you.
You think Sheldon's out there?
I hope not.
If he is, he's dead.
Let's go to the newspaper office.
Oh, I hope I didn't wake you.
No, it's fine.
Look what I got.
They had it at the store.
There was a whole batch of them.
As soon as I saw it, I slammed my
money down. I got the first copy.
Then the roads are open.
The one to town is, but that's about it.
I called the hospital and I talked
to the head orthopedic surgeon...
...and I told him who you were
and what had happened.
And he said as long as
there's no infection...
...you're not in danger.
As soon as the road to the hospital
is open, they'll send an ambulance.
The phone's working?
Mine's still out.
The ones in town were working just fine.
I called that agent of yours.
Oh, Paul, I peeked at the very beginning.
What a wonderful first page.
- The name Misery Chastain.
- My daughter must be going nuts.
Like a visit from my--
I'm supposed to be home
for her birthday. It's today.
The agent said she would tell her.
You'll have to wait...
...till tomorrow if you
want to talk to her yourself.
Oh, Paul...
...what a poet you are.
I made you my specialty:
Scrambled eggs à la Wilkes.
And I'm on page 75.
I guess that means it's okay.
No.
No, it isn't. It's...
Oh, pooh.
I can't think of any words.
Would "great" be insulting?
I can live with "great."
No.
It's not just great, it's...
...perfect.
A perfect, perfect thing.
I thought it was time you two should meet.
Paul, say hello to my favorite
beast in the whole world.
My sow, Misery.
Misery?
Yes. I told you
I was your number one fan.
Yeah, I'm...
...starting to believe you.
This farm was dreary, what with
a few cows and chickens and me.
But when I got Misery here,
everything changed.
She just makes me smile so.
She's a fine...
...pig, is what she is.
I'm on page 300 now, Paul.
And it's better than perfect.
It's divine.
What's the ceiling that dago painted?
The Sistine Chapel.
Yeah.
That and Misery's Child.
Those are the only two divine
things ever in this world.
When my husband left me,
I wasn't prepared.
It wasn't an easy time.
For a while I thought I might go crazy.
I know how that can be.
I don't know about you...
...but what I did to get through it
was I dove into work.
Days, nights.
Night shifts can be lonely at a hospital.
I did a lot of reading.
That was when I first discovered Misery.
She made me so happy.
She made me forget all my problems.
Of course, you had a little
something to do with that too.
Yeah, well...
I just kept reading them over and over.
I've only got two chapters left
and when I finish...
...I'll turn to the first page...
...and start reading it
all over again.
I'm, uh...
- Done?
- Yeah.
No problem.
Thanks.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not against marriage per se, but...
...it'd take a special guy to make me
want to walk down that aisle again.
Yeah, it's not something you
should enter into lightly.
It boils down to respect.
People don't respect the
institution of marriage anymore.
They have no sense of real commitment.
Well...
...I'd love to chat,
but I'm right at the end...
...and I gotta find out what happens.
You.
You...
...dirty bird.
How could you?
She can't be dead.
Misery Chastain cannot be dead.
Annie, in 1871, women often died
in childbirth.
Her spirit is the important thing
and Misery's spirit is alive.
I don't want her spirit!
I want her!
And you murdered her!
No.
I didn't.
Who did?
No one.
She died.
She just slipped away.
Slipped away?!
She didn't just slip away!
You did it!
You did it! You did it!
- You murdered my Misery!
- Annie! Annie!
I thought you were good, Paul...
...but you're not good.
You're just another lying,
old dirty birdie...
...and I don't think I better be
around you for a while.
And don't even think about
anybody coming for you.
Not the doctors...
...not your agent...
...not your family...
...because I never called them.
Nobody knows you're here.
And you better hope nothing happens to me.
Because if I die...
...you die.
No, Ms. Sindell, there's no
point in coming up here now.
Everything that can be done is.
We're working close with the police,
and the FBI's been informed.
Right. Right.
As soon as we know anything
we'll let you know.
No bother at all.
Call anytime. Bye, Ms. Sindell.
All right. Well, I sure
appreciate it. Thank you.
According to Sheldon's credit charges,
there's nothing after Silver Creek.
No calls about the article either.
You poor, dear thing.
What are you doing on the floor?
It's all my fault.
If I had a proper hospital bed,
this never would've happened.
Here, let me help you back in.
I know this hurts,
but it will only take a few seconds.
Upsy-daisy.
- Please. Wait. Wait.
- Oh, you're such a crybaby.
There you go. Comfy?
Perfect.
Such a kidder.
I have a big surprise for you. But
first there's something you must do.
Do you suppose I could have a little
snack while I'm waiting for it?
I'll get you everything you want,
but you must listen first.
Sometimes my thinking
is a little muddy. I accept that.
It's why I couldn't remember things
on the witness stand in Denver.
But this time I thought clearly.
I asked God about you.
And God said, "I delivered him unto
you so that you may show him the way."
Show me the way?
Yes.
When I mentioned a snack,
I was thinking more of a...
...cheese and crackers kind of thing.
Paul, this is no time for jokes.
You must rid the world of this filth.
You want me to burn my book?
I know this may be difficult for you,
but it's for the best.
It's really not difficult at all.
My agent made dozens of copies.
There'll be an auction in New York.
Publishing houses in New York
are reading it now.
So if you want me to burn my book, fine.
But you're not really
ridding the world of anything.
Then light the match, Paul.
It's no big deal.
So you've indicated.
Do it.
This is the only copy, Paul.
You didn't think your first book would
be taken seriously enough to copy.
They did. You've never made copies
because you're superstitious.
It's why you always come back
to the Silver Creek Lodge.
You told that
to Merv Griffin 11 years ago.
I'll tell you what.
It doesn't ever have to be published.
No one has to read it,
I'll just keep it for myself.
No one will even know it exists.
As long as it does exist,
your mind won't ever be free.
I think you should light the match, Paul.
Can't you see it's what God wants?
You're so brilliant, I'd think
you'd certainly be able to see that.
We're put on this earth
to help people, Paul.
Like I'm trying to help you.
Please, help me help you.
You're doing the right thing.
Oh, my goodness! Goodness gracious!
Oh, goodness! Heavens to Betsy!
Oh, my goodness! Oh, my goodness!
Heavens to Betsy! Oh, goodness!
Well, isn't that an oogy mess?
That's the Steadman place down there.
And that's the Wilkes farm straight ahead.
That's no '65 Mustang.
There's nothing else out this way.
Let's circle back.
I do believe the winters are getting
shorter every year.
People say it has something to do
with the ozone layer.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Yeah, well, it's a theory.
Here's your Novril.
We're back. Now, remind us
who the audience chose.
- They chose Kevin.
In fact, say hello to Kevin Andrews.
Hi, Kevin.
How you doing, Chuck?
Make yourself at home and Sheri
will tell us about the date.
First of all, I picked out
a very classy restaurant.
It was so classy, and he shows up
without no tie...
See, isn't this nice?
Great, I always wanted to visit the
other side of the room.
Look what I got for you.
An electric razor so you can
shave yourself now.
For this surprise
I'd have burned all my books.
Now, don't poke fun.
This is a big day for you, Paul.
Sit tight and I'll set everything up.
Set what up?
That's the big surprise.
Your new studio.
After all, writers do need
a place to work.
Work? You mean, write?
What in the world would I write?
Oh, but Paul, I don't think. I know.
You've burned that nasty manuscript.
Now you can do what you're great at.
You're gonna write a new novel.
Your greatest achievement ever.
Misery's return.
Misery's return?
You didn't mean it when you killed
her, and now you'll make it right.
It'll be a book in my honor...
...for saving your life
and nursing you back to health.
Oh, Paul, you're gonna make me
the envy of the whole world.
You just expect me to whip something off?
I expect nothing less
than your masterpiece.
You understand that this is not
the ordinary way books get written.
Some people might consider this
an oddball situation.
I have total confidence
in your brilliance.
Besides, the view will inspire you.
You just inhale that.
I'll be right back.
I guess neighbors don't bother you?
Don't you worry...
...you'll have total solitude
so you can concentrate on your work.
Great.
I got you this expensive paper to type on.
And I got a good deal on this clunker
on account of it's missing an "N."
I told the lady "N" was one of the
letters in my favorite writer's name.
It's two of the letters in my
favorite nurse's name: Annie.
You fooler. Did I do good?
You did great.
There is just one little thing.
I can't work on this paper. See, it's
Corrasable Bond and it smudges.
I thought maybe if you...
...went back into town, you could
get some white long-grained mimeo.
But mine cost the most,
so I don't see how it can smudge.
Come here, I'll show you.
It does smudge after all.
Isn't that fascinating?
I thought you'd be interested.
I'd like you to be in on
everything, Annie.
Not just the finished book,
but how it's written.
Thank you for thinking of me.
Anything else I can get while I'm in town?
Any other crucial requirements
I can satisfy?
Would you like a tiny tape recorder?
Or how about handmade writing slippers?
Just the paper will be fine.
Are you sure? If you want,
I'll bring back the whole store.
Annie, what's the matter?
I'll tell you what's the matter!
I go out of my way for you!
I do everything to make you happy!
I feed you! I clean you!
I dress you!
And what thanks do I get?!
"You bought the wrong paper, Annie!"
I'll get your paper, but you better
show me more appreciation, Mr. Man.
Shit!
Come on, you've written about this,
now do it.
What do you know? It works.
What a surprise.
You crazy bitch.
Paul, I've got your paper.
I hope it's enough.
Three reams of long-grained mimeo.
Just the kind you asked for.
Paul.
You're dripping with perspiration.
Your color is very hectic.
What've you been doing?
You know damn well what I've been doing.
I've been sitting here suffering.
I need my pills.
Poor dear.
Let's get you in bed, and I'll get them.
I want my pills now!
- It'll only take a second.
- No!
I want my pain to go away, Annie.
Please, make it go away.
Please, Annie.
Please.
It just breaks my heart
to see you like this.
I've done a lot of thinking on the drive.
Here you go.
And I'm absolutely certain.
The main reason I've never been
more popular is because of my temper.
You must be so mad at me.
The truth, now.
Well...
Who doesn't let off a little steam
every once in a while?
My genius needs his rest before he writes.
Footsies up.
There you go.
Here.
In case you think of any ideas.
I wouldn't expect too much.
Don't be silly. You'll be brilliant.
Think of me as your inspiration.
I have faith in you, my darling.
Catch this.
The presumption must now be
that Paul Sheldon is dead.
We know he somehow managed
to crawl outside his car...
...but we haven't found his body
in the vicinity of the accident.
Also, had anyone found him,
they would've taken him to a hospital.
Undoubtedly, he is buried
somewhere out there in the snow.
We'll find him after the thaw.
Unless the animals get to him first...
...which is a distinct possibility.
That was a statement from Colorado
Police Chief, Sherman Douglas.
We will update you--
You don't think he's dead, do you?
Well, he might well be,
but not the way they say.
He never crawled out
of that car by himself.
You can see the dents on the door there.
Someone pulled him out.
I'm sorry, Paul. This is all wrong.
- What?
- You'll have to do it over again.
It's not worthy of you.
Throw it all out.
Except naming the gravedigger
after me. You can leave that in.
I really value your criticism, but
maybe you're being a bit hasty here.
What you've written just isn't fair.
- Not fair?
- That's right.
Growing up in Bakersfield,
my favorite thing...
...was to go to the movies on
Saturdays for chapter plays.
- Cliffhangers.
- I know that, Mr. Man!
They also call them serials.
I'm not stupid, you know!
Anyway, my favorite was Rocket Man.
And once it was a no-brakes chapter.
The bad guys put him
in a car on a mountain...
...knocked him out, welded the doors,
and started him to his death.
He woke up, tried to steer,
tried to get out.
But the car went off a cliff before
he escaped and crashed and burned!
I was so upset and excited!
Next week, I was first in line.
It starts with last week's ending.
There was Rocket Man, trying
to get out and here comes the cliff.
Just before the car went
off the cliff, he jumped free!
And all the kids cheered!
But I didn't cheer.
I stood right up and started shouting:
"This isn't what happened last week!
Have you all got amnesia?
They just cheated us!
This isn't fair!
He didn't get out
of the cock-a-doodie car!"
They always cheated like that
in cliff-- Chapter plays.
But not you.
Not with my Misery.
Ian rode for Dr. Cleary at the end
of the last book, but his horse fell.
Ian got hurt and lay in the ditch.
He never reached the doctor.
So there couldn't have been
a blood transfusion to save her.
Misery was buried
in the ground at the end...
...so you'll have to start there.
Is it fair?
Should I continue?
You better.
Oh, Paul!
When Ian realized
they'd buried Misery alive...
...because the bee sting had
put her in that temporary coma.
When Gravedigger Wilkes
recalled how 30 years ago...
...the same thing had happened
to Lady Evelyn-Hyde!
Then Dr. Cleary deduced Misery must be
Lady Evelyn-Hyde's lost daughter...
...because of the rarity of deadly
bee stings. My heart just leapt!
I've known from the start that Misery
was born of nobility, and I was right!
Yeah, yeah.
Paul, can I read each chapter when
you finish? I can fill in the "N" s.
Will she be herself after Ian's
dug her out, or will she have amnesia?
Have to wait.
Will she still love him
with that special, perfect love?
You'll have to wait.
Not even a hint?
Misery's alive! Misery's alive!
Oh, it's so romantic! Oh, this whole
house will be filled with romance!
I'm gonna put on my Liberace records!
You do like Liberace, don't you?
Whenever he played Radio City,
who do you think was in the front row?
I'll play my records all day
to inspire you.
He's my all-time favorite.
Would you have dinner with me tonight?
To celebrate Misery's return.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Oh, Paul.
It would be an honor.
No, he's not here.
I don't know where he is.
He never tells me anything.
He's probably out having
an affair somewhere.
Wait a minute. He's coming in now.
It's Jim Taylor. He wants to know
who you're having an affair with.
Hello, Jim. What's doing?
Jim, we've been through this before.
If you have benches
in front of your store...
...people are gonna want
to sit on them.
I don't like him either...
...but I'm not coming over there
to tell him to move.
Give my best to Denise. Bye.
Well, whoever she is,
she sure likes to read a lot.
I'm flattered that you think
I've got that much energy.
I figured if I can't find Paul Sheldon...
...at least I can find out
what he wrote about.
What do you expect to find?
A story about a guy who drove his car
off a cliff in a snowstorm?
You see, it's just that kind of sarcasm...
...that's given
our marriage real spice.
I hope you like it.
It looks wonderful.
So do you.
I've never had meat loaf this good.
What do you do to it?
My secret is I only use
fresh tomatoes, never canned.
To give it that little extra zip,
I mix in Spam with the ground beef.
Can't get this
in a restaurant in New York.
Let's have a toast.
A toast?
Yes. To Misery.
Let me pour you some wine.
No.
To Misery.
Wait.
Let's do this right.
Do you have any candles?
I don't know. I-- I think so.
I'll go look.
Did you study decorating
or do you just have a flair?
Oh, you!
I just picked things up over the years.
Well, it certainly says "you."
You really think so?
Absolutely.
If you can't find any, it's okay.
I just thought it'd be nice.
Are you kidding?
If anyone had told me I'd be having...
...a candle-lit dinner
with Paul Sheldon in my own house...
...I would've checked both legs
to see which one was being pulled.
Will this do?
It's perfect.
To Misery...
...and to Annie Wilkes,
who brought her back to life.
Oh, Paul, I get goosebumps
every time I think about it.
Oh, my God. What have I done?
I'm so sorry, Paul.
I ruined your beautiful toast.
Will you ever forgive me?
Here, let me pour another one.
Can we pretend this never happened?
To Misery.
Paul, this is positively the best
Misery you've ever written.
Here's your pills.
Annie?
Annie, what is it?
The rain.
Sometimes it gives me the blues.
When you first came here...
...I only loved the writer part
of Paul Sheldon.
Now I know I love the rest of him too.
I know you don't love me.
Don't say you do.
You're a beautiful...
...brilliant...
...famous man of the world...
...and I'm...
...not a movie-star type.
You'll never know the fear
of losing someone like you...
...if you're someone like me.
Why would you lose me?
The book's almost finished.
Your legs are getting better.
Soon, you'll be wanting to leave.
Why would I leave?
I like it here.
That's very kind of you.
But I'll bet it's not altogether true.
I have this gun.
Sometimes I think about using it.
I better go now.
I might put bullets in it.
"There is a justice higher
than that of man...
...I will be judged by Him."
What?
They're hauling Misery into court.
That's nice.
"There is a justice...
...higher than that of man...
...I will be judged...
...by Him."
Welcome to Love Connection!
Where old-fashioned romance
meets modern-day technology.
Where you hear all
the intimate details of the date.
See you in the morning.
Paul.
I know you've been out.
- What?
- You've been out of your room.
No, I haven't.
Paul.
My little ceramic penguin
in the study always faces due south.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Ceramic penguin?
Is this what you're looking for?
I know you've been out twice.
At first, I couldn't figure out
how you did it, but last night...
...I found your key.
I know I left my scrapbook out.
I can imagine what you
might be thinking of me.
But you see, it's all okay.
Last night, it came so clear.
I realized you just need more time.
Eventually, you'll come to accept
the idea of being here.
Paul, do you know about the early days
at the Kimberly Diamond Mines?
Do you know what they did to
the workers who stole diamonds?
Don't worry, they didn't kill them.
That'd be like junking a Mercedes
because it had a broken spring.
If they caught them, they had to make
sure they could still work.
They also had to make sure
they couldn't run away.
The operation was called "hobbling."
Annie.
Whatever you're thinking about doing,
please don't do it.
Annie, for God--
Shh, darling.
Trust me.
- God's sake!
- It's for the best.
Please!
Almost done.
Just one more.
God, I love you.
You cock-a-doodie!
- Sit on this!
- You poop!
Just leave it, all right?
Oh, I like that tone.
How many times I have to tell you?
I have a system here.
- Where the hell is that thing?
- What thing?
The thing!
Here it is. Right where it should be.
What is it?
I'm not sure. Maybe nothing.
Well, I'm glad you found it.
There's that spice again.
Come on, Mizzy.
Come on.
Hi, pumpkin!
Such a kidder.
Come on, Misery.
Come on, Mizzy.
Hey, Pete.
Buster.
Answer me a couple of things.
If I can.
Do you have any new Paul Sheldon books?
Well, we had a batch.
Sold them all out in three days.
Would you happen to know
if Ms. Wilkes bought one of them?
Are you kidding?
Every time he writes a new book,
she has me set aside the first copy.
Has she been buying anything odd lately?
Ms. Wilkes?
Same old stuff.
Lest you call paper odd.
Newspaper?
No. The typing kind.
Oh, that kind.
Nothing odd about that.
Ms. Wilkes done something?
Not a thing.
I'll never understand you.
I cook your meals, I tend to you
practically 24 hours a day...
...and you continue to fight me.
When are we going to develop
a sense of trust?
Oh, my.
I didn't mean to startle you, but you
didn't give me a chance to knock.
You can tell from my reaction, I'm not
all that used to visitors out here.
What can I do for you?
I was wondering, do you happen
to know anything about Paul Sheldon?
- What do you want to know?
- Anything you could say might help.
He was born in Worcester,
Massachusetts 45 years ago...
...the only child of Franklin and
Helene Sheldon, majored in history.
That isn't the kind
of information I'm after.
You see, he's been missing
for quite some time--
I know. It's so upsetting.
I'm his number one fan.
I've got all his books,
every sentence he ever put down.
I'm so proud of my Paul Sheldon
collection.
Well, here I am, prattling on
and my manners have just flown away.
I haven't invited you in. Please.
Thank you.
You must know
all about that horrible accident.
- Mind if I take a look around?
- Of course not.
That accident almost killed me too.
I prayed when I heard the news.
I got down on my knees and I begged
for it not to be true.
You're gonna laugh at what I'm about
to say, but go ahead, I don't care.
When I was praying,
God told me to get ready.
- Get ready for what?
- To be his replacement.
He gave so much pleasure
to so many people.
There's a shortage of pleasure these
days, in case you hadn't noticed.
God told me, since I was
his number one fan...
...that I should make up new stories
as if I was Paul Sheldon.
So I went to town, and I bought
a typewriter and paper to type on.
The same kind Paul Sheldon used.
I turned the guest bedroom
into a writing studio.
- Would you like to see it?
- Sure.
It's right this way.
I know how he wrote,
the kinds of words he used...
...the wonderful stories he told.
I've spent the last four weeks
trying to write like him...
...but I can't do it right.
I try and I try and I know all
the words, but it's just not the same.
Maybe it takes time to get the hang of it.
I could give you 200 pages,
and you could tell me what you think.
- I'm not much of a critic.
- Well, I just thought...
Look at me. You'd think
I'd never had a guest.
- Would you like a hot cup of cocoa?
- No, I--
It's no trouble.
There's some already made.
Must get lonely, living out here
all by yourself.
If you can't enjoy your own company,
you're not fit company for anyone.
Well, you've got a point there.
- Here you are.
- Thanks, Ms. Wilkes...
...but I don't want to take up
any more of your time.
I best be going.
But you didn't even taste your cocoa.
I'm sure it's wonderful,
but I should be getting back.
If you wouldn't mind, perhaps I
could pay you another visit some time.
I'd be delighted.
Now that you know the way.
Ms. Wilkes?
Ms. Wilkes, are you all right?
Here!
Here! I'm down here!
I'm down here!
Mr. Sheldon?
Don't feel bad, Paul.
It was bound to happen sooner or later.
It's a sign.
You see, I've known for some time
why I was chosen to save you.
You and I were meant
to be together forever.
But now our time in this world must end.
But don't worry, Paul.
I've prepared for what must be done.
I put two bullets in my gun:
One for you and one for me.
Oh, darling, it'll be so beautiful.
Now, don't be afraid.
I love you.
I love you too.
And you're right.
We are meant to be together.
And I know we must die.
But it must be...
...so that Misery can live.
We have the power...
...to give Misery eternal life.
We must finish the book.
But the time is now.
Soon others will come.
It's almost finished.
By dawn...
...we'll be able to give Misery...
...back to the world.
I'll fix you something to eat.
Paul, I'm dying. Does she wind up
with Ian or Winthorne?
You'll know very soon.
I've just thought of the last chapter.
You know...
...when I finish, I'd like
everything to be perfect.
I'll need three things.
What things?
You don't know?
I was fooling, silly.
You need a cigarette.
You used to smoke, but you quit
except when you finish a book.
And you have just one.
And the match is to light it.
And you need one glass of champagne.
Dom Perignon.
Dom Perignon it is.
Annie?
Yes, Paul.
I'm almost done.
Oh, Paul, this is so romantic.
Ian and Winthorne dueling
for the right to Misery's hand.
Does Ian win? Oh, don't tell me.
It's Winthorne, right?
You'll know everything in a minute.
Get the champagne.
Did I do good?
You did perfect.
Except for one thing.
This time we'll need two glasses.
Oh, Paul.
Remember how for years nobody knew
who Misery's real father was...
...or if they'd ever be reunited?
It's all right here.
Does she finally marry Ian,
or will it be Winthorne?
It's all right here.
Paul, you can't!
Why not?
I learned it from you.
No, no, no!
Not Misery! Not my Misery!
Not my Misery!
I'm gonna kill you, you lying cocksucker!
Here, you want it?! You want it?!
Eat it! Eat it till you choke...
...you sick, twisted fuck!
This is it. The very first copy.
The word I'm getting is the Times
review is gonna be a love letter.
That'll be a first.
And my contacts at Time and Newsweek
tell me they're both raves.
Don't laugh, but for the first time,
you've got a shot at prizes.
Great.
I thought you'd be thrilled.
You're being taken seriously.
I'm delighted the critics like it,
and I hope the people like it too...
...but I wrote it for me.
Now, don't think
I'm completely nuts, but...
...in some way Annie Wilkes...
...that whole experience...
...helped me.
Paul, since you brought her up,
I have to ask...
...or I'll be drummed out
of the agent's union.
How would you feel about a nonfiction
book about what went on in that house?
If I didn't know you better
I'd think you suggested...
...I dredge up the worst horror of my
life so we could make a few bucks.
I thought you were over it.
I don't know if anyone could ever
totally get over something like that.
It's weird.
Even though I know she's dead...
...I still think about her
once in a while.
Excuse me. I don't mean to bother
you, but are you Paul Sheldon?
Yes.
I just want to tell you
I'm your number one fan.
That's very sweet of you.