[opening theme music playing]
[electronic chirp]
[electronic warbling]
[car engine roaring]
[brakes squealing]
[sheriff speaks indistinctly]
[indistinct]
Follow my lead, boys.
We'll be home in time for dinner.
- [all speak indistinctly]
- [guns cocking]
[alien diplomat speaks indistinctly]
[sheriff speaks indistinctly]
[alien diplomat] Humans, we come in peace.
[speaks indistinctly]
...together.
- [deputy] He's got a gun!
- [gunshot]
- [alien diplomat groaning]
- [gunshots]
[sheriff speaks indistinctly]
- [deputy indistinct]
- [sheriff indistinct]
[gunshots]
- [sheriff speaks indistinctly]
- [gunshots]
[indistinct]
- [exclaims]
- [gunshot]
[shouting]
[sheriff grunting, yelling]
[gunshot]
- [beeping]
- [ominous music playing]
[beeping continues]
[ominous music crescendos]
[cow moos]
[farmer speaks indistinctly]
[smooches, speaks indistinctly]
[cow moos]
[farmer sighs, speaks indistinctly]
[farmer grunts]
- [indistinct]
- [cow moos]
Oh my God! Oh no. Oh my God!
[farmer screaming]
[dramatic sting]
[farmer speaks indistinctly]
[speaks indistinctly, screams]
[whirring]
[alien conspiracist] They're here!
They're here!
They're coming for all our asses!
[people yelling]
[dramatic music playing]
- [man] Wait! Wait! Take me! Take me!
- [spaceship whirring]
- [whoosh]
- [laughs]
- [people screaming]
- [lasers shooting]
[dramatic music continues]
[whale calls]
- [people screaming]
- [brakes squealing]
[music ends]
[speaking alien language]
[alien trooper speaks indistinctly]
[alien trooper 2] Teabag.
[wheelchair bomber] Geronimo!
[veterans speak indistinctly]
[invigorating music playing]
[pub guest speaks indistinctly]
[yelling and fighting]
- [pub guest] Back to the moon with ya!
- [screaming]
[gangster speaks indistinctly]
[brakes squealing]
[US president speaks unintelligibly]
[crowd cheering]
- [people screaming]
- [gunshots]
[whirring]
- [tense music playing]
- [lasers shooting]
[whooshing]
[man speaking indistinctly]
[man screaming]
[blasting]
[man speaking indistinctly]
[people screaming]
- [whooping]
- [honking]
[heroic music playing]
[alien] No!
[stadium leader] All clear!
Bases loaded, motherfuckers!
[lasers building]
[heroic music builds]
[cracking]
[multiple explosions]
[music crescendos]
[silence]
[farting]
[musical flourish]
[electronic warbling]
[ominous music playing]
[music fades]