[low, thrumming rumbling]
[high-pitched tone]
[ethereal music plays, fades]
[radio announcer] And, of course, the news
that everyone is talking about in LA today
is that the Tom-Kitten has a name.
That's right. Tom and Katie
have issued a statement
naming their new baby Suri.
That's right, folks, Suri Cruise.
According to the statement, Su--
[keypad beeping]
[phone line ringing]
[man 1] Hey, Bo. What's up?
Yeah, J.P., I've been sitting here
for two hours,
but there's no sign of them.
So, they're still at it?
-Are you sure it was him?
-Have I ever let you down?
I'll let you know.
[camera shutter clicking]
[computer chimes]
Hey. Can I talk to you?
You with an agency?
I can pay.
For those pictures.
Five hundred dollars?
You're killing me.
-Please.
-[car engine starting]
-Shit.
-Lady, please. You can't do this.
-[tires squeal]
-You're killing me!
Fuck.
Fucking animal!
[man] TV's Justin Camley
enjoys a little afternoon delight
with a male buddy.
Okay. This, this, and this.
-Two-fifty each.
-Two-fifty?
Come on, man. Three hundred.
Camley hasn't been on TV
in, like, four years.
He was on that VH1 thing.
And he offered me 500.
Okay.
Three each.
["1 Thing" by Amerie playing]
♪ Don't wanna tell you what it is ♪
♪ Ooh-wee, it felt so serious ♪
♪ Got me thinking just too much ♪
♪ I wanna set it off, but… ♪
[man] Bo?
♪ It's this one thing
That got me trippin' ♪
-Bo.
-Hey-- Oh!
-Hey, sorry.
-Hey.
-Sorry.
-["1 Thing" continues in earbuds]
I got paid. It's a new toy.
Can you believe how small it is?
-That's great.
-Yeah.
-Cool, right?
So,
you know I don't like to judge
other people's lifestyle choices.
But I have really delicate sinuses.
And when you fry garlic and ginger,
it just makes the whole apartment
a little acrid?
Yeah, sure, I'll, um…
-Yeah, I'll open the window, Nathan.
-Thank you so much.
Yeah.
["1 Thing" resumes faintly in earbuds]
[TV announcer] US and Iraqi troops
have been engaging the militants
in a house-to-house battle
as they try to clear out
the remaining pockets of resistance.
The US military…
Hey, I'll take a skinny vanilla latte.
[barista] Sure.
…to support the ongoing operation.
And we have celebrity news
breaking right now here in Hollywood.
Former Sea of Tranquility star
Justin Camley
has been found dead
in his Hollywood Hills home.
TMZ are reporting he was found hanged
in an apparent suicide.
Only days ago, the scandal broke
that Justin had been cheating
on his long-term girlfriend
with another man.
[sighs] This whole Justin Camley situation
is sad as shit, Bo,
but it's not your fault.
You were just doing your job, that's all.
Yeah, I know.
-Can't say I sympathize with the guy.
-[man 1] Whitty, come on.
Sorry. Did someone force him
to become an actor?
Whitty, shut the fuck up.
He wanted his face out there,
money, the rest of it.
And then he gets sad
because he feels "exposed."
It's just dumb.
Can't handle the consequences,
don't enter the game.
Duke's right.
And half of these assholes
would kill themselves
if we didn't take their picture.
My limo guy says
he's got Sydney Alberti in the back.
Slutty Alberti.
[Duke laughs]
-[whistle in distance]
-[photographers clamoring]
[man 2] Where you going
to stay tonight, Sydney?
[man 3] Come on, Sydney!
[man 4] Sydney!
-Sydney, over here.
-Come on!
-Right here.
-You're looking beautiful. I love--
Sydney, right here!
-[man 5] Sydney!
-[man 6] Looking great. I love that dress.
-You look great in white.
-What are you wearing?
Sydney! This way, you skank!
I love your sex tape. Fucking whore!
You piece of shit!
Say it to my fucking face!
-Say it to my face!
-You touch me again. That is assault!
I've got witnesses!
You tou-- Touch me again!
You're gonna hear from my lawyer.
[ethereal music playing]
[ethereal music continues]
[camera shutters clicking]
[ethereal music fades]
[man in Scottish accent]
Miss Cattermole? Is everything all right?
[in English accent] Never better.
Cut!
Okay, guys, that's a wrap for day two.
Take your sides for tomorrow
if you don't have them.
Make sure you check your call sheets
for pre-call. Great job.
-Um, give me that.
-Thank you.
Um, there's a treat in the pocket
from Stephan.
[in US accent] Oh.
"I was schooled at Wycombe Abbey."
Wick.
Wick-um.
Abbey.
[in English accent] Abbey.
"I was schooled at Wycombe Abbey."
I was schooled at…
Wycombe. Wycombe Abbey.
["Supermassive Black Hole"
by Muse playing]
♪ Ooh, baby, don't you know I suffer? ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, can you hear me moan? ♪
♪ You caught me under false pretenses ♪
♪ How long before you let me go? ♪
♪ Ooh, oh ♪
♪ You set my soul alight ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
[glass shatters]
♪ You set my soul alight ♪
♪ Glaciers melting in the dead of night ♪
[gasps]
♪ You set my soul alight ♪
♪ Glaciers melting in the dead of night ♪
-♪ And the superstars ♪
-♪ You set my soul ♪
[song continues playing muffled]
[breathing heavily]
-[loud thud]
-[tires screeching]
[thunder rumbling]
-[song continues playing]
-[breathing heavily]
♪ You set my soul alight ♪
♪ Glaciers melting in the dead of night ♪
-♪ And the superstars ♪
-♪ You set my soul ♪
[breathing heavily]
♪ Supermassive black hole ♪
[unsettling string music playing]
[car horn honks in distance]
[unsettling string music continues]
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[speaking Czech]
-[driver speaking Czech]
-[officer speaking Czech]
[in English] Road is closed. I go around.
What did he… what did he say?
[driver] They found man in road.
A man?
Mm-hmm. They think hit-and-run.
[unsettling string music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[knocking at door]
[woman] Mazey, Hair and Makeup
are ready for you.
[exhales]
[TV announcer] It's been two whole weeks
since Mazey Day,
star of the EverWish saga,
abruptly left the set
of the third installment of the franchise.
No one has seen her--
-[Nathan] I… I heard you come in.
-Yeah.
This is really hard for me.
I'm not good at confrontation,
so my therapist
suggested that I use cue cards.
And…
[Nathan clears throat] Mm.
"As you know,
your share of the rent is late."
"And I have noticed groceries disappearing
from my clearly marked personal shelf
in the fridge."
-"While I truly value our friendship--"
-Nathan.
Please.
"I do not feel it is appropriate for me
to financially support--"
Nathan.
I'll get the money.
[exhales]
Thank you.
All right, that's Erika and Brad.
Have a nice day, y'all.
'Sup, Bo?
Haven't you heard? No dogs allowed.
Meow.
You got a minute?
Like I said, Hec, I'm out.
I'm not trying to tempt you back in.
Yeah, 'cause you're scared
of the competition.
[scoffs]
Maybe I respect your decision.
Thought about that?
So, why are you here?
I thought that maybe
you could help me with something.
Help you with what?
Mazey Day.
The actress.
Yeah, Mazey Day. What about her?
You know, she's filming
in Czechoslo-somewhere, one of those.
Started day drinking. Erratic behavior.
Stopped showing up to set.
Angry one day, fucking weeping the next.
Basically gone fucking wacko.
So, that's your professional
psychiatric opinion of the situation?
She got kicked off the movie set
two weeks ago,
flew home, and no one's seen her since.
Not home, nowhere.
So, everybody's cool
with leaving her alone, then?
Nick's offering 30K
for the first photo of her.
-30K?
-30K.
Forty if you catch her
looking like a junkie.
I've been hitting up all my peeps, but
no leads. Nothing. Nada.
You, um, still keep in touch
with your snitch?
I took his number off my phone.
All right, well, if you happen to find
that you wrote it somewhere,
let me know.
[tense music playing]
[breathing nervously]
[phone line ringing]
-Hey, J.P.
-Hey, stranger.
Um… [clears throat]
-Have you heard anything on Mazey Day?
-Thought you'd given up on all this.
Yeah, this could be
the kind of payday I could use.
Look, I only know
what everyone else knows.
She's not at home.
Gotta be holed up somewhere, but no clue.
All right, cool.
Uh, let me know if that changes.
[woman] Hello? Food delivery.
Oh, I think I have some money in my purse.
It's okay.
Mr. G said
while you're a guest in his house,
he's left money to cover everything.
[pensive music playing]
[phone dialing]
[dial-up internet static]
So, she still has a membership,
but she hasn't been since when?
You haven't seen her in a while.
You can give me a call
if she pops by again.
Let me know if that changes.
You can call me here if anything changes.
Thank you. Bye.
[pensive music continues]
[whispers] Where the fuck are you?
Hmm.
[pensive music fades]
Mazey Day's a fan, huh?
[Bo chuckles]
She says she orders here every week?
Mm-hmm.
-Come on.
-[woman] She still does.
Saw her yesterday.
[Bo] Really?
[woman] She's staying
at some, like, producer's house.
[exhales]
[unsettling string music playing]
[restless exhale]
[exhales]
-[loud thud]
-[gasps]
["Supermassive Black Hole" playing]
[whimpers]
[unsettling string music playing]
["Supermassive Black Hole" playing]
[unsettling string music fades]
-Ms. Day?
-[gasps]
[door closes]
[beep]
[camera shutter clicks]
[man] The first step is to recognize
that you're not in control of this.
It has taken you over.
And you must be humble
in the face of it.
Hm?
I've arranged a place
where we can take you.
Private, out of town, just for a few days.
You need isolation.
Away from anyone
and anything.
[Mazey] Dr. Babich.
Can you get me better?
Well, it's about
getting you through tonight.
And then the next night.
Then we see.
Okay.
[Bo] Shit.
[pensive music playing]
Fuck yeah.
[camera shutter clicking]
This better be you, Mazey.
[car engine starting]
The fuck are we going?
[tense music playing]
Fuck it.
Oh shit.
Fuck.
[car door closes]
Oh shit.
[air hissing]
Hey. What the fuck?
Goddammit!
[air hissing]
Fuck!
[country music playing faintly]
[man] Thanks, guys. Thank you very much.
[guest] Thank you.
[Bo exhales]
[sighs]
[man] Day going well?
Absolutely not.
I'm guessing you could use a coffee.
Or a beer?
Coffee's fine.
Coffee it is.
Do you know anyone with a tow truck
around here?
-Car trouble?
-Yeah.
Uh, Mitch runs the repair shop in town,
but he came by here this morning.
He'll be gone for the day.
Would he come if I called him?
No, I mean, you know…
[mimics drinking]
…gone for the day.
Oh God.
Is there a motel within crawling distance?
Uh, the only place near here
is the Cedar Wood Retreat.
That's really more of a rehab place.
A rehab?
Yeah, but for, like,
rich hippie types, you know?
It's a little New Age for my blood.
Maybe they have a bed for the night?
Yeah, you got no chance of that.
Uh, Kyle, that's my uncle,
most days he's a masseuse there.
He says someone hired the entire complex
for the weekend.
The whole place?
All the staff sent home,
so it's empty, ultra-private.
The whole place
for, like, one person the whole time.
Any clue who the one person is?
Someone rich who wants to get straight
on the down-low.
[phone line ringing]
Oh, hey. You were right.
-Compliments to the chef.
-Mm-hmm.
-Thumbs up for the pecan pie, Jesse.
-[Jesse] We aim to please.
Wait, wait, wait. Hey, hey, no, no.
-Come on. Let's go.
-I just got here.
That's a long-ass ride.
No time for a soda?
You want a soda, or you want Mazey Day?
Yeah, that's what I thought. Thank you.
-You actually know where we're going?
-Just shut up and trust me.
[adventurous music playing]
[keypad beeping, buzzes]
-It was worth a shot.
-Was it?
-What if it would have opened the door?
-No one's hopping this fence.
What is this, Jurassic Park?
Got a T. rex in there or something?
No, they're just keeping
people like us out.
How sure are you she's in there?
85%.
85%?
Maybe 80.
-Eighty? It's gonna be 75 in a--
-Wait, wait, wait. You hear that?
-[vehicle approaching]
-[Bo] Hide the bike.
Oh shit.
Is that Whitty's car?
-Did you tell him?
-No, did you?
No!
Hey, ladies.
-Where'd you put it? Underneath my seat?
-Where's what?
Your fucking tracker is what.
I think of it as an unpaid informant.
It's under the gas tank.
[Hector] Two chunks of shit!
Like you've never popped one under a limo.
-This is legit journalism.
-Oh, Mr. Pulitzer.
-He's adorable.
-[Hector] This is stealing intel.
[Whitty] Ooh, yeah, some intel.
Fuck you doing out here, huh?
It's gotta be Mazey Day, right?
-This was my find.
-Yeah, I heard of this place.
Private A-list "holistic experiences."
Super kooky.
[Duke] Sounds like a rehab joint.
Let's find a way in.
Fuckin'…
Fucking privacy screen.
Which means whatever they do
on the other side
has gotta be worth seeing.
[grunting]
-You're literally crawling in the dirt.
-[Whitty] Shut up.
Ladies first.
-[man] Terry.
-Hey, Clay.
-I'll do the chicken.
-Sure thing.
[power tool whirring]
What the hell is that sound?
It's like a power tool.
[camera shutter clicking]
Door's opening.
[camera shutters clicking]
Is he carrying a rivet gun?
Fuck, that's the guy who slashed my tires.
Mazey Day is here.
[camera shutters clicking]
Okay, my friends. That's Dmitri Babich,
specialist doctor to the stars.
Ah, the big addiction guy.
My guess says she's on crystal meth.
More like coke.
Isn't Babich into holistic voodoo
or some shit? Is he even a doctor?
For Hollywood, just about.
She must've been desperate to call him in.
[camera shutters clicking]
-[vehicle door closes]
-[vehicle retreats]
[Whitty] Okay.
[Mazey panting]
[ethereal music playing]
-["Supermassive Black Hole" playing]
-[ethereal music playing]
[camera shutters clicking]
[Hector] Is that her?
-[Duke] I think it's her.
-[Hector] Holy shit. This is 30 grand.
[Bo] Is that a fucking chain?
-Is that a fucking chain around her neck?
-Kinky shit.
What?
Babich shackled her up
for the cold turkey.
That's fucking illegal, Hector.
-Shit.
-Jesus!
-[Bo grunts]
-Bo, what the fuck-- Bo, what are you--
Shit!
[Bo] Oh shit.
[Hector] Oh shit. Fuck.
Oh my God.
[Bo] Shit!
Guys, she's burning up.
So much for sexy shots.
[panting]
-[loud thud]
-[tires screeching]
You gotta go.
Guys, can you just stop for one minute?
Stop! She's chained to the floor!
They say I gotta be alone.
Gotta get through this alone.
They say a lot of shit!
-Okay. We're gonna get you out.
-[bleating]
-[Hector] What the fuck?
-[Bo grunting]
Get the fuck away from me!
-Here we go.
-[sobs] Get the fuck away.
-[Bo] Mazey?
-[sobs] Please.
You don't understand!
Mazey, I just--
["Supermassive Black Hole" playing]
Mazey.
Go!
Run! Run away!
["Supermassive Black Hole" playing]
[ethereal music playing]
["Supermassive Black Hole" playing
muffled, warped]
-[snarls]
-[retches]
-Oh fuck!
-What the fuck is this?
-[Bo] Oh!
-[Mazey screams in pain]
Just go!
-Please!
-[Duke] Bo, Bo, Bo.
-[Mazey whimpers]
-[bones crack]
[screaming in pain]
-Oh my God!
-Oh my God! What the fuck?
[bones cracking]
Bo, Bo, Bo. No, we gotta go, Bo.
-[snarls]
-We have to go, Bo!
[Bo] Oh my God. What's wrong with her?
-[bones cracking]
-[snarls]
[growling]
Oh, fuck me.
[both panting]
[snarling]
-Go, go, go, go, go!
-Shit, shit.
-[Duke] We gotta go!
-Just a couple more.
[snarls]
-[roars]
-[Whitty screaming]
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
-[flesh tearing]
-[Whitty choking]
[Duke whimpering]
[Whitty screaming]
[tense music playing]
[Bo, Hector panting]
[Hector] Come on! Let's go!
[panting, whimpering]
-Guys! Guys, help!
-[Hector] Shit.
[whimpering] Help!
[Duke whimpering]
-[beast snarling]
-[Duke screaming]
-[Bo] Hector, what are you doing?
-His shots are worth a million each, Bo.
[strained] A million…
-[Duke groans]
-[Bo whimpers]
…each!
[Duke whimpering]
-[beast growls]
-[Duke screaming]
-[Bo] Come on.
-[Hector] Come on! Go, go, go, go!
Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck!
[snarling]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[tense music playing]
[Bo whimpers]
[car horn honks]
[Bo groans]
[Hector groans]
[shouting in Spanish]
[man screams]
[tense music playing]
[both panting]
[beast panting, snarling]
[beast growling]
Goddamn.
[Terry] It's good, right?
Another satisfied victim.
Goddamn, Jesse.
Good to know.
That's what you ought to call that,
"pecan perfection."
I mean, the chicken was perfection.
The chicken was perfect.
-It is so easy to screw up chicken.
-[Terry] Oh yeah.
Not many people know this.
They think, "Oh, well,
you just drop it in the deep fryer." No.
It's not about frying chicken.
You're gonna sauté it, bake it…
But it's gotta be done, you know…
Because you undercook it, and, you know,
people die.
-[Bo panting]
-Lock it.
-Whoa, whoa! What--
-[Bo whimpers]
-[Terry] What--
-Okay.
[Terry] Are you okay? What--
[grunting]
What is--
It could come in. It's out there!
It could be coming this way!
We need to block the door!
Ma'am. What has happened?
-Ma'am, calm down.
-Officer. Please just call for help.
-Calm down.
-[Bo] Call for help! Call for help!
-I will momentarily, ma'am, but first--
-[Bo] Please.
-Fucking call for help!
-Calm down.
Take a few deep breaths, settle down,
and explain to me what has happened.
Then maybe we can figure out
how we're gonna move forward.
[Bo] No, just please
fucking call for help!
-[Clay] I will do that momentarily, ma'am.
-She's here.
But first, I need to understand--
No, no, no, no!
-Okay, back up!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, Officer. Sir.
-Stay down. Stay down.
-No, you don't under--
Officer! Officer! It's out there, Officer!
You need to call for backup, Office--
-[Jesse screams]
-[dishes clattering]
[Bo gasps]
[tense music playing]
[Terry] Hey, Jesse, you okay?
Jesse?
[woman gasps softly]
[beast growls]
[man, woman screaming]
[blood squelching]
[woman] No!
[woman screaming]
[woman gasping, choking]
[Hector screams]
[Bo sobs]
[dishes clattering]
[Clay screaming]
[tense music swells]
[Bo screams]
[tense music subsides]
[labored breathing]
Hec. Hec.
[country music plays faintly]
[Hector gurgles]
[Mazey] Kill me.
Please.
Kill me.
[sobs]
Please.
[somber music playing]
Just… just shoot me.
[somber music continues]
[Mazey breathing heavily]
[somber music fades]
[gunshot]
[tense music playing]
[tense music fades]