Wouldn't you rather give it all at once
to something real?
What would we be stealing?
The quarterly payroll
for an entire Imperial sector.
That's why you're here? Revenge?
Yeah, that's good enough for now.
I didn't mark you for a team player.
Working with other people is never easy.
VEL: We're taking crates of payroll
from that vault,
loading the freighter,
and escaping out of the runway tunnel.
Escaping? In a Rono?
You'll be lucky to make the horizon.
No one's stupid enough to try it.
No one but us.
TARAMYN: It's about confidence.
We belong here.
We're followin' orders.
Wait!
(WHOOSHING)
Surprise from above
is never as shocking as one from below.
-Don't move.
-(GRUNTS)
He comes here with nothin'
but the clothes on his back
and a stone worth 30,000 credits?
Who brings a treasure to a robbery?
I'm being paid.
You can't live with that?
I don't wanna walk in
looking over my shoulder.
CASSIAN: Looks just like your model.
(CHUCKLES) Should do.
I've had plenty of time to study,
and we've been
sneaking up here for months.
KLEYA: There's nothing else
you can do, Luthen.
They're either gonna be okay or not.
The thief. Andor.
I wasn't careful.
It'll all be over this time tomorrow.
Or it'll just be starting.
I couldn't sleep.
CASSIAN: It's natural.
I need to be at my best.
Don't worry.
The excitement will kick in.
I'm struggling to understand
why my faith doesn't calm me.
I believe in something.
Why am I so unsettled?
I mean, you have nothing,
you sleep like a stone.
I write when I can't sleep.
Wrote about you last night.
Not you specifically, not "Clem."
Although I'm assuming
that's not your real name, anyway.
"The Role of Mercenaries
in The Galactic Struggle for Freedom."
My conclusion is simple.
Weapons are tools.
Those that use them are, by extension,
assets that we must use
to our best advantage.
The Empire has no moral boundaries,
why should we not take hold
of every chance we can?
Let them see how an insurgency adapts.
(SIGHS) Well, you're half right.
The Empire doesn't play by the rules.
And how am I wrong?
(SIGHS)
They don't care enough to learn.
They don't have to.
You mean nothing to them.
Perhaps they'll think
differently tomorrow.
Be careful what you wish for.
So you think it's hopeless, do you?
Freedom? Independence? Justice?
We should just submit and be thankful?
Just take what we're given?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Do I look thankful to you?
(SMACKS LIPS) No.
But I'm glad that you're here.
No matter what the reason.
Don't worry.
You'll be fine.
You'll sleep when it's done.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
The Dhanis, they're a simple people.
They breed a sad combination of traits
that make them particularly vulnerable
to manipulation.
On a practical level,
they have great difficulty holding
multiple ideas simultaneously.
We've found the best way to steer them
as we'd like is to offer alternatives.
You put a number of options on the table,
and they're so wrapped up in choosing,
they fail to notice
you've given them nothing
they thought they wanted at the start.
Their deeper problem is pride.
The Dhanis would rather lose,
they'd rather suffer, than accept.
Which is wildly ironic
as they've choked down
everything we've thrown at them
these last 12 years.
It's a ten-day trek up from the Lowlands.
We offered them a transport
because we know they'll refuse,
but then, along the way,
we've placed a series of "Comfort Units,"
shelters and taverns
with cheap local beverages.
Quite predictably,
what began as 500 pilgrims at the bottom
has already dwindled down to...
-Where are we now, Lieutenant?
-We counted 60 last night, sir.
They may pick up
some highland stragglers along the way,
but it's developing as we'd expected.
Not that long ago,
they'd put 15,000 out there.
Have they any idea this is the last time
they'll be allowed up here?
No, there's no profit in that.
We've spent the last decade promoting
an Imperial viewing festival
down in the Enterprise Zone.
They'll have that going forward.
It is their sacred valley, is it not?
Well, ultimately, they will return,
won't they, Colonel?
When you need plenty of arms and legs
to build all you've got planned.
You've been here the longest,
haven't you, Lieutenant?
Yes, sir. Seven years.
Will the Dhanis let us build
our new facility in peace?
I don't see them having a choice.
The Eye, Colonel, you're in for a treat.
(CHUCKLES) It really is something to see.
Quite the celestial spectacle.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, what do you make of him?
Colonel Petigar?
He's an engineer. You won't charm him.
Well, it won't be for lack of trying.
Are we secure?
I've brought in 30 sentries from Alkenzi.
I'll be supervising them.
I've sent our best men to the perimeters.
-Tonight must be perfect.
-That's the plan, sir.
Perfect.
I want that word ringing in your ears.
TARAMYN: Echo-One.
Echo-One.
Echo-One on spot.
-NEMIK: Go ten up.
-What is that?
-Fieldcomm. It's a battle radio.
-(RADIO WHIRRING)
Looks Imperial.
Not anymore.
TARAMYN: Echo-One.
-Echo-One.
-Go three up.
CASSIAN: What? It's not working?
NEMIK: It will. It locks in.
When it does, it will carry on working
long after everything else is fried.
VEL: (OVER RADIO) Valley-One. Valley-One.
Valley-One, go. Valley-One.
Valley-One. Valley-One on spot.
Valley-One. Valley-One.
TARAMYN: Echo engaged. Lockin' now.
-(BEEPING)
-Lock and confirm, Echo. Lock and confirm.
(RADIO WHIRRING, BEEPING)
Confirm. We're locked in.
We're dialed in.
-Movin' now.
-(BEEPING)
Safe travels.
TARAMYN: And to you.
VEL: Valley-One out.
Let's pick it up.
Fallin' behind.
He likes giving orders, doesn't he?
Makes sense, right?
What do you mean? (BREATHING HEAVILY)
They didn't tell you, did they?
(SIGHS)
He was a stormtrooper.
Really?
Pick it up!
You should've been here
when Cinta found out.
They slaughtered her whole family.
TARAMYN: Pick it up.
(GRUNTS)
(WHOOSHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHIRRING)
(WHOOSHING)
Has it started?
LIEUTENANT GORN: Well, the Dhanis
don't believe it ever ends.
So, yes, sir, it has definitely started.
Gorn here. Go ahead.
CORPORAL: Low Road Unit reporting, sir.
The guests are arriving.
LIEUTENANT GORN:
Let's have a peaceful welcome.
Will do, sir.
Form up!
But do it quietly.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
TARAMYN: Tighten up. Eyes front.
They'll be here any minute.
You're a soldier now, Clem.
These people hate us.
The ones that have climbed this far
have made a life of it.
Do not engage.
We meet soldiers from the garrison?
We're from Alkenzi.
They're from Alkenzi?
We're from the garrison.
Keep your mouths shut,
and remember, we belong here.
(GRUNTS)
VEL: It might be best
if we split these up between us, and...
SOLDIER 1: Hysterical.
I said, "You can't both be right."
(SOLDIERS LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING DHANI)
(IN ENGLISH) They're just gonna be
waiting for him, right?
I had a good look at her.
Believe me, patience was not
the first thing that came to mind.
(SOLDIERS LAUGHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
SOLDIER 2: Oi, here comes another one.
Whoo!
(WHOOSHING)
Oh, look at that.
SOLDIER 1: Come on.
Let's get back to base.
Escort, march!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(JAYHOLD GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Roboda?
-Roboda.
-I'm dressing Leonart.
He's 12, he can dress himself.
Come and look at this sash.
None of this was stored properly.
It's all compressed.
Perhaps you've expanded.
JAYHOLD: Where's his Imperial blouse?
I'm not wearing that.
You'll do as you're told.
Mother, I don't feel well.
You'll make an effort tonight
if it kills you.
He might have a fever.
-He might feel the back of my hand.
-The boy is ill, Jayhold.
He's always ill.
Look, you wanna get out of here, do you?
Get that transfer,
leave this stinking planet?
You certainly whine about it enough.
Colonel Petigar
will be making those decisions.
Now, I want everyone
on their best behavior this evening.
I look forward to seeing that.
(JAYHOLD SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Company, halt!
Squad, halt!
(SPEAKING DHANI)
(PILGRIMS MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(IN ENGLISH) Let them pass.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
TARAMYN: Quick, march!
(WHIRRING)
Get ready. I think I hear two coming.
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
(WHOOSHING)
VEL: Let's go.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-You were right.
-(SNIFFLES)
I'm not tired at all.
Tighten up.
All right, listen up!
Squads One, Two, and Four,
you're here for the night.
Get comfortable.
I want no surprises.
Squad Three, standby.
You'll be joining the return escort
with the Commandant and his family.
If you don't bother them,
they won't bother you.
So I want mouths shut and eyes open.
Corporal.
Right turn.
With me.
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Squad, halt!
(MUFFLED WHOOSHING)
(JAYHOLD CHUCKLES)
Everybody ready?
Ah, the skin?
We trade goat hides
for a three-year lease.
If they didn't smell so badly,
it might be amusing.
Come on, you two.
The Dhanis have a rough appetite
for fragrance.
Yes, I've been warned.
A bit of ceremonial nonsense,
and we can tuck into a fine table.
Above the stench.
(PETIGAR GRIMACES)
-Has she checked in?
-(SIGHS)
Not yet.
Problem?
She'll be there.
Wrong time to mess up.
They were supposed to call us!
-When are you gonna learn?
-SOLDIER 1: We were waiting!
KIMZI: You were waiting?
That's your excuse?
You should know better.
Don't let Gorn catch you.
VOICE ON COMM: Alkenzi Wing Seven.
Eastern sweep completed.
Returning to base.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Attention!
Corporal.
Sir.
These men from Alkenzi?
Yes, sir.
-(SIGHS) You do the talking, eh?
-Yes, sir.
Let's make quick work of it.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CINTA AND VEL PANTING)
(SPEAKING DHANI)
Where is she? We're late.
-(DEVICE WHIRRING)
-KIMZI: Random.
Alkenzi?
No, they're shutting down right now.
Everything's grounded.
No one wants to be up in this.
(PANTING)
CINTA: Vel, get down.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
It's solid?
Call them.
VEL: You're sure?
You're stalling.
TARAMYN: (OVER RADIO) Echo-One.
Echo-One.
Echo-One. Echo.
Valley-One.
Valley-One at go.
Call it.
Are you on point?
TARAMYN: Yes.
We're here on point.
Are we going or not?
(TENSE MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
Vel.
Go.
We go.
TARAMYN: Copy.
(SPEAKING DHANI)
(IN ENGLISH) He says,
"May The Eye find the good in all of us."
Indeed.
Tell him we'll give him the gift
of our absence and be on our way.
(WHOOSHING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-LIEUTENANT GORN: Corporal.
-At your service.
Fall in.
Right turn.
With me.
(PILGRIMS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY IN DHANI)
(GONG SOUNDING)
(CHIEFTAIN SPEAKING IN DHANI)
(PILGRIMS EXCLAIMING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
SOLDIER: Sir.
-LIEUTENANT GORN: Everything in order?
-Yes, sir.
LIEUTENANT GORN: You take the point
and send your men down.
I want no one up here
without my permission.
Will do, sir.
You know, it's the old ones
causing all the problems.
Always trying to...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(DOOR BUZZING, OPENING)
It'll all be much easier.
The days of passing skins
and ritual nonsense
will be soon behind us.
No great loss there.
It's not as if
there's much Aldhani civilization
-to even forget about in the first place.
-(DOOR CLOSES)
-Drop it. On the floor.
-What's all this?
-ROBODA: No!
-TARAMYN: Drop it there.
(ROBODA WHIMPERING)
Where's Lieutenant Gorn?
-Down, on the ground. Down.
-(CRYING)
-What's the meaning of this?
-Be quiet!
(ROBODA CRYING)
-Move.
-ROBODA: Please.
-This is an outrage!
-SKEEN: Quiet! Stop talking!
Stop right there.
(ROBODA SOBBING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
COLONEL PETIGAR: Let the boy go.
(ROBODA CRYING)
-Let the boy go!
-Jayhold...
Colonel, please.
Nobody has to die.
-(BLASTERS FIRING)
-(PETIGAR GRUNTS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
SOLDIER: Everything all right, sir?
All good.
You can join your men
at the bottom of the hill now.
Enjoy the Eye.
SOLDIER: Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
You'll never get out of here.
(GRUNTS)
(WHIRRING)
We're good.
(PILGRIMS CHEERING)
-You do everything they tell you.
-Just what are you after?
VEL: You'll be taking us
to the payroll vault.
-That's insane.
-Or we die together.
-I can't open the vault.
-Time check.
-Falling behind.
-Go. We'll finish.
JAYHOLD: Didn't you hear me?
I don't control the vault!
It's on a code from the air base.
It's done remotely.
Keep lying
and it'll be a short night for you.
We know how the vault works.
We need your hand to key the sensor.
We can take just that if you'd prefer.
JAYHOLD: You'll never make it out.
-VEL: You better pray we do.
-You have no idea...
One path! One choice.
We win, or everyone dies.
Starts now.
(LEONART WHIMPERS)
(WHIRRING)
Jayhold, please just do what they say.
(BEEPING)
(ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
(STATIC)
Welcome, sir.
Put them down.
Down!
Against the wall. Move.
Move!
Down.
Sorry, just having a problem
with the comms.
Try the inverse channel.
Hands away from the console.
Get up, now!
Move!
Let's go! Move!
(ROBODA SOBBING)
(STATIC)
(PILGRIMS SINGING IN DHANI)
(SPEAKING DHANI)
NEMIK: Lights. Parapet.
Base Floods. Turrets. Launch Tunnel.
Comms, you know.
This?
Don't touch, that's Alkenzi,
that's the Air Base Link.
You're coming with us.
Everyone else stays here.
Your comms have been disabled.
Ours are working.
If you don't help us,
your family will die.
If you slow us down,
if you stall, if you argue,
if you play us in anyway, they will die.
You'll kill us anyway.
'Cause that's what you'd do, right?
No.
If we get what we came for,
everyone walks away.
But if we go down,
you're right there with us.
-NEMIK: 14 minutes.
-VEL: Move.
Tell me you'll be all right.
I'll be fine.
Go.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROBODA BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
(PILGRIMS SINGING IN DHANI)
Are you having trouble with your comms?
It just went down.
The Alkenzi line is still open,
but everything else is fried.
Weird, right?
Must be the Eye.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Clem out first.
(WHIRRING)
SKEEN: Clear.
TARAMYN: Vel, take him.
VEL: Move.
TARAMYN: Clem, with me.
-GUARD 1: Forty credits.
-GUARD 2: I'm in.
GUARD 3: Deal.
Hexba.
GUARD 4: Hexa.
GUARD 5: Hoxla.
-GUARD 1: Come on.
-GUARD 6: Oh, come on.
(GUARDS LAUGHING)
TARAMYN: Commandant on the floor!
Commandant inspection!
-Muster up! Let's go.
-GUARD 1: Yes, sir.
Line it up!
Move!
Hands on heads!
Hands on your heads!
TARAMYN: Drop it! Now!
-Out! Out!
-JAYHOLD: This is not an inspection,
-it is a robbery!
-VEL: Move!
JAYHOLD: They've taken
the tower and communications.
They're holding hostages,
including my wife and son.
Move!
They've already killed, and I am sure
that they will do so again,
which is why I am urging you to cooperate.
VEL: Enough! Move! Move!
(GUARD 4 GRUNTS)
Hey!
You are gonna load us out
as fast as possible.
Anyone doesn't want to hustle
for the next ten minutes, raise your hand.
All right, up! Up! Up! Up! Let's go!
Two men to a trolley. Let's go!
You got power?
Yeah, I do indeed.
SKEEN: Let's go! Move! Move! Move!
(SINGING IN DHANI)
(SPEAKING DHANI)
(BEEPING, WHIRRING)
JAYHOLD: I can't unlock the trays.
It takes a signal from Alkenzi.
-VEL: Get with the others.
-JAYHOLD: I only control the gate!
-Move!
-They won't open!
JAYHOLD: Do you hear me?
I don't control the vault!
Get ready.
Fire in the hole!
(WHIRRING INTENSIFIES)
(EXPLOSION)
They're in.
Go. I'm almost done.
I'll be right behind you.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Let's go!
-Let's go! You, here! Move, move! Move!
-VEL: You, up there! Move! You up there!
NEMIK: (OVER RADIO) Echo-One. Echo-One,
on spot. Echo-One. Echo-One, on spot.
Valley-One. Loud and clear.
NEMIK: We've taken the vault
and breached the vault door...
(DISTORTED) In... Repeat. We're in...
the freighter now.
CINTA: Copy that. All good up here.
(BEEPING, WHIRRING)
NEMIK: Get ready.
Alkenzi should be calling in soon.
CINTA: Will do. Valley-One out.
(SINGING IN DHANI)
(SPEAKING DHANI)
-VEL: Come on!
-(GUARDS PANTING)
Come on!
-TARAMYN: Load!
-Out of the way!
-VEL: Come on! All the way around!
-TARAMYN: Move! Bring it in!
Get it turned around! Move! Move!
TARAMYN: You're taking too long!
Let's go! Let's go!
-Go! Get out! Out! Out! Okay!
-VEL: Come on!
-TARAMYN: Faster! Get it round and moving!
-VEL: Move! Move! Come on, move!
MAN: (OVER RADIO) Tower One,
this is Alkenzi Wing Command.
Requesting status rep.
We have a vault-breach indicator
lighting up over here.
(BEEPING)
(SINGING IN DHANI)
MAN: Tower One, please respond.
A vault-breach indicator light
has gone off, and we need clari...
(BUZZES)
(BEEPING, WHIRRING)
(POWERING DOWN)
(PILGRIMS SINGING IN DHANI)
SOLDIER: Where are we going?
KIMZI: Heading to the vault.
SOLDIER: But we'll miss the Eye.
Move! Let's go!
-Let's go! Move! Move! Move!
-SKEEN: Move!
Bring 'em in, bring 'em in. Keep loading!
-VEL: Come on!
-Now! Now!
VEL: Move, move, move!
SKEEN: All right! Move! Let's go!
-TARAMYN: Keep moving!
-VEL: Come on!
-CASSIAN: Go, go, go!
-VEL: Move it!
-Get out of here.
-TARAMYN: Keep loadin'!
-VEL: Let's go!
-TARAMYN: Faster!
-SKEEN: Come on.
-Move! Move!
-VEL: Come on! Faster! Move!
-Move!
-Get loading!
-VEL: Get it on. Come on.
Come on!
(SINGING IN DHANI)
-VEL: Move!
-TARAMYN: That's it. Let's go!
GUARD: All right, got it.
TARAMYN: Move, move! Move! Move!
VEL: Keep moving! Keep moving.
Go! Move around him! Move!
Time check!
Five-nine.
Faster! Faster! Faster!
VEL: Come on! Let's go! Come on!
(WHIRRING)
KIMZI: Watch yourselves!
It's a long way down!
(WHOOSHING)
(PILGRIMS GASP)
Almost home! Everyone can go home!
Let's move!
Move!
Right, get it out! Out!
LIEUTENANT GORN: What are you doing?
You're still loading?
VEL: We have two minutes.
LIEUTENANT GORN:
I was afraid you'd be leaving!
We need to be locking up!
GUARD: Easy there... Yeah...
Quickly, quickly...
You.
Quit gawking and get pushing.
Close it down! Let's go! Last call!
You'll hang for this.
Seven years serving you?
I deserve worse than that.
Are we good to go?
We're good.
Okay, come on! Come on!
(KLAXON ALARM BLARING)
(THUDDING, CLINKING)
LIEUTENANT GORN: Are you crazy?
Just leave it! Get this thing in the air!
KIMZI: What's going on here?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
You're off your post, Corporal.
Sorry, sir, but...
This is a classified mission,
and you're not cleared to be here.
Commandant?
Tell him, sir. Tell him he needs to leave.
KIMZI: Sir?
I am giving you a direct order, Corporal!
What is going on here?
-(GASPING)
-KIMZI: Sir...
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(BLASTERS FIRING)
-(GRUNTING)
(BLASTER FIRES)
(GRUNTS)
-(BLASTERS FIRING)
-(GRUNTS)
(SOLDIER GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(FIRING CONTINUES)
-Go and get us ready!
-Cover me!
Now!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(GROANING)
-(BLASTER FIRES)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(BEEPING, WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH STRAINING)
(CASSIAN GRUNTING)
(CASSIAN CHOKES)
(BLASTERS FIRING)
I'm pinned down!
(GROWLS)
Cover me!
(TARAMYN GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
No!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING, GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(BLASTER FIRES)
-(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(SOLDIER GROANS)
Where's Taramyn?
(SHIP WHIRRING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BLASTS RICOCHETING)
(WHIRRING)
(WHOOSHING)
Get this thing in the air!
Go! Go! Go!
(BEEPING, WHIRRING)
(POWERING UP)
Hang on!
(WHOOSHING)
(GUARDS SCREAMING)
(SKEEN AND NEMIK GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHOOSHING)
(ALL GASPING)
-SKEEN: No!
-VEL: Nemik!
-(NEMIK GROANING)
-(GRUNTS)
SKEEN: No! No! No!
-Lift him!
-(NEMIK GROANS)
I can't feel my legs. I can't,
I can't feel my legs.
-VEL: Nemik.
-SKEEN: Hey.
VEL: Nemik, can you hear me?
(WHIMPERS)
VEL: Can you hear me?
I need a flight path.
SKEEN: He's hurt! Hold on!
-What are you doing?
-Hold him still.
What is that?
-Med-spike. Keep him still.
-SKEEN: (SHUSHES) Go, go, go.
No. (WHIMPERS)
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(VEL BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
Where am I heading? I need numbers!
Hold on!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(VEL AND SKEEN GRUNT)
CASSIAN: I'm flying blind!
(BEEPING, WHIRRING)
(WHOOSHING)
(BEEPING)
Climb!
Climb? Look out the window.
Climb. Full climb now!
What did you give him?
I'm pegged here!
I don't have the speed to make it!
And now you want me to climb?
(SCREAMING) Climb!
(VEL AND SKEEN GRUNT)
(WHIRRING, BEEPING)
(WHOOSHING)
(BEEPING)
Dive!
(WHOOSHING)
Vector six-five-five-five-one.
Full boost thrust on level!
Come on!
(GLASS BREAKING)
(YELLING)
(WHOOSHING)
(EXPLOSION)
(PILOT YELLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PILGRIMS GASP)
(CRYING)
(WHOOSHES)
(THUDS)
I need to know where we're going.
VEL: Is he still with us?
Yeah, you disappointed?
That's not fair.
CASSIAN: Where are we heading?
-She wants to bail on him.
-He's dying.
SKEEN: You don't know that.
There's a doctor.
We have it built into the contingency.
She doesn't want to
jeopardize the mission.
This kid, I mean,
this kid is the reason that we are here.
He's alive.
-(CLICKING, WHIRRING)
-How do we get to the doctor?
(SIGHS)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(DEVICES BEEPING, WHIRRING)
(DR. QUADPAW GRUNTING)
SKEEN: You think he'll make it?
CASSIAN: He could get lucky.
Yeah, luck.
(SCOFFS)
It drives the whole damn galaxy,
doesn't it?
(SIGHS)
You wanna guess how much is in there?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Eighty million, give or take.
What'd you tell me?
You wanna win and walk away.
Well...
forty million apiece.
Don't tell me you haven't
thought about it.
See, I can't fly the trawler,
but I do have a safe place we can hole up.
Between the two of us,
we could be the winners here.
So no rebellion for you?
Oh, I'm a rebel. It's just, uh...
me against everybody else.
(SIGHS) Where would that put me?
Forty million credits is enough
for me to forget all about you.
(SCOFFS)
Your brother, with the orchard?
I don't have a brother.
So just leave them here?
Don't play the high mind with me.
You're not here to save
anybody but yourself.
I saw it the first minute
you came into camp.
You're like me, we were born in the hole,
all we know is climbing
over somebody else to get out.
There's a moon eight parsecs
from here with nobody home.
Put that thing down,
catch our breath,
split up the winnings, and walk...
(SKEEN GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
VEL: Thank you. Thank you for trying.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
I did everything I could.
It's not you, Doc.
And it's not what you think, either.
Oh, surprise me.
I'll give you 30,000 credits
for the ship in the barn.
That's twice what it's worth.
Excuse me?
Where's Skeen?
Skeen! Skeen!
He's dead.
He wanted to take the money
and leave you here.
He wouldn't do that.
(SCOFFS)
You're gonna have to think about that.
You disgusting bastard.
Taramyn warned me.
I'm taking my cut.
The number I was promised.
I'm leaving you the freighter
and what's inside.
I did my job.
I'm done.
And I wouldn't stick around if I were you.
Return this to your friend.
Wait.
Nemik's manifesto.
He said to give this to you.
I don't want it.
He insisted.
(SIGHS)
MAJOR PARTAGAZ: Don't get comfortable.
This is not a meeting.
No one is going home.
Tell your staff, tell your families.
I want every Star Sector
and Planetary Emergency Retaliation plan
in the building ready
for presentation by midnight.
MON: Senator Dhow's proposal
is both temperate and timely,
far more reasoned and thoughtful
than the calls for decree
we've been hearing from the other side.
There will be a fact-finding commission
put in place this session,
and it will prove
that this is a boot to the throats
of all Ghormans,
who've done nothing more than
request their basic rights.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MON: My bill assails the coarse
and blatant domination
of a peaceful and faithful ally.
(DELEGATES CLAMOURING INTENSIFIES)
(BEEPING)
WOMAN: The blue is lovely.
KLEYA: It's a Devaron blue.
There's an inscription on that one.
In a language no one remembers.
How sad.
No, it's liberating.
You decide what it says.
Your own secret language.
MAN: Got anything from Aldhani?
Excuse me?
MAN: Aldhani.
Big rebel attack last night.
It's all the news.
I'll have to look.
Maybe we have something in the back.
MAN: Really? I was kidding.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES)