- Why are we waiting in line for food?
- It's a pop-up.
It's a rare, pop-up restaurant thing
that only enters our solar system.
Rick, you're gonna spoil your appetite.
That's a weird way to say
I'll stop being hungry by eating food
- but whatever. Three crispy, four wiggling.
- You're probably not even hungry.
You don't like lines
because they aren't about you.
Another weirdly aggressive way to describe
a friend respecting themselves.
- [groans]
- What a wonderful thing to say.
I was merely inspired
by the wonderful thing you said.
- Sirs? Guys? You dropped this.
- Please take it as a reward.
- So courteous.
- How nice it will be for you to eat
what you were willing to stand in line for
so much sooner.
Oh, no, that's okay.
I came to stand in line and then eat.
- I wouldn't wanna do it differently.
- [both] Hmm.
Dear fellow, I choose this moment
to surrender my sword
so that you may succeed me
as the newest Knight of the Sun.
What? No.
I didn't even want your sandwich.
I don't want your sword.
- Oh, believe me, son. You want it.
- I don't understand. You're knights?
- With a K? Of the Sun with a U or an O?
- Your alphabet is of no concern here.
We are sworn defenders of Helios,
the center of this system.
- Okay, so it's sun with a U--
- [Rick] Morty, don't take the sword.
Oh, I'm shocked
you're against something, Rick.
You know these guys?
I know how they're dressed
and how boring this sounds.
You take that sword, you're gonna get
sucked into a whole complicated-- Oh, shit!
- Come on, take it.
- Uh--
- If that kid's not gonna take the sword--
- He didn't offer it to you.
Can I just ask some stuff?
What does a Knight of the Sun do?
- He takes the sword, for one thing.
- Maybe you made a bad call.
- He doesn't want the sword.
- I didn't say that.
You sure aren't taking it.
- Would you just take a random--
- Obviously, yes. And I did.
Best decision of my life.
And you're shitting on it.
- Excuse me? Is this just a free sword?
- [both] No.
- I'm taking the sword.
- Thank you, Dawnling. What is your name?
- Morty.
- Now it is Sir Mortaniel.
I made it a little knightlier.
- Good day.
- Wait, did he just--
Goddamn it, Morty.
You took the sword? So boring.
Oh, like you're not at this point?
You drunk, cranky fuck.
Ouch.
You guys still gonna stand in line?
You're not gonna take this food?
The pop-up pays us to stand here.
To drive up business.
Knew it.
[theme music playing]
Everyone. Sir Helios' successor,
Sir Mortaniel.
♪ Sir Mortaniel, face so bright
Serves the sun with strength and might ♪
♪ Sir Mortaniel, come and see
Just what the sun provides for thee ♪
- Wow, my own song.
- Now you know why Sir Helios
had to change your name
to something with three syllables.
- Welcome, Dawnling, to the sun.
- So it is the sun, like Earth's sun?
- Aha! He's heard of us.
- How come I'm not burning to a crisp?
You are currently protected by our powers,
but soon they will be yours.
Our flesh is indestructible.
Our lives are never-ending,
but not even in the dumb vampire way
where after a while you hate it
and you can't die.
We can die whenever we want.
- We just don't have to.
- But you're not allowed to leave, right?
- Like I'll never see my family again?
- We leave constantly.
I met you on an asteroid.
Oh, yeah.
Between us, that wasn't a deal breaker
but it's better that there's options.
You'll have more freedom
than you've ever known.
Our king.
The sun is the center of the solar system.
It is the home of the solar scepter,
around which all worlds revolve.
The men who keep it safe
are admired by all and live as gods.
- Any more questions?
- Uh, yeah, where do I sign?
- Huzzah.
- Well, that does it.
- Off to the parapet to make this official.
- Yeah, let's do this.
Now just cut off your penises
and throw them into the sun.
- Okey-dokey.
- I see Mortaniel wants to go first.
Uh, not true.
Do I just leave the sword wherever?
ls there a sword bin?
What are you saying,
you don't want to cut off--
- Guys, can we not--
- It's a terrific and painful sacrifice
we all make for the most important
and powerful job in the universe.
- We've done it since the dawn of dawns.
- [Morty] Yep.
There it is in stained glass. It's official.
And I'm not judging it.
And I'm not doing it.
People really live here?
This is nuts, I thought it was a metaphor.
We have to go.
- Boy. They're not messing around, huh?
- How are you not burning?
Oh, it's just science,
which, unless I'm misinterpreting,
is clearly not a priority here.
Okay, common Lil Junebug,
I won't rub your face in this one.
- I'm guessing you're feeling pretty stupid.
- Yes. Thank you.
Sir Helios gave his life with that sword.
Mortaniel took it.
He cannot leave unless
he bests me in combat.
Hmm. Okay, one sec.
I'm guessing these guys are like
pseudo immortalish
so playing by their rules
might be the fastest way out.
- Just best him in combat. Here.
- What?
This sword uses Al to learn
from an opponent's attacks.
- I have to get attacked first?
- The sword has already seen Blade.
And loved it. You'll be fine.
- Okay, so we're done here.
- No. We're not done, I am done.
You are now king of the sun.
- Protect the Scepter always.
- No, no, I don't want to--
How is that supposed to work?
He's king but he was never even a knight?
- I mean, that's stupid.
- It's definitely a sun first.
- A king with a penis?
- What do you want from me?
[knights] All hail King Mortaniel.
Uh, as your king, I hereby,
declare a vacation, for me,
I'll come visit you guys on like Sundays.
Sundays. if I forget, just wait a week,
keep doing that, keep the crown, peace.
Hell yeah. See? That's from
when he's fighting Deacon Frost.
- I don't know. I thought it was cool.
- Okay. So...
So you dragged me to a fake restaurant,
yelled at me for not doing what you wanted
then did something I told you not to
and it almost cost you your pud
but I saved your life and you're waiting
for me to make you feel like shit.
- That's-- Yeah, you nailed it.
- Morty, I'm sorry
I let your opinion of me get this low.
- I get it.
- There's nothing to get, I'm for real.
I'm a drunk, I'm a psychopath, I'm a murderer,
but when you called me boring--
- I shouldn't have--
- I needed to hear it.
You took the stupid sword
and I was like, "Holy crap,
this is who I am to this kid?
He just does the opposite of my advice now?
I mean, I gotta fix that."
So I'm gonna be like 22%
more agreeable with you for like,
maybe one episode or one adventure.
- We'll see how it goes.
- ls 22% a lot?
I won't tell you what percentage
of our time together
I'm mean to you because it'll hurt
your stupid feelings but 22 is substantial.
- You're gonna feel the difference.
- Okay. I mean, I appreciate it.
You should because you made a real mess.
- Oh, man.
- Sire.
- You can't leave.
- Go away.
My king, it is our duty to follow you
till the sun sets on our watch.
I mean, it set yesterday,
so you're done. Bye.
Sire, the sun never sets on the sun.
- Can you get rid of them?
- You want me to...?
Well, you guys know
he can kill you, right?
I think he'd find that quite difficult, sire,
but if it pleases you.
Can't I just tell you it pleases me
for you to go away?
- No. Not really.
- So you'd rather die than leave me alone?
[knights] Yes.
♪ A pheasant plucked for my good king
A merry jig, sweet songbirds sing ♪
These guys live on our sun?
I've never heard of them.
I don't see them doing a lot
to earn interplanetary fame.
I beg your pardon, wizard,
the Knights of the Sun
protect the solar scepter,
around which even this world turns.
You do mean that,
like, symbolically, right?
Oh, quite literally. The scepter is
the center of the solar system.
All planets orbit it.
We keep it on the sun so that
Jupiter and Saturn don't bump
into each other.
- Oh, my God.
- They don't even know sixth-grade science.
That's it.
Yeah, so there you have it.
Traditions suck ass and your most
foundational beliefs are total bullshit.
We're supposed to take your word for it?
Anyone can draw circles on a board
and spout numbers.
Yes, this sounds like a fun theory, sire,
but it would take more than this
for us to give up.
How do you guys think it works?
- Well, the scepter--
- Oh, you mean this old thing?
[knights shouting]
You want it? Here. Take it back home.
It's a symbol. It's your culture.
That's not the same as reality.
Does this mean we cut off our penises
for absolutely no reason?
That's the bad news.
The good news is you're free.
- Oh, that stings.
- Fuck this knight shit.
A query? I just used your computer phone
to search "despair."
- Where can I get this heroin?
- I'm not telling you that.
No matter, I'm seeing from most of your
song lyrics that I can get it anywhere.
[clears throat]
Um, you guys,
someone just used critical thinking
and basic physics
to destroy their first entire religion.
- Good job, Morty.
- Nice.
- So no more sun-tour age?
- Yep. All done.
Plus, Rick and I both learned
to support each other better.
So that's it, we're done.
Feels early, but we're done.
What's happening? Appliances
are breaking that I haven't touched.
Maybe the sun is celebrating?
The Sons of the Moon
are storming the Walkway. Doesn't matter.
Their aggression will be kept in check by
a host of interplanetary treaties and alliances.
It's complicated, but as long as
The Knights of the Sun stand together,
the solar system will always have
complete political stability.
Where are the Knights of the Sun,
by the way? I'm done pooping.
Hmm? Did the Knights of the Sun disband?
While I was pooping?
Sun-kward...
How many planets in our solar system
have these clowns?
I guess if the sun can support life,
any planet can.
Maybe we all descended
from a common ancestor?
Haven't you seen
all of the universes?
Exactly, so why would I hang out on Pluto?
That's some Jerry-league shit.
If the Sons of the Moon
can attack the sun,
why should the Viscounts of Venus
continue sitting in Saturn's shadow?
How's this for a reason?
We got all the rings and all the balls.
- Oh, fuck you.
- Really?
If the Saturno-Venusian detente
is no longer honored,
I declare you all moons of Jupiter.
Because that's what you are to us.
A bunch of moons!
Do the Knights of the Sun plan
to protect Mercury from this chaos?
Because if we're on our own,
there's a new, very tiny sun in town.
- It's all you, pal.
- Um, hello?
Don't I have, like, authority
over this Sons of the Moon meeting?
That all depends. Who the hell are you?
This guy's the king of the sun.
- King of the sun.
- When did this happen?
Then tell your knights to do their jobs.
Yes, Your Majesty.
We all know the sun's power
lives and dies with your knights.
- Who are you?
- Who--? I am the Marquis of Mars.
And I declare war on all of you.
War on all of you!
Where are the Knights of the Sun
when we need them most?
- Funny you should ask--
- They're gone.
- [all gasping]
- They've abandoned their duties.
- I see it in the bones.
- Damn, the bones nailed it.
Okay, so you have spaceships
and magic ladies?
I'm not gonna read all the books.
What will it take to let this Sons of the Moon
fiasco resolve itself?
Excuse me.
How did you become king of the sun?
- You look like an Earthling.
- Santa?
Santa? What the hell is that?
I'm the Earl of Earth, goddamn it.
I agree with Earth on one thing:
Venus questions the legitimacy
of this king's authority.
[indistinct chatter]
I'm the king.
I've got the scepter right here.
- What the fuck?
- Yeah, I know you're freaking out
- because it's not on the sun.
- No, because whoever has it
- rules the solar system.
- It's up for grabs, get it.
After it.
Yes. I have the scepter.
Soon Jupiter will be
the center of our solar system's
- newest dark--
- Fuck that.
- Mercury will now be the shining beacon of--
- Time to throw it all against the wall.
I think you crushed it.
I mean, not just anybody
can start Solar War I.
- Stop supporting me.
- Can do.
["Goodbye Blue Sky" playing]
♪ Goodbye, blue sky ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Did you see the frightened ones? ♪
♪ Did you hear the falling bombs? ♪
♪ Did you ever wonder
Why we had to run for shelter ♪
♪ When the promise of a brave new world
Unfurled beneath a clear blue sky? ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Did you see the frightened ones? ♪
♪ Did you hear the falling bombs? ♪
♪The flames are all long gone
But the pain lingers on ♪
♪ Goodbye, blue sky ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
Who would've thought giving the Amish nukes
would threaten the solar system?
- Maybe we should just jump universes.
- I don't know,
feels like we're kind of more about
trying out commitment now, you know?
Maybe there's something we haven't tried.
- Oh, here's an idea: fuck you.
- Hey!
Rick, I can't take it. I admit I'm wrong,
I screwed up, you're killing me here
"yes, and-ing" me to death.
What is this, Vat of Acid again?
I'm sorry I've been such a dick in the past
that you think I'm doing a thing here.
I'm honestly just trying to do better by you.
- Are you a robot? A clone?
- Morty.
This family's got enough
clones and robots in it.
Stop asking what you're asking
and let's just get back to our crisis.
I'm sorry, it's just been
a hard road with you, Rick.
I get that, but you can trust me
when I say I'm trying to do right by you.
Okay, Rick. You're right.
Maybe I just need
to round up some knights?
If I disillusioned the old ones,
I'll just have to re-illusion them.
It shouldn't be that hard, right?
Cousins, we need to return
to the Walkway at once.
Why are you laughing?
Did I say something funny?
Oh, Mortaniel.
The only person we bend the knee
to these days is that sweet Black Betty.
- Yeah, man, all hail Mr. Brownstone.
- And his doctor.
Feelgood, that is.
They're talking about heroin, Morty,
they like it.
- Obviously.
- Obviously?
Apparently living on the sun has turned
our veins into triple-bonded carbon,
so try this tale on for size, Mortaniel:
We can't OD.
Come on, you guys are a mess.
They actually seem awesome.
Let me be your king.
I admit I wanted what you once had:
brotherhood, tradition,
stability, purpose.
I just didn't want to cut
my dick off for it.
Yeah, that's the point.
We were quick to follow this boy before,
without even forcing him
to commit to our traditions.
And all he did was break our faith
and our Walkway.
And now this random fucking guy is here
again to tell us what to do?
No fucking way.
What if I cut off my dick?
But you'd be cutting it off for no reason.
Yeah, that's the point of tradition,
doing things for no reason,
but it'd be reason enough
doing it for you guys.
Well, you do that,
that would compete with heroin.
Cool, cool, can I maybe get a minute?
- [sobbing]
- Buddy, what's up?
Reaching some sad conclusions
about your situation?
Yes, but that Walkway
needs those knights,
those knights need a king
and that king needs no dick.
Damn, Morty, you really are stepping up.
Now do you want me to help you
not have to cut your dick off?
- Yes, please.
- Then I got you.
- You really mean it, Rick?
- Of course, buddy.
I'll give you a fake dick.
With three layers of failsafes.
They'll never know the difference.
Shh. Morty, we're gonna make your dick
so fake, buddy.
The signal.
Sir, the Knights of the Sun are once more.
Hold fire.
If this return to the Old Ways is true,
I'd be willing to return home
and put an end to the bloodshed.
[all cheering]
[inaudible dialogue]
Sir? Shall we hold off on the anti-matter
hydrogen bombing?
Those crusty knights won't do
the sun much good without their--
Let's hear them out.
[crowd cheering]
I, Lithdor, son of Thrifdor,
personally oversee
the stumping of thy king's stem.
If his stem burns true, peace will be
restored between the spheres.
[crowd cheering]
Present the shears of stumping.
- Morty the brave.
- You got this, my king.
First thing's first,
step through this machine
which checks for nanotech no logical
hologram dicks.
- What?
- War opened our eyes
to the wonders of new technologies.
Please, step through, my liege.
- Ooh.
- Sorry, my lord,
but we're gonna need you to step through
this second machine
which checks for emergency clone dicks.
Oh wow, you guys really embraced
a lot of specific new tech?
- Whoa, a sunspot.
- What? Where?
Boy, is that a third detector
I see as well?
You'll find out after the second one.
We don't like to reveal them
until the previous detecting threshold
- has been crossed.
- Right.
The third detector is going to scan
for a prosthetic dick.
- Oh, good.
- Okay, well, go on through.
And of course, by "prosthetic,"
we mean witchcraft dick.
- Shit.
- I sense one.
The bones say he's still packing.
[all gasping]
Can't get nothing
past the chicken bone lady.
- Just testing her.
- Stump. Thy. Stem.
[Rick] Morty? Morty, don't answer out loud,
can you hear me?
I'm talking to you with my mind.
- I can hear you.
- You said that out loud.
- Don't speak.
- Sorry--
- Sorry.
- [Rick] I uplinked a telepathic nanosatellite
so we could hear each other's thoughts.
Carefully do everything I tell you
in the exact order I tell you to do it.
- [Morty] Okay.
- [Rick] Grab the scissors.
- [Morty] Okay. Got the scissors.
- [crowd cheering]
- [Rick] Now run.
- [Morty] Oh, shit.
Guards, seize them!
[Morty]
Run? You couldn't have just said that?
You don't have to use telepathy,
you can ask
your rhetorical questions out loud.
I don't understand.
Here's something that's easy
to understand.
I'm proud of you
for trying to solve your own shit.
- I didn't wanna have to do this.
It's okay this time.
We don't have any choice.
- I love you, Rick.
- Love you too, buddy.
[both screaming]
[Fairenheat] And that's when King Morty
and Rick were left with no choice
but to leap into the sun.
Such shame he felt
for what he'd done to our society,
sacrificing his dick wasn't enough,
he gave his entire body
and wizard servant as well.
And after a while,
their sun-proof bones floated up to the top.
We even checked with a royal ladle
to ensure it was real sun,
not just them hiding beneath
in a vat of fake sun.
Such a violent death.
And finally,
when our grief could bear no more,
we decided to abolish
our medieval act of stem stumping.
And we have King Morty the Molten
to thank for that.
[both]
Morty the Molten. King Morty the Molten.
See, Morty? Worked like a charm.
Aren't we risking it all coming back here?
Morty, we had to know,
plus the heat, it's good for my joints.
- King Mortaniel? You're alive?
- Yeah, go tell everybody.
Your reward's gonna be cutting off
your own dick.
Right. Point taken. RIP and cheerio.
Ooh.
[theme music playing]
- One crispy, one wriggling.
- Coming right up. Three loozums.
How about ten years? In jail.
Special Agent Mongo Bongo,
you're under arrest
for illegal hot dog trafficking.
[all groaning]
Be free, my little babies.
Ah.
Surprised they actually made it.
Kind of thought maybe
some birds would swoop down or--
[screaming]
I jinxed it!