Wouldn't you rather give it all at once
to something real?
What would we be stealing?
The quarterly payroll
for an entire Imperial sector.
DEDRA: If I was them,
this is how I'd do it.
I'd spread it out.
Never climb the same fence twice.
-(WHIMPERS)
-TIMM: Bix!
Who did this? (GRUNTS)
Timm!
NEMIK: So you think it's hopeless, do you?
Freedom? Independence?
We should just submit and be thankful?
Do I look thankful to you?
-LIEUTENANT GORN: Corporal.
-At your service.
Fall in.
Turn.
With me.
Tell me you'll be all right.
I'll be fine.
Go.
(EXPLOSION)
Let's go!
What is going on here?
(BLASTERS FIRING)
-I'm pinned down!
-(GROWLS)
-(GROANING)
-No!
Hang on!
(WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTS)
EEDY: My assumption is,
you have no prospect for the future.
I'm calling Uncle Harlo.
I'm calling in the family favor.
You wanna guess how much is in there?
Forty million a piece, give or take.
-So no rebellion for you?
-Oh, I'm a rebel. It's just, uh...
me against everybody else.
(SKEEN GRUNTS)
He wanted to take the money
and leave you here.
-He wouldn't do that.
-I'm taking my cut.
I did my job.
I found someone I think can help me.
We're vulnerable enough.
We need funding, not more people.
Don't lecture me on vulnerability.
No one's more at risk than I am.
EEDY: Syril?
Syril!
(SIGHS)
Is that what you're wearing?
SYRIL: It would seem so.
What makes you believe
the Bureau of Standards
is in the market for individuals?
It's a brown suit.
It's your interview.
Perhaps, you would like to come along.
(NEWSCAST PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
Uncle Harlo's influence
is not a thing to be trifled with.
How am I trifling?
He's done us a tremendous favor.
You need to remember you're not just
representing yourself today.
It's a brown suit. (CLEARS THROAT)
The collar.
-What about it?
-It's high.
You've had it raised.
I had it tailored.
Everything says something, Syril.
I've tried to make you understand that,
you've resisted.
(CLICKS TONGUE) What is it
that you hear my collar saying?
"Look at me.
"I don't believe in myself.
"I am desperate for approval."
MAN: (ON NEWSCAST) We have
distressing reports are reaching us
that a terror attack and robbery
have taken place
at the Imperial Armory on Aldhani,
with multiple fatalities reported.
What happened?
-EEDY: Rabble.
-...a Blockade Order was issued...
EEDY: They attacked a garrison.
They'll regret it.
MAN: ...officials on the scene
are still assessing the loss
and searching for the conspirators.
YULAREN: The criminals responsible
for last night's atrocity on Aldhani
think they've taken
the Empire by surprise.
We know better.
We know the real shock will be
when they discover how ready
and eager we are to respond,
to be prepared, to be here this morning
and know that the only question
we need to answer
is how tight to close our fist.
This is why we plan.
This is why we work so hard
when we're at peace.
This is why we recruit so carefully
and demand so much.
The following measures
will be adopted Empire-wide as of today.
A tribute tax equal to five times
the amount stolen from Aldhani
will be levied on any sector
harboring partisan activity.
We will make it clear
that no one steals from the Empire.
The use of any local custom, festival,
or tradition as cover for rebel activity
will trigger permanent revocation
of Imperial tolerance.
I spoke with Emperor Palpatine last night,
and he's assured me that the ISB
will be taking the lead going forward.
No one in this room
should have trouble accessing
Army or Naval resources in future.
The Emperor will be convening
an emergency session of the Senate
to propose a legislation package
of bills and amendments
that will free our hands in all matters
of surveillance, search, and seizure.
We will be invoking the Public Order
Resentencing Directive later today.
P-O-R-D.
Any criminal act,
with even indirect effect on the Empire,
will henceforth be branded
a Class One Offense.
All prison sentences
are immediately re-evaluated.
All outstanding fines and levies
are to be paid in full.
-I have assured the Emperor...
-HEERT: You're not pleased.
DEDRA: We're playing
straight into their hands.
-HEERT: Whose hands?
-The rebels.
This is exactly what they want.
We're treating what happened
at Aldhani like a robbery.
HEERT: What would you call it?
An announcement.
MAN: (ON RADIO)
Preliminary investigation puts the loss
at over eighty million credits.
All military personnel
at the garrison have been replaced
and are being interrogated by ISB.
ISB confirms the tracking devices
in the escape craft were disabled
prior to it reaching hyperspace.
134 Aldhani residents
have been taken into custody
under suspicion
of abetting the terrorists.
(STATIC, BEEPING)
Mon Mothma.
Without warning?
Wipe the smile off your face. (CHUCKLES)
(WHIRRING)
(DOOR HISSES)
(SIGHS) I should've called.
We're on our way to the Senate,
I realized we'd be passing by.
-I'll be right back.
-KLORIS: Ma'am.
Perrin likes it,
I'm just not sure he loves it.
-Ah.
-I think I might want the other one.
(MON SIGHS)
Was this you?
LUTHEN: What do you mean?
(SOFTLY) The garrison. Aldhani.
Ah! Is it true?
Kleya was just... (MUFFLED)
MON: (MUFFLED)
I've been worried
you might do something like this.
(LAUGHS)
How I wish I had.
Let's have a look.
I don't believe you.
-Well, you'll have to try harder.
-Don't you dare talk to me like that.
Revolutions are expensive.
I told you, I'm doing everything I can.
(CHUCKLES) Your "everything"
seemed to be all about
bringing in a savior
to access your family funds.
(SOFTLY) It was you, wasn't it?
I explained to you the risk of new faces,
but you seemed to know better.
(SHUDDERS) You realize what you've done?
I thought you were here
to tell me about the meeting.
It's tonight.
They may reschedule.
I warned you when we started.
-You told me we were building a network.
-What were my words?
This is something else entirely.
LUTHEN: "Turning back will be impossible."
You knew where this was going.
You've always known.
(LAUGHS)
Has anyone ever made a weapon
that wasn't used?
The network's been built. It's up.
It grows or it dies.
(ON COMMS) We've waited long enough.
You realize what you've set in motion?
LUTHEN: It was time for that as well.
-Palpatine won't hesitate now.
-Exactly!
We need it.
We need the fear.
-We need them to overreact.
-You can't be serious.
The Empire has been choking us
so slowly, we're starting not to notice.
The time has come to force their hand.
People will suffer.
That's the plan.
You're not angry at me.
I'm just saying out loud
what you already know.
There will be no rules going forward.
If you're not willing
to risk your conscience,
then surrender and be done with it.
(SIGHS)
We need every credit
we can get our hands on.
Let me know how the meeting goes.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
I'm afraid I won't be taking
either of these pieces this morning.
(LAUGHS) I'll have some new things
coming in very, very soon.
MON: I'll be sure to come by.
LUTHEN: (LAUGHS)
Always at your service, Senator.
Always at your service.
I hope she's worth it.
LUTHEN: Well, we'll see, won't we?
We can't hide forever.
(LIMO WHIRRING)
People all think we're kidding
when we say it, but it's true.
There are no small jobs
at the Bureau Of Standards.
(INHALES DEEPLY) I spoke with your uncle.
Some sectors might naturally appear
more exciting from the outside.
Weights and Gauges
may seem a more vibrant arena
than Redundancy or Verification,
but walk the floor,
talk to any lifetime employee,
you'll be surprised.
I'm sure.
Morlana One.
SYRIL: Yes, uh... (BREATHING HEAVILY)
There's a rebel murderer running free
because of corruption and laxity
in the corporate authority.
I was punished
for trying to uphold the law.
Do my job. Maintain public safety.
Two men dead.
Co-workers.
I believe that we have laws for a reason.
I fully intend to clear my name
and have my record expunged.
Why don't we start that process now?
Probably best for everyone to just edit
this a bit before signing you in.
-I'm sure your uncle would approve.
-(BEEPING)
Fresh start, eh?
New beginnings.
We just happen to have
an immediate opening in Fuel Purity.
I'd hate to see you miss your chance.
(BEEPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON PA)
MAN: (ON PA)
Exit right for the Senate level.
(LIVELY CHATTER)
Exit left for the downtown, midtown level.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
STORMTROOPER: Four-nine vector six.
L-U-H-three-four-one.
Security clearance code...
-MAN: The food is superb.
-WOMAN: It's quite exquisite...
(DOOR HISSES)
-DEDRA: At ease, Attendant.
-(GASPS) Yes, sir.
Ma'am. Sir.
Your tunic.
Sorry, sir. Ma'am.
Sorry.
What is your name?
Felzonis.
Attendant Felzonis.
Hmm. I need a Multi-Sector Data Blend
going back two years.
The survey pool is Imperial Naval bases
and repair facilities.
I want a record of all missing avionics,
comm, navigation, and targeting equipment.
For which star system?
All star systems.
Is that a problem?
I'll need this report kept confidential
and a copy sent exclusively to my office.
Can I rely on you
for that level of discretion?
Absolutely.
Yes. Can do.
Will do.
Right. Get on with it.
(CINTA PANTING, GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(PANTING)
Where is he?
I shouldn't even be here.
Neither of us should.
The money's safe.
We know.
It's been moved already.
You've done exceptional work.
It's the trawler
that we're more worried about.
It's buried. Gone for good.
-You're sure?
-Yes.
He read your message.
(SCOFFS)
I really thought he'd be here.
Every loss is different.
Every one's the same.
I recruited Taramyn myself.
Nemik, Gorn, they'll all be remembered.
That's it?
He had doubts about Skeen.
It's one less thing to worry about.
Have you heard from Cinta?
She's doing what she was told.
Receiving messages
is just as dangerous as sending them.
You should keep that in mind.
We have a loose end.
Cassian Andor, who you know as Clem.
You need to find him.
Find him?
We can't have him walking around
with Luthen in his head.
You mean kill him.
This is what revolution looks like, Vel.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
We'll send you what we have on him.
(WHOOSHING)
(WHIRRING)
-(BLASTER WHIRS)
-MAARVA: (SOFTLY) Who's there?
-I hear you!
-(WHIRRING)
(RATTLES)
MAARVA: Just, just hold on!
(MAARVA PANTING)
-B2EMO: Cassian.
-Oh! Get in here. (BREATHES HEAVILY)
-Since when do we lock the door?
-Oh!
B2EMO: Where have you been?
Look at you. (SIGHS)
(KETTLE BEEPS)
You can't stay here, Cass. It's not safe.
B2EMO: There is t-t-troopers now.
-CASSIAN: That was fast.
-Yeah, they came the next day.
Kicked out Pre-Mor, took over the hotel.
Ferrix is under Imperial authority.
(GROANS)
You shouldn't be here. (SIGHS)
Someone turned me in.
You don't know?
Know what?
-B2EMO: T-T-Timm.
-What?
Timm Karlo turned you in.
No point in stewing over it,
he's dead now.
The Corpos killed him
when they were coming after you.
How do you know all this?
Everyone knows it.
-Bix knew about it?
-No.
She was coming to warn you,
and Timm was trying to stop her,
or to catch her, I don't know.
I've... I've heard both.
But you can't be here, Cass.
The Imperials are here to stay.
They're not going away this time.
It's all come undone.
We won't have to worry about that.
What are you talking about?
We're getting out of here.
We're leaving.
To go where?
Anywhere we want.
(CHUCKLES) I got lucky.
I scored.
I've got enough credits
to get us anywhere.
We're gonna clear out.
Leave this mess behind.
B2EMO: When d-d-do we go?
-We go tonight.
-Tonight?
Yeah, why not?
What do we need to take
but the three of us?
-(WHIRRING)
-Huh? Get out of the cold and damp.
Find somewhere warm and easy.
I can make it happen.
It's all gonna be different now, Ma.
(KETTLE HISSING)
(GRUNTS)
(CASSIAN SIGHS)
-(KETTLE BEEPS)
-(GRUNTS)
CASSIAN: What's wrong?
MAARVA: Just such a lot to take in.
No one knows I'm here.
We take what we can carry,
and we disappear.
It's just such a big idea,
you know, I... I get so tired.
You surprised me. (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES) What am I thinking?
It's... It's late.
Yeah, yeah. You... You gotta rest.
I'll check up on Bix, and we'll pull out
first thing in the morning.
-All right?
-B2EMO: F-F-First thing.
-Let's do that.
-Ah.
(LIVELY CHATTER)
Thank you.
Sorry we're not having dinner.
How long are you staying?
I'm back to Chandrila tomorrow.
I haven't been home all year.
You haven't missed much.
I've missed you.
You always seem to be away when I'm there.
I'm not that hard to find, Mon.
Not for a Senator.
You're right.
-I've been a poor friend.
-No, that's not what I meant.
Life takes us where it will.
You've become all this. All these years.
We're both a long way
from where we started.
MON: Have I changed so much?
-We've all had to adapt.
-Is it that bad?
(SMACKS LIPS)
I just can't imagine living here, Mon.
Like this.
Coruscant.
No escape.
Just this glimpse of what it's like here,
what you have to do.
It can be challenging.
You carry it gracefully.
Can I trust you, Tay?
Can I call back our old kinship
and share some truth with you?
LEIDA: Mother.
Leida.
-Do you remember my daughter?
-Of course.
This is Tay Kolma,
one of my oldest friends.
How do you do?
You've met before.
Bank Of Kolma?
You know Adrine and Marsa from back home.
-My sisters.
-Um, I'm not sure.
It's been a long time,
and you've certainly grown up.
-(MON CHUCKLES)
-So everyone says.
Typical banker.
No one pays me to be original.
Oh. Father said I needed to ask you
if I may be excused.
Yes.
You're excused.
-TAY: Lovely seeing you again.
-LEIDA: Uh, yes. Have fun, Mother.
Another part of the challenge.
It's a difficult age.
I've spent a great deal of time
thinking about this conversation, Tay.
I want to tell you something
that only three people
in the galaxy know about.
Why would you want to do that?
Because I need your help.
And I'm hoping I can trust you.
Is this personal or political?
Political.
-Then I'd suggest you hesitate.
-Why?
TAY: Like I said, we've both changed.
I've done more
than grow weary of the Empire.
I'm afraid you'd find my politics
a bit strong for your taste.
Your world is inescapably
linked to the Empire.
You're with these people all the time.
(CLICKS TONGUE) I'm not sure
you're aware how far afield
some of us have taken
our political allegiances these days.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Sorry, I think I've had too much
of Perrin's Embassy punch.
(CHUCKLING) Drink up.
Drink up, Tay, and keep smiling
(CHUCKLES) as if we're having
a happy chat about childhood days.
I'm not sure I understand.
No, you don't.
What you see, what people say about me,
it's a clear picture, isn't it?
I'm a polite, sometimes-indecisive Senator
who spends her days fighting and failing
to protect Separatist do-gooders
and battle Empire overreach.
An irritation, as you so harshly put it.
-I've made you angry, I...
-No, no. You've set me free.
I've been wondering all day
how I could be sure of confiding in you.
I don't know what we're talking about.
It's a lie.
The Mon Mothma
people think they know, it's a lie.
It's a projection.
It's a front.
Smile. (CHUCKLES)
I've learned from Palpatine.
I show you the stone in my hand,
you miss the knife at your throat.
Where is this going, Mon?
The Grand Vizier has infiltrated
my Separatist Coalition meetings.
My driver is an ISB plant and reports
on my secret humanitarian programs.
They know they watch me, and I want that,
because as long as everyone
thinks I'm an irritation,
there's a good chance
they'll miss what I'm really doing.
What are you really doing?
Raising money.
I need to access my family accounts.
Until recently,
I was able to dip in and out of
my family fortune without concern.
(INHALES) That's changed.
I need help.
Raising money for what?
I'm forming a Chandrilan
charitable outreach program.
I'll ask you to be chairman.
It will involve visits here to Coruscant.
It will appear to be another
of my benevolent and useless irritations.
(WHISPERING)
I've explored the alternatives.
You're my best shot.
You haven't answered my question.
And I won't.
You're better off not knowing.
Or perhaps, you'd find my politics
a bit strong for your taste.
Perrin's on his way over.
He knows none of this.
He's not to be trusted.
Smile.
There you are.
Reminiscing, are we? School days?
-Are we that predictable?
-(CHUCKLES)
-There's a reunion coming up.
-Oh, don't remind me. (CHUCKLES)
She pretends not to care,
but we both know better, don't we?
It was ever thus.
May I steal her back? There's a few guests
that require special handling.
Of course.
To be continued.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(PANTING)
(KNOCKS)
(RADIO STATIC)
Hey.
BIX: (ON COMMS) Cass?
What are you doing here?
Remember when your father caught me
climbing over that wall?
This is the last place you should be.
(CASSIAN CHUCKLES, SNIFFS)
I think those
were his exact words. (CHUCKLES)
It's not safe here.
Timm?
I guess he thought
you and I were back together.
Why would he think that?
You can't be as surprised as I was.
(DOOR OPENS)
What happened to you?
I ran into a wall, like I do.
You can't be here, Cass.
Troopers won't catch me.
Not here.
They won't have to.
You'll be turned in.
-By who?
By anyone.
People blame you for what happened.
Blame me?
You killed two Corpos
and came home to hide.
Put the entire town at risk.
-Now there's Imperials on the street.
-If Timm had kept his mouth shut.
If this, if that. If you, if me, if Timm.
We were doing a deal you...
You scam, you borrow,
you lie, you disappear.
Your crazy boyfriend tries
to get me killed, and I'm the villain?
You need to get as far away
from here as you can.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SCOFFS) Wow.
I will.
I am.
You won't have to worry about me anymore.
(SCOFFS, SIGHS)
I need to know about the other guy.
The buyer, who is he?
-I don't know.
-You're lying.
I'm not.
Paak introduced us,
but swears he doesn't know either.
I have a comm. I call. I wait.
Sometimes they respond.
He knew all about me. How?
I... I don't know.
And you're right, he did know.
He knew that the Corpos were on you.
But not from me.
(INHALES) You ever talk to him again,
tell him I held up my end of the deal,
and he needs to forget about me.
And that goes for everybody. (SIGHS)
I've done it before.
12,000 credits.
That's everything I owe. (SIGHS)
Xan, Nurchi, Brasso, Deema.
Twelve should cover it.
Be careful, Cass.
You too.
(METAL LADDER RATTLES)
(STORMTROOPER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(MARCHING)
-CLEM: This is not our fight, Cass.
-(FRANTIC CHATTER)
(SIGHS) Don't worry.
They won't be here long.
They're just gonna raise
their silly flag and fly away.
MAN: Long live the Republic!
-MAN 2: Free Ferrix!
-(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Don't move. Stay here.
Hey, guys! Calm down!
-You're only making things worse!
-OFFICER: Halt!
(SHOUTING STOPS)
OFFICER: Turn!
(PEOPLE GASP, WHISPER)
Ready arms!
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHING)
-(DOOR HISSES)
-(WHIRRING)
B2EMO: M-M-Maarva.
He's b-b-back.
I was coming to find you.
CASSIAN: Here I am.
You haven't done much packing.
B2EMO: She says we can't go.
MAARVA: Bee. Quiet.
CASSIAN: What is this?
I'm not going.
What are you talking about?
MAARVA: I'm staying.
CASSIAN: But it's... it's not safe.
I know all that.
CASSIAN: I can't be here.
You said it yourself,
"It's all come undone."
There's an Imperial barracks on Rix Road.
Good luck to them.
-You wanna live under that?
-It's happening everywhere.
(SIGHS) Well, we'll find a place
they haven't ruined yet.
I'm already there.
That place is in my head.
They can build as many barracks
as they like, they'll never find me.
(SIGHS) What's left to keep you here?
The Rebellion. (SIGHS)
What?
Ferrix has been hiding long enough.
So now you're taking on the Empire?
(SIGHS) Laugh if you want to.
Who's laughing? This is madness.
No, it's not.
It's overdue, and probably doomed,
and I'm too old, and I don't care anymore.
For 13 years,
every time I walk down Rix Road,
I turn off before I get to the square.
I take the long way around
so I don't have to think
about Clem hanging there.
(ICE CRACKS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(ROPE CREAKING)
-(WIND WHOOSHING)
Then yesterday,
I heard about this attack at Aldhani.
Have you heard about this?
What about it?
Well, Bee played me the news.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
CASSIAN: Yeah, yeah,
the garrison at Aldhani.
I heard that, I put on my best coat,
and I walked across the square
-with a smile on my face.
-(SIGHS)
If there are heroes brave enough
to take on a whole Imperial garrison,
I'm brave enough to stick it out here.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
I... I don't expect you to understand.
Aldhani was just a robbery.
People are standing up.
Yeah, and getting killed for it.
But there's work that will need doing.
Yeah? (STAMMERS) What is that?
Whatever it takes.
I've been lying around
waiting to die long enough.
(CHIRPS SADLY)
You can't beat them, Maarva.
Not if I run away.
(WHIRRING)
You have a different path, Cass,
and I am not judging you.
Everything you've been through,
everything that was taken away from you
before you even started?
(SCOFFS)
Take all the money you've found
and go and find some peace.
I won't have peace.
I'll be worried about you all the time.
That's just love.
Nothing you can do about that.
I've never loved anything
the way I love you,
and I've never fretted on anything more,
but this time...
(GULPS, SIGHS)
you can't stay, and I can't go.
(SIGHS)
-B2EMO: C-C-Can I speak now?
-No!
(CHIRPS SADLY)
Tell me you understand.
I don't.
You will. (STAMMERS) You'll see.
(SIGHS)
And just one more thing... Just... (SIGHS)
Stop searching for your sister.
It's a fantasy.
There were no survivors on Kenari.
What happened there
was not your responsibility.
You were a child.
-Let it go.
-(SIGHS)
I'm coming back. (BREATHES DEEPLY)
MAARVA: Of course you are.
(DOOR HISSES)
JUNG: The alternative analysis is that
by comparing the detention numbers
to the frequency of surprise inspections
we're under-allocating
our harbor patrol units.
So, three theories, Mr. Jung?
Yes, sir.
Three possible explanations
for why you have failed to keep pace
with your neighboring sectors.
-That's correct.
-I'm correct?
Your approval is heartening.
Your guidance would be welcome, sir.
Very well, let's have a full audit
of all hyperspace lanes
leading to Ord Mantell
on my desk by this time tomorrow.
As you wish.
-PARTAGAZ: Mr. Blevin.
-Sir.
I sense something eager
in you this morning.
Am I mistaken?
(SIGHS) No, sir. And at risk
of repetition, you are correct.
Good news, is it?
I'm afraid not.
I wish to lodge a charge
against a fellow supervisor.
Proceed.
I believe our Sector Protocols,
as described in the ISB Code Of Conduct,
are being violated by Supervisor Meero,
and that this overreach,
for which she was previously reprimanded,
risks compromising Imperial safety
to a degree that silence
is no longer possible.
You think this forum appropriate?
I do.
It's a serious charge.
BLEVIN: I believe
you'll share my sense of urgency.
Supervisor Meero,
do you mind having your integrity
ventilated in public?
No, sir.
Supervisor Blevin obviously finds
my conduct a more interesting subject
than the advancement
of Integrated Imperial Security.
He's put a lot into it,
I'm curious to hear his insights.
PARTAGAZ: This is Ferrix, is it not?
Yes, sir.
Your sector.
There was an unusual piece
of Naval equipment recovered.
Meero wanted your crime reports.
You determined her request
was out of order
-and in violation of the chain of command.
-DEDRA: That's not accurate.
You advised me
to reinforce my suspicions with data
and to be careful
in my work going forward.
Careful?
Is that your defense?
You've been "careful"?
I'd be curious
how many people at this table
will think it "careful" that you've found
a way to access our sector data
without ever filing a request.
PARTAGAZ: Is that true, Dedra?
(INHALES) Yes.
I used the Imperial Emergency Act
in the wake of Aldhani
to gather data across multiple sectors
without official sanction.
But that is the wrong question.
I'd like to know if anyone here believes
the Rebellion plans its actions
around the artificially constructed
boundaries of our sectors.
Major Partagaz created those sectors.
As organizing principles,
not personal playthings.
Do you think the rebels care
about the lines we draw on maps?
You think the relevance of my work
has been supplanted?
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Systems either change or die.
Sir.
Thesis, please.
DEDRA: There is a focused,
organized rebel effort
to acquire highly-restricted
Imperial military components.
Your evidence?
By accessing unfiltered
Sector Crime Reports
I can now prove a link between the theft
of our most secret equipment
and its distribution
to rebel groups across the galaxy.
This is hard, verifiable data
you are prepared to present?
Yes, sir.
I believe Supervisor Blevin is aware
I have a documented file ready to go.
I believe his accusations
here this morning
have more to do with self-preservation
than any sense of urgency.
What's more urgent
than a renegade intelligence officer?
Imagine if everyone in this room played
as loose with the rules as you.
Excellent suggestion, Blevin.
I'm wondering where we'd be right now
if everyone here
showed the same endeavor
as Supervisor Meero.
I'll have to think about that.
For the moment, I'm reassigning
the Morlana sector to Supervisor Meero.
Ferrix is of great interest to her
and has clearly
become a distraction for you.
(INHALES) I see no urgent problem,
but, as always,
I salute the provocative
exchange of ideas.
Supervisor Grandi,
you will accelerate your schedule.
Jung, I will expect your report
on Ord Mantell tomorrow.
Thank you all for the lively session.
Dedra, if you'd walk with me a moment.
PARTAGAZ: Well-played.
Thank you, sir.
Watch your back.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
-(SHOWER RUNNING)
-(SIGHING)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
Keef.
Keef?
(BEEPS)
I'll be out in a minute.
What're you doing?
Washing up.
I'm gonna take a walk.
WINDI: Well, we need stuff.
Arkie's up the beach.
He'll be open.
CASSIAN:
I was planning to go the other way.
Mmm, Arkie has the new flavors.
And we need Peezos.
Don't forget the Peezos.
We ran out of Peezos?
Peezos and Revnog.
-The greenie green ones.
-(SIGHS)
WINDI: The greenie Revnog.
You liked it, too.
Keef? Are you listening?
-(UPBEAT DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
-Ah. (SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(LAUGHS)
MAN: Go! Go! Run!
Go, go, go, go!
(CHATTER IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
-SHORETROOPER: Hey, you! Stop!
-(PANTING)
SHORETROOPER: Hold it!
SHORETROOPER: Freeze!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(WHIRRING)
SHORETROOPER: What are you doing?
-Excuse me?
-SHORETROOPER: You keep looking around.
Just trying to figure out what's going on.
SHORETROOPER: You a part of it?
Part of what?
SHORETROOPER: Don't play dumb.
No, I'm on my way to the store.
SHORETROOPER: Back up.
Stand right there.
You look like you're sweating.
-Well, it's hot.
-SHORETROOPER: Or you've been running.
Why would I be running?
SHORETROOPER:
Because you're a part of it.
Part of what?
-SHORETROOPER: I'll ask the questions.
-MAN: Go! Run!
Pier Nine, Pier Nine,
runners heading south!
MAN: Move it! Go!
I can wait for you here, if you want.
SHORETROOPER: Friends of yours?
-What?
-SHORETROOPER: You heard me.
CASSIAN: Wait, no... Uh...
(CHUCKLES) I don't know anybody here.
I'm a tourist.
SHORETROOPER: Tourists don't run.
But I'm not running.
SHORETROOPER: You got that right.
That window is shut.
-(WHIRRING)
-(MEN GROANING)
(GROANING)
I'm just going to the store.
It's right there.
SHORETROOPER: You need to calm down, sir.
Droid assistance, please.
(MEN GROANING)
Uh... What? Wait. What is he...
No, this is crazy. (LAUGHS)
SHORETROOPER: Hang onto this one for me.
I wanna check the shelter.
(MAN SCREAMING)
KX UNIT: He said hang?
No, no, no. No.
No, you misunderstand.
No, he... he meant watch.
-KX UNIT: Hang?
-No, no, he means watch. (GASPS)
(GROANS, CHOKING)
KX UNIT: Hang.
(CHOKING)
Tell him! (GASPING)
Tell him you mean watch!
JUDGE: Charges?
PROSECUTOR: Loitering at a crime scene.
-Walking an unleashed massif.
-(SIGHS)
PROSECUTOR: Animal fouling.
JUDGE: Four months.
Next.
BAILIFF: Keef Girgo?
Keef Girgo!
Here.
-Name?
-(CHUCKLES) Hey, uh, Keef Girgo.
-Charges?
-PROSECUTOR: Civil Disruption.
-Anti-Imperial speech.
-(NERVOUS CHUCKLE) No. No.
PROSECUTOR: Fleeing the scene
of anti-Imperial activity.
-(SIGHS)
-PROSECUTOR: Attempted damage...
-I... I'm sorry, there's something wrong.
-JUDGE: I wouldn't.
You've got enough trouble
without a Resisting Judgement charge.
I'm just a tourist.
Oh, apologies all around then.
This used to be a six-month sentence.
Six years.
-Six years?
-PEOPLE: Six years?
-No, no, wait!
-BAILIFF: Take him.
-Change of guidelines.
-SHORETROOPER: Take him away.
-I didn't do anything! Hey!
-Take it up with the Emperor.
Wait. I'm just a tourist!
-JUDGE: Next.
-Wait!
-(SYSTEM BEEPING)
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)