My sigil marks me as wild and untamed.
It is a secret prayer,
my longing to be free.
Everything that does not please our overlords
has been stripped away.
In the darkness above Europa,
they take everything from us.
A wolf alone can be outrun,
out-fought, out-maneuvered.
But the wolf pack is an apex predator.
The aristocracy mate for money and power.
But we who can own nothing...
...have something real,
something primal, something true.
She is magnificent.
Fuck!
Turn! You big bastard!
The Tyrannosaur no longer screams.
He has had his fill of blood.
But you up there...
...you will never have enough.
Come... let us end this our way.
In the darkness above Europa...
...they take everything from us,
even our memories.
Yet some fragments linger...
...like the last leaves of autumn.
Among the blossoms,
I am alone with my wine.
Lifting my cup,
I ask the moon to drink with me.
Its reflection in the wine,
with mine, just we three.