[rock music playing]
Hey, you, I'm no fool
What you got going
what you got going
You've got temptation eyes
What you got hiding
So, after the butterfly flew out
of Goff's head, what happened to it?
I shot it. It blew apart.
Would have been
nice to have captured it,
but I guess it's good
it didn't get away.
[Vigilante groans]
- I'm not sure I'm ever gonna walk again.
- Why?
Motherfucker cut half my pinky toe off,
it's the most important toe there is.
- Yeah, that's not true.
- That's not true.
Yeah, it is. You can't walk without it.
You can walk just fine
without a pinky toe.
You'll fall over all the time,
look stupid,
and everyone will laugh at you.
Who's gonna laugh at you
for falling over
because you don't have a toe?
[laughs]
I was just imagining it. I'm sorry.
You can't walk
if you lose your metatarsal.
That's like the knuckle
of the pinky toe.
But if you just lose your pinky,
it's fine.
What are we gonna do about him?
[gun cocking]
- Hey! No!
- No, no!
[theme song playing]
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
- Get it on
- Get it on top
Make a move extreme
- Make a pose
- Shortcut to your dreams
Float straight to the stars
On that flying thing
- Getting high
- Getting brave
- Getting snowblind, game
- Set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon
In a world beyond
Get a beat, got a heat
On a phony string
Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
What's going up must come down
Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it
Baby, you're losing ground
Blind to what you'll soon become
The mirror lies, the whole world's wrong
- But you
- Dancing with your blinkers on
Throw your dog the invisible bone
[groaning]
- You okay to drive now?
- Yeah.
Harcourt and Adebayo, go through
those boxes from the Goff residence.
See if there's anything
to lead us to other butterflies.
Me? Why not John?
He's gotta keep Judomaster alive.
Peacemaker, in my office.
You sure your head is in this?
- What?
- You choked last night.
Are you kidding me?
Maybe that wouldn't have happened
if you put a goddamn dove of peace
on the sniper rifle.
One of the most important things
about killing someone to me,
is a fucking dove of peace
on the weapon.
That's bullshit, and you know it.
You also told me to kill kids,
you didn't say why.
Yeah, okay, one was homely.
That didn't make it better,
it made it worse.
I started feeling sorry for it.
Yeah, I may have pushed you too hard
on that one.
I made a vow to have peace at any cost.
No matter how many men, women,
and children I need to kill to get it.
But I'm not fucking killing kids
just because you say so.
You're sure that's all it is?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Because right now,
the world needs a son of a bitch,
and you're the only one I got.
[Vigilante] Fuck yeah!
Well, I guess, him now, too.
[groans] Fuck, it hurts to walk on.
- You sure about that?
- Yes.
Why?
Vigilante's a bit...
[whistles]
You think that's something
I wouldn't have noticed?
Yeah, you're right.
Ever since I had a team-up
with Matter-Eater Lad,
my sense of what's normal
is a little fucked-up. [sighs]
You have to keep Vigilante close.
If he talks, he could ruin everything.
I once saw him eat
an entire Wendy's restaurant.
- Vigilante ate a restaurant?
- No, Matter-Eater Lad.
That's his power, he can eat anything.
They took too long with his fries
or something. Guy's a fucking lunatic.
His name is Matter-Eater Lad?
Yeah. With all that's going on,
why are you so interested in him?
Not the time
to be getting distracted, Murn.
Okay.
Hey, these butterflies,
they're like alien bugs that crawl up
into human brains and control people?
Get some rest, come back tonight,
we'll explain the whole thing.
Okay.
Listen, again,
I'm sorry about last night.
I've never killed anyone before.
You said.
I've never shot anyone.
I've never shot at anyone.
Hell, I'm a pescatarian!
So, you're okay with making
that poor bastard's last minute of life
the worst suffering imaginable
because you're too much of a coward
to put him out of his misery,
but you won't eat a fucking fish.
Got it.
I do eat fish.
Pescatarians, we don't eat pork...
I don't give a shit, Adebayo.
The truth is, you wanna do this job,
you can't balk, ever.
You have to make the hard choice
when necessary.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
[exhales deeply]
Hey! You just gonna keep him here?
What else are we supposed
to do with him?
I don't know, a hospital?
What, so, he can narc?
God, there's so many secrets!
Yeah, that's what black ops is, dude.
[sighs]
And, um, don't worry about Harcourt.
She doesn't really like anybody.
Yeah, I just got to show her and Murn
that I got what it takes, I guess.
Well, I got what it takes.
Stomped his ass.
Uh-huh.
Don't fuck
with John Economos, motherfucker.
Hey, swing by my dad's on the way home.
He's got a helmet
I think I can use in all this.
Listen, I've been meaning to thank you
for allowing me
to be tortured last night.
You're welcome?
You know, for a minute,
I was kind of PO,
like, you didn't care about the fact
that I was in, you know, agonizing pain.
- [stutters] Okay.
- Yeah, but then I realized
you were... you were just supporting me
and helping me to become
the best me that I could be,
someone who doesn't spill the beans
while being electrocuted
and having half his toe cut off.
You seem to be walking okay.
Well, I'll probably never walk
as good again.
But it's worth it, you know, for being
a more evolved human being,
so thank you.
Never had a friend quite like you.
- What?
- It just seems like under the surface,
- you're kind of angry about it.
- I'm not.
- Seems like you are.
- Well, I'm not at all, dude.
- The way you said "dude" right there.
- What?
- Seems miffed.
- I said it like I always say it.
You know what?
If anything, you should be grateful
because you would feel really guilty
if I gave that guy information
'cause you were too much of a candy-ass
to take a little torture.
Oh, yeah, I would've been real guilty.
You see? That.
That right there was angry.
No, it wasn't! It was normal!
I was... I was agreeing with you.
Why does your father have an upside-down
American flag on his lawn?
I don't know, dude,
it's a Deep State thing.
Or your dad is a racist wack job.
Oh, yeah?
Your dad left your mom for another dude.
- Hey!
- He did.
Yeah, and they're deeply in love.
I doubt it. You know, I think he's just
pretending to be gay
to get away from you.
Okay, maybe, but what does that
have to do with anything?
I don't know.
I thought we were talking about dads.
Stay here. I'll be back.
Shit.
Fuck it.
Oh. Hey, it's you!
This is KWUE, your news at noon.
Chaos at the Evergreen Zoo this morning,
as zookeepers report
Charlie the silverback gorilla
is missing.
The facility has been closed
and forensics teams
have been sweeping the area.
Zoo officials say they have no idea
how the gorilla was stolen...
And I hope Charlie comes back, too.
I love that gorilla.
[beeping]
- There are gaps in the armor.
- What?
Your dad's White Dragon costume, right?
There are weak points
where the cloth is.
I thought I told you to wait in the car.
All the radio stations
are playing commercials.
How is it so big in this place?
It's a quantum unfolding storage area.
It leads to a dimensional nodule
outside normal space.
Well, I guess your dad's pretty brainy
for a racist to make a place like this.
And if your dad's a racist
and you work with him...
I don't work with him!
He makes me stuff.
If it walks like a duck...
That's all I'm saying.
The fuck's that supposed to mean?
If it walks like a duck,
it's either a duck
or a duck wearing
some type of human costume?
I don't know. He's unable
to hide his distinctive walk.
- How the fuck could that even happen?
- How would what happen?
A duck in a human costume.
The sizes are completely incompatible.
I don't know. Ducks are sneaky, I guess.
I guess that's the whole point
of the phrase.
That, and they could give two shits
about their best friend's pinky toe.
- Get outta here. You don't belong here.
- Don't push me.
Batman has a coterie of supervillains.
Joker, Riddler, Mad Hatter.
So what?
You said you were a superhero
like Batman.
Do you have a coterie of supervillains?
No, he doesn't.
So, maybe,
you're not a superhero after all.
You wanna know why
I don't have a coterie of supervillains?
Why?
My coterie of supervillains
is six-feet-fucking-under!
There, you see?
Batman doesn't kill people.
- Because he's a pussy!
- He's a dark creature of the night.
He's a jackass
who wrestles with murderers
dressed like clowns
and throws them in prison,
so they can break out of prison
and then murder more people.
Riddle me this, how many people
you think Batman's indirectly murdered
by being too much of a candy-ass
not to kill these fools who clearly
need to be smoked once and for all,
you wrinkly, shar-pei-looking
dementia-infested fuck?
Jesus!
I was just trying to make conversation.
Fuck it.
With an attitude like that,
you're definitely a supervillain.
You're going to end up in jail
with your father soon enough.
What are you talking about?
[vibrating]
- Peacemaker.
- What the fuck, Murn?
The only way to get the cops
off our tails
is to frame my dad for what I did?
It wasn't the plan.
It was an impulsive decision.
He's my dad, man. Jesus!
You ever have a fucking dad?
I did. I wasn't created in a Petri dish.
If you want to come back,
we can talk about this like adults.
No, no. My dad's in jail.
I'm going to see him.
Smith, I don't think that's wise.
Yeah, well, fuck you, man!
You people only fucking care
about yourselves, anyway.
[Emilia]...where all this money
is going.
[John] Holy shit.
[Emilia] Yeah.
Me?
Yeah, it's probably because
you're the one
who framed Peacemaker's father.
[mouthing] Fuck you.
Yeah.
What?
Just, I told you those people
weren't best-friend material.
You were right.
Hey, I'm sorry, man.
I wasn't more compassionate
about you being tortured and everything.
[sighs] Get out of here.
You kidding me? Come on.
That's the stupid, dude.
I was being stupid.
- No, I was.
- Pinky toes aren't that important.
Yeah, you were being weird about that.
[chuckling] Yeah, I was. Sorry.
Hey, you want me to take you
to the jail, see your dad?
Yeah.
Even though I know he's a racist.
Shouldn't you kill him, then?
No, I'm not gonna kill my dad.
Why not?
Because I love him.
Oh.
My dad and I both hate crime.
It's the only thing we agree on.
And he makes me stuff, okay?
Sure. Yeah. No, I mean,
my dad never made me anything.
He was too busy off pretending to be gay
just to get away from me.
- Me?
- He trusts you most.
I think he trusts Harcourt the most.
No, he wants to have sex with Harcourt.
He trusts you.
He said you were the only one
he was sure wasn't a butterfly.
I need you
to talk him out of seeing his father.
That could screw us in a number of ways.
Your lack of a résumé made me hesitant
to bring you onto this team,
but Amanda Waller insisted
you were ready.
Prove her right.
Well, go.
[grunts, straining]
Hey, Peacemaker.
- Fuck off, Adebayo.
- We messed up, we know it.
But that doesn't mean you should destroy
what we're doing because of it.
- Was it Murn?
- No.
Harcourt?
No, man, I... I shouldn't say.
Economos?
Motherfucker. How did he do it?
He changed your car registration
for your father's name
and changed out your fingerprints
for his.
Why didn't they just
re-fingerprint him?
They're a government bureaucracy.
They can, but double-checking things
isn't exactly protocol.
I can't just abandon him in there.
I have to go talk to him.
Do you? Really?
Look, we all know what he's done to you.
You don't know shit!
We do.
It's in your files, Chris.
[scoffs] It's "Chris" now?
How he's treated you your whole life.
What's it say?
Nothing, just...
- Okay, he's got his issues, right?
- Issues?
He's a white supremacist
who used to dress up as a supervillain
called the White Dragon.
He's not as bad as he seems!
He thinks people with my color skin
are second-class citizens.
That's fucked-up, okay?
- People change!
- And he's actually a good guy inside.
Yeah.
Well, we all wanna believe that
our parents are flawed,
but innately good,
and maybe, usually, that's the case.
But not here.
Your dad is not a good man.
Not to the world,
and especially not to you.
He's still family.
Chris.
Well, he has to do
what he has to do, I guess.
I take it you're Vigilante.
- No.
- You sound like him.
- No, I don't.
- That's a fake voice.
No.
It changed from what it was
two seconds ago.
I was about to cough,
but yeah, this...
this is more my real voice.
- Why are you limping?
- Snowboarding accident!
Totally unrelated
in any way to Vigilante.
I don't even know who Vigilante is.
Who is he?
Might even be a she.
I have no way of knowing.
Except, the Vigilante's voice
sounds like mine, according to you.
Which makes me surmise,
"Yeah, maybe it's a he."
You ain't killing it right now.
Ugh.
That's right.
- No.
- Yeah. It don't matter.
- Oh, yeah.
- Get the fuck outa here.
- I got no...
- Smith. You got a visitor.
Dad, listen.
I didn't know anything about this, okay?
The people I'm working with,
they did their own thing.
They switched your fingerprints
for mine.
They did what?
I know, it's fucked up,
but I had nothing to do with it.
They think this is gonna stick?
No, I don't know.
All I gotta do
is go to these assholes and say,
"Hey, check the fingerprints.
They don't match."
I know.
I saw you
come out of your mother's cooch.
I should've slit your throat
then and there.
Come on, Dad.
I never had any feelings for you,
not like your brother.
Him, I fucking loved.
But you, you were just
a blob of flesh I felt nothing for.
You know, Dad,
maybe I'm a grower, not a shower.
- What?
- I don't mean like a dick.
I mean, like a... a person.
Like a guy you like more
as time goes on.
An individual you don't like,
and then...
[stuttering] you learn to like.
You're comparing yourself to a choad?
Not in a bad way.
Deep State's got you so twisted up
in their agenda,
that you're comparing yourself
to a little cock.
No, this is the opposite
of the Deep State.
Bullshit!
No, Dad, if anything,
we're working against the Deep State.
I'll make sure
I fill the detective in on that.
Listen, I can't say much,
but you don't like illegal aliens.
These are real illegal aliens.
I'll turn myself in, I swear,
soon the operation's over.
This is bigger than me.
It's bigger than you.
And I'm just asking, for once,
just make the sacrifice.
You're a rube like you've always been.
I'm not letting my own damn son
work for them.
I'm no rat, but the first chance I get,
I'm spilling everything.
I don't mean to be a jerk here, Dad,
but technically,
that... exactly makes you a rat.
Technically, just factually...
Get the fuck out of my sight!
My use for you is over.
Guards! Open it up.
Get him out of here.
You think they'll arrest Peacemaker
in there?
I hope not.
He's bogged down by his old man.
Chris is.
He's a good man.
Like you.
You think I'm a good man?
Yeah.
I can tell.
But his father?
I'd say he's one of the worst people
to ever set foot on this planet.
Now, Chris, he has a big heart,
so he wants to find
something to love there.
But there is nothing to love
inside of that man.
And it kills me...
'cause I don't think
Chris is ever gonna be happy
as long as his father's around.
And I just wish there was some way
he would just...
go away.
I gotta go do something.
Okay.
Fuck.
- Where's Vigilante?
- Vigilante? That was Vigilante?
Shut up.
He had something to do, I don't know.
What did your dad say?
He said he's gonna rat us out.
Have you slept?
- No.
- Let me drop you off, then.
Hey.
- What do we do about...
- Your dad?
- Yeah.
- Murn'll work it out. It'll be fine.
I just didn't want you to get arrested
while you were in there.
Murn said I gotta keep eyes
on Vigilante.
Don't worry about it.
It'll be fine, too.
[sighs]
You're gonna be all right.
[scoffs]
My dad hates my guts.
Everybody hates my guts.
I'm a choad, and not the good kind.
I don't hate your guts.
And I think you're...
the good kind of choad.
Hmm. Thanks.
- What's going on here?
- [grunts]
God! I fucking promised...
What the fuck are you doing?
I don't have to
tell you that, motherfucker.
Get face down on the ground now!
Fine, I don't care.
I'll get on the ground all day long.
Just watch my pinky toe
on my right foot.
Pinky toes aren't that important,
you don't need it to walk or anything.
But I sustained an injury
and it hurts, so...
Ow.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, tell him to go fuck himself.
- Hey, John.
- [John] Oh, my God.
We are so incredibly fucked.
Like, next-level fucked. Okay?
I checked the restraints,
they were tight.
I don't know how the fuck he got loose.
[Leota] Who?
Who the fuck do you think? Judoma...
Fuck.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
Fuck!
I think Cobra Kai just got out.
[buzzes]
Hey, I wanna see that detective Song.
I've got some information
about the case.
All right.
[John gasping]
Where'd he go?
[continues gasping]
Here, here, here.
Hallway window.
Re-match, motherfucker.
Kiai!
[groans]
[both grunting]
Fuck you!
- Fuck you!
- Fucker.
[both grunting]
You...
have a weird bubbly-shaped body.
Personal insults?
Real mature, shrimp.
You have no idea.
Butterflies, they're not what you think.
- They are...
- [muffled gunshot]
I was gonna win that fight.
What?
This was the big rematch...
and I was reclaiming my honor...
and I was gonna win that fight.
You fucked it all up.
Jeez, you're welcome.
I'm not trying to be ungrateful.
It's just...
- Fuck!
- I've never killed a man before.
You still haven't.
These martial artists,
they are hardcore.
Their heart stops beating,
they just concentrate
and move a kidney up into its place,
and the kidney circulates the blood
through the system.
No, that's not something that happens.
Only the greats, just a few times.
No, that's never happened ever.
Yeah, it has. One or two times it has.
No one has ever replaced
their own heart with a kidney.
We have to get him back inside.
Okay. Hey, what do you think
he was about to say?
"Butterflies, they're not
what you think. They're..."
Chase.
Let's go.
I need to terminate
I'm like a bomb
A nuclear one
I'm gonna detonate
Do you wanna, do you wanna dance
With a jawbreaker
I just wanna be the way I wanna be
The crazier my life is the better for me
I'm grinding to the left
I'm grinding to the right
Jawbreaker
I just wanna live the way I wanna live
The bumpier my ride is the better I feel
I'm bumping to the left
I'm bumping to the right
All I wanna do
is rock'n'roll until I die
Road rage fever pumping through me
And I'm feeling great
Cannot hit the brakes
Don't wanna hit the brakes
Who likes to party
Come join the party
I'm gonna break your face
Do you wanna, do you wanna dance
With a jawbreaker
I just wanna be the way I wanna be
The crazier my life is the better for me
I'm grinding to the left
I'm grinding to the right
Jawbreaker
I just wanna live the way I wanna live
The bumpier my ride is the better I feel
I'm bumping to the left
What's your story, motherfucker?
All I wanna do
is rock'n'roll until I die
Eagly, hey, hey! No, no, no.
[sighs]
This time, you didn't balk, huh?
Do you think he's gonna die?
Probably.
I'm not cut out for this shit.
The first time I killed someone,
I didn't have my period
for three months.
And then it gets easier?
No, not really.
But it's good it hurts.
Otherwise, you become like Amanda Waller
and you start treating human life
like it's nothing.
None of this sits right with me.
First, I manipulated Vigilante
into going into prison
and killing Peacemaker's father,
and now, this.
Back up. What?
Every time I turn around,
one of you is doing something fucked up!
I thought Waller gave me soldiers.
Instead, it's the fucking
Apple Dumpling Gang!
[laughs] Classic pull.
Who are the Apple Dumpling Gang?
Incompetent dinguses.
But they always triumph in the end.
- Fuck you, John.
- Jesus.
You told Vigilante
to kill Peacemaker's father?
I didn't tell him to.
I just kind of put the idea in his head.
That Peacemaker would be better off
without his father.
His father
is gonna go to the authorities
and tell them
how we switched out the fingerprints.
I was just trying to make
the hard choice.
Seeing as we're already losing
Peacemaker's trust,
how's he gonna feel when he finds out
we manipulated his best friend
into killing his father?
Actually, that would be Eagly.
- What?
- Nothing.
It's just, he claims that Eagly,
that that's his best friend.
You said "best friend," okay?
I'm just making sure
we're all on the same page
in case someone here thinks that
Adebayo convinced Eagly
to kill Peacemaker's father.
Who would think that?
Maybe Harcourt.
- Fuck you.
- Why's everybody "fucking-you" to me?
I'm gonna believe
she mentally manipulated
the pet eagle into killing his father?
You're gullible. I call in sick
all the time and I'm lying.
I know you're lying.
I just don't give a fuck.
- I'm not stupid.
- Neither is Peacemaker.
But you seem to think he is.
I don't think he's stupid.
He'll know exactly what you tried to do.
Not only that, his father, the goddamn
White Dragon, is a trained killer.
He could kill Vigilante,
and without Vigilante,
we're taking on the butterflies
one man down.
Half a man down, the guy's a psychopath.
[chuckles] It is the four of us
against the damn alien invasion.
We need a psychopath.
I'm sorry, Mr. Murn.
Can you get Vigilante out of the system
before he screws us
worse than we're already screwed?
[sighs]
I don't even know this guy's name.
White male, 5'11", 30s, green eyes.
[John] I think I got something.
Found him. Adrian Chase, the Vigilante.
That's him.
Wasn't he our busboy at Fennel Fields?
"Jesus. Yeah, sure.
I'll teach him how to fight.
Hey, kid, look over here."
Kid looks over, he whacks him
on the back of the head, and says,
"That's the first fucking rule.
Keep your eye on your goddamn opponent."
[all laughing]
Hey. What's up, fellas?
But you totes seem like
the coolest guys in this place.
So I was thinking, you know,
we should get to know each other.
- What?
- Let's pick a topic,
and then everyone goes around
in a circle
and says their feelings on that topic.
Let's start with, uh...
I don't know. Let's each
say something that we're grateful for
that Black people have contributed
to American culture.
- Is this dude joking right now?
- No.
Hey, look, I'll go first.
I'm grateful that Black people
gave us rock and roll music.
Lynyrd Skynyrd, ZZ Top, 38 Special,
all those guys owe everything
to Black American
folk and blues musicians.
I mean, they wouldn't exist
without them.
And then white redneck music
would just sound like...
Well, what it sounded like
before Black people,
which was the wet, sloppy sounds
of fucking your sister.
Okay, so that's my turn.
Which one of you dumb,
sister-fucking, tiki torch-carrying,
sloth from The Goonies-looking
pieces of shit wants to go next?
Who the fuck are you?
You're first? Cool.
Okay, wait. No. Let me guess.
Your favorite contribution
to Black-American culture
was all the Black guys
who fucked your mom in the ass,
while you watched from the closet,
jerking off.
[all groaning, grunting]
Fuck! Fuck.
You never answered. Who are you?
I'm just the guy
who's gonna fuck you so hard,
your asshole's gonna be
dragging behind you like a tail.
No, you're not gonna goad me
into attacking you.
We both know
there's cameras all over this place.
And now these morons
look like the aggressors.
On the ground! Now!
Both of you!
Yo, the Aryans started it.
This dude did nothing.
You're a bad dad.
I need to talk to Detective Song now!
I need to talk to Detective Song!
I got information important
to this case.
My son's trying to kill me.
Get me Detective Song!
Come on.
[all cheering]
Hey.
Oh, no. Jesus.
Yeah, I figured you'd be here.
[sighs]
Smith, you really have to leave me alone
in my off hours
unless it's work related.
Well, this is kind of work related.
What?
What's it say in my file
about what my dad did when I was a kid?
What?
Adebayo just said
there was some stuff in there.
About me and my dad when I was a kid.
- I never studied your fucking file.
- Yeah.
But still.
[sighs]
Fine. It says that he trained you
to kill from when you were very young.
And it says that your brother died
under mysterious circumstances
and that you were involved in that.
Thanks.
That's it?
No. Your tits look stellar
in that shirt.
And I'm saying that as a compliment.
That's not in a sexist way.
[cheering continues]
[music playing]
Free to go.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Guess you got friends in high places.
It's a little past suppertime
I'm still out on the porch step
sittin' on my behind
Waitin' for you
Wonderin' if everything was all right
Momma said, "Come in, boy
don't waste your time"
I said, "I've got time,
well, he'll be here soon"
Five years old and talkin' to myself
Where were you? Where'd you go?
Daddy, can't you tell?
I'm not trying to fake it
and I ain't the one to blame
No, there's no one home
in my house of pain
I'm here to take you home.
Get in.
And I didn't write these pages
and my script's been rearranged
No, there's no one home
In my house of pain
No, there's no one home...
He's still alive.
...in my house of pain
I'm Adrian.
Okay.
I think I might have made things worse.
Where were you? Where'd you go?
Daddy, can't you tell?
I'm not tryin' to fake it
and I ain't the one to blame
No, there's no one home
In my house of pain
I'm not tryin' to fake it
And I ain't the one to blame
Peacemaker.
What a joke.
...in my house of pain
And I didn't write these pages
and my script's been rearranged
No, there's no one home
In my house of pain
And I'm alone again, yeah
No, there's no one home
In my house of pain
There's no one home
I'm alone again
[indistinct TV chatter]
[cell phone vibrating]
- Leota.
- I think I found something.
Great. I'll be right over.
So you're looking for an enemy
You found an enemy in me
You spit the venom
But your rattle couldn't make it bleed
Get rid of the cigarette
If you're serious
Put your money where your mouth is
Freak out with no control
Put your crayon away
'Cause this scene is getting real old
Cracked inside your shell
Please break out
Tripped out on violence
Put your trust in every word you say
But you fucked me over anyway
Embrace the silence
'til you tell me where you were before
Give it up,
you're twisting my desires to war
Come on slit me with your best lie
In the mind of a blind eye
Forget forgiveness
cause there's battle and it has begun
What's the thrill
with the sugar the pill
All that shit you said
Well, it didn't mean a thing no
Strip off and join the show
You got your two middle fingers
But I'm waiting with a fist full
You're the enemy in me
One is never enough...
If it walks like a duck,
it's either a duck
or a duck wearing
some type of human costume.
I don't know. He's unable to hide
his distinctive walk.
- How the fuck could that even happen?
- How would what happen?
A duck in a human costume?
The sizes are completely incompatible.
I mean, my pants would be caught
in my tiny webbed feet,
they'd be sagging all over the place.
It wouldn't fucking work.
How would they do the mask
with the beak?
And how would he even talk?
How would the mouth work?
I don't even know any of this.
Vigilante, you've had
a lot of fucking stupid ideas,
but a duck in a human costume?
That's the stupidest idea
you've ever fucking had.
And it's offensive to me.
Because I have a soul. Not a duck.