[ominous music playing]
[snoring]
- [chimes]
- [sheep bleating]
[Jerry] Uh-uh. Uh-uh.
[groans]
[ominous music playing]
[screams]
What are you doing?
Dad?
Dad? Hello?
What is wrong with you?
Really?
Oh. Okay.
[rooster calls]
Morning, ass... [burps] ...holes.
What's this? Pancakes? Sold.
What was up with you last night?
I was talking to you
and you acted like I wasn't there.
I did? Oh, yeah, no, that wasn't me.
Technically. That was my Night-Person.
Been having him do crunches
while I sleep. Check it.
- Damn. Check out that washboard, yo.
- Hey. Too hard.
What the hell's a Night-Person?
I nabbed a Somnambulator
while passing through
the Goobie-Joob System last week.
Best investment I've ever made.
Before going to bed,
I type a list of shit I wanna get done.
Then the Somnambulator programs
my unconscious body,
or Night-Person, to do it while I sleep.
I'm getting so much done.
Can my Night-Person get me
an ab stack like yours, Rick?
I'll have my Night-Person
learn me Spanish
so I can pass my test next week!
No one gets a Night-Person but me.
This tech is way too advanced
for you zeebs.
[sighs]
- What?
- Nothing.
- No. Go on. Say it.
- Say what?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Okay, fine! Fuck it!
Everybody gets a Night-Person.
Whatever.
Stick out your fingers.
It needs a blood sample.
Blood? Can't I just give it
Beth's credit card number?
This isn't Postmates, Jerry.
The Somnambulator
needs your DNA profile
to send commands
to your subconscious.
It can poke all the fingers I got
if I get abs like Rick.
Looks like I'm learning the trumpet.
Okay, remember,
somebody has to catch me if I faint.
Yay! Night-Family!
[all cheering]
[theme music playing]
[Beth playing trumpet]
[speaking Spanish]
How's my honor student doing?
All the niños and niñas
at school think
I should run for class president a.
'Sup, ladies. Wanna see something?
You wanna drop
this bowling ball on my abs?
Hell yeah, I'm only human.
Oh! Watch this.
[grunts]
'Sup, ladies. You ready, Morty?
- The stream's about to go live.
- Where are you two going?
Morty and I started a podcast
we call "Fab-so lutely Ab-ulous."
It's an ab-centric hour of fun.
Hoping to get Nancy Pelosi
on the show next week.
- Wanna drop her on our abs.
- Yeah.
Guess who has a new pen pal.
- No takers? It's me.
- Pen pal?
Night-Jerry and I
write letters to each other.
It's super fun.
"I also like Tori Amos."
"Hope you like our new pajamas."
"What is the sun?"
Jerry, this isn't how you're supposed
to use a Night-Person.
You two are being
a couple of Debbie Down-theres.
Wait until Night-Jerry
reads about this.
[playing trumpet]
Who wants cake?
[dramatic music playing]
[playing trumpet]
[both grunting]
- Abs are cool.
- Way cool.
But as above, so below,
know what I'm saying, Rick?
Morty, you must be referring
to these excellent boxer shorts
we got from the good folks
at Boxer Lobster.
Boxer Lobster boxers feel like they're
warm butter on your schwantz.
And they come in all sorts of styles:
neon, plaid, orange--
I even got a pair
with that little, uh,
the raccoon man from
that one movie printed on it.
Chewbacca.
Do yourself a favor and level up
with Boxer Lobster boxers.
You'll be glad you did.
Rick, they want you to say
"Wub-a-lubba-dub-dub" at the end.
Screw that. We're not whores.
Guys, dinner's getting cold.
You know what's not getting cold?
This hot stack of ab-jacks, son.
Pow, pow, pow...
No notes!
Oh! One more thing: Night-Jerry said
Night-Summer would appreciate it
if everybody could rinse off
their plates.
- What?
- You know,
rinse the schmutz off after eating.
Makes it easier to clean up later.
What?
Our job is not to make
the Night-People's chores easier.
It's a reasonable request.
Takes two seconds.
They exist only to do the shit
we don't want to do.
So, until further notice,
which will be never...
Request denied.
[crowing]
Hello there. [clicks tongue]
What the cock?
Where are the dishes?
[Beth] Uh, Dad? They're in here.
They busted up all our dishes.
What are we supposed
to eat off of now, brains for shit?
[groaning]
- [growls]
- You owe me.
We'll eat off these.
"Brains for shit."
Seems like you spent
an awful lot of energy
just to not give
the Night-Family what they want.
Jerry tell your boyfriend
to suck my dick
and good luck breaking
super-alien dishes.
I'll let him know,
but he's not gonna like it.
What?
Why won't you rinse your dishes?
It takes two seconds.
[whispering] if you don't, the schmutz dries
and makes the dish harder to clean.
Rinse your dishes!
[both] Rinse! Rinse!
Let me go. Who locked my implants?
I told you to, after you fell asleep.
You see, Night-You is not in charge.
Night-I am.
I don't care, I ain't rinsing shit.
Hey! What are you doing?
If you refuse to clean your dishes,
then I will have to do it for you.
[groaning]
I have always been here, Rick.
Deep inside the mind
of your grandchild.
Waiting to come out.
[utensils screeching]
Your machine allowed me
to steal the night, and soon...
I will seize the day.
[retching]
Oh, Baby Jesus!
Oh, it's awful,
oh, Baby Jesus! Awful!
What the fuck's your problem with me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I just got force-fed diarrhea
by your Night-Person,
who's also convinced Night-me
to lock me out of my tech.
[Morty] Uh, Rick? There's been
a pretty clear escalation down here.
The Night-Family stripped the house.
Everything's gone,
including the Somnambulator.
They locked us out of the garage.
I don't know about you,
but I got the hoo-ha's.
Goddamn it.
Are you happy now, Summer?!
I didn't do anything!
I'm trapped in this bullshit too.
Glad you think so, because
I got a plan to beat Night-Summer.
You're going undercover.
Did you have to make mushy garbage-science
on the living room carpet?
No choice, Jerry. Night-Summer
had Night-Rick take away my tech.
Had to improvise.
There are different levels of cortisol
in your bloodstream when you're asleep.
This interface only works off
my awake saliva samples.
No one asleep
will be able to deactivate
the laser-cage until I win.
- Where's Summer?
- Never mind her.
All of you get to bed.
Ugh, it itches.
This whole thing is way uncomfortable.
Yeah, that's the idea.
The Sleep Deprivation Suit is designed
to keep you awake until morning.
Aren't they going to be suspicious
seeing Night-Summer
covered in all this Terry Gilliam?
They're not gonna question her.
She's the leader of the Night-Family,
for some stupid reason.
When the Night-Family activates,
blend in.
Make them think you're Night-Summer.
If you start to nod off, suck on this tube.
What is it?
A cocktail of Mountain Dew
and DayQuil.
The kids in Southern Europe
call it DewQuil.
- Smells gross.
- It is.
Once you find the Somnambulator,
use this deactivator Puck.
Stick it on the Somnambulator.
When the puck activates, it'll fry its circuits.
Remember: Stay awake. All night.
Meet me back here at sunrise.
[sighs]
[keypad beeping]
Why are you wearing that suit?
- Yeah, why?
- Yes.
Yeah.
Because
you're all such clothing experts.
That's fair.
- Fair enough.
- Point taken.
Get back to work.
I rule the night and stuff.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Will do.
- As you wish.
[beeping rapidly]
Grandpa Rick! Rick, wake up!
What? I'm up! I'm up!
Did you find it?
For sure. You were souping up
the Somnambu-whatever
so they could extend
its range beyond the house.
But I defeated that shit when
I put the thing on top of the thing.
Everybody, wake up!
Summer fried the Somnambulator!
- The nightmare is over!
- Really? Oh! That's amazing!
Almost got pinched but yeah,
say adiós to the Night-Family.
Bye-bye, pen pal.
- I want Shoney's pancakes!
- Yes! Shoney's pancakes!
All right, brunch is on me,
Day-Family.
For a second there, I thought
Night-Summer was gonna win.
- That chick is the absolute worst.
- Sorry, Rick.
But your opinion
means very little to me.
Did you think you could
stop me with this, Rick?
[drone 1] Halt, Day-manoids!
Everyone! Get behind my abs!
[drone 2] Do not move! Do not move!
[drone 3] You are most definitely surrounded.
You are the slaves now.
If you have any doubt,
I suggest you sleep on it.
- She's Night-Summer!
- Thanks, Jerry.
[drone 1] Work! Work! The function
of the Day-manoid is to serve the night.
Work harder! Harder!
It is natural for the day
to serve the night.
Night was here long before day.
Half of all time is night time.
[drone 2] 157, 158...
- One hundred and--
- No more, please! I hate exercise!
[drone 2] Silence! Crunch harder! Harder!
We have to escape
the Somnambulator's reach.
- Do we even know how far that is?
- No.
Cards on the table, we may be
really eff-ed in the A this time.
[drone 3] Report to your designated
sleep pod for rest period.
[whispering] I'm a friend of your son-in-law.
Come with me.
- What?
- How?
Hurry. We don't have long before
the Proxy-drones go back online.
Thank you, Night-Jerry.
Anything to help Day-Jerry's family.
He's a very special per so--
Hey! Ow! Why?
- Nice. You got our Jerry back.
- Uh, yeah. Totally why I did that.
- Everybody in Rick's car!
- Morty! Wait!
Having a bit of trouble with your car?
- [Rick] Not now, Gene!
- [drone 1] Day-manoids are restricted
from the outside world!
Halt! Halt!
Hold on to your tits.
[tires screeching]
- Where am I going?
- To the airport!
We have to get far away
from the Somnambulator
before we fall asleep.
What about Summer?
We can't leave her behind.
She's not your sister anymore.
Consider her dead. Eat shit, Summer!
You gotta shake those robots.
I think we lost 'em!
[Beth] Son of a bitch!
[Rick] Damn it, we lost Morty!
Beth! Watch out!
You cannot escape-- Ah! Shit!
Huh?
- [siren wailing]
- Stop or I'll shoot everyone!
- Take the wheel.
- As you wish.
Let go of me, you little shit!
- No! You're going the wrong way!
- Silence, Day-breather!
- [Jerry] Morty, you're choking me.
- I know!
Ow. What the heck, Dad?
[truck horn honking]
Help me stop your mom!
Look out, you useless old man.
What the hell?
- Give me that gun and take the wheel, stupid.
- Jesus! Sorry!
[shouting]
Ugh.
[screams]
The Night-Family's trying to make us go home!
You gotta turn around!
Why even bother, Gene?
- Good job, Mom. Back on course.
- Almost didn't make it.
[drone] Hit the sheets, Day-manoids.
- Night-Person!
- Hey! I'm on your side!
- I'm on your side!
- Oh, that's right.
Sorry! Rough day.
[drone] Day-manoids.
Fla-Hoigan!
- Come on! Jump!
- Why?
I'm already in
a perfectly functional car!
Uh... family?
Aw.
- Everybody awake?
- Ow!
- We are now.
- Hey, what the hay?
- Looks like we're gonna make it, kids.
- Ow.
Nighty-night, slaves.
Fuck.
[tires screeching]
Take that!
- Hold him down.
- No! No!
[whispering] Stop! Rick, we're all the same people.
There must be some agreement
we can reach to stop
this god-awful conflict?
Oh, like what?
I would consider a truce,
if the Day-manoids
would rinse their dishes.
- Yes, rinse!
- Fine by me.
That seems fair.
We can end all of this right now
if you agree to rinse your dishes.
What do you say, Rick?
Let's go home. Right, Grandpa?
Great idea, Summer.
[soft rock music playing]
[man] So until you pay that fee,
plus the multiple overdue charges,
your account will remain frozen.
Normally this would have been dealt
with by our Day-manoid oppressors
but we recently freed ourselves
from the shackles of the night.
I got 30 more calls to make today.
The bank repossessed the car.
Aw, man.
I got logged out of my Twitter account
and don't know my password. Shit.
We spent all the Day-people's money
on vacations,
renting concert halls and night-centric
streaming subscriptions.
We're broke.
I guess, there's a lot more work
to seizing the day than I thought.
[all groaning]
I have a device that
will solve all of our problems.
- Whoa. How long have we been asleep?
- Can't be that long.
Oh, my God! No!
They killed the choco taco!
[all screaming]