Thank you.
Would anyone else
like to share?
I'm Tammy.
Hi, Tammy.
Hi.
Things have been okay.
Yeah. Um...
Still really hoping
to get a bigger car.
It's one of our goals
for TSDY.
Uh, sorry.
Um... try something
different year.
It's like a thing
we found online.
We decided to try it
out once I got better.
Um...
Uh...
I've been cancer-free
for 12 months.
But, um...
You know, I still just
live with the terror
that it's gonna come back.
It's not coming back.
He always says that,
but, you know,
I just have a lot
of anxiety.
Focusing on my business
really helps.
Um...
My friend Devin
makes me laugh hard.
So...
Devin?
Yeah, my ex.
The firefighter.
Um, rekindling
that friendship has...
it's really helped me.
You know, community
is so important.
But I worry.
Will I ever see my son graduate?
Will I ever orgasm again?
Sorry. This is, uh,
not so exciting,
but this group really helps,
so, thank you.
Craig...
Anything you wanna share?
Everything is really awesome.
Tammy deserves a parade.
And I'm orgasming fine.
I'll share, I'll share.
Um... this has been
a great week for me.
Craig.
The mailman screwed up again.
Can you bring the package
to the neighbor's?
Craig Waterman. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm in the car now.
Actually, I'm in
the parking lot.
I'll be up there
in two seconds.
Perfect. Perfect.
Perfect. Bye.
Hello?
Hi.
Howdy.
Are you Austin?
Guilty.
Yeah, the, uh...
mailman screwed up.
Uh, I'm down there
at the end of the block there.
Oh, with the for sale sign?
Yeah. About to leave
the neighborhood.
It's a bummer.
Wish I could've gotten
to know you, but yeah
we're leaving.
Sorry about this.
Oh, not your fault.
Some mailman idiot
always messes up.
Well, it's gonna happen,
I guess.
Yeah. I didn't open it
or look or anything.
I know that that's illegal.
Oh. Thank you.
Yep. No worries.
Hey, I didn't catch your name,
by the way.
Oh, it's, uh,
Craig Waterman.
Stay curious,
You too, Austin.
Full mug coming
through here.
Careful, careful, careful.
Full mug.
Hey, java king!
Fuckin' moron.
Nicholas from Serotonin
Solutions. Sam is on.
How was everyone's weekend?
I need to get a bigger car.
I know. Let's sell
the house first.
I can't fit this stuff.
Look what happened,
it fell over.
Hey, Shannon.
Hey, gang.
Hi.
You didn't steal anything,
did you?
House has got good bones, right?
Sorry my wife's stuff
is everywhere.
Yeah.
A beautiful neighborhood too.
Nice people there.
Really good people there.
You have a good day.
Awesome.
Shit.
Didn't even fucking
talk to me.
Can you put that
in the front?
Like, try and find a spot?
I don't know where to put it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ah, I got water on me!
Stevie...
can you pass me that, please?
Super beautiful.
Thank you.
What are those?
Oh, honey. The new
neighbor Austin.
He brought these over
for us earlier.
He also invited you
over for a drink
at 8:00 tonight.
I said you'd go.
You don't know my schedule.
You sit there every night.
It might be nice
to have a pal,
you know, a bud.
Hello, Tammy's florals,
Steven speaking.
Just welcome him
to the neighborhood.
There's a new Marvel out.
It's supposed to be nuts.
We should go see that.
Oh... my ex-boyfriend Devin,
he invited me out
for a drink tonight.
Thank you so much.
Okay. Two Luna
arrangements for a 90th.
Extra lavender.
Stevie, your mom's
abandoning us.
It's just you and I.
We gotta go see
that Marvel tonight.
I already saw it.
It's sorta--
Ah! Don't spoil it.
Do not spoil it.
What's going on?
Honey.
Please don't go out
with this fucking
dumb clown tonight.
You and I, we'll go see
this new Marvel.
People are saying
it's actually nuts.
It's driving people crazy.
It's nacho, nacho time!
Never...
Never underestimate the nacho.
Yummy. Oh, good work.
Mwah.
Delicious, huh?
Anyway, I gotta go.
But I love you.
Have fun.
See you later.
Thank you.
You guys kiss each other
on the lips?
Honey.
Go.
Err...
Hmm.
Oh, you know, I, uh...
I actually got those speed bumps
put in on our street.
Yeah. It was a frickin'
nightmare
dealing with the city.
But now the whole neighborhood's
not a goddamn racetrack.
Well, thank you.
Welcome.
Well, what do you do
for a living?
Well, I dabble in a few
things, but, uh...
I pay those criminals
at the bank
by covering the weather
for Channel Three.
You're a weatherman?
I usually work evenings,
but I got tonight off.
I knew you looked familiar.
That's so awesome.
What do you do for a living?
I work for a company called
Universal Digital Innovations.
We work with clients
who are trying to make
their products
more habit forming.
I work with apps, specifically.
Like...
trying to get people
addicted to products?
Uh... we prefer to use
the term "habit forming".
It appeals to the most primal
aspects of the brain.
So when the person tries
to detach themselves
from the product, they become
extremely displeased
and they just continue using it.
Fucking brutal.
Yeah, it's brutal.
I got a product you might like.
Alright.
Porno mag?
Better.
Look familiar?
Just a box from my yard.
What's this?
That's a 400,000-year-old
stone hand axe
carved by Homo Erectus.
These are the first human
objects ever made.
You're holding the very same
tool that some
ancient person held on
in East African Savannah.
As they paused in awe
to watch the land
swallow the burning
golden ball in the sky.
Whoa, buddy.
Oh!
Shoot! Uh...
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I am so sorry.
This never... oh!
Fuck.
Let's go somewhere.
Uh...
It's a school night for me.
I'll get you a clean shirt.
Okay.
Alright.
What's here?
Come on, come on.
This way.
Quick!
Before the pigs see us.
It's the Aqueduct.
It was built in 1837.
Look at this.
It connects the entire city.
Oh my God.
Aw, fuck!
I got stuff all over me.
Ah, it looks like OVD's
gonna get
a little bit more
of my money.
OV what?
Ocean View Dining.
It's the only clothes
that fit me just right.
- Oh. Wow.
- Yeah.
Looks good.
Yeah, this is all OVD.
- Nice.
- All this is. Yeah.
Alright.
They even make food.
This way.
Alright.
There you go.
Come on. You got it.
Grab my hand.
There you go.
You okay?
You got it.
Pull up, pull up. Pull up.
- There you go.
- Oh...
You okay?
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Alright.
- Nice job.
- Thank you.
What's wrong?
Lost my shoe.
Oh.
Ah, we'll get it on
the way back. Come on.
This is so cool.
Yeah, there's a way into
the building through here.
Oh my God!
Oh... I thought
that was a guy.
Where the hell are we?
City Hall. Come on.
What?
Oh.
It's a normal ciggie,
it's not cannabis.
Oh. Excellent.
Oh, hey.
My band's playing
tomorrow night.
Bring Tammy.
Your frickin' band?
You're in a band?
Yeah, it's gonna be
a big show.
Hopefully my boss
doesn't make me work.
I tell ya...
I am so over nightly news.
I wanna do mornings.
Why don't you just ask?
I wanted my own office
at work.
I just asked.
Did you get it?
Eat in there alone
every single day.
I can eat whatever
the hell I want.
Something big and messy.
Something really embarrassing
I don't want anybody to see.
Something that stinks.
All you gotta do is ask.
You'll be on the list
tomorrow night, rock star.
I'll be there, rock star.
Alright.
Ehh.
You crack me up.
- I do?
- You crack me up.
Yeah!
Alright,
friends. That's it.
That's our national forecast.
Take care of yourselves
out there.
We'll see you tomorrow night.
I'm not clicking anything.
I think my clicker
ran out of batteries.
I tell ya, sometimes I feel
like I've run out of batteries.
I gotta go change
my double A's.
See ya tomorrow night.
Alright. How y'all doing?
Sorry about the tie,
I just got off work.
We're Mayor Nichols Sucks.
This song goes out
to my wife, Bianca.
♪ I just want to enter
the night ♪
♪ Cut the dark open
with a knife ♪
♪ Out there's
the courage to fight ♪
I feel like we need
to add something
that makes the user feel
expressed or judged.
So they keep coming back to
use it over and over again.
Like... like here.
You see the...
they have the key
emoji down there.
See that key?
Someone named Austin Neighbor
Weatherman is calling you.
One second. Pardon me.
- Hey, buddy.
- Hey Craigy, whatcha up to?
Just boring old crap, really.
I hear you.
Hey, quick question: You up
for going on an adventure?
- When?
- When? Right now.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Smooth cap.
Forked gills along the stipe.
Throw that on your grill
with a little butter...
got yourself a meal.
Go on, smell it.
Oh, wow. That's vanilla.
You know...
I can't stop thinking
about your band.
That's so fucking amazing.
Thanks, bud.
You play anything?
Nah, I always wanted
to play drums, but just...
Didn't.
Get yourself a set.
We'll jam.
Play some punk music
or something.
It isn't about
how well you play.
It's about how passionate
you are.
Oh, wow. Drums.
Yeah. Well.
What color would I get?
I guess it probably
doesn't matter what col--
Well, actually it might matter--
Oh shit! Oh shit!
Help! Help me! Help me!
Oh my God, help!
I got you.
Oh, Jesus!
What the hell?
Well, looks like
Ocean View Dining's
gonna get more of your money.
Yeah. Honestly though,
their new fall collection,
it looks superb.
I'm really excited about it.
Oh shit, my phone!
Oh, fuck! My phone!
Can... can you call it?
Can you call it?
Can't. I don't have a phone.
Are you insane?
I'm looking at a free man
right now.
Come on.
Look at this.
Oh...
- Yeah.
- Crap.
Oh, look at this.
Oh man, that's cherry.
Whoa!
Oh, yeah.
This is my dream car.
I hope you get it one day.
This thing is absolutely cherry.
Yeah.
Well, it might happen
sooner than you think.
I took your advice.
They offered me
the morning news slot.
Oh my God!
- Really?
- Yep.
Congratulations!
Holy crap.
Thank you, buddy.
Truly.
Now, if I get this
stupid car,
you're going for
the first ride.
I promise.
You're good luck.
I'm good luck.
Yes, you are.
I can see the future.
It is full of pals.
My husband!
Somebody help us, please!
Helping pals.
I got you, buddy.
Thank you, Craig.
Oh, it's so cold out there.
And being a boss.
Civilization has collapsed.
But Craig has led us
to the future.
To Craig!
The neighborhood would be
a racetrack without you.
I'm on the edge
of life...
and the view is gorgeous.
What the...
what are you doing?
Can I wake you up
with a lick?
- A lick?
- Yeah.
- Is the door locked?
- Okay.
Something's burning!
- Fuck!
- Something's burning?
What did you do?
I hope you like wild mushrooms
on toast, honey.
What?
Seriously, what happened?
What'd you do?
Nothing.
Good morning.
You like this?
- Punk?
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, I like punk.
- Fuck yeah.
You don't listen to music.
Yeah, I do.
I listen to punk.
I even took a walk
this morning.
Got up. Went for
a full walk.
Picked some of those
flowers right there.
- You made these?
- Yeah.
Oh shit, tastes like
McDonald's.
I love it. So good.
- Thanks.
- Okay, I'll see you guys.
- Love you.
Austin invited me
to hang out
with some of his
buddies tonight.
They seem like
pretty cool guys.
Wow, honey.
Hey, how are you?
I'm Craig.
Austin invited me.
Oh, there he is!
Alright. Hey, guys.
This is my neighbor, Craig.
He's the best.
Hey, hey! To the new
morning weatherman!
This is the life!
I'll drink to that,
I'll drink to that.
I appreciate you.
It's great to talk to you,
Chris.
Hey, I'm gonna grab
another brew.
Alright. Yeah, for sure.
I'll see you inside, alright.
Yeah.
You're smart.
You have a good job.
There's nothing to be
nervous about.
Just be yourself.
You're a frickin' prince.
You okay?
Thought it was open.
You... you hit that hard.
Can I use your restroom
really fast?
So how'd y'all meet?
That reminds me, Zed
ran into me at the mall
and I was all stressed out.
I was buying a bra
for my daughter.
She's 13 and she's already
a size C.
And, uh... you know,
I was just spiraling.
But I just... I see the way
that guys look at her.
You know, I'm just...
I'm scared.
I'm sorry you're going
through that, man.
You know we're here
for you anytime, right?
Sheila's lucky to have
a dad like you.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
♪ Boy, you should
know that... ♪
♪ I've got you on my mind.
♪ Your secret admirer.
♪ I've been watching you.
♪ At night I think of you.
♪ I want to be your baby.
♪ If your game is on,
give me a call, boo. ♪
♪ If your love is strong,
gonna give my all to you. ♪
♪ At night I think of you.
♪ I want to be your ba--
Alright. Who's next?
Who's next?
Oh! Let's get the new guy
in there.
Hey.
Get him, Craig.
Hit him!
- Come on!
- Get him!
Stay right.
Alright!
Everybody watch out
for my face.
Some of us have calls
with CEOs tomorrow.
Got a big shot
in the house.
- Focus.
- Come on, Craig!
Alright. Alright.
- To a good match.
- Yeah, heavyweights!
Ding, ding!
Oh! The first punch.
Damn!
You okay?
You alright, Craig?
You alright, buddy?
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
- Sorry about that.
Let's both try to be
a little safer.
- Absolutely.
- Excellent.
- You and me fight okay.
- Yes, yes.
- Friend to friend.
- Friend.
Here we go. Alright.
- Let's go, Craig.
- Ding, ding, ding.
Like you did the last time.
Yeah.
- You didn't want that.
- Hands up. Hands up.
Oh... this fight's over.
Fuck!
Oh... you alright?
Oh, my God.
This guy can't take it, Austin.
You gotta stop.
Okay, great.
Maybe you should sit
this one out then, Craig.
Sorry about that.
You're okay. Alright.
Anyone else wanna go?
- What the fuck, man?
- Winner!
Winner!
You knocked him out, idiot.
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Nah, he's good.
Guys, help him up.
No, you're good.
He's solid.
He's good.
Hey, am I bleeding at all?
What the fuck is wrong
with you, jackass?
Cheap shot bullshit.
That was fucking bullshit.
- Sucker punch!
- What the fuck?
It's alright.
Let's get these off.
There we go.
Take this off.
Okay. Easy, easy, easy.
- I'm okay.
- You good?
Yeah, yeah.
I think, uh...
I think maybe, uh... uh...
we call it on boxing
for tonight, huh?
Hey...
look...
I know my punishment.
I messed up.
I'm a bad boy.
I'm sorry.
What'd I do?
What did I do?
I'm such a bad boy.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Alright. I gotta go
home now.
Yeah, me too.
He's gonna call his--
Alright. Yeah, yeah.
You sure? Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You call somebody.
I'm okay. I'm alright.
Just watch your back.
Watch out for this guy.
Yeah, thanks.
- Alright. So long, fellas.
- See ya, man.
Okay.
Sure you know how
to get home?
I'll do my best.
- Okay.
- Alright.
Hey, man. Nice job,
you fucking cock.
Alright.
You've reached
Austin and Bianca,
you know what to do.
And with us today is
our newest edition
to the Rise and Shine family.
He's someone you're probably
already familiar with.
Austin Carmichael,
our new meteorologist.
Howdy, folks.
Happy to be her.
Err... here.
Happy to be here.
Looks like I could use
another cup of java.
Better make it
a big one.
When we come back,
Austin will join us
as we talk with what
some people are calling
a six-year-old Tiger Woods.
Alright, we're back
live in 60 seconds.
Hey man.
Crushed that.
That was awesome.
How'd you... how'd you
get in here?
I have a meeting here.
Who's your meeting with?
Just some dickhead or whatever.
Oh, I have a check for you.
I gotta give it to you
next time we hang out.
Are you wearing makeup?
I'm not gonna tell your wife.
What was up with that stumble?
Oh, uh... yeah.
Sorry about that.
Um... new job jitters.
It won't happen again.
It better fucking not.
This your father?
Uh, no. It's my neighbor.
Not really sure
why he's here.
Hey, what are you doing
after this?
I was gonna go to Rick's Bar
and try this new thing.
They have a SEAL Team
Six lunch.
I guess that's what the guys ate
after they killed Osama.
It's 22,000 calories.
It's got four racks of ribs,
mac and cheese...
Caesar salad.
Look, it's really distracting
that you're here.
I need to focus. Okay?
Hey, buddy.
Looking good.
I like it.
Oh! You're dressed
as a little doll?
Wanna smoke a cigarette
with us, little doll?
Hey. Look, you gotta go.
Alright?
I'm under a lot of
pressure here.
It's a lot harder than nights.
Just please leave.
Thank you.
You have a phone?
Yeah, of course I have a phone.
Back live in
10 seconds.
Let's get Austin on his mark.
I'll hang out with you soon.
And did you wanna upgrade
to the hero plan?
It's unlimited talk,
text and data.
Plus you get one of these
five limited phone cases.
Oh. Yeah, definitely.
Yeah, that sounds great.
Uh... I'm gonna do...
oh, Mars Rover.
Oh...
Twins!
Beer drinking time, huh?
Yeah, I mean...
or something else.
Hey, is that, uh...
bar across the plaza
any good?
I've never been.
I've seen a few gnarly
fights outside though.
Yeah. I might step over
there and have a sip,
or a few, if you wanna
join me.
It'd be cool.
Oh.
I'm 18.
Ugh.
Teenage girls these days,
they look like
they're 25 years old.
I guess it's the same
with the guys too.
Receipt in the bag?
I'd love a receipt
in the bag, yeah.
Alright.
Oh, and sir...
If you ever want something
a little stronger
than a few drinks...
you let me know.
Stay curious.
You may
begin to detach...
from realities you had
claimed as your own.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
A package came for you.
Oh, yes!
Oh my God. Holy shit!
- Ooh, that's exciting.
- Holy shit!
These are fucking awesome!
These for you?
Oh yeah.
Hey, hey! Is your
better half here?
One moment.
Honey.
There's someone
at the door for you.
It's Craig.
Alright.
Dude.
Check it out.
Wow. You, uh... you got
the expensive ones.
Yeah. I got green
to match your guitar.
- Let's jam.
- Um...
- Whoa. You look awesome!
- Oh, thank you.
Uh... look, uh, Craig...
We had a couple of
really nice hangs,
but I think it best that
we go our separate ways.
Is it 'cause of
the sliding glass door?
I told you I'd
pay for it, buddy.
No, Friday night
was really strange
for me and the guys
and I don't wish to continue
this friendship at the moment.
You made me feel too free.
You all accepted me
way too fast.
You can't do that.
People need rules.
I've gotta get to this
Renaissance Fair.
I'm doing a segment
for work.
Um... much luck selling
the house.
Austin, come on.
Craigy, isn't it beautiful?
Doesn't seeing this
make you certain
that some unknowable
intelligence
is behind all things?
Thank you, Rebecca.
Uh... my producers told me
that there was
a Renaissance Festival
here today.
And, uh...
clearly I'm the only one
dressed up, so...
it's a fun... fun prank
on the new guy. Ma'am.
Right...
Stevie, come on.
There's nothing over there.
Come here.
Look.
Free food.
That's ancient stuff
you're holding there.
People have been doing this for
hundreds of thousands of years.
Cool, huh? Take a bite.
No. How do you know
they're not poisonous?
I'll show you.
This one needs a little ranch.
This is fun.
Hanging out at the mall,
this is fun.
Got any crushes at school?
Of course. Dad.
That guy on that pig
was flying.
What the hell?
That was crazy.
God!
I told you those mushrooms
were poisonous, Dad.
I told you.
Fuck.
Jesus Christ,
there's fuckin' blood in it.
Couldn't believe that.
You know?
Fuckin' hell, dude.
Fellas.
How we doing?
What's up, man?
We're the smokers,
we're the smokers.
It was awesome.
Anybody need a light?
Good?
Beers at my house
this Friday.
Heck yeah.
I'll stock the fridge.
Let's do a boys night.
Can my wife come?
No, you don't know her.
You never met her.
No, no.
No, let's keep it
a boy's night.
I gotta call my wife.
Tell her things might
get a little rowdy
this Friday night.
This is a sword.
From Europe, 1700's.
Let me see this thing.
Hey, don't rip it outta
my hands.
It's priceless.
Be careful with that, okay?
Dude, you scare the fuck
outta me, like, so easily.
Imagine.
You're a knight.
Staring out...
at the enemy army coming at you.
Your heart is racing.
Why are you showing
us this thing?
'Cause it's cool.
I collect stuff like that.
It's so small, dude.
It's like... for babies.
This is a sword for babies.
It's not for a baby,
it's for a knight.
It's like when Thanos
drinks the elixir.
Sorry, sorry, sorry,
sorry, sorry.
I gotta stop you.
This is a, uh, no
Marvel spoiler garage.
Sorry, it's a little
rule here.
I apologize.
Dude. When that ship
fucking comes in...
I'm dead serious.
No Marvel spoilers.
- I like to go in fresh, so...
- Alright.
Yeah, yeah. No worries.
No worries. Yeah.
Are those your
wife's drums?
That's funny, I already
told you they're mine.
They look like no one's
touched them, bitch.
Why don't you jam for us,
Coltrane.
Give us a little taste.
Come on, man, don't hide.
Don't use the knife like that.
Don't point the knife at people.
He's like The Hulk, man.
Get the fuck out!
Get the fucking hell outta here.
I said no spoilers.
Let's go. Get up.
We've been here, like,
40 minutes.
Move, move, move!
Yeah, yeah. There he is.
Jesus Christ.
Craig.
My key card mysteriously
stopped working.
Uh... do you need
to change?
- No.
- You sure?
Yeah. I've been
through worse.
Okay. Well, um...
we have a new client
that I'm really,
really excited about.
Mr. Mayor... Seth Nichols.
Seth Nichols
is about trust.
Now, he wants us
to modernize his
re-election campaign.
Make it much more interactive.
Now, Craig... who do
you want on your team?
Besides a towel?
I'll just be a lone wolf
on this one, I think.
Honey.
You're home?
Yeah. I don't trust my lunch
in the work fridge.
I think somebody's
fucking with it.
- Can you help me load these?
- Yeah.
I gotta scarf, though.
I gotta get on a call
with the mayor
about the mayor thing
or whatever.
The mail guy screwed up again.
Craig.
Your nose.
- Oh.
- I've never...
Yeah.
Never seen you get
a bloody nose before.
No, it's not a big deal,
don't worry about it.
- You okay? Here.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Let's get these in.
- Be careful with that.
- Pick it up from the base.
- Yeah, yeah. I gotta go.
I gotta have a fast lunch.
I have a big call.
Honey. I'm sick of struggling,
I need a bigger car.
I gotta go!
You still have blood
on your nose.
- That's fine, that's fine.
- Wipe it off.
Bye! Bye, bye, bye.
Ah...
Motherfucker.
Hey, hey.
Putting you through
with the mayor's office.
Jen's on.
Joanna and Monkey
See Inc. are on.
Barry from Digitonis.
Craig Waterman is on.
So, Craig...
before we start,
I wanna clear something up.
Austin? Honey?
Hello?
Craig? Hello?
Hello, hello.
It's the craziest thing that
you don't have a cell phone.
Somebody knocked on the door.
Hey, baby.
Come snuggle.
Are you there?
It's nap time.
Did we lose Craig?
Is Craig there?
Chad from Dopamine
Unlimited is on.
He's not responding
'cause he probably doesn't have
his cell phone.
- Craig?
- Yeah.
There you are.
For a short period, I didn't
have a phone, as an experiment.
Where would you like to start?
That is really brave of
you, that is crazy.
I cannot imagine. I'm looking
at this thing constantly.
Uh-huh.
Hello?
Craig? Hey.
I tried calling you.
I need you to go to the store.
I had a nuts day.
No, honey.
Tonight...
it's Austin and Bianca's
housewarming thing.
I need you to get some things.
That's tonight?
Maybe I can borrow
some things from them?
Do you have their number?
Uh... yeah... I'll call 'em.
What do you need?
Um, I need vanilla extract.
I need brown sugar.
If they have powdered sugar
that'd be really great.
Hey Austin,
what's going on?
Yeah, yeah. We're about
to head over, actually.
Oh.
Oh, for real?
Oh, that sucks.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I actually, uh, have
a bad case myself right now.
No worries at all.
Yeah.
Okay, we'll--
Okay, we'll talk to you soon.
Bye.
I guess Bianca came down
with a really bad case
of diarrhea.
Oh God.
Yeah.
Maybe I should make her
some chicken broth.
I wouldn't do that.
It'd probably just rip
right through her.
Let's just invite people over.
Maybe Devin's available.
Devin?
Do you ever listen?
Hey.
Hey!
Turn those burners off.
We're going on an adventure.
Craig. Absolutely not.
This was built in 1837.
Goes all over the city.
It's called an aqueduct.
- Is this piss?
- Some of it.
Wait...
Yes, this is it.
This is it.
This is it. Yes!
Oh, my God.
Are we lost?
No, no, no.
This way.
- Craig, there's a bat.
- Where?
- Right there!
- Alright. Let's go this way.
We're not going that way,
so that's not a problem.
Who showed you this?
I found it myself.
Come on.
Seriously, who showed you
this place? Was it Austin?
No, I found it.
Come on.
You go up here and there's
some really...
- I'm not going up there.
- beautiful shit--
- I wanna go home!
- The bat's back there.
I don't wanna walk by
that bat again.
Come on. There you go.
There you go.
Go, go, go!
Perfect. Perfect.
Okay, this is insane.
I wanna go.
Help me down.
Christ almighty.
Can you just give this
a chance?
You're always complaining
that we don't do anything new.
Well, we're here now.
You're healthy...
and we're here now.
So... Jesus!
Just go ahead and I'll catch up
to you in a sec.
Thank you.
Okay.
Shit!
Where the fuck is it?
Fuck it.
Oh, God damn it.
Don't worry, honey.
We're really close.
Tammy?
Tammy, where are you?
Where did you go?
Tammy.
Tammy!
Tammy!!!
Please hang up...
No!
My phone!
Where the fuck is it?
Fuck!
Tammy!
We are currently
cruising at an altitude
of 1,000 feet,
at an air speed of 4100
miles per hour.
400 miles. Err...
You make me a little
nervous sometimes.
Are you still there?
...The weather is pleasant with
light turbulence here and there.
I need to use the phone.
I'm in the middle of something,
let me finish.
I need to use the phone,
Stevie.
What the hell is going on?
- Sir, do you live here?
- Austin?
How's the party going, bud?
We had to cancel it 'cause
someone broke in.
I don't know, so why
don't you tell me, bud?
What the hell's going on
with him?
Sir, are you the primary
resident?
Jesus! Yes, I am.
What is this about?
We had a break-in
down the street.
The dog picked up a scent
that led here.
You think my house got broken
into by the same person? What?
You broke into my house!
Hey! Hold him back.
Do your job.
You broke into my house!
What do I pay taxes for?
Hold him!
Are you and your sons the only
ones who live here?
My wife does too.
- Was she here today?
- She's here all day.
Can we speak to her?
- She's not here.
- Where is she?
She's in the sewer.
What? What'd you say?
- She's where?
- I said she's in the sewer.
And what happened next?
We were trying to go
to City Hall.
You can get there through
the basement. Right?
Well, yeah, but it's...
it's tricky.
Why'd you come down here
on your own?
Attempted trespassing.
No, it's not trespassing.
It's adventure.
I was showing my wife
a fun night.
We beat cancer.
How you doing?
You look really good.
I know these pipes.
Do you mind if I take the lead?
- You know the pipes?
- I do.
I explore.
That's trespassing.
That's Penal Code 602.
We don't have time for this.
Everybody meet me
on the next level.
Yeah, I agree. It's time to
practice teamwork right now.
- Hold on, just take him in.
- Take me in?
What are you talking about?
I'm a program manager at
Universal Digital Innovations.
This fucker showed me
this place.
He picked the lock.
We broke into City Hall!
He called you guys fucking pigs.
He called all you guys
fucking pigs!
- Easy, take it easy.
- You're fucking pigs!
Let go!
I'm a bit nervous.
Nervous.
Fuck, man.
Not at all.
Hey, I think I'm a little bit
nervous too.
Nice to meet you, Jason.
Austin, Channel Three.
Okay.
I appreciate your service.
Yeah, man. No problem.
Let me ask you a question.
You mind if we get
a picture together?
- Of course.
- Yeah?
- I'll be right back.
- Alright.
This is...
this is literally
the last thing I need.
Do you have any idea
how much pressure it is
to be on morning news?
No, of course you don't.
You don't because
you're a child.
You're just a boy.
Come on, Austin.
I'm a man.
Do you know the kind
of stress I'm under?
It's cutthroat
and they're so mean to me.
Go back to nights.
I can't!
That position is filled, Jerry
Pulmas is in it, and he's good.
So I'm stuck.
Plus they made me quit my band.
They said it was a bad look.
Ah... shit, man.
You guys rock.
You could've been
a little more punk, though.
Just get outta my life.
Aw, piss!
Fuck!
Fuck.
Shit. Shit.
There. Is it good?
Is it good?
Yeah.
- What?
- Yeah.
- What? Do I...
See fellas, told you
it's him.
Let's get the selfie now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Alright. Alright.
Right over here.
Right in the middle.
Let's do this.
By the way, my mom
loves you.
She watches every day.
Aww. Tell her thank you.
I appreciate that.
Steven?
Hi.
Hello.
Replaced your mother
already, huh?
Sorry, just messing around.
Congratulations.
Any news?
Everybody's looking for her, alright.
You gonna go to school?
My mother's missing.
Are you going to work?
I have to.
You should be out there
looking for her.
Hold on.
Sorry about that.
Tammy's Florals.
Oh wow. Yeah.
She's actually never done
a bar mitzvah before.
So lemme get your
info here.
Hello?
Craig. Um...
I'm really sorry about
this Tammy situation.
I can't help but feel
some sort of blame for this.
Oh. No, it's
okay. It's alright.
So, um...
Last night is
our secret, right?
I mean I could lose it all
if that leaks out.
Yeah, man.
It's our secret.
I trust you.
- I trust you too.
- Be well.
You be well as well.
What do people want more than
anything in the whole world?
A good relationship.
So I propose,
we don't frame you
as a politician.
We frame you as a friend.
Digital applications
will make it so people
can interact with their
new friend.
You.
The trick is,
you gotta get these people...
What the fuck is it?
Uh... the trick
with these things
is you gotta give people
the illusion
of self-expression.
That's all these people have.
That is definitely, definitely
something we can build off of.
Craig, thank you.
I've also asked Ian to put
together a second pitch. Ian?
Yeah. Hey, thank you, Craig.
Great.
So... piggy-backing off that,
why don't we flip this thing
on its head?
Mayor Seth Nichols.
Superhero.
I look like a Marvel.
Like Hulk, remember him?
You wanna know
what this looks like?
Another four years.
I just had a great moment
of inspiration.
This might be it.
How about this?
Mayor Nichols.
Coward. Pig. Fuck.
Uh... his wife is missing, sir.
You only care about yourself,
you sack of shit.
You don't care about the city.
I had to go to war with the city
to put in a speed bump.
I'm gonna beat the fucking
shit out of you.
You motherfucker.
Get the fuck off me!
I'm gonna beat
the shit out of you.
- Come on, let's get him out.
- Don't pick me up, Ian.
This is embarrassing.
Do not-- watch out for my chair!
Watch out for my chair!
Ah! I'm gonna beat
the shit outta you!
Get him out!
Oh, you spilled that water.
You spilled water.
If it was you actually doing it,
I would be afraid.
But he's all like...
Craig.
Craig, get your stuff.
Right now.
I was joking around.
Craig...
...leave.
Craig Waterman.
Craig. Detective Person's here.
We found Tammy.
Is she...
alive?
- Here mom.
- Thank you.
Careful.
Blasting the heat.
It's so fucking hot in here.
What tea did Stevie
give you?
Is that, that apple berry?
It's really good right after
a bite of fudge.
I'm going to get dressed.
We have people coming
over tomorrow.
What people?
- Welcome back, Tammy.
- Welcome back, Tammy!
Oh, hey, sorry.
Is there a bathroom around?
Hey, man.
You're the husband, right?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm Craig Waterman.
This is my house.
- Cool, cool.
- The bathroom's right there.
Awesome. Thanks. Yeah.
Dude. Cool drums, man.
Oh, thank you, man. Yeah, these
things are fucking awesome.
You don't see a lot of
green drums.
You know kind of like 70's type.
'70's. That's what I was
going for. 70's vibe.
- That's a cool decade.
- Very cool.
- Got a lot of good music.
- A lot of good music.
Yeah. Economically,
could've been better.
Absolutely. Yeah.
- But we came back.
- Right.
Hey, I gotta ask you, man.
How does it feel?
Oh, to have Tammy back?
It's honestly, uh...
an incredible relief.
Yeah. How does it feel
to ditch your wife?
You can't use my fucking toilet.
You know what I would do?
I look at your wife
and I say, oh my God.
I would love to even be
a non-sexual partner with her.
You know what I mean?
In business or something.
And I would never say, hey,
come into a sewer
so I can fucking kill you.
I didn't try and kill her
in the sewer.
- It was an adventure.
- You should be dead!
You shouldn't even be alive.
You don't know me,
get the fuck outta here!
Hey! Don't do that!
Fuck you! You fucking
piece of shit!
And she's so beautiful!
- Get the fuck outta my garage!
- Fuck you!
Fuck you, you psycho!
Who are you?!
Excuse me.
Hey!
Sorry about that.
Uh... just, uh...
wanted to give a little
speech to the, um...
the guest of honor,
my wife Tammy Waterman.
When we went to those tunnels,
it was for adventure.
Most people think
getting dessert
at Spaghetti Freddy's is wild.
Well, Tammy and I do things
a little bit differently.
And, uh... this one, just...
this one got away from us.
But here we are.
On the edge of life.
And the view...
is absolutely gorgeous.
To Tammy.
Austin. Austin.
Look, I got up here.
Come on, you should get
up here if you wanna talk.
Since we're doing toasts.
Um...
Man, my heart is
overflowing with relief
that one of the brightest souls
in this dark world
is still with us.
When she was lost,
I was like a caveman
who lost his fire.
No pun intended.
This is a special woman
right here.
She's a warrior.
She's a healer.
She's a...
a mother, um...
Me and my crew was up
all night looking for her.
I'm just so lucky
that she's safe.
You know, because I don't know
what I would be without you.
To Tammy Pinto.
Uh, Tammy Waterman.
It's actually Tammy Waterman.
For 16 years.
That's my best friend.
I just wanna thank you
all so much for coming.
You are all like my family.
You're my friends, but really,
you're my family.
This has turned into a little
bit of a free for all.
Uh, if you wanna talk...
uh, please get on the chair.
And you can form
a line here
by the dips and spreads. Okay?
You know what? We should
maybe even kick it up a notch.
Let's kick it up a notch, huh?
How about a parade?
Wouldn't that be fun?
A parade for Tammy.
Come on, folks!
Come on, Tammy.
People are gonna say,
what the fuck--
Uh... my name's Patton.
Um... I just wanna get up here.
Uh, I'm like,
suddenly so nervous.
Um...
Come on, everybody!
Fucking little rats.
We're just so happy
that you made it out
and, uh... the world's
a better place.
I'll leave you guys with this.
We should still be
in Afghanistan
and I don't know why
we pulled out
in the way we did,
it was a shame.
Hey there,
and welcome back.
We are very lucky today.
He's joining us now...
Hey Stevie.
Where's your mom?
Let's take a look at
that seven-day forecast.
And... whoa!
Look at all that sun.
It is on the way.
It is absolutely on the way.
Whoa!
Did you just nut your OVD's?
Come on, Stevie.
I didn't nut my OVD's.
Take a picture,
your mom's on TV.
And that means a storm is...
Heading out.
That's right.
It's heading out.
It is heading out.
You are doing a terrific job.
I tell ya. Are we hiring?
I think we've got
a candidate right here.
- Oh no.
- Thank you,
Austin and Tammy.
Back with much more
after this.
Oh, I love this commercial.
This guy's really funny.
Hey. I got the day off.
Wanna do something?
Go to Rick's Bar?
Rick's Bar?
It's 7:30 in the morning.
And we're 16.
Oh, you can have my drums.
They're yours now.
Thank you. I gotta go
to school.
Um... You ready?
Thanks for the baked potato.
Yep.
Didn't even know you had it.
So just keep peeling
them back.
- Okay.
- As many as you'd like.
I feel so...
I'm a little nervous.
- Are you?
- I'm nervous.
It does look like
you're shaking a little bit.
Just a little bit.
I had a banana
this morning
and I'm afraid
I'm gonna overdo it.
You're too funny.
So, I just want you
to take a look
right here at this
gorgeous flower.
Wow.
Tell me... doesn't it look like
an artist painted that?
Okay, you know what?
You just gave me goosebumps.
I love how you see
the world.
You've reached
Tammy's Florals.
Leave a message and I'll get
back to you.
Hey honey, it's me again.
Craig. Craig Waterman.
Said my fucking
last name to you.
Uh... sorry. I've already
had a few boots to drink,
to be honest with you. Um...
I made us a reservation.
Under the last name Fudge.
So we're gonna have to show up
and say, uh,
we're the Fudges.
Okay. Call me at Rick's Bar.
Love ya.
Honey? Hey.
I was worried about you.
Come on, let's go to dinner.
I told you I had plans tonight.
You did?
Was that someone else?
I sent you a voicemail too.
I made us a little reservation.
I'm fine to just order in too,
if you want.
How was your day?
It was amazing.
Yeah, I saw...
I saw you chatting up
with everybody
on the idiot box.
My heart is still racing.
I met so many great people.
Austin.
So sweet.
Yeah.
You looked so good
on there.
You looked beautiful.
Oh, I think I might...
I'm think I might try
to make those biscuits I made...
tomorrow too.
You're wearing, like,
a perfume?
It's a cologne.
Huh.
Yeah, it's a cologne.
Hi.
Uh... okay.
Okay. Bye, hun.
Wrong number?
If we're gonna go to dinner,
we should probably go right now.
I have a dinner
with the TV people.
They're gonna be here
any minute.
Well, is there room
for one more?
I didn't know you were free.
Yes, I'm free.
Of course I'm free.
I'm always free.
And, you know...
you wouldn't be a big TV star
if I didn't take you
to that little cool place.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Sorry.
I...
I had an orgasm
in the sewer system.
That's great.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
That's really good.
How?
I was just, you know...
sitting there in the dark
and, uh...
I had this... realization.
And then this release.
And boom. Just, uh...
my whole, my whole body
was vibrating.
I mean...
Wow.
It wasn't as fun for me.
I just lost my phone and I got
arrested by the pigs.
You know...
that my mom never left
my narcissistic dad.
I'm not gonna let
that happen to me.
I'm gonna go stay
in Devin's pool house.
Until I can find
a place of my own.
Who?
I was able to get you
the last one.
Oh.
Did you wanna do another
Mars Rover case with that?
Yeah. Um...
I want something a little
stronger than beer.
Last time I was here,
you said you'd give me
something that's stronger.
Ramon.
I'm on break.
Come with me.
My name's Tony,
but when my hair's down,
people call me T-Boy.
What are you looking for?
I'm stuck.
I'm about to lose everything.
I can give you weed,
X, uh... shrooms.
Adderall.
Um...
Do you have, uh...
do you have ayahuasca?
Oh, no.
Uh... but I do have Toad.
Toad?
Yeah.
The Buffalo River toad.
You, uh... you lick
the psychedelic venom
that it excretes off
its rear glands.
He's similar to ayahuasca,
but the trip is way faster.
How much is the frog?
The toad. 100.
What the hell am I supposed
to feed him?
No. It's $100 for a lick, man.
I'm out of ideas, man.
Lick a toad.
Sorry, my money kinda
smells really bad
for some reason.
The bank gave it to me
and it smelled really bad.
Here. You gave me too much.
Oh.
That was sweet of you.
You ready?
I don't know.
Here's a little pillow.
Thank you.
Your mind is about
to disintegrate.
And then your consciousness
is gonna expand
to become all of infinity.
You will feel a pain
unlike anything
you've ever felt before,
followed by a bliss, which...
can't even be described.
You will die and be reborn.
I'm gonna turn off
the lights for you.
I'm gonna put on some music
and I'm gonna go get some lunch
because it's my lunch break.
You're gonna have such
an incredible journey.
I love you.
It is like ice cream
on a hot summer day.
Don't pop him.
You look like you're gonna
pop him.
Can you...
can you stay with me?
I'm sorry.
I need to go get some
Marlboros and a Red Bull.
It's time for you
to touch God.
Oh, big lick.
Was that too big?
Fuck. Was that too big?
I love you, toad boy.
It's T-Boy.
I love you T-Boy.
Hey.
I actually did a little work
for Red Bull.
They were so mean to me.
Oh, hey.
How you doing, man?
What's for lunch today?
Black Forest ham.
Perfect choice.
What kind of bread?
Let's go with...
Italian herb and cheese.
Alright.
Foot long, right?
Yes.
Usual toppings?
Foot long cookie
on the side.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Not toasted, right?
Ehh... let's be wild.
Toast it.
Okay.
Welcome back, Craig.
Is it over?
Yeah, it's over.
How long did your trip feel?
Four or five months?
It was like a minute.
I went to Subway.
The eatery? What happened?
I ordered.
Did you get the answer
you were looking for?
No, I ordered a sandwich
at Subway!
The toad is mysterious.
That frog ripped me off.
Little asshole, little fucker.
Welcome to your new life.
This is why guys
shouldn't have friends.
It'll get you in a ton
of trouble.
People need rules.
All I need are goals.
Like trying to eat the full
SEAL Team Six lunch
at Rick's Bar.
Oh my God.
I can't fucking finish
all this stuff.
It's the meal the guys ate
after they killed Osama
and buried him at sea.
It's 22,000 calories.
Yeah, eat up.
I'm Craig.
You're gonna grow up to be
a beautiful old guy.
Thank you, Steven. I hope
you're serious about that.
If you want a pal,
just have a son.
At the end of the day...
I'm a lone wolf.
I accept that.
Hey, Dad, you didn't tell them
it was my birthday, did you?
Of course not.
Did you?
Nuh-uh. No.
Okay good, 'cause you know
I hate that shit.
You know I hate
that shit.
Anyway, I'm gonna
go get a waiver.
- What's it called?
- It's an application.
Application. Like literally,
having two girlfriends
is killing me financially.
How's, uh, Devin's
and the pool house now?
Oh, I saw him, uh,
on the news.
I saw Devin on the news.
They interviewed him
'cause one of his friends
got all burnt up.
He looked good.
- Devin looked good?
- Devin looked good.
Is Dad talking about that wild
hike we went on
where he ate all those
bad mushrooms?
Oh my God!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
That just, that scared me.
It's fine.
Sir.
No, it's fine.
Sir?
You just bumped into
this young lady here
and I think you should
apologize.
Did I?
Yeah, you did.
She almost spilled her stuffed
pepper all over herself.
Can you please apologize?
I'm not scared of you.
I bought a van today.
Apologies, ma'am.
Enjoy your peppers.
Thank you.
You bought a van?
I think we gotta get
the fuck outta here.
What?
I think we gotta get the fuck
out of here.
Oh, come on.
Let's all enjoy our meals.
What the hell did I just do?
It's fine.
Oh, you motherfuckers.
You motherfuckers.
Happy birthday!
Blow it out.
Come on, we gotta go.
Craig... this is too much.
Well, you needed it
and you deserve it.
Hey Mom, do you wanna
come inside after this
and watch a movie or something?
Um...
Yeah.
Yes. Whatever you want,
birthday boy.
Cool.
Oh!
Austin got a new car.
Sick.
That is so fucking pimp.
There's lots of cars.
They must be having a party.
Oh, by the way.
This came. Um... it's
the wrong address again.
Alright.
Can you run it down to him?
I'm gonna give Ma the tour.
Oh! There's a new Marvel
we should totally rent.
I heard it's pretty crazy.
Yeah, that'd be really nice.
Craig.
I can't believe you got me
that van.
Seriously. It is... it's so...
I should've done it
a long time ago.
I wasted so much
time doing nothing.
Hey.
You been working out?
I'm just losing weight 'cause I
walk all day, every single day,
everybody screams at me.
Everybody fucking hates me.
Huh.
You look like you've been
working out.
You been working out?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah. You wanna
feel my abs?
Yeah, if that's alright.
Yeah.
Okay. I don't know
how to do it.
No, do it hard!
Oh... ouch!
This is good, right?
Well, I didn't say hit me!
Hi.
You trying to wrestle
each other?
Oh shit.
I forgot to get candles.
I gotta get candles.
We'll do presents
in five minutes.
Alright? You little
heartbreaker.
Hey, Craig.
You wanna take it for a spin?
Yeah. Hell yeah.
It's really nice having you
in the house.
I'll see you soon.
Alright, I'll be back.
♪ I get away every day
My holiday ♪
♪ I'm gettin' paid
♪ I live it up, on the go,
♪ I'm getting high,
I'm getting low ♪
♪ Kickin' off
and I lose control ♪
♪ I'm born to fly,
I want it all ♪
♪ Take off and I'm everywhere,
I'm in the air ♪
♪ I'll meet you there.
I get away every day ♪
♪ My holiday
I'm gettin' paid ♪
♪ I live it up, on the go
♪ I'm getting high.
I'm never low... ♪
Who's he?
Hey Zed!
Look at this.
We're just getting started
and I'm already double-fisting.
Hey everybody.
It's been a minute.
Craig.
You can't just
come in here.
I just came to congratulate
you on that hot rod.
That thing is pimp! My God!
Heck yeah.
Come on, why don't
we, uh...
I actually got
a new car myself.
I got a Town and Country,
midnight envy green,
gently used. It's so cool.
Let's catch up--
Hey! Snacks are going
all out tonight.
Oh, Garrett.
I've been thinking so much
about your little busty daughter
who everybody
keeps staring at.
Why are people
such bad people?
Alright.
I'll be outta your hair
in just a sec.
I just wanted to apologize
for how I acted
the last time we hung out.
I wanna say sorry to Austin
for popping you.
Making the night weird
and have to end early.
I just think it's...
a lot of stress I'm dealing
with right now
and it came out in that way,
I'm sorry.
Well, look, hey, we appreciate
that, Craig.
Honestly. Come on.
Let me show you the hot rod.
Come on.
Is it cool if I stay?
I apologized.
So that's it.
I did one strange thing
and I'm toast?
One thing.
That's it. One thing
and you throw me out.
Maybe you guys are
the bad guys. Huh?
Are you guys the bad guys?
I mean, I know you're not.
But can you give me
a second chance?
Give me a second chance.
Get to know me.
Ask me something.
Alright, come on. Let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on! Ask me something.
Whoa, whoa!
Get to know me, come on!
Get to know me!
Ask me something!
I got great "would you rathers"!
Don't I, Austin?!
Would you rathers?
Would you rather, like...
Would you rather, uh,
do stand up
for one whole year
just for your dad
or would you rather fucking...
I don't know.
I can't think of anything!
I'm too nervous!
I'm too nervous and stressed!
You.
Ask me something!
Alright, uh...
What...
what's your favorite food?
Fuck, I can't fucking
think of anything!
I'm too nervous!
Somebody else ask me!
You!
Who the hell are you?!
You guys got a new guy?
There's a new guy?!
What's your name?
Jimp. I got two twin girls.
Jim?
No, Jimp.
It's like jump...
with an I.
Jimp?
Jimp. Yeah.
I'm sorry.
This is fucking insane.
This is insane.
I'm sorry.
Should we just sing?
Let's sing.
♪ Boy, you should know that
♪ I've had you on my mind
♪ Your secret admirer
♪ I've been watching you
at night ♪
Fuck!
Everybody get the fuck
on the ground!
I'm in charge now!
I'm the one in charge!
Don't even fucking
look at me!
Keep your heads down!
I'll blow your heads off!
Keep 'em down!
Garrett, I wanna blow your
fat fucking head off!
You demand attention!
I'm sick of it!
You rich babies!
Alright, folks.
This has been a blast.
But unfortunately...
it's a school night
for your daddy.
You rats!
You called the fucking cops?!
Great hanging, Craigy.
So fun, dude.
Great to see you guys.
Great to see you, man.
Of course, of course.
I'll see you Friday night.
Yes. Yes. I'll be there.
I'll call you later.
Yeah, see ya. See ya.
Alright. Alright.
Hey.
You know how to get home, right?
I'll do my best.
Hey.
I love you, rock star.
I love you, Craigy.
♪ At night I think of you
♪ I want to be a lady maybe
♪ If the game is on
give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your love is strong
♪ I'm going to give
my all to you. ♪
♪ At night I think of you
♪ I want to be a lady maybe
♪ If the game is on
give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your love is strong
♪ I'm going to give
my all to you ♪
♪ Every day I pray
my heart can win ♪
♪ Every night I pray I can
call you my man ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ I need you
♪ I want you
♪ to have you, hold you,
squeeze you ♪
♪ So I am going now,
every weekend ♪
♪ Just to see my boo again
♪ At night I think of you
♪ I want to be a lady maybe
♪ If the game is on
give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your love is strong
♪ I'm going to give
my all to you ♪
♪ At night I think of you
♪ I want to be a lady maybe
♪ If the game is on
give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your love is strong
♪ I'm going to give
my all to you ♪
♪ These feelings
I have for you ♪
♪ That go deeper
if you can come ♪
♪ Correct with your game boy
♪ No, no
♪ No you can't be lame boy
♪ But if you can please me
♪ then my love will come easy
♪ I'll do anything you want
♪ Freak me boy
♪ I'm thinking of you
♪ At night I think of you
♪ I want to be a lady maybe
♪ If the game is on
give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your love is strong
♪ I'm going to give
my all to you ♪
♪ At night I think of you
♪ I want to be a lady maybe
♪ If the game is on
give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your love is strong
♪ I'm going to give
my all to you ♪
♪ Boy, you've got all I need
♪ From what I see
♪ And boy
♪ Every night I am constantly
thinking of you ♪
♪ At night I think of you
♪ I want to be a lady maybe
♪ If the game is on
give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your love is strong
♪ I'm going to give
my all to you ♪
♪ At night I think of you
♪ Cop killer
♪ Let's kill the cops tonight
♪ Kill every cop in sight
♪ Cop killer
♪ Let's kill the cops
tonight. ♪
♪ Cop killer
♪ Kill every cop in sight.