Previously on Dexter:
Dex.
Shoot him.
Do what you gotta do.
Oh, my God!
Whoever Deb was before
killing LaGuerta, that person is dead.
Oh, my God!
What we think is the shooter
approached the vehicle from behind.
El Sapo drew his gun.
I know you killed El Sapo.
What if I weren't here
to cover your ass?
You really wanna play
that game?
What's going on with Debra?
-It's between me and her.
-It's affecting you.
We're not going to talk about Deb.
I thought we'd make it to one minute
before you mentioned your fiancée.
I got your brother on my ass
about taking the sergeant's test.
You're on my ass about Deb.
Interior insular cortex is missing,
just like the last one.
So we have a serial.
Vogel was right.
"Lyle Sussman."
-I don't know anybody by that name.
-It doesn't mean he doesn't know you.
He was coerced.
Sussman was never a real killer.
He's just another victim.
You were wrong about me.
I destroyed Deb.
I'm a mistake.
You're exactly what you need to be.
Daddy?
Harrison?
My tummy hurts.
Harrison, did you eat
a whole box of popsicles?
Harrison.
-Why?
-Because I love them.
All right. Come on.
Drink this. It'll make you feel better.
I promise.
Good boy.
A tiny shot of pink
is all it takes to fix my son's pain.
I just wish it were that easy
to help Deb.
-What?
-Lieutenant Morgan?
Formerly known as.
Have you been drinking?
There a problem, officer?
Well, yes. You're in a car,
drunk, with an open container.
Several, actually.
Well, at least I pulled over.
I've had a really bad couple of days.
Maybe you could just
cut me some slack?
-I wish I could, but--
-But what?
There's been damage to city property.
Property damage?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm gonna need you
to get out of the car, please.
Oh, mother shit.
Is there someone I can call?
Your brother?
No, fucking don't call Dexter.
Quinn.
Yeah. I'll be right there.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Just cop stuff.
-Okay.
-I'll call you later.
Okay.
-Deb.
-I'm up.
You okay?
I feel like I got hit by a truck.
Jesus, Deb.
Oh, God, please,
just save me the lecture, okay?
My head hurts like a motherfucker.
I'm not gonna lecture you.
They book you yet?
No, not yet.
They kept me out
of the drunk tank, though.
Thank God for professional courtesy.
All right.
Let me see if I can get you out of this.
Hey. How you doing?
Can I get a little help?
What can I do for you?
Deb's had me
on such a roller coaster...
...I actually appreciate
walking into familiar territory.
Lyle Sussman's cabin.
But where's the body?
Dex? This is our guy, Sussman.
The Brain Surgeon.
Not exactly.
Did the real Brain Surgeon
restage the crime scene...
...obscuring any evidence
that Sussman's body...
...was ever hanging
from a hook in the back of his skull?
Give me a hand?
His front teeth are broken.
Looks like Sussman put this shotgun
in his mouth, and blam...
...blew his head off.
Or someone put the gun in his mouth
and pulled the trigger post-mortem.
GSR on Sussman's hands.
Maybe he finally found his conscience,
couldn't live with what he did.
No note, though.
Ah, suicide.
-Makes our lives so much easier.
-You should put that on a T-shirt.
Whoever's after Vogel
wants the cops off the case.
-Is Vogel here yet?
-I just called her.
Where the fuck is Quinn?
You can thank me later.
You still keep a stash of gum in here?
I can smell my own breath.
You sure you want to go to work...
...after spending the night
in the station?
I mean, I could take you home.
You could shower.
I keep deodorant in my desk.
Thanks for the ride.
Deb, wait.
What?
-Should I be worried?
-About what?
About you.
Think you might have a problem?
You mean like a drinking problem?
I'm just saying.
Are you serious? You, of all people...
-...accusing me of a drinking problem?
-Not accusing you of anything.
How many times have you shown up
at a crime scene smelling like booze?
A lot, okay?
Which means I've been down this road,
so I get it.
I'm not down any fucking road.
But at least when I was spinning out,
I had a reason.
-What do you mean, you had a reason?
-You, dumb-ass.
You turned down my proposal.
That was my reason.
So, what's yours?
Maybe I just don't know my own limits,
or something.
-I didn't--
-That's my boss. I gotta go.
Deb--
You might want to straighten up.
We have a new client coming in at 9.
I'm frightened. He's escalating,
and we're left to play catch-up.
I'll run tests at the lab, but I'm guessing
this tissue belongs to Sussman.
Explains why the killer
blew his head off with a shotgun...
...so nobody'd notice the pieces were
missing. What part of the brain is it?
It's the occipital lobe.
It's responsible for vision.
He's sending us a message.
He's watching us.
That, and the "His" and "Hers" boxes?
He's aware of me now, not just you.
I'm sorry, Dexter,
to have dragged you into this.
He sent both packages to you.
Maybe doesn't know how to find me.
Probably doesn't even know my name.
-Yet.
-Yeah, I know.
I need to get to him
before he gets to me.
I've been going through your book...
...and cross-referencing it with the
source files and list of suspects.
Any progress?
I managed to clear
the first two names.
So who's next?
Ron Galuzzo.
According to your files, he strangled
his best friend in high school...
...but convinced you
that it was a bully?
Yeah.
It's rare
that someone can fool me like that.
At his hearing,
I argued for leniency...
...but when I eventually got him
to admit he'd been lying...
...I reversed my recommendation.
So if Galuzzo read your book
and recognised his story--
He would've realised
that he'd been institutionalised...
...until he was 21 because of me.
That's a pretty good reason
to hold a grudge.
Dex.
Excuse me.
It's about your sister.
What about her?
She got brought in
for a DUI last night.
Shit.
I managed to get her out of it,
but still, it was pretty bad.
She asked me not to say anything
so I feel like a shit friend for telling...
...but I'm worried about her.
What the fuck's going on?
-She's been having a hard time.
-Yeah, I know.
But, man, this is, like,
a whole new level.
What are we gonna do?
I'll figure something out.
Thanks for the heads-up.
I'm putting you up for sergeant,
and you show up late?
Are you trying
to make me look like an asshole?
Sorry. I had a situation.
You want a situation?
Come to the cabin.
What is it?
It's Deb. She was brought in
for a DUI I need to check on her.
Is alcohol an issue for her?
I'm an issue for her.
She's acting this way because of me.
But you can't keep taking on your
sister's problems, especially right now.
It's my fault, okay?
Deb found out what I am.
She knows everything.
Everything?
How?
It's a long story. Just suffice to say,
she's not handling it well.
You do really feel badly, don't you?
Are you analysing me now?
-It's just so unusual.
-It's really not a good time.
Most of the time, when people think
their partner's having an affair...
...their partner's having an affair.
-But not always, right?
-No, certainly not always.
This is for you.
My assistant will explain
the retainer and payment schedule...
...and we'll get back to you
when we've found something.
So nervous.
Is that normal, to be nervous?
Well, people go through
a wide range of emotions.
I think the important thing
is finding out the truth.
Don't look at me.
I think the truth is overrated.
Call us if you have any questions,
and we'll be in touch.
Yeah.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
Well, it looks like we have to work on
our client-relation skills.
Are we done? I need a fucking nap.
No, we're not done.
I've got something for you.
What is that? A fucking shit shake?
Special custom-made
supplement formula.
It's got vitamins, some electrolytes,
a couple Chinese herbs.
-It'll knock the hangover right out.
-How do you know I'm hung over?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
It's your brother.
Awesome. Fucking awesome.
What do you want?
I heard about
what happened last night.
Fucking Quinn.
He's worried about you.
We both are.
You almost got a DUI?
I think the operative word
is "almost."
It's not a big deal.
It's a very big deal.
This is why I didn't tell you.
Knew you'd freak out.
I'm not freaking out.
I'm just trying to help.
Fuck, Dexter.
I don't have time for this, you know?
I have to find out if some asshole
is banging some chick...
...which he probably is,
so I can tell her...
...and she can get
a killer divorce settlement...
...and they can move on with
their stupid, fucking boring lives...
...and I can move on with mine.
-Because this is my life now.
-Well, it wasn't always.
How about dinner tonight?
-We can talk.
-I don't want to talk to you.
Well, I'm gonna keep showing up here
until you do.
If I agree to dinner, will you leave?
Yes.
Fine.
Great. I'll pick you up at 8.
ME's report is back from the cabin.
They've officially ruled
Lyle Sussman's death as a suicide.
So with that, the Brain Surgeon case
is officially closed.
Okay. I'll call Evelyn,
thank her for her help.
Evelyn? Someone's got
a high hard one for the good doctor.
What did I say
about standing so close?
Any progress
on that El Sapo shooting?
Still no leads. I've been going back
and forth with Fort Lauderdale P.D.
Apparently, El Sapo was a suspect
in the stabbing...
...of a smash-and-grab lowlife
by the name of Andrew Briggs.
The cops will never find out
that Deb killed El Sapo.
So right now,
I can focus on protecting Vogel...
...and myself.
Ron Galuzzo.
He could be hunting me right now.
Or he could be selling
fitness equipment at the mall.
Good work today, everyone.
Deputy chief, got a sec?
Wanted to let you know...
...I've been thinking about
what you said, finding a new sergeant.
And I've got my eye on Joey Quinn.
Quinn? No way.
-He's not sergeant material.
-He's a good cop.
He's irresponsible, unpredictable...
...not to mention unintelligible.
No way he can pass
that sergeant exam.
He'll pass.
If you say so.
-Are you getting all this?
-Yeah.
This guy's making this
way too easy for us.
Yeah, it's really fucking classy.
So tell me, who's the guy
that dropped you off this morning?
Who? Quinn?
He's a friend.
Kind of friend that drops you off
in last night's clothes?
God, we're not sleeping together,
if that's what you're implying.
Not that it's any of your business.
No judgement, no judgement.
You are certainly allowed
to be a player...
-...if you so choose.
-What makes you think I'm a player?
First there's Briggs,
then there's your new friend.
Well, he's not a new friend.
We used to date, just not anymore.
Really?
So what happened?
He proposed. I said no.
Jesus Christ.
He's certainly a better man than I am.
Woman turns down my proposal,
I'm not gonna stay friends with her.
Yeah, but that's just because
you're a giant pussy.
Yes. Could be.
Ron Galuzzo.
If he is a killer, then a mall
is the perfect watering hole...
...for him to choose his prey.
So any of our products is gonna make
you stay in the shape that you are.
And I need to do some more work,
so I'll see you a little bit later, okay?
It was dark at Sussman's cabin.
Does he recognise me?
You've got a keen eye, my friend.
The Chiseller 300.
-Top of the line.
-Or is he just trying to make a sale?
Just looking for an all-over workout,
maximise my time.
-Mind if I take a body measurement?
-Sure.
Looks like
you're already in pretty good shape.
Oh, you have
a very low fat-to-muscle ratio.
Well, thanks.
I do what I can, you know.
Yeah, this equipment
is more for beginners...
...people who don't already have
an established routine.
Does he know who I am?
Is he trying to get rid of me?
I'm just looking
to change up my workout.
I'd love any suggestions.
That baby...
...cut you up faster
than a chef at Benihaha.
-Come on, give it a try.
-Okay.
He doesn't seem to recognise me.
Careful.
Maybe a grudge against Vogel
will be harder to hide.
I like to read when I work out. Keeps
me from getting motion sickness.
This one, I can't put down.
Heard of it?
I'm not much of a reader.
You probably heard of the author.
She's pretty famous.
They call her
the Psychopath Whisperer.
Dr. Evelyn Vogel?
-Never heard of her.
-Of course he's heard of Vogel.
She treated him. He's lying.
You know, a fit guy like you...
...you need to get up to at least
level five to feel the full effect.
But why lie,
unless he has something to hide?
Yeah, I feel it.
-Yeah?
-Oh, yeah.
Don't forget to breathe.
You went to see Galuzzo?
You could have exposed us both.
It was worth the risk.
He's definitely hiding something.
So now what?
I break into his house tomorrow,
when he's at work...
...try to find evidence
that he's our man.
And in the meantime,
what if he comes for me?
Do you have any way
to protect yourself?
A gun. I haven't used it for years.
Keep it loaded
and call me if you need me.
I'm meeting Deb for dinner.
-I'll check in with you later.
-Wait. Just--
There's one thing I was wondering
about since we last spoke.
Yes?
When Harry and I
came up with the code...
...he insisted
that you only kill bad people.
And I insisted
that the first rule of the code be:
"Don't get caught."
Giving you a little wiggle room.
Okay.
So my question is this:
When your sister found out about who
you were and what you were doing...
-...why didn't you kill her?
-What?
Not that I'd advocate such a thing...
...but since Debra knew the truth
about you, she's clearly a risk--
I would never kill Debra.
She's my sister.
I love her.
What exactly do you love about her?
What do you mean?
When a psychopath
speaks about love...
...it doesn't really mean the same thing
as for typical people.
So what do you love about her?
I don't know.
I love having steaks
and beer with her...
...and until recently...
...the fact that she was always there
for me, the way she looked up to me.
But none of that
is really about Debra.
It's about what she does for you.
So you're saying I'm selfish?
I'm not criticising.
Selfless love is hard enough
for typical people.
And for psychopaths...
...it's impossible.
Why are you telling me this?
So I'll feel bad about myself?
Quite the contrary.
I want you to revel in what you are.
I told you, you're perfect.
How can you say that
when you know what I've done to Deb?
That's my point.
You're perfect as a psychopath.
All this talk about helping Debra,
and loving her...
...it's like you're Michelangelo
trying to play the banjo.
I'm trying to be a good brother.
Why don't you let me help Debra?
Because she wouldn't even listen
to you.
I'm the only one who understands her.
Dexter, you admitted
to being the cause of her pain.
How can you expect to be the solution?
I can handle Deb.
I've been doing it my entire life.
All right, next question.
Physically evasive movements to defeat
an officer's attempt to control is:
A, active aggression,
B, physical resistance...
...C, active resistance,
D, active evasion?
B, active aggression.
Okay, active aggression is actually A.
And B, it's wrong.
The answer is C, active resistance.
Wait, I'm confused.
Of course you are.
Matthews was right.
You're a fucking lost cause.
Jesus, Angel. Easy.
Yeah, Angel. Easy.
I stuck my neck out
on the line for you with Matthews.
You better not fuck this up.
Will you please cut him some slack?
He's tired from being called out
in the middle of the night on that case.
What case? There's no case.
I'm...
I'm gonna let you guys talk.
So where did you really go at 4 a.m.?
Deb was in trouble
and needed my help.
She's been going through
kind of a hard time.
And why did she call you?
Why not her brother?
I don't think they're getting along,
you know, and she's a friend.
-I couldn't say no.
-She's more than a friend.
I mean, you used to fuck her.
And now she's calling you
for everything.
What am I supposed to think?
Jamie, I swear to you, there is nothing
going on between me and Deb.
Then why lie about it?
Because I didn't think
you'd understand.
Well, you're right.
I don't.
Enjoy your dinner.
The fuck are we doing
in this hellhole?
Can I get you something to drink?
We have a wide array of cocktails.
I'll take a bourbon, neat. Thank you.
Two cokes, please.
I knew this was a mistake.
I wanted to show you something.
You see that man over there?
The father?
-Yeah.
-Does he look familiar?
Fuck if I know.
Fuck. He's wearing Kevlar.
Don't fucking move!
So what, Dex?
That was a long time ago.
Yeah, but look.
See this guy, the guy you saved?
That's him. Right there.
His little girl wouldn't have a father
if it weren't for you.
That's why I brought you
to this hellhole, to show you that.
I know you think you're a bad person
after all that happened, but you're not.
You're a good person.
You brought a lot of good to the world.
I'm fucking starving.
Have a nice day at the mall.
I realise this is not the outcome
you were hoping for...
...but it can help
with a favourable divorce settlement.
If you want,
we can forward those to your attorney.
I don't know.
You don't have to decide now.
I realise it's a lot to take in.
I mean, I don't know if that's him.
I'm sorry?
This man in the pictures,
I'm not sure that's my husband.
That's him, all right.
Look, you can see his face.
Not clearly.
The lighting isn't very good.
Mrs. Gerard, I assure you,
we're always very careful--
This was a mistake.
-Mrs. Gerard--
-I'm sorry that I wasted your time.
I'll leave a cheque at the front desk.
Is she fucking kidding?
That's obviously her husband.
She just didn't want to see it.
People get used to living in denial.
It's just easier, you know?
Galuzzo has to be the guy
we're looking for.
Why would Galuzzo be such a slob
everywhere else but here?
That's why the kitchen is so clean:
It's a kill room.
Galuzzo wasn't checking my body fat
for my own fitness.
He was checking to see
if I was fit to have as a main course.
He's definitely a butcher. But does
that make him the Brain Surgeon?
Our killer leaves bodies out...
...but Galuzzo keeps his bodies
to season and savour.
This brain is completely intact...
...marinating in some sort of...
garlic sauce.
Galuzzo wouldn't waste brains
by sending them to Vogel.
They're a delicacy. He eats them.
Which means whoever's after us
is still out there...
...and he still has the upper hand.
Fuck. He's wearing Kevlar.
Deb, what are you doing here?
I want to make an official statement.
How much have you had to drink?
One or two.
-Why don't we get some coffee?
-I don't want coffee.
I want to confess.
You want to confess to what?
I killed LaGuerta.
-You what?
-I killed LaGuer--
Why don't we go some place quiet
where we can talk?
-Fuck!
-I got you.
Take it easy.
Calm down.
What are you talking about?
I told you. I killed LaGuerta.
-That doesn't make any sense.
-It does.
On New Year's Eve, I was at Papa's.
I called dispatch to find out
where she was going.
They said she was going
to the shipping yard...
...where she met Estrada before.
So you feel guilty
that you didn't back her up.
I don't feel guilty.
I am guilty.
No, you can't let yourself
think that way.
You had no way of knowing...
-...what she was doing there.
-I did know.
I killed her.
Deb, Estrada killed LaGuerta.
We both know that.
That's not what happened.
I'll tell you what happened.
I know what happened.
The bullet that killed LaGuerta
came from Estrada's gun.
He shot first. It was a through and
through. Bullet was never recovered.
She shot back. He went down.
He got one more shot off, and that
bullet was traced to Estrada's gun.
They both died at the same time.
-That's not true.
-It is.
Remember,
Dexter walked us through it.
Dexter! Oh, fuck.
Hey.
Oh, God, Joey, you have to believe--
Okay, okay. I believe you.
I believe you. All right?
Okay.
Here, just write down everything you
remember from that night, all right?
-Okay.
-All right.
Good. Good.
-Okay.
-I'll be right back with you.
What about Arnold Gordon?
Trauma surgeon.
He definitely has the right skill set.
Motive?
He always resented
that I called him a psychopath...
...and he threatened to hurt me
if ever I told anyone that he was.
-Morgan.
-You need to get down to the station.
-I'm a little busy.
-Your sister just confessed...
-...to killing LaGuerta.
-What?
She's drunk, high, fucked up--
I put her in a room...
-...so nobody could see her.
-Make sure she stays.
-I'm on my way.
-All right.
Is everything okay?
It's Debra.
I need you to come
to the station with me.
-Has something happened?
-Yes.
I can't believe she actually confessed.
I thought I got her to see
that she's a good person.
This could have been the only way
she could relieve herself of the guilt.
Need you to help get her out of this.
Give your expert opinion
that she's having a breakdown.
Are you sure?
This could be the best thing for her.
Spending the rest of her life in prison?
-That's the last thing Deb needs.
-Or the last thing you need.
If Debra goes away,
odds are, you'll join her.
Admit it, Dexter.
You're mostly worried about yourself.
That's not true.
I told you, I love her.
Not the same way she loves you.
When Debra killed LaGuerta,
it was real, selfless love.
She sacrificed
everything she believed in for you.
Can you see that?
Your sister needs professional help.
There's nothing more you can do.
Well, I can't just give up on her.
I can't.
Dex, hey. Dr. Vogel.
She's an old friend of Deb's and Dad,
so I figured she could help.
-Is she still in the interrogation room?
-Yeah.
-Have you told anyone what she said?
-Course not. It's crazy, right?
She's going through something.
She's likely suffering
from posttraumatic stress disorder...
-...after Captain LaGuerta's death.
-She wasn't even there.
One of the most common components
is survivor's guilt...
...the belief that she could have
somehow prevented what happened.
-That's what I was telling her.
-Not an uncommon response.
We have to get her out of here.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Watch the hallway.
Deb, this is Dr. Vogel.
She was a friend of Dad's.
You can trust her. She can help.
-Hello, Debra.
-I don't give a fuck who you are.
Get the fuck out.
Debra, I know how much pain
you must be feeling.
But we need to talk about this before
you do something you might regret.
Regret?
The thing that I regret
happened six months ago.
I'm confessing everything.
I'm telling the whole fucking truth!
There's nothing you can do
to stop me!
-Deb, please, let us--
-Quinn, let me--
-That was interesting.
-Here. Hold this.
She passed out.
We must take her home to rest.
Let's get her out of here.
Is she gonna be okay?
Absolutely.
There may be some work to do,
but I promise...
...Debra's gonna get through this.
-Is there anything else you need?
-Not right now.
Thanks for calling.
You did the right thing.
What the fuck?
Are you sure she'll be all right,
with everything she has in her system?
Physically, she's fine.
It was a very low dose.
But emotionally...
This is all my fault.
Go easy on yourself.
I should have listened to you.
I thought I could fix this,
but you're right. I can't.
I don't want to just keep
making her worse.
Do you really think you can help her?
Yes.
Okay.
Go now.
Let me do what I do.
Wait.
Dexter, what are you doing?
She's gonna be pissed
when she wakes up...
-...maybe even violent.
-I can handle her.
You don't know my sister.
Thanks.
Vogel was right.
I am perfect.
But only at one thing.
You disgusting...
...cannibal.
Consumer of human flesh.
There was a time when I couldn't
imagine anyone being what you are...
...and doing what you do.
But now I realise I'm just like you.
I consume everyone I love.