(CLICKING SOUND)
(CROWD CHEERING, FAINT)
(RHYTHMIC CLICKING)
(CROWD CLAPPING IN RHYTHM)
MAN: So this is the world, and there
are almost six billion people on it.
♪♪(GUITER) When I was
a kid, there were three.
It's hard to keep up.
There. That's better.
That's america.
See, America still sets
the tone for the world.
In Indiana, Clark Hodd, 13, the
best point guard in the country.
Last week he scored
a hundred points...
in a single game.
Erica Sorgi. You'll see
her in the next olympics.
(DIVING BOARD VIBRATING)
In Seattle, Dallas Malloy, 16.
Her lawsuit helped pave the way
for women boxers everywhere.
She's picturing her ex-boyfriend
right now. (BELL DINGS)
In Indio, California, Art Stallings.
Check out what pure
joy looks like.
In Odessa, Texas, the
great Frank Cushman.
This april, 26 teams will be
falling all over themselves...
to sign him in the
next NFL draft.
He's my client, my
most important client.
When are you gonna try? When are you
gonna concentrate? You wanna be a champion?
(MAN CONTINUES) Believe me, there's genius
everywhere, but until they turn pro...
It's like popcorn in
the pan; Some pop...
What the heck, coach? You don't
know diddly-squat about golf!
MAN: Some don't.
You little shit!
I'm the guy you
don't usually see.
I'm the one
behind the scenes.
I'm the sports agent. Wayne,
I'm gonna hurt you this year.
How're you doin'?
I'm doin' fine.
Listen, door's always open if you
wanna come and get a real agent.
Thanks.
You're welcome, Johnnie.
I'm gonna go to a meeting now,
and I'm gonna talk about you.
'Cause I kill for you.
I'm an animal for you.
We gotta win super bowls.
I hail you.
Hey, Jerry, how're you doin'?
All right.
MAN: How much is
this gonna cost me?
You and I both know there's
a number you can afford.
So I'm just gonna write it down, and
we can move forward from there.
I can't afford that. No one
said winning was cheap.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
You know those photos...
where the new player holds the team
jersey and poses with the owner?
That's me on the left.
Inside that building,
that's where I work.
S.M.I... Sports
Management International.
Reebok came in
with four million.
(CONTINUES) 33 out-of-shape agents
guiding the careers of 1,685...
of the most finely
tuned athletes alive.
You gotta be tough.
I already have 18 million.
I handle the lives and
dreams of 72 clients
and get an average of
216 phone calls a day.
It's what I do.
I will not rest until I
have you holding a coke,
wearing your own shoe,
playing a sega game...
while singing your own song in
a new commercial starring you,
broadcast during the super bowl
in a game you are winning.
I will not sleep
until that happens.
It's what I do best. I'll give
you 15 minutes to call me back.
(SIREN WAILS)
I'll be honest with you.
I started noticing it a few years
ago and didn't say a word.
FEMALE REPORTER: Was
the girl 16 or 17?
In the quest for the big dollars, a lot
of little things were going wrong.
There's no proof of anything except
this guy is a sensational athlete!
There was no girl!
That's bullshit!
Are you Calvin Nack?
Can you sign my card?
I'm sorry, little fella. I can't
sign this particular brand of card.
Only pro-jam blue dot cards.
I just wanted an autograph.
Lately, it's gotten worse.
SPORTCASTER: Remo with the
puck, and... oh, he goes down!
Hi, baby.
Do you know your name?
Uh...
(WHISPERS)
Steve Remo. Uh...
WIFE: Steven Remo.
Oh, wait. It's coming.
My name is Steve Remo.
Yeah.
I play for Chicago. This
lady here is my wife.
(CHUCKLES)
Hi, baby.
And this is my boy,
and this is, uh,
Uh, uh, wait.
My agent. My agent.
I gotta play this weekend. If I play
65% of my games, I get a bonus.
I gotta get the bonus.
Okay, Jesse. You take
care, little guy.
Mr. Maguire? Yeah?
This is his fourth concussion.
Shouldn't somebody get him to stop?
(BEEPER BEEPING) It would
take a tank to stop your dad.
It would take all five Super
Trooper Vr Warriors...
To stop your dad.
Right?
Fuck you.
(CONTINUES) Who had I become?
Just another shark in a suit?
(MAN TALKING, INDISTINCT)
With the skyrocketing salaries, and
you are one of the guys responsible.
(JESSEE'S VOICE)
Fuck you.
(VOICES OVERLAPPING)
(JERRY CONTINUES) Two days later at
our corporate conference in Miami,
A breakthrough.
MAN: I already had 18 million on the table.
Breakdown? Breakthrough.
BOY: I just want an autograph.
JESSE: Fuck you.
DOCTOR: Do you
know your name?
JERRY: I couldn't
escape one simple thought.
I hated myself.
No, no, no.
Here's what it was.
I hated my place
in the world.
I had so much to say
and no one to listen.
(TYPING, BEEPS)
And then it happened.
It was the oddest,
most unexpected thing.
I began writing what they
call "A Mission Statement."
Not a memo,
a mission statement.
You know, a suggestion for
the future of our company.
A night like this doesn't
come along very often.
I seized it.
What started out as
1 page became 25.
Suddenly, I was my
father's son again.
I was remembering the simple
pleasures of this job...
How I ended up here
out of law school;
The way a stadium sounds when one of
my players performs well on the field;
The way we are meant to protect
them in health and in injury.
With so many clients, we had
forgotten what was important.
I wrote and wrote and
wrote and wrote,
And I'm not even a writer.
I was remembering even the words of
the original sports agent, my mentor,
The late, great Dicky Fox,
who said...
The key to this business
is personal relationships.
JERRY: Suddenly it was
all pretty clear.
The answer was: Fewer clients.
Less money. More attention.
Caring for them, caring for
ourselves and the games too.
Just starting our lives, really.
I'll be first to admit it. What I was
writing was somewhat touchy-feely.
I didn't care. I had lost
the ability to bullshit.
It was the me I'd
always wanted to be.
I took it in a bag to a copymat
in the middle of the night...
And printed up 110 copies.
Even the cover looked like
the catcher in the rye.
I entitled it, the things
we think and do not say:
The future of our business.
That's how you
become great, man.
Hang your balls out there.
Thanks.
Everybody got a copy.
There are dangerous animals in the world.
Some walk on two feet.
They don't want peace.
They're not capable of love.
Society... and that means you and you...
need protection from these warped minds.
♪♪(TV)
Boom.
Hi, this is Jerry Maguire.
Did those manuscripts get...
MAN: They've all gone out.
Oh, they did?
Would you like me... oh, no, no.
That's fine.
Thank you.
(PHONES RINGING) I could
connect you, if you'd like.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING, PHONE RINGING)
MAN: Front desk.
How may I help you?
All right! Hey, finally
somebody sane.
MAN: Good work, Maguire!
MAN: Yeah, yeah!
Yeah!
(CHEERING)
MAN: Unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
Oh, yeah.
(SIGHS)
JERRY: I was 35.
I'd started my life.
How long do you give him?
'Bout a week.
(CHUCKLES)
(CHEERING CONTINUES, WHOOPING)
(SIGHS)
You're with the sports people on the plane?
Yeah, I'm Jerry Maguire.
S.M.I. Bobbi Fallon, B.P.I.
I'm producing the coke
commercials for the play-offs.
Good luck with that.
(CHUCKLES)
(BABY CRYING)
Oh, hi. Hi.
My son is really allergic to
the material in the blankets,
And I was wondering...
that's all we have, okay?
(COUGHING)
(GASPS)
(COUGHING CONTINUES)
(BOTH) Ohh!
I'm sorry if I was
rude just then.
That's okay. We're
in it together now.
Why is it so easy to talk with you?
Tell me about your fiancee.
More champagne? I don't think
we're at your pitch yet.
Tell me how you proposed.
Honey, are you all right?
You want some juice
or something?
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
Thank you. But we're hiking
up through the pools.
I got the ring in my pocket, and...
(LAUGHS) I'm a little nervous.
I'm lagging, you know, and
she says to me... get this...
"Hurry up, klutz."
It bothered me
somewhat, you know?
I got quiet and she got quiet.
And I decide, I'm
not gonna propose.
The mood is not right.
Why be impulsive?
Now, at this point I
know she knows...
That I was gonna propose and
didn't, and she knows I know.
So we check back into the
pro bowl hotel. How sad.
No. But wait.
Little do I know...
That my assistant has assumed
that I've now proposed.
So she's gotten a lounge band to
actually play "Here Comes the Bride"...
When we walk back in.
I love that song.
All the football guys are
in the lobby, watching.
There's even an ESPN crew.
So I turned to her,
sort of grandly say,
"Well, this is me, klutz,
Asking you, Goddess of rock
climbing, to marry me."
I took out the ring.
You know, I don't
much like big scenes,
But, uh,
She said "yes" right
there in the lobby.
Some of the toughest men in
football wept like babies.
We're gettin' married
in February.
WOMAN: Oh, Jerry, you two
are gonna be married forever.
(BABY CRYING CONTINUES)
What's wrong, mom?
First class is
what's wrong, honey.
It used to be a better meal.
Now it's a better life.
P.A. ANNOUNCER: Mr. Waters,
Mr. Charles Waters, Ray!
Your party is waiting for you
at the information gate... Ray!
On the upper concourse.
Come on, buddy!
High five! Ray!
Oh, God. Ray! Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Jerry Maguire.
I work in your office.
I was on the junket.
I know who you are.
Dorothy Boyd in accounts.
You have the side-middle cubicle with
the poster of Albert Einstein's face...
Morphed on shaquille
O'neal's body.
That's pretty good.
Wh-what did you lose here?
My son, my mind.
(MOANS) Ray!
Ray!
- Listen, while I look... Dorothy?
- Huh?
While I go look for him, why don't you
grab this curious gentleman here?
- Hee hee!
- Oh. Oh, thank God.
Oh. Ohh!
You scared me.
Don't do that again, ever!
Okay, mommy.
Ever, ever, ever!
Okay? Ever!
Dorothy? Take care.
Thank you so much.
I loved your memo,
By the way.
- You did?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Uh, actually it was just a mission...
Statement.
I think, in this age, optimism
like that is a revolutionary act.
- You think so?
- Oh, yeah.
I appreciate that because I
didn't know if I should write it.
I mean, it was 2:00
in the morning.
I don't know. Some of the
stuff, I just... whoo!
No. That part about how we should embrace
what is still virginal in our enthusiasm...
Uh... not right now, honey.
And force open the tightly clenched fist
of commerce and give a little back...
- for the greater good?
- Uh-huh.
God, I was inspired, and I'm
an accountant, you know?
One, two, three, swing!
I mean, to respect yourself enough
to say it out loud?
To put yourself out there like
that, so openly, so nakedly?
I don't know. It got me.
Swing! Whoo!
Swing!
Is this bothering you?
- Whoo!
- No, this is, uh, great.
Whoo! Th-this is great.
One, two, three, swing!
Do you need a ride? Are you okay?
What?
- Do you need a lift?
- Oh, no.
Oh. (LAUGHING) Yeah, I'm sure
that would just make your day.
To drive us all the way
out to Manhattan beach,
making that left on
tiny Waterloo street,
Playing chicken with traffic, your
life flashing before your eyes.
I've obviously had too much
coffee, huh? (LAUGHING)
It's no problem.
Uh, um, oh,
There's my sister
Laurel to pick us up.
Thanks. Sure.
Ray,
Dorothy,
A pleasure.
Bye.
P.A. ANNOUNCER: Rachel Adams, please
pick up the white courtesy phone.
Hey, Ray. Hey, you. Hi, Aunt Laurel.
I'm double parked. Let's go.
Oh, sorry, honey.
Is this everything?
These three? Come here.
Let me see you.
Dorothy?
Man, whoever snagged him
must be some classy babe.
(PANTING)
Don't... Ever... Stop...
Fucking me!
(MOANING) Sooner or
later, I will have to stop.
Oh! Never been better!
(GRUNTS)
Never better!
(SCREAMS)
Ohh! Oh.
(SIGHS)
Open your eyes.
If you ever want me to be
with another woman for you,
I would do it.
I'm not interested in it. There was
a time, yes, it felt normal for me.
But it was a phase,
a college thing,
Like torn Levi's or
law school for you.
Want anything from the kitchen?
I'm gonna get some fruit.
(SIGHS)
I don't think we need to do the thing
where we tell each other everything.
Jerry, this is what intimacy is.
Oh, don't forget... tomorrow we
have dinner with Wade Cooksey.
I know about the bachelor party.
Your buddy dooler worked his ass
off to make you a tribute film.
All those guys from the office are coming.
Everybody loves you.
Just calm down, relax,
act surprised...
And have an amazing time.
Ohh, no!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Oh! Oh!
(ALL LAUGHING)
Oh, my God. All right.
You! You! Sorry.
Congratulations, Jerry!
- Jerry!
- Got you, man!
Ethan Valhere. Hey.
- Old college buddy, congratulations.
- Thank you.
For you. Thank you.
And this is for you,
the finest cigar...
My club has to offer.
This is what it's
all about, man.
Everybody loves you.
Pisses me off.
Whether you're country,
redneck or a freak,
Young or old,
From Moscow, London or Memphis,
(WOMAN'S VOICE) Jerry Maguire...
(NORMAL VOICE) will still be
the king of rock and roll to me.
Jerry, Jerry, Jerry.
Little black book.
When I think about Jerry,
my heart starts pounding.
Oh. I know Jerry pretty well.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING) Hi, Jerry.
Remember me?
We're still on for lunch tomorrow?
Yeah.
He was no slouch in bed.
This is the
funniest thing I've
ever seen in my life.
- You guys are crazy. I'll see you later.
- It's probably a good idea...
That Jerry get married;
He won't be alone.
He cannot be alone.
He-he can't be alone.
He's almost phobic.
Jerry is great at friendship.
He's just really
bad at intimacy.
(WOMEN'S VOICES) he can't be alone.
He can't be alone.
- He can't say "I love you."
- Are you listening, Jerry?
Lies, lies, lies. He's an agent.
He lies.
- I love you too.
- Hey, love you too.
Love you too. Love you, Jerry.
I love you, man.
(WOMAN) I love you.
♪ Got a pocketful of rainbows
- I love you.
(KISSES)
♪♪ Mr. Heartache
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
♪ I found a way to make you weep ♪♪
Good morning, Jenny. Sorry I
missed the bachelor party.
Good morning, Jerry. Marcee's already
in your office and she's late...
For her plane back to phoenix.
Thank you, Wendy.
Marcee.
Jerry, I'm glad to see you finally made it.
Rod is very, very upset.
Tyson! (CHILD ROARS))
No.
Okay, mommy.
Tyson, hello.
Hello, Jerry. Long time no see!
What did I say, Tyson? How
can I make your life better?
Jerry, this is humiliating, and I'm
pregnant and I'm incapable of bullshit.
- Where is our offer from Arizona?
- Cronin's okay for lunch?
This is one of our agents, Bob Sugar.
He needs to learn to knock. Pleasure.
You've called our house, right?
I-I'm sorry to interrupt you guys.
Now, I don't know what you
do for your four percent,
But this man, my husband,
has a whole plan, an image.
When you put him in a waterbed warehouse
commercial, you're making him common,
When you know we deserve the big four...
shoe, car, clothing line, soft drink.
I know about the four jewels of
the celebrity endorsement dollar.
Wow. I majored in marketing,
baby, and so did my husband.
We came to play.
(LOUD CRASH)
The dirty man is back!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Hey. Hey, buddy.
You okay?
Fine. What's up?
Came here to let you go.
Pardon me?
I came here to fire you, Jerry.
It's real. You should say something.
It was the funniest story.
(LAUGHING)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
GROUP: ♪ Happy birthday to you.
Oh, shit.
♪ Happy birthday to you.
A crowded restaurant, so
there won't be a scene.
♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪♪
(PEOPLE WHOOPING, CHEERING)
You... Ungrateful, unctuous...
You did this to yourself. You said "fewer
clients." you put it down on paper.
Jesus christ! What about me?
You know what I went through, knowing
I was gonna have to fire my mentor?
Carrying that around in my head for a week?
Could you get past yourself?
- You'll lose.
- You wanted smaller.
Oh, I'm over it. Now I want
all my clients and yours too.
Whatever.
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- (BUSY SIGNAL BEEPING)
(GRUNTS)
Wendy, bring me my numbers.
(PHONE BEEPING)
(RINGING)
(BUSY SIGNAL BEEPING)
(RINGS)
This is Cush.
Cush! It's Sugar.
Look, I'm calling you first'cause you're
the most important guy in sports.
I wanna know one thing: How
does that feel, to be a legend?
I just want to play football.
It's about to get better.
Dad! It's one
of the agents.
Wendy, Cushman's line is busy. You
keep calling him 'til you get through.
And please bring
me my numbers!
J.J., what's up, kid? Yeah, boy.
Have you talked to Maguire?
Homeboy had a
meltdown or something.
I wanted to tell you I
was talkin' to Doritos
about you, and they're
very interested.
Martinez. Hold on.
Talk to Rick, okay?
Martinez, hombre.
¿¿ Como esta?
Carlo, right now you're paying 25%
of your endorsements to S.M.I.
I would cut my commission
by seven percent.
I don't wanna say it was drug-induced,
but the guy completely freaked out.
You want a guy like that representing
you going into the draft?
I've said my piece.
How's your mom?
I'm gonna make this decision
easy for you, okay?
Just what does your
heart tell you?
I'm sorry to hear that.
(PHONE RINGING) I can't
believe they fired him.
He's gone.
Hey, what's going on?
They fired Jerry Maguire.
Did it at Cronin's.
S.M.I. This is Cleo.
Hey. Listen to me. S.M.I.
Represents...
I think you're making a big mistake.
That's how I feel.
I'm concerned about your
family, your future.
If you stay here, I don't
know what's gonna happen.
Jerry, I'm sorry. I have a
longstanding relationship with S.M.I.
Do you think Maguire knows what
it's like to be a black guy?
Bob Sugar? He's, uh, he's a...
He's an entertaining, funny...
He said I don't know what it's like to
be a black person? I'm Mr. Black people!
(LAUGHS) like I say, I mean,
don't make it harder than it is.
I've got to be honest with you. This
is very personally distressing for me.
I haven't seen you since we were
with that stripper in Laguna beach.
You remember her name?
I do. It was April.
That's my job... to remember the names
of scanks you bang on the road.
It's not about the money.
I do it all for you.
Hello, Merilee? This is Jerry
Maguire still holding for Katarina.
I'm talking about money. Ho!
I gotta tell you. It's been a great day.
Are you in or out? It's not show friends.
It's show business.
You are in. That's good.
He can't do shit.
Jerry, I want to cry for what
they did to you at S.M.I.
I-If we weren't right in the
middle of the acura deal,
You know I'd go with you.
Oh, Jerry! Oh, God!
(PHONE CLICKS)
Call waiting. Who could
be calling me now?
(BEEPS) Hi! Kathy Sanders.
It's still me, Kathy.
(WAILING)
(KATHY SOBBING)
(SOBBING)
Kathy! Why are you crying?
Oh. (LAUGHING)
So you're in.
Rod? Rod, Rod, Jerry Maguire.
How are you doing?
Jerry Maguire! (LAUGHING)
How am I doing? I'll tell you
how I'm doing. I'm sweating, dude!
I'm sweating my contract.
I'm sweating Bob Sugar...
Telling me I'm missing the big
endorsements by being with you.
That's how I'm doing. I'm sweating!
You know what I'm saying?
That's why I'm calling.
No, I hear that you hear what I'm sayin',
but do you truly hear what I'm sayin'?
I hear what you're
sayin', daddy.
Maybe the best thing is that
we get together in person.
Rod, I'm sorry. Would you mind holding?
I just got someone.
Didn't you tell my wife,
"more personal attention"?
Did you not tell my wife,
I said, "more personal
attention." Good!
You got eight calls. We're getting started
on my list of things you need to know!
Take notes if you want to!
I will kill for you. I will
maim, rape and pillage for you.
I am a valuable commodity!
I go across the middle!
I see a dude coming at
me, trying to kill me,
I tell myself, "get
killed, catch the ball."
Boo-ya! Touchdown! I
make miracles happen!
I need to know...
are you in or out?
I'm from Arizona, Jerry! I
broke Arizona records! Rod.
I went to Arizona state.
I'm a sun devil, man!
- You want Arizona dollars.
- Exactly!
I understand. I'm sitting
here with an ant problem.
I got ants goin' up
and down my hallway!
My brother Tee Pee's room is
flooded with... look at this!
Rod! We got a flood
in Tee Pee's room!
- Say hello to Jerry Maguire.
- Hello, brother Maguire.
H-hello, Tee Pee. Jerry,
my house is fallin' apart!
Nobody's looking out
for Rod Tidwell!
We don't know where we
gonna live in a year!
And I'm supposed to
be a superstar, man!
Rod, I need a decision from you.
Are you in or out?
You're gonna be so happy you stayed with
Bob Sugar, 'cause I am the terminator!
- I am a role model, Jerry!
- (PHONE LINES BEEPING)
I have a family to support.
Hear me?
♪♪(R & B) I wanna stay in Arizona.
I want my new contract.
But I like you. Yes,
I like you, Jerry.
My wife likes you. You're good
to my wife. ♪♪(LOUDER)
I will stay with you.
That's great. I'm very happy.
Are you listening?
Yes.
That's what I'm gonna do for you.
God bless you, Jerry.
This is what you're gonna do for me.
You listening?
Jerry? Yeah, wh-what
can I do for you, Rod?
Just tell me, what can I do for you?
It's a very personal,
Very important thing.
Hell, it's a family motto.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Wanna make sure you're ready.
Here it is.
♪♪(VOLUME DOWN)
Show me the money. Oh-ho-ho!
♪♪(VOLUME UP)
Go!♪♪
(RAPPING)
Hey! Hey!
Money!
(LAUGHING)
Jerry, doesn't that make you
feel good just to say that?
Say it with me one time, Jerry.
Show you the money.
No, you can do better than that, Jerry.
Say it with meaning, brother!
I got Bob Sugar on the other line.
I better hear you say it!
Show you the money.
Not show you! Show me the money!
Show me the money.
Yeah! Louder!
That's it, but you got to yell that shit!
Show me the money! I
need to feel you, Jerry!
Show me the money!
You better yell!
(YELLING)
Show me the money!
- Do you love this black man?
- I love this black man!
Show me the money!
I love black people!
(CONTINUES YELLING) I love black people!
- Who's your motherfucker?
- You're my motherfucker!
- What you gonna do, Jerry?
- Show me the money!
Uhh! Congratulations.
You're still my agent.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING, PHONES RINGING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(RINGING CONTINUES)
Well... don't worry.
(CHUCKLING)
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna do what you
all think I'm gonna do,
Which is just flip out!
Let me just say...
As I... ease out
of the office...
I helped build...
I'm sorry, but it's a fact!
That there is such a thing...
As manners,
A way of treating people.
These fish have manners.
In fact, they're coming with me.
I'm starting a new company, and
the fish will come with me.
You can call me sentimental.
The fish, they're
coming with me.
(WATER SLOSHING)
Come on. Come on. You come on.
Come here. How is that?
Okay.
If anybody else...
wants to come with me,
This moment will be the
moment of something real...
And fun and inspiring...
In this Godforsaken business,
And we will do it together.
Who's comin' with me?
Who's coming with me?
(MAN COUGHS)
Who's coming with me
besides flipper here?
This is embarrassing.
All right. Wendy?
- Shall we?
- Ah, jer, I'm...
I'm three months away
from the pay increase.
I...
Okay.
I will go with you.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
Dorothy Boyd, thank you.
(WHISPERING)
Right now?
Don't do it. Shh!
DOROTHY: Bye.
(WATER SLOSHING)
We'll see you all again.
Sleep tight. Bye.
JERRY: Let's see how
they do without us.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS, DOORS CLOSE)
(CHATTERING RESUMES, PHONES RINGING)
I'll just... oh. Thank you.
It's...
I know this is a bad time, but
you will have a medical program?
Oh, sure, yes. Medical.
I don't know what I...
When you think about what you
did there, don't... don't panic.
We're gonna be okay.
We're gonna be great.
We're gonna be... great.
(BELL DING, DOORS OPEN)
Yes.
(PHONE RINGING)
(BELLl DINGS)
(DOORS OPEN)
(DOORS CLOSE)
I wonder what he said.
My favorite aunt is
hearing impaired.
He just said, "you complete me."
(WOMEN CHATTERING)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
WOMAN: We've all got a problem.
We're all stuck in
some kind of pattern.
It's true. I think he was
making an excellent point.
First of all, we have come
here to support one another...
And we don't even
listen to one another.
Women are... are taught not to
see each other as good people.
We see each other
as the enemy. We're...
competition for men.
We're competition for...
It's true. We are... we have this
terrible competition going on.
I really hated women.
And then I met you guys,
and you're like me.
And it's important because I
know you can be my friends.
What about medical?
Of course, medical.
You are a single mother. You have
given up the right to be frivolous.
If you had read what he wrote, you
would have left with him too.
And I can always take
that job in San Diego.
Do you know how much those
well-child exams cost? Of course.
(BOTH) A hundred
and Fifty dollars.
- That's just when he's well.
- Wait. Where is Ray?
Asleep in the living room.
That's wonderful.
The next time you
decide to lecture me,
Don't leave my little boy in that room
with that divorced women's group.
So I finally, finally got
in touch with my anger!
(ALL CHEERING)
You go, Alice!
(CHEERING, LAUGHING CONTINUE)
What's her problem?
She quit her job today.
My God. What did I do?
Function, function, function.
Forward motion is everything.
Cush saves all.
You go to texas. You keep one
superstar, and they'll all follow.
There's no real loyalty. None.
The first person who told me
that, Jerry Maguire, was you.
I think I was trying to sleep with
you at the time. Well, it worked.
I will not let you fail.
You are Jerry ma-fucking-guire.
That's right. King of the house calls.
Master of the living room.
Okay, okay. This is working.
This is working.
You are not a loser.
Who said anything about loser?
Mistake. I meant something else.
When do you want to leave?
(AIRPLANE ENGINES ROARING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
- Matt?
- I'm in the back den, Jer.
- Hey, you like a bloody beer, Jerry?
- I'm fine.
Beer and tomato juice. Huh?
I'm fine.
Listen, I'm here today. We spent
a lot of time together, Matt.
You know how much I care
about you, your son.
You know I'm a straight shooter.
I'm quite concerned, because
if you stay with S.M.I.,
Your son... we decided
to stay with you.
(LAUGHS)
Oh.
Okay.
I'm not really a hugger, yet...
I can't let go.
(LAUGHING)
I told myself,
"he shows up, we stick with him."
(LAUGHING)
MATT: Hey!
- Hey, Jerry. How's it going?
- Hey! Cush.
How are you, Cush?
How are you?
Remember Keith? Yeah, Keith.
How're you doin'?
I want him to go number one in the
draft, and I want him to play.
It'll either be Denver or San
Diego trading up to take him.
He'll go number one.
I'll either surf or ski. I don't care.
- Denver's where he should be.
- I'll give it everything.
You know I don't do contracts.
But what you do
have is my word,
And it's stronger than oak.
♪♪("BITCH"  by ROLLING STONES)
♪ I was so... I was so tired.
♪ Can't understand it
♪ Can't...
♪ Just call me angel of the morning.
♪ Angel...
(COUNTRY)♪ She had faith
she had believers.
♪ Breakin' her heart and I'm free.
♪ And I'm free.
(SINGING ALONG)♪ Free fallin'.
(LAUGHS)
♪ Yeah, I'm free-ee-ee...
♪ Free fallin'. Whoo!
♪ Yeah, I'm free.
(PHONE RINGS)
♪ Free fallin' ♪♪
Hello?
- Dorothy? Jerry Maguire.
- Hi.
Is Avery there?
Uh, she had to fly to Atlanta.
- She had a meeting at the NFL office.
- The playhouse rocks.
Wait. Oh, God. Jerry!
Hello? Hello?
Go sit by Chad. Sorry.
That was my
son and the nanny.
What are they all doing
in our office? Nanny?
I prefer "Child Technician."
Dorothy? Hello? Yeah, I had the
calls transferred to my house...
So I could go over
some of your stuff.
That's fine. Dorothy,
we are back.
We are so very, very back.
I re-signed Cush. We're set!
I am so happy for you.
Happy for us!
Happy for us.
Okay. Happy for us.
JERRY: Rod, being at the
draft with me is a good idea.
Nobody's showing up at my house!
No, Rod, get on the plane,
Meet us at the gate. Why not?
Good. We'll see you there.
God bless you, Jerry.
Avery'll meet you at  the "B" gate
at 4:15. Don't be late.
Jerry, do you know the human
head weighs eight pounds?
Did you know that Troy Aikman, in only
six years, has passed for 16,303 yards?
Do you know bees and
dogs can smell fear?
Oh, I put Tidwell on the same
floor at the Marriott Marquis.
He doesn't smoke, does he?
I don't know.
Did you know the career record for
most hits is 4,256 by Pete Rose,
Who is not in the hall of fame?
Do you know that my next door
neighbor has three rabbits?
I can't compete with that.
Okay. So did we go over everything?
Yes? Yup.
Back on tuesday, right?
(SIGHS) Yeah.
Hey, Ray, have a
good time at school.
- Wish me luck.
- Luck!
♪ That's the way it's
gonna be little darlin'.
♪ We'll be riding on the horses yeah
♪ Way up in the sky little darlin'
♪ If you fall, I'll pick you
up, pick you up. ♪♪
Hey! Rod!
How're you doin', Jerry? Wai...
Cush! How are you, man?
Hey!
CUSH: Jerry, we should
really be sellin' these.
This is my agent. You might
want to get his autograph.
- Man, my hand's getting tired.
- Excuse me.
- Hey, what's happenin'?
- Are you hootie?
No, I am not hootie.
No, punk.
(ALL SHOUTING) Cushman, what's
it gonna be, San Diego or Denver?
Uh, surf or ski?
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
He'll either surf or ski.
FEMALE REPORTER: Go to Denver!
MALE REPORTER: San Diego!
I'll either surf or ski.
REPORTER: Cushman,
right here! Hey!
(SIGHS)
Rod, at last... I find you.
What am I doing here? I feel like
I'm five years late for the prom.
Come with me. Nobody gives a
damn about me being here.
We're gonna go downstairs and
walk through this lobby.
I want every media guy, every
player's rep, everybody...
To see you for what you are...
The best-kept secret in the NFL.
The most commanding wide
receiver in the game.
You are fast, fierce,
wildly charismatic.
You are the man. You are the man.
Are you ready?
Let's go. Let's walk.
You are the greatest, fiercest.
You are the man.
Let's do it.
Hi. How're you doing?
Tom, how's it going?
Where's Cush?
He's upstairs.
It's good you were able
to hang onto Cushman.
San Diego or Denver?
We'll know tomorrow. I want you
to meet Rod Tidwell right now.
How're you doing? 110 receptions,
1,550 yards last year.
How are you?
Meet Rod Tidwell.
What's up, man?
(VOICES OVERLAPPING)
Gentlemen, I want you to
meet Rod Tidwell. Hey!
110 receptions, 1,550 yards last year.
That's right.
Hi, Jerry.
Rod, feeling good?
Feeling great, baby.
I'm gonna talk about Rod Tidwell, who is
the fiercest wide receiver in the NFL.
Hey. Nice to meet you.
I came all that way
just to walk the lobby.
Yeah. Might have
even worked too.
Yeah? Shit, let's
do that shit again.
(GIGGLES)
Hey, hey.
They're shooting a
Reebok ad down there.
Where are my endorsements?
I didn't get no love from Chevy.
I didn't get no love from Pepsi.
I didn't even get no love from
that little energizer bunny.
I ain't getting no
love from Nike. Rod.
Obviously, I ain't getting
no love from Reebok.
Did I ever tell you about
my Reebok story? Rod.
Gotta get back to Cushman.
Oh, you gotta
get back to your
golden paycheck.
Wait just... I'll
boil it down for you.
Fuck Reebok. All they
do is ignore me.
Always have. Always have.
You know what was great
about you down there?
For five minutes you unloaded
that rather large chip...
That resides right there
on your shoulder.
You let people in. Ohh.
You were brilliant.
Brilliant? Brilliant.
Really? Now, take care.
I'll see you tomorrow.
You're lovin' me
now, aren't you?
I'm not about love. I'm about
showing you the money!
I was just testing you, Jerry!
But to hear you say that
makes me love you, baby!
You know? Jerry, come back!
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
How was your flight?
Good. How was yours?
Good.
CUSH: What size are you?
Twelve and a half. Grab a couple
pair of them new shoes by the door.
(CHUCKLES)
CUSH: ♪ It's okay to eat fish...
♪ 'Cause they haven't
got no feelings.
Cush? Matt? We have
a decision to make.
♪ Somethin' in the way.
San Diego just came in with
a last-minute scenario.
- It's big.
- Well, he's got to go number one.
He still goes number
one, but San Diego wants
to trade up with Denver
and they want him bad.
What happened to Denver?
This stuff tends to happen the night
before a draft. People get crazy.
San Diego, Matt...
(PHONE RINGS)
San Diego is crazy to the tune of 7
years for 30, signing bonus of 8.
Should I unplug the phone? Reporters.
They been callin' all night long.
Be friendly and say, "no comment."
we'll tell the world in 12 hours.
Talkin' and saying nothing, man,
it is an art I have not mastered.
Well, then let me do it.
(RINGING CONTINUES)
If it's for you,
it's a pleasure.
(LOW VOICE) This is Cush.
Hey.
It's Sugar. Is Maguire there?
Just sniff if he's there.
- (SNIFFS)
- Okay. All right, buddy, just remember.
You're swimmin' with the big boys now.
Let your dad do the talking.
I'm the one that got you
the deal you needed.
This is business, not friendship.
You gotta be strong.
You're global now, worldwide.
Okay, buddy?
I'll see you later. Bye.
(CHUCKLES)
No comment.
(HANGS UP RECIEVER)
(CHUCKLES)
He's got it all wrong.
Hey, it's Cush on the big TV again.
I'm sick of me already.
I got "Cushlash."
♪♪ Cushlash.
♪ Cushlash, cushlash
cushlash, cushlash ♪♪
(LAUGHS)
Now, Matt, before I
go back to Denver,
We should put something
down on paper.
Something that says, "Hey, I'm with
Jerry Maguire." Not right now.
Do I know everything there
is to know here, Matt?
(CHUCKLES) You fellas aren't talking
with Bob... Bob Sugar, are you?
Apparently, Denver wanted to
deal with him instead of you.
Said who? Sugar?
(CHUCKLING)
I'm learning as I go here.
So you empowered Bob Sugar to
deal with Denver behind my back?
I'm sorry. I, uh...
I love my son.
I love your son. I love your son!
I brought Denver to 20 million.
Denver deals with me all the time!
You listened to Sugar!
Bob Sugar, Matt, is a child.
You let that snake in the door?
Okay, hey, Matt. This
is a rookie mistake.
You want Denver. I'll fix
this whole thing up for you.
You didn't sign anything
with Sugar, right?
Matt...
Tell me you didn't sign.
Tell me you didn't sign,
'Cause I'm still sort of moved by your
"my word is stronger than oak" thing.
We signed an hour ago.
You were in the lobby
with the black fella.
CUSH: I'm sorry, Jerry. I
just wanna play football.
What do I do?
How do I spin this?
Oh, honey, it's spun.
What did I do to you?
It's all about you, isn't it?
Soothe me. Save me. Love me.
Could you stop moving?
I have to finish my job.
Everything is on the fucking
run with us. Everything!
Jerry, you and I are
salespeople. We sell.
It's not "Love me." It's
not "Trust my handshake."
It's "Make the sale,"
"Get it signed."
There shouldn't be
confusion about that.
Just jump right into my nightmare.
The water is warm.
So honesty is outlawed here?
I can't be honest?
I would prefer loyalty.
What was our...
...deal when we
first got together?
Brutal truth, remember?
I think you added the "Brutal."
Jerry, there is a sensitivity
thing that some people have.
I don't have it.
I don't cry at movies.
I don't gush over
babies. I don't start
celebrating christmas
five months early!
I don't tell a man who just screwed
up both our lives, "Oh, poor baby."
That's me,
for better or worse.
But I do love you.
- Avery.
- No.
It's over.
Didn't hear it.
There's something missing
here, don't you think?
- You have never been alone.
- Listen to me.
- You can't be alone.
- It's over.
No one has ever dumped me.
I'm not trying to
make history here.
I did the 23-hour nose route
to the top of El Capitan...
in 18 hours and 23 minutes.
I can make this work.
No.
Oh, Jerry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I didn't ever want to hurt you.
Oh! Ohh! Ohh!
I won't let you hurt me, Jerry.
I'm too strong for you. Loser!
Oh, fuck.
Roll with the punches.
Tomorrow's another day.
Taxi!
You lovin' me now, aren't you?
Very much. Taxi!
Is it my imagination, or
didn't we arrive in a limo?
The question I have to say is this,
and I hope this doesn't come off...
Like I'm a shrink.
(SOBS)
What's wrong?
Man, I'm just a big
disappointment.
- Look at this. Jerry.
- Can't change it.
Everybody cries on this show.
Can't change it.
You mad you tested positive?
Quit doin' blow!
Upset about your baby girl?
Why'd you leave the mother?
I knew her. She was all right.
People, like the media,
don't understand...
What kind of problems and
pressures 54 million come with.
This is some bullshit. What
are you doin' with me, Rod?
(TV)
But I'm still poor in life.
What?
JERRY: Don't you even see?
(TV)
I don't have nothing! I'm finished.
I am fucked.
Twenty-four hours
ago, man, I was hot.
Now... I'm a cautionary tale.
See this jacket I'm wearing?
You like it?
'Cause I don't need it, because
I'm cloaked in failure!
I lost the number-one draft pick
the night before the draft!
Why? Let's recap.
Because a hockey player's kid made
me feel like a superficial jerk.
I had two slices of bad pizza,
went to bed and grew a conscience!
Well, boo-fucking-hoo.
(GROANS)
I got a shelf life
of ten years, tops.
My next contract gotta
bring me dollars
that'll last me and
mine a very long time.
I'm out of this
sport in five years.
What's my family gonna live on?
Huh? (SLURPS)
What you get me. So I don't
want to hear your shit, Jerry.
I don't wanna hear
your "nah, nah, nah!"
I lost Cush, Avery and shit."
I'll have another drink, please.
Anybody else would've
left you by now.
I'm sticking with you.
I said I would.
If I got to ride your ass like zorro,
you're gonna show me the money.
You gonna show
me the money.
♪♪(HEADPHONES: JAZZ) We together
on this. Know what I'm saying?
We gonna be one. Uhh!
The both of us! You know?
Oh, my God.
(ANSWERING MACHINE) You
have no messages. (BEEPS)
(PHONE BEEPING, RINGING)
He's coming over.
- Tonight?
- He just lost his best client.
I invited the guy over.
Dorothy, this is not a
guy, it's a syndrome:
Early-midlife-hangin'...
on-to-the-bottom-rung...
Dear-God-don't--
let-me-be-alone...
I'll-call-my-newly--
long-suffering-assis-
tant-without-medical-
-for-company-syndrome.
If, knowing all that,
you still want him
to come over...
Honey, he's engaged.
And for the first time
in my professional
life I'm part of
something I believe in.
Okay. But he'd better
not be good-looking!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hi.
I'm Jerry Maguire.
Oh.
(CHUCKLES) Hello.
You are... Just the
way I pictured you.
I'm her disapproving
sister Laurel.
Honesty.
(GROANS) Mmm. Thank you.
Thank you.
(CHUCKLES)
Dorothy!
Dorothy! Your... Boss is here.
Hello.
Oh, careful.
Hey, you.
- Hi. Thanks for inviting me over.
- Sure.
Where's, uh...
Where's the little guy?
He's sleeping.
Oh, yeah. Sleeping.
I'm so glad you're home.
You know, I just... that, uh, alone
thing is not my, uh, specialty.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, yeah. Oh, my God, uh...
Well, I broke up with Avery.
(CHUCKLING)
It's just, uh...
That... gosh, you
know, that's too bad.
No, it's... it's better,
Because we're still gonna
be friends, and...
You know, it's better now than later.
Sure. Sure.
You know, I mean, I'm...
I'm dyin' here, aren't I?
Yeah, it's a really bad cut.
Well, just think if I'd got
her the ring she really wanted.
(LAUGHING)
- Yeah.
- Why don't you have a seat.
Yeah. I'll, uh...
I'll get some Aloe Vera for that cut.
(TOY SQUEAKS)
- Do you have something to drink?
- Sure.
- I heard.
- No kidding.
I looked over and saw
the shadow of two
curious shoes in the
doorway of the kitchen.
This guy would go
home with a gardening
tool right now, if
it showed interest.
Don't use those. Use
the frosted glasses.
Thank you. You're welcome.
I warmed up some of that
chicken with salsa for you.
Ohh, that's the girl I love.
I'm not gonna say
anything, just this:
You have always been very
responsible with Ray.
I don't think it's right
for him to wake up and
hear some strange man's
voice in the house.
Some drunken stranger.
Oh, as opposed to
ten angry women?
Whoa! Oww!
Lean forward.
Okay, I've got it.
Ohh. Still edible.
Change your shirt.
Everything's fine.
Hi, Jerry.
Hi, Ray.
Aren't, uh, you
supposed to be in bed?
Yeah. Yeah.
(WHISPERS) All right.
I won't tell.
The human head
weighs eight pounds.
(RINGING)
(PHONE BEEPS)
Jerry Maguire.
(RINGING CONTINUES)
I think it's this one.
ROD: You should be
dreamin' about me, baby.
My agent should be
thinking Rod Tidwell.
That's when the big
dollars are gonna flow.
That's when we truly will materialize
the "kwan." Who is this?
Who is this? You are
speaking to the Rod Tidwell.
I need to speak with my agent.
I need to be my agent.
My agent and I should be one.
Are you a football player?
Am I a football player? I'm a school
teacher about to whomp your ass!
Put Jerry Maguire on the phone!
One more thing: You don't
have the luxury of
falling for some
drowning man. Be practical.
"Practical"? High Turtleneck
sensible or Low V-Neck sexy?
Turtleneck, Turtleneck. Come on.
Don't tell me to be practical.
Do you know what other women
my age are doing right now?
They're out partying, trying to
get a man, trying to keep a man.
Not me, Laurel.
I'm trying to raise a man.
This one.
I've got a 24-hour-a-day reminder
of Roger for the rest of my life.
I've had three lovers
in four years.
That's not bad. And all of
them ran a distant second...
To a good book
and a warm bath.
Look at me, Laurel.
I'm the oldest 26-year-old
in the world.
- Now, how do I look?
- Good.
Yeah? Thanks.
ROD: Seventy-two percent of
new buyers are african-american!
I am african-american. Make
the connection. You talk too much.
No, no, no! Talking is only a
primitive form of communication!
Fun talking to you. Bye, Rod.
J-Jerry!
LAUREL: Make a sandwich.
DOROTHY: Good idea.
Ham sandwich?
I just wanna say one thing:
You do listen to me.
Well, I love you.
Mayo? Yeah.
JERRY: Oppression... As a religion.
My daddy worked for the
united way for 38 years.
You know what he said
when he retired?
"I wish they'd given me a
more comfortable chair."
38 years he sat in that...
wait, wait, wait. And then my dad died.
My mom took me to the
zoo, and I love the zoo...
No, wait, wait, 'cause I wanna
tell you more about my dad.
No, let's go to the zoo.
(SIGHS) Okay. Okay.
No, you're right.
I don't know, it's just my whole life
I've been trying to talk, I mean...
Really talk.
But no one wants to listen to me.
You know that feeling?
They just look at you...
let's go right now. Let's go to the zoo.
Ray, the zoo, you know...
The fuckin' zoo's
closed, Ray, I mean...
(WHISPERS) You said "fuck."
Yeah, I did. I, uh... is that...
I won't tell.
Well...
Now I'm gonna have to
take you to the zoo.
(PLATES CLATTERING, LAUREL, DOROTHY CHATTERING)
I gotta go to bed.
My mom's coming. I gotta go to bed.
W-wait...
(CHATTERING CONTINUES) I hear my mom.
I gotta go to bed.
Hey, thanks for listening. Sure.
Whew. Okay.
Drinks, food, and I
called you a cab.
Good idea.
And we should keep our voices down.
I have a little boy asleep.
Right.
Our company.
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Look, uh, a little, uh,
A little speech before I go.
Do... Not... Worry...
About your future.
You and your son...
We... are just fine.
You still have a job.
But let me tell you something...
About Jerry Maguire, okay?
You come after me, and you...
will... Lose.
You know, because
I am a survivor.
I'm a survivor.
Dorothy Boyd, you are
with the lord...
of the living room,
The, the king of the kingdome,
And I... Am...
Drunk.
We meet again.
(GURGLING)
(SIGHS)
Here.
The truth?
Sure.
I care about the job,
Of course,
But mostly I just
wanna be inspired.
Me too.
What you wrote inspired me.
Ohh... no, no, no. No, hey.
I'm working with you
because of that memo.
I loved that memo.
It was a mission statement.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Well...
(SNICKERS)
Sorry about the hand.
Huh?
Do you know that feeling, uh,
You're not...
(GRUNTS)
Completely embarrassed yet,
But you glimpse
tomorrow's embarrassment?
Don't worry about it, boss.
Oh, shit. You said "boss."
Yeah, I did. Now I
feel like Clarence Thomas.
No, don't feel like
Clarence Thomas.
No, no, I do. I feel
like Clarence Thomas.
I'm, like, harassing
you right now.
Well, I may not sue.
(LAUGHS)
- Good evening.
Look, don't worry, okay?
I mean, don't...
We're gonna be okay, because I
am gonna take my one client...
And we are gonna go...
All the way.
'Cause, hey,
I'm back.
(ENGINE STARTS) D... Don't worry.
(LAUGHS)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(MAN SHOUTING) Frisco! Razor! Razor!
(CONTINUES SHOUTING, INDISTINCT)
Hut! Hut!
(GRUNTING, YELLING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
JERRY: Way to go! Good catch!
Good catch.
ROD: Hey, man, you can't...
(MEN CHATTERING)
MAN: All right! Good job! Good job!
We gotta talk about
his contract, Dennis.
Meet me at the
Crocodile, 8:00.
You bet.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Thank you.
JERRY: Tell me you got
lost last night, because
I know you wouldn't
do that to a friend.
Something came up.
Yeah, well, it's okay.
Ten million dollars
for four years.
It's early. You're still dreamin'.
Ten for four, it's a deal.
Look, the guy's got
an attitude problem.
- I can help you with that. He listens to me.
- He's a shrimp.
"Shrimp"? Rod Tidwell broke every
receiving record you had last year.
I want a prototypical wide receiver,
Jerry... somebody who's 6'3, 220,
Not some guy who's 5'10 and
bitches in the locker room.
Dennis, I'm asking you...
For a favor.
I introduced you
to your wife.
We've spent Christmases
together, holiday cheer.
(CHUCKLES) Dennis...
Jerry, you're reachin'.
I-I'm asking you for a favor!
Don't do this to me. We
have history, Dennis.
Oh, yeah, we got history,
all right, Jerry.
You drove the prices
up on me for years.
It's your turn to spend some
time at the back of the line.
No, no, no, dennis, don't...
(SIGHS)
I started talking with Dennis Wilburn
about your renegotiation this morning.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
Talking?
Jerry Rice.
Andre Reed.
Chris Carter. I smoke
all these fools!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yet they are
makin' the big, sweet dollar.
They are makin' the kwan.
And you're talking.
"Kwan." that's your word?
Hell, yeah, that's my word.
You know, some dudes might have the
coin, but they'll never have the kwan.
Wh-what is... it means love,respect,
community and the dollars too.
The entire package.
The... Kwan.
Great word.
- Towel?
- No, I air dry.
Uh, listen, Rod.
I-I say this with great
respect for you,
But those players
you mentioned, Rod,
They're marquee players,
and this deal, we're...
Y-you know, we...
m-m-marquee?
Here's what I'm saying.
This is a renegotiation.
We want more, so let's give them more.
Let's show them your pure joy of the game.
Let's bury the attitude a little
bit and show them...Wait.
- You're tellin' me to dance.
- No.
I'm saying to get back to the guy who
first started playing this game.
Remember way back when,
when you were a kid?
It wasn't just about
the money, was it?
Was it?
Do your job.
Don't you tell me to dance!
Fine.
Hey. Hey! Fine!
I am an athlete!
I am not an entertainer!
- Fine!
- These are the ABC's of me, baby!
I do not dance, and I do not start
preseason without a contract.
Fine, fine! Fine!
Jerry, talk to me. Breathe.
Breathe, Jerry.
I am out here for you.
You don't know what it's like
to be me out here for you.
It is an up-at-dawn,
pride-swallowing siege...
That I will never fully
tell you about. Okay?
Just, God, help me.
Help me, Rod.
Help me help you.
I'm sorry.
You are hangin' on by
a very thin thread.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
And I dig that about you!
(GIGGLING) No contract?
"Help me, help me, help me!"
That's my... that's my man!
Hey, I'm happy to entertain you.
"Help me! Help me!"
(LAUGHS)
I'll see you in Los Angeles.
Jerry! Come on, man!
Hey! See, that's the
difference between us.
You think we're fightin', and I
think we're finally talkin'!
Unless you love everybody,
you can't sell anybody.
Dennis Wilburn called
from Arizona...
To say he's faxing in the new offer
for Tidwell on thursday morning.
He said you'd
be happy. Glad.
Well, did he say
"happy" or "glad"?
Glad. He said
glad. Glad.
Glad's good. Yeah.
Glad's good. Yeah, we could
sure use that commission.
Here, I did a rundown on
where you stand financially.
Well, I sunk most of what I had into
this condo, you don't have to explain.
Which devalued and...
Look, the other night,
uh... I want to apologize.
Yeah. What happened there?
We're two people working together.
We can't have atmosphere.
No, I'm really relieved
you said that.
The other night I was lonely...
And I felt you
understood something.
But look, we've got a company
to think about here. Yes.
I will never take advantage
of you in that way again.
Good. You walked out on a job for
me, and this is how I repay you?
Can this be right?
Exactly.
I know this is one of
those times when you
need to be alone with
your thoughts...
And think about everything that's gone
wrong and how to fix it and, you know,
Just be alone.
Alone. Alone,
alone, alone.
Alone.
- You wanna go out to dinner?
- I know a great place.
The guy's an utter
loser so I broke up
with him, and then he
started stalking me.
What's the current
definition of stalking?
WOMAN: Coming over uninvited.
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
"Coming over uninvited." So, like,
Romeo under the balcony is a stalker?
Exactly. Oh, stop.
What?
(WOMEN EXCLAIMING, CHATTERING)
I love guys like that. I would
date somebody that way.
I would too. I would date
anybody, for that matter.
He's always just coming
over uninvited... excuse me.
Ladies? Ladies?
(CHATTERING QUIETS)
Good evening, I... I'm
looking for Dorothy Boyd.
She's in the kitchen.
Laurel. Jerry. Hi.
Where you takin'
her tonight, huh?
(CHATTERING CONTINUES, FAINT)
You're the nanny, is that...
- au pair.
- A-au pair, is it?
Yeah.
Jerry! Whoa! Ray!
- Ray.
- He likes you.
My goodness. Look, Ray, I
got some gifts for ya.
Do you like presents?
Yeah.
Good, good. All right.
Here's the Arizona Cardinals.
This is the team
that Rod plays for.
Dropping your
laundry off, Jerry?
Would you like, uh, a hat?
Steelers? For me? Wow.
Got some things, you know.
Got it in gray too.
RAY: Thanks, Jerry.
You're very welcome.
Oh, my goodness, look what
I've got here. This is an energy bar.
This will keep you up all night.
See, that's not a good idea.
I'll take that.
Yeah. Aunt Laurel'll eat that.
Hey. Looks like
you've got a fan.
Wow. That's more than a dress.
- That's an Audrey Hepburn movie.
- Yeah.
I guess I got a little
revved up at the idea
of an evening among adults.
No offense, buddy.
Jerry, did you meet Chad? Chad, Jerry.
Jerry, Chad.Yeah, we di...
Am I dressed okay?
I didn't realize...
(WOMEN CHATTERING)
Chad, don't let him
stay up too late.
Tonight I'm going to teach
Ray here about jazz.
Good. That'll put him to sleep early.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
- I wanna go too.
- Oh, no, no, sweetheart.
You stay here with Chad, okay,
and be good? Give me a kiss.
Let's go. Excuse me.
Let's go. Hmm?
Okay. Good night.
- Good night.
- Give me a hug.
(WOMEN CONTINUE CHATTERING, FAINT)
Hey!
- Go ahead. I'll meet you at the car.
- Okay.
Just forgot the keys.
No big deal.
That is the first time I have ever
seen him kiss a man just like a dad.
Wasn't that just thrilling? He must
really have been needing that.
Take it easy. Don't cry at
the beginning of a date.
Cry at the end, like I do.
You all right?
All right. Okay. Okay.
And don't be a shoulder
for him to cry on either.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Keys, keys. Oh, keys. Okay.
(SIGHS) Oh, dear.
♪ She'd let you in her house
♪ If you come knockin' late at night
♪ She'd let you in her mouth
♪ If the words you say are right
(CUSTOMERS CHATTERING, LAUGHING )
♪ If you pay the price ♪♪
Ever since you've met me,
I've been...
ble-ea-eah! Right?
(BLUBBERING)
It was laziness, you know,
my breakup with Avery.
That thing you say... "It's nobody's
fault." It's one of the great lies.
Somebody is always to blame.
You go for it like you do a job.
Work at it.
But maybe love shouldn't
be such hard work.
Yeah, yeah, maybe so.
I mean, it's not every day you say
good-bye to a woman like that.
A song for the lovers?
No, thank you. Oh, no.
No, no. We work together.
This is like an office meeting.
But thank you. Thanks.
But I know what you mean.
It wasn't like my marriage to
Roger was any good even before...
♪♪ (MARIACHI)
Before?
♪♪
Jerry. What?
Let's not tell our sad stories.
♪♪ (CONTINUES)
♪♪
I'll be back in just a second, okay?
♪♪ (ENDS)
(APPLAUSE)
♪♪
♪ I realize you're seeing someone new
No, they sting.
Let Chad catch the bee in the glass.
No, he won't hurt him.
♪♪ (CONTINUES) You've got such
a good heart, buddy. I love you.
♪ Your temperamenta I moody side
♪ The one you've always
tried to hide from me
♪ Me estoy muriendo poco
a poco frente a ti
♪ Me estas robando todo
aquello que te di ♪♪
Well, this... Would
be good night.
Good night.
I'll see you tomorrow. Big day.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Oops.
Let me fix this.
Good idea.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
I think you should not come in.
Or come in.
Depending on how you feel.
Same to you. No.
I have to go in.
(GASPS)
I live here.
All right.
I'll come in.
Good.
Are you sure we wanna do this?
Oh, hell, yes. Yeah.
(TV, INDISTINCT)
Hey. Hi.
How is he? Did he have a good night?
Yeah. He's asleep.
Good. How'd it go
with sport boy?
Still going.
All right.
Chad.
How are you?
Treat her right.
Yeah. She's, uh...
She's great.
Yeah.
And, uh,
I know this might be a bit awkward,
but, uh, I want you to use this.
Oh, look... God. Chad.
Oh, no, no, no.
This... is Miles Davis
and John Coltrane.
Stockholm, 1963.
Two masters of freedom playing at a
time before their art was corrupted...
By a zillion cocktail
lounge performers...
Who destroyed the legacy of
the only american art form:
Jazz.
I put some
mingus on there too.
No barriers,
No boundaries.
Chad, I got it.
♪♪ (TAPE DECK: JAZZ)
♪♪
♪♪ (CONTINUES)
Come here.
♪♪
(CONTINUES)
You know this is gonna
change everything.
Promise?
♪♪
(CONTINUES, TEMPO CHANGE: RAPID)
What is this music?
♪♪
(CONTINUES, FAINT)
DOROTHY: Ohhh!
(LAUGHS)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(JERRY WHISPERING)
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
♪♪ (LOUD ROCK)
I love getting up in the morning!
I clap my hands and say, "This
is gonna be a great day!"
♪♪ (CONTINUES)
Great. You really
needed to do this.
♪♪ (ELECTRONIC GUITER RIFF)
(LIQUID DRIPPING)
I'm getting him up,
so don't worry.
What?
Just waiting for the coffee.
I don't care about...
Just tell me one thing. No.
(SIGHS)
Why are you acting like that?
Because I'm worried...
That you're putting all
your faith in this guy who,
Because of the way
things are going, might
not have an emotional
marble in his head.
Laurel, please.
If I start talking...
LAUREL: You please. So what does that
make me for taking the opportunity?
LAUREL: Men are different people when
they're hanging onto the bottom rung.
Maybe I am taking advantage.
Does that make
me a bad person? Huh?
All I know is I found someone and
he was popular and charming...
And not so nice to me,
and he died, okay?
So why should I let this guy go
when everything in my body says...
That this one is the one.
Take it easy, all right? I was just
looking for a few fun details.
Oh. Well, why didn't you say so?
Well, I don't know if you're
interested in this one little detail...
Yeah. What? I was just
about to tell you...
Uh-huh?
That I love him.
I do! I love him!
And I don't care what you think.
I love him for the... for
the man he wants to be,
And I love him for the
man that he almost is.
I love him, Laurel.
I love him. I love him.
Hi, Jerry!
Act natural.
Hi.
Tell me he's not there.
He's not there.
Oh, God.
Easy, ladies, easy.
- Coffee, Jerry?
- Oh, no, thanks.
We bottom feeders, we
prefer cereal first.
RAY: Let's have apple jacks.
Apple jacks? Apple jacks, it is.
Dorothy.
♪ That's the way it's gonna be
Good morning, darling.
♪ Little darlin'
Morning.
♪ We'll be riding on the horses
What's going on, Jerry?
Well, a lot, actually.
We've got a big fax today.
♪♪ (CONTINUES)
we need this commission, buddy.
Need this commission. Milk?
Yeah.
♪ If you fall
♪ I'll pick you up pick you up ♪♪
Cheers.
That was really great
of you this morning.
Look, let's just root
for a big offer...
So we can move out of this
room and into a real office.
(GIGGLES) Yes.
Would you mind?
Thanks a lot.
Shit.
You know, it's just...
One-point-seven for three years?
Man, we owe more than that!
This is how the game is played.
Now I'm gonna go back to them.
And say what?
- "Please remove your dick from my ass"?
- Marcee.
I'm sorry, I'm just a little
pregnant right now. That's okay.
I feel like cryin', Jerry. I feel
like bustin' the room up. I know.
Rod, let's not take
this emotionally.
We're gonna roll with
this problem, okay?
What are you so calm about? What do
you mean, "roll with this problem"?
"Don't take it emotionally"?
You haven't gotten emotional enough
over this man! Well, I disagree.
Somebody get me Bob
Sugar on the phone.
Marcee.
You wanna leave me?
A lot of agents say a lot of shit.
So, what do you stand for?
You wanna leave me?
What do you stand for?
How about a little piece of
integrity in this world...
That's so full of greed
and lack of honorability
that I don't know what
to tell my son...
Except "Have a look at a guy who
isn't yelling 'show me the money'?"
You know he's broke?
He is broke and working
for you for free.
Broke. Broke, broke, broke.
I'm sorry. I'm just not as
good at the insults as she is.
- No, that was pretty good.
- No shit.
Let me show you something.
Here.
Rod, read this. Whoa,
no, no, no, no.
Jerry, I just think that...
(WHISPERING) Jerry, I
think it's important...
That came from your heart and you
shouldn't deny it. I appreciate it.
You should be proud
of that, and I
think they should read it.
ROD: Jerry.
Tell me what to do.
You tell me to eat lima
beans, I'll eat lima beans.
You tell me this is the best we
can get, this is all we can get...
"All we can get"? Marcee, please,
I'm talking with my agent.
No, no, no, no, listen. This
is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna reject
that shitty contract,
You're gonna play out your existing shitty
contract and be a free agent next year.
Come on. Hey. Hey.
Baby, this is us.
You and me. We
determine our worth.
Baby, you are a strong, proud,
surviving, splendid black man.
Marcee...
You are the shit.
Oh, baby.
(GIGGLES)
If you get injured,
you get zero.
- Won't happen. I'm strong in mind.
- That's right.
Rod...
It's a risk.
You bet on me like I bet on you.
Huh?
You know?
(LAUGHING)
My man! You know?
MARCEE: You know? Okay.
You know, baby?
Oh, you so crazy.
I love you, baby.
MARCEE: Lemme kiss that head.
Mmm.
(MUTTERING)
(MUTTERING CONTINUES) Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
(KISSING SOUNDS)
I'm gonna take that
job in San Diego.
Don't even talk about that yet.
You can't afford me.
I'll find something... no,
you can't afford me, Jerry.
I'll find something
fast for Tidwell.
I refuse to be a drain.
We'll stay afloat.
Don't leave.
Rod, get on the camel! Shoot me from
the bottom, make me look more powerful!
He's my client. Just... I-I know...
then get him on the camel!
I'm gonna get him on the camel. You
don't need a camel. You got Rod Tidwell.
It's Kammell Chevrolet. Kammell Chevrolet.
(CAMEL GROANS)
That's how I feel. Hear him? He's feelin' my pain!
(CAMEL CONTINUES GROANING)
Get on the camel! Enough. Enough.
I'm pulling him from this.
Pulling him? I'm just saying, get rid of
the camel and we can get busy with this.
An athlete of your stature, this isn't
what I had in mind. You're pulling him?
You're right. Let's bounce.
Pulling him? Then you shouldn't
have begged me to hire him!
(CAMEL GURGLING)
ROD: I know you needed
that commission,
But we ain't gonna bring Reebok to their
knees with no regional kammell ad.
Comin' through!
Excuse me, darlin'.
Can I ask you a question that's
totally unrelated to your career?
Oh, what, we gonna
be friends now?
What do you know about dating
a single mother? Plenty.
I was raised by a single mother.
Well, tell me, because
I think, after this,
She's gonna have to take
that job in San Diego.
First of all, single mothers don't date.
They've, uh...
Watch it.
Watch this thing.
They don't date. They've been
to the circus. Know what I mean?
They've been to the puppet show
and they've seen the strings.
Do you love her?
How do I know?
What do you mean?
You know when you know.
I don't want her to go. I been
hanging out at her place a lot.
Oh, wait, wait, no, wait. That
right there, that's bullshit.
You gotta be fair to her.
A single mother, man, that's a sacred
thing. You gotta have "the talk."
She loves you.
If you don't love her,
you've got to tell her.
The kid's amazing.
He... no. No.
(CHUCKLES)
I feel you. I feel you, dog.
But a real man would not shoplift
the pootie from a single mother.
I didn't shoplift the pootie.
All right.
I shoplifted the pootie.
You know, uh,
John Coltrane once said
to Miles Davis, uh...
When you say good-bye
to him, don't make a
big, dramatic thing out of it.
Just be cool.
What's meant to be, will be.
You'll still see each other.
What about me?
I'm losing the only
person that ever listens
to me, and you only
listen partially.
Quit making me laugh.
Come on. What?
You're doing the
right thing, Dorothy.
You need to start your life, and he
needs a warm body to cushion the fall.
Check out exhibit "a" on
the front lawn. Look at that.
LAUREL: I'm almost sympathetic
to the guy. Good-bye.
All right. Good-bye.
You know, I mean...
Bye.
(SNIFFLES)
Listen, you're gonna like
it in San Diego, Ray.
(SNIFFLES)
Ray?
It's gonna be great
there because, uh,
You'll make a lot
of friends and...
I'm gonna see you this
weekend, you know.
Go ahead and go.
(SNIFFLES)
(KISSES)
Are you sure you're okay
to drive this? This rig? No problem.
I'll see you this
weekend. Okay.
Get in the car.
Get in the car, Dorothy.
I'll see you in a couple of
days, and, uh... I love you.
I love you, too, you know.
What? Nothing.
I'll see you soon. Okay.
Look, um... mm-hmm.
If this weekend should
turn into next month...
And next month should turn into
whatever, don't make a joke of your life.
Go back and read what you wrote.
You're better than the rest of'em.
You're better than
the Bob Sugars.
Don't forget that.
Wait. Wait a second.
No, no. Oh, God.
I know a way we can
save on medical and rent.
Don't listen to him, Dorothy.
What if we stayed together?
What if we got married?
If I said that, would you stay?
No, no. Don't do that.
Don't say that unless...
Well, say it if you want to.
Will you marry me?
What are you thinking?
(BOTH LAUGH)
Laurel? We're
getting married.
Hmm.
MAN: Do you, Jerry
Maguire, take this woman...
To be your lawfully wedded wife?
No, no, no. Not yet.
And do you, Dorothy Boyd, take this man...
Not now, sweetheart.
To be your lawfully
wedded husband?
Almost. I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
Okay, sweetheart.
ROD: Oh, yeah.
♪ Mother, mother
MAN: Yeah!
♪ There's too many of you crying
(GUESTS CHATTERING)
♪ Brother, brother brother
♪ Far too many of you dying
♪ You know we've got to find a way
♪♪ (VOVALIZING)
♪ To bring some lovin'
♪ Here today, yeah, yeah
♪ Picket lines, sister.
♪ Brother
♪ And picket signs sister
I should go.
♪ Don't punish me through brutality
Come on, brother!
Come on and talk to me, brother!
(GRUNTS)
♪ 'Cause you can see
oh, what's goin' on
♪ What's goin' on ?
♪What's goin' on?
♪ What's goin' on?
We did it!
We sure did.
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
You fuck this up,
I'll kill you.
(GULPS)
I'm glad we had this talk.
Yeah!
MARCEE: Oh, look at them.
(VIDEO TAPE: GUESTS CHEERING)
MARCEE: Mm, she is so beautiful.
♪♪
(ORGAN)
TYSON: I just figure you
two will have lots of kids.
MARCEE: I do not believe
they have this on tape.
JERRY'S BROTHER: That's my bro.
(ROD ON TAPE)
♪ Mother, mother
See, now, I'm going to release
this to ESPN. (SINGING CONTINUES)
(MARCEE LAUGHS)
You think I'm
joking. No, no.
It's all right.
I know where you live.
♪ Far too many of you crying
You didn't have
the talk, did you?
Hmm?
(ROD ON TAPE) Hey, hey!
No.
♪ To bring some lovin'
Well, this definitely
was another way to go.
(LAUGHS) Hey, hey.
Hey, Dorothy,
come here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. And Mrs. Maguire!
(TYSON CHEERING) Yay! We're gonna
have a great season! Whoo-hoo!
(SPECTATORS SHOUTING, CHEERING)
(PLAYERS SHOUTING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Hey, Scotty.
Tidwell, four for 36.
TOM: Hey, Jerry.
JERRY: Hey, Tom.
- Jerry.
- Dennis.
He's having a good game...
So far. You bet he is.
You're going to
miss him next year.
CUSH: Everyone's been
very kind to me.
I've been fortunate
enough to slip right in.
I've got a great team behind me, and
I'm loving it. I'm loving life.
Hut!
(GRUNTING, SHOUTING)
(CHEERING, SHOUTING)
That's my mo-fo!
(EVERYONE GASPS)
Uh-uh. Come here.
Come here.
Why don't you be the first man in
your family not to use that word?
And then we'll let you live.
Now go kiss daddy.
(FRIENDS CHEERING)
Come on, now.
MARCEE: Come on, Rod!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
I saw you limping after
the first quarter. What happened?
Yeah, I dropped my...
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK)
(CLEARS THROAT) Tried to make
it on the ice. It was cold.
It was kind of slick. Twisted my ankle.
REPORTER: Thanks.
Okay. That went well. Anybody
else here worth talking to?
REPORTER: No. All right.
Let's get outta here.
How's your head?
Bubblicious.
Can you sign this?
How are you?
Hey, Rod. How're
you doin', man? Hey.
Hangin' in there. Good game.
Tough one out there.
(SIGHS)
Quarterback sucks, man.
Thanks, man.
Gonna get me killed.
Throwing high and across the middle.
I'm worried.
I'm worried the only reason I'm
getting my brains blown loose...
is' cause you weren't
asshole enough to get
me my ten million three
fuckin' months ago.
Shit.
Take care of yourself on
that field, you hear?
You're my entire client roster.
Don't I know this. Now,
go home to your wife.
What's that supposed to mean?
What are you doing here? You could've
told me this shit over the phone.
How about dedication for an answer?
Personal attention?
You don't want to go home, do you?
What are you saying?
I'm just trying to talk to you.
How's your marriage?
You know, the husband and wife thing?
How is that?
Huh?
Not everyone
has what you have.
Then why did
you get married?
I'm just asking as a friend.
You want an answer?
Loyalty. She was loyal.
I mean, you know, everything...
Grew from there.
It just... Grew from there.
That's an answer.
That's the answer.
(LAUGHING)
It's not sexy. Shit.
That's an answer. Tell
him what he's won, Bob!
A beautiful marriage!
(LAUGHING)
Shit! Well.
I'm happy to entertain
you, as always, Rod.
Shit.
I have a question for you, Rod.
Are we really friends?
Why not?
Because friends can tell
each other anything,
If we have our "friends hats" on, right?
I think so.
All right. I'll tell you why you don't
have your ten million dollars yet.
Right now, you are
a paycheck player.
You play with your
head, not your heart.
In your personal life, heart.
But when you get on the field, it's
all about what you didn't get,
Who's to blame,
who under-threw the pass,
Who's got the contract you don't,
who's not giving you your love.
You know what? That is not
what inspires people.
That is not what
inspires people.
Just shut up. Play the game.
Play it from your heart.
And you know what?
I will show you the kwan.
And that's the truth, man.
That's the truth.
Can you handle it? It's just
a question between friends.
(IMITATING ROD'S VOICE)
You know?
And when they call you shrimp,
I'm the one who defends you!
- I don't want to be friends no more.
- Fine.
And quit using that word
"kwan." that's my word!
I'll see you in L.A.
No heart.
No heart?
I'm all heart, motherfucker!
(GRUNTS)
MAN: How many
concussions has he had?
But he keeps... I don't
get no respect. This is bullshit.
Know what I'm saying?
I'm making miracles happen.
(GRUNTS) You guys, I go to see this
so-called black film the other day...
Honey, no more salt. The biggest
game of the season's coming up.
I don't want you dehydrated
for monday night football.
(RAY LAUGHING) Anyway, 20
minutes of coming attractions.
All black films, all violent.
And I'm talking about
brothers shooting brothers.
I hate you going to the movies without me.
Oh, baby. Mm.
My pieces queen.
Oh, baby.
Mm.
I hate seeing
movies without you.
(CHUCKLING)
I won't do it anymore. Okay?
Okay. Okay. I promise.
(KISSING, MOANING CONTINUE)
Another one. Mmm! Mmm!
Chi-chi-bear. Mm!
Baby! Baby!
Oh, baby. Baby.
Oh, baby. Oh! Baby!
Now? Oh, baby, baby,
baby! Baby now!
Baby?
DOROTHY: Ray, it's time to go!
- Baby. Come on.
- You got'em?
Hey, you take visa? Take it!
(CREDIT CARD HITS TABLE)
What were you thinking tonight,
watching them go through...
The entire human
emotional experience?
I was thinking, "I hope
he doesn't get injured."
I felt responsible.
Sometimes I can't tell at all what's
going on in that head of yours.
(CHUCKLES)
Uhhhh...
And I really don't
know your noises yet.
Well, when you
wonder, ask me.
Okay, I will.
I thought I just did.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) Why do you love me?
Why do you love me?
(FOOTSTEPS, DOOR OPENS)
Can I come in and watch TV?
In a minute, sweetheart.
Just for a few minutes.
(FOOTBALL GAME ON TV)
(TV: CROWD CHEERING)
(TV: COMMENTATOR, INDISTINCT)
Hang in there, okay?
He's not going anywhere.
I know. Could we talk
about something else?
I don't think so. I'm
incapable of small talk.
(CHUCKLES) But that's
why you love me, right?
I want you to know I'm
about personal attention.
This is my life. I'm available
to you 24 hours a day.
I'm in my office.
Call me anytime.
I'll be in Phoenix tomorrow for monday
night football. I can be in Indiana...
By 11:30 tuesday morning.
Just give me 20 minutes. I'm
not asking for an answer now.
Why don't you...
I'll call you tomorrow.
Just enjoy the rest of your day. Tell
Douglas I said hello, would you, please?
All right. Thank you. Same
to you, Marilee. Bye-bye.
(BEEPS)
Indiana, tuesday.
I'll be there.
(CHUCKLES)
It's my fault.
What?
It's not fair to you,
this whole thing.
Here. Tell me.
Let me help.
I took advantage of you.
The worst of it is that I'm not alone.
I did this with a kid.
I was just...
On some wild ride...
Where I thought that I was in love...
Enough...
For both of us.
I pretended that proposal
by the car was real,
And it might've just
been a hypothetical.
I did this,
And at least I can do
something about it now.
I'm not a guy who runs.
I stick.
Well, I don't need you to stick.
What do you want?
I don't know.
My soul or something?
Why not? I deserve that.
What if I'm not built that way?
I think we made a mistake.
No, no. Listen.
What if it's true? It's...
Great at friendship,
bad at intimacy.
I mean, come on, it's the theme...
of my bachelor film, for God's sake.
I know. I watched it.
I sort of... Know it by heart.
I don't like to give up.
Please, Jerry.
My need to make the
best of things...
And your need
to be responsible.
If one of us doesn't say
something about it now,
We could lose
ten years being polite.
Let's just call this next
road trip what it really is:
A nice, long break.
What about Ray?
Well, you'll be friends.
Friends?
(WHISPERS) Friends.
Of course you'll be friends.
I'll take him to the zoo.
So this break is a breakup.
That's...
Come on, Jerry. You know
this isn't easy for me.
On the surface
everything looks fine.
I've got this great guy,
And he loves my kid,
And he sure does like me a lot.
And I can't live like that.
(SNIFFLES)
It's not how I'm built.
♪ She's got a secret garden
♪ Where everything you want
(KISSES)
♪ Where everything you need
♪ will always stay
♪ a million
♪ miles away ♪♪
If this is empty,
This doesn't matter.
It was just a
mission statement.
(KISSES)
WOMAN: Put your arms out.
Let's see.
All right, let's see
what you've got here.
(SPECTATORS CHATTERING, SHOUTING)
Hey, Rod, buddy, dude. I was wondering
where you were. How's it going?
Get outta here. Go.
Where's your agent?
I don't know.
I know this is uncool to do this now,
but you belong with the big boys.
You belong with the big money. You're
fuckin' Rod Tidwell. Hey! Hey!
Get away from my guy. Hey,
Jerry, I was just hailing you.
Just go. Flee.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
This is a nice moment for you.
I'm going to let you have it.
Give me a call, Rod.
Say hi to Marcee for me.
Thanks for coming.
I missed you.
What can I say? You're all I've got.
(SPECTATORS CHEERING)
Hello again, everyone. Frank Gifford
with Al Michaels and Dan Dierdorf.
Welcome to Tempe, Arizona's
sun devil stadium...
Where the story
tonight is the Cardinals.
They are still alive
for a play-off spot.
The reason the Cardinals are alive is
the outstanding play of Rod Tidwell.
(ALL CHEERING)
That's my daddy!
Meanwhile, the Dallas
Cowboys continue to roll.
They know they're
in the play-offs...
And going in looking for a
second consecutive super bowl.
Who could've believed this?
Here's the deal.
If Arizona wins tonight and next
week, amazingly the Cardinals...
will make the play-offs for
the first time in 21 years.
Whoo! Better not mess up
for monday night football.
What'd I say? Everybody knows he gets
nervous for nationally televised games.
GIFFORD: The Cowboys continue their super
bowl mission on monday night football,
A Christmas edition.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(HORN BLOWING)
Hey, Shannon.
Hi, Jerry. Good game.
Yeah. Hey, great column this morning.
Thanks.
Fuck you, punk!
(PLAYERS GRUNTING, GROANING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Boy, guys, it's a real
bruiser out there tonight.
MICHAELS: the cardinals just refuse
to go quietly into the desert night,
As their seemingly interminable
season winds down.
Come on, guys. I'm trying
to be a little poetic here.
DIERDORF: Wax on, Al.
(GRUNTS)
Ouch! Oh, a tough
hit on Rod Tidwell.
Nothing poetic about that. I would've
taken it for the touchdown all the way.
MICHAELS: That's his
sixth catch of the night.
Split to the right. Swenson
looks that way, hits him.
It's enough for a first
down at the 19-yard line.
DIERDORF: Another savage hit
across the middle on Rod Tidwell.
GIFFORD: He took some
shot, didn't he?
GIFFORD: They are working Tidwell.
What does daddy always say?
"It looks worse than it
really is." That's right.
TEE PEE: He ain't gonna have
nothing left for next season.
Will you be quiet?
What'd I say?
Less than two minutes to play.
Dallas leading by three.
Second down and one now at
the Dallas 11-yard line.
Hut! Swenson back to pass.
A blitz! Down he goes.
(CROWD BOOING)
He's sacked for a six-yard loss.
DIERDORF: Good move coming with
the blitz, getting after swenson.
GIFFORD: Swenson's limping back.
He had too many men in that pattern.
They did not have enough
to pick up the blitz.
Listen up. Shut up!
(PLAYERS SHOUTING)
Ninety Razor, x out, on one.
Ready? (TOGETHER) Break!
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
GIFFORD: He had a chance to get rid
of it, but he had to tuck it away.
MICHAELS: From second and one,
they've now gone to third and seven.
In the waning moments of this
game, Dallas 17, Arizona 14.
- Set!
- Come on, card...
MICHAELS: Tidwell in motion,
moving back to his left now.
Play fake. Swenson protected
well, lofts one to the end zone.
Yeah!
MICHAELS: Touchdown Cardinals!
GIFFORD: What a great effort!
Did you see him go up on that ball?
DIERDORF: He held on to the football.
He's still down on the ground.
But Rod Tidwell, upside-down,
hits the ground hard...
And manages to maintain
control of the football.
GIFFORD: He's hurt too.
Yeah.
DIERDORF: He's not getting up.
- Look at the faces of these Cardinal players.
- Get up, baby.
Elation turns into concern
for their fallen teammate.
MICHAELS: Cardinal trainer
comes onto the field...
As Tidwell makes his ninth catch
of the night... Oh, my God.
And gives Arizona
the lead. Hey!
GUARD: Hey, hey, hey, hey!
(SHOUTS)
CARDINAL TRAINER #1: Rod, can you hear me?
tRAINER #2: Blink, baby.
Come on, blink. Rod.
♪♪(TV: THEME MUSIC)
♪♪
(MARCEE SOBS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
TV ANNOUNCER: Welcome back to...
Why are they going to a commercial?
Tell me what's wrong with my husband.
I told you he was too small
for the NFL. Shut up!
I got a commitment to the truth. I'm not
putting him down. I'm keeping it real.
Tee Pee, shut up!
(PHONE RINGING)
Can't you be loyal to your
brother that loves you?
Get the hell outta my house.
Get out of my house!
Get out of my house, Tee Pee! Hello?
Hold on. It's Jerry Maguire!
Punk!
Jerry? Oh, my God, Jerry,
I am freaking out.
Marcee, he's unconscious.
Jerry, Jerry... I know. Just stay calm.
Keep the phone lines open.
I will call you back. There's good
doctors on the field. Stay calm.
You have to tell me something.
I cannot stay calm. I am freaking here.
Please. You gotta stay calm. Your
family needs you to stay calm.
(MARCEE SOBS)
I know,
But my whole life
is this family,
And it does not
work without him!
DIERDORF: As we look at
it from another angle...
(DIERDORF CONTINUES)
MARCEE: Jerry, I am so sorry...
Everything that I
said about your job.
Just do whatever you can
to get Rod to me, please.
Just do whatever you can.
Please, Jerry.
(MARCEE SOBBING)
GIFFORD: At a time like this,
You just hope his family
is not watching this.
Check his neck. It could be his neck.
It could be his back.
Blink, baby! Come on, wake up!
FEMALE FAN: We love you, Rod!
(LOUD CLAP)
TRAINER #2: Rod! Rod,
can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Do you know where you are, Rod?
The trainer is still trying
to revive Rod Tidwell.
You'd love to see
some movement.
Rod.
MAN: Let's get him off the field.
Get the gurney.
No. No, no. Get the gurney.
Let's get him off the field.
No, wait, wait. Just let me
enjoy this for a minute.
DIERDORF: You're looking for
any movement out of Rod Tidwell.
Is that his head
coming up I see?
GIFFORD: He's going
to try to get up.
And he is getting up!
Oh, my God! Look at him.
Mommy, he's okay!
MARCEE: Oh, my God!
Help me.
MICHAELS: Everybody's standing
at sun devil stadium. Help me.
He's up on his feet, and the crowd
loves it. (CROWD CHEERING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(CHEERING GROWS LOUDER)
(HORN BLOWS)
(LAUGHS)
Here's a guy who most of
the season has been very
truculent with the media,
has been standoffish. Whoo!
(FRIENDS LAUGHING)
Whoo! Whoo!
(YELLING)
(DIERDORF CHUCKLING)
Rod, we're happy for you, buddy.
GIFFORD: He's gonna get a
flag on this, but who cares?
♪♪ (HORN)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
ROD: You know!
You know!
Congratulations, Jerry. Thank you.
Hell of a game.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
Bye.
Jerry. Jerry! Maguire!
I know. I know.
(PLAYERS SHOUTING, CHEERING)
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
It's Tidwell!
(CROWD SHOUTING, CHATTERING)
Rod! Rod!
(REPORTERS SHOUTING QUESTIONS SIMULTANIOUSLY)
Hey, Tidwell! Can you believe
you're in the play-offs?
ROD: Jerry. Where's Jerry?
(REPORTERS SHOUTING)
WOMAN: Hey, Rod!
WOMAN: Over here, Rod!
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(SOBBING)
We did it.
You did it.
(LAUGHING)
Why don't we have that
kind of relationship?
(PHONE RINGING)
Is that your porty or mine?
(RINGING CONTINUES)
(BEEPS)
Dorothy?
Marcee. No, no, no.
He's right here.
Marcee. She couldn't get
through on your phone. Marcee.
MAN: Rod!
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
We did it.
I love you! I love
you so much, baby!
Oh!
(SOBS) Yeah!
I love you!
(SOBS) Whoo!
(LAUGHS)
I love you, Tyson!
I love you, baby! How's the baby?
How's Kaydee?
(SOBBING, LAUGHING)
oh, I love you so much.
(LAUGHS)
No, I'm okay. You know there ain't
nothin' gonna happen to me.
I think the problem is...
Alice, you were saying earlier,
something about the biorhythms or...
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
I was saying that the
neural pathways are set.
That's why it's hard for people to change,
why behavior doesn't change often.
(WOMEN ARGUING)
- Rochelle, what's wrong?
- I'm sorry.
These stupid holidays are making
me feel more divorced, you know?
Absolutely! I mean, with the songs
and the constant chocolate-eating...
(WOMEN CHATTERING)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
You know what?
I have a confession to make.
I've listened to you all
tell a thousand sob stories,
(WOMEN MURMURING) And, well,
I've been very judgmental.
Maybe you're all correct,
you know. Men are the enemy.
Thank you. No,
they're not the enemy.
But... but... but I
still love the enemy.
Well, there you go
contradicting yourself.
She doesn't even make sense.
(ALL CHATTERING)
I mean, I've
had it up to here!
The men I know
are the enemy.
I'm not gonna say
the entire group of...
Hello. Hello.
(ARGUING QUIETS)
I'm looking for my wife.
Wait. Okay.
Okay.
If this is where
it has to happen,
Then this...
Is where it has to happen.
I'm not letting you get rid of me.
How about that?
This used to be my specialty.
I was good in the living room. They send
me in there, and... I'd do it alone.
And now, I just...
(WHISPERS) I don't know.
(SIGHS)
But tonight,
Our little project,
our company,
Had a very big night.
A very, very big night.
But it wasn't complete.
It wasn't nearly close...
To being in the same
vicinity as complete,
because I couldn't
share it with you.
I couldn't hear your voice...
or laugh about it with you.
I miss my...
I miss my wife.
We live in a cynical
world, a cynical... world,
And we work in a business
of tough competitors.
I love you.
You...
Complete me.
I'm not just...
Shut up.
Just shut up.
You had me at "hello."
(SOBS)
Oh!
WOMEN: Aw.
This is the best talking group
I've been in. (WOMEN CHATTERING)
Your father leaves
home on Christmas eve,
Leaves your family all alone;
Had a mother who had to sweep
out the steps at a prison...
To earn enough money
for tuition for you.
Your brother loses a leg in
a bass fishing accident.
There's been a horrific list of
things that have happened to you.
I'm not gonna cry, Roy.
Actually, we have some good news for you.
This has just been handed to me.
A memo, it's signed. It's
a contract guarantee:
"Arizona Cardinals, four years,
$11.2 million."
You're going to get to play in
Arizona, where it all started.
What do you think of that?
(EXHALES)
(WHISPERS)
Oh, my God.
(LAUGHS)
Whoo!
(LAUGHING)
I love everybody!
(SOBBING)
I love my wife!
Whoo, Marcee!
Baby, I love you.
I love my kids...
Tyson, my baby...
my new baby Kaydee...
My older brother who's got one
leg but he's still doing it,
And my younger
brother Tee Pee.
You're militant, but I ain't mad at you.
I got nothing but love for you!
I love my teammates. I'm leaving
somebody out here, Roy.
We only have a half-hour.
I wanna send some beautiful love
out to my offensive line... Jerry.
Hey. Nice to see you. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Good for you. Thank you.
How are you, Lee?
Jerry, how're you doin'? Remember
Troy from the super bowl party?
I sure do. We met in'93.
Hi, Jerry.
I enjoyed your memo.
Thank you. Thank you.
You're a little slow,
but you come around!
We're almost out of time...
wait, w-w-wait!
I'm forgetting somebody.
Jerry Maguire,
My agent.
You are my ambassador
of kwan, man.
Rod, thank you so much.
(ROD SOBBING)
Congratulations. We'll be right back.
(SOBBING, MUTTERING)
RAY: Whoo!
How'd you like the zoo,
buddy? Swing!
It was great!
One, two, three, swing!
MAN: Yeah!
BOYS: Hey, kid,
throw the ball!
Come on! Come on!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Throw the ball!
Whoa!
BOYS: Good throw, man!
Nice throw! Yeah.
Did you see?
Oh, no.
(CHUCKLING) Let's go.
JERRY: What? What?
DOROTHY: Nothing.
I'm not saying we're going to throw him in
the major leagues tomorrow. That's right.
But if he's got natural talent,
you're lucky you know me,
Because I know the right people that will
help develop his talent. (LAUGHING)
♪ When blackness was a virtue
and the road was full of mud
♪ I'd come in from the wilderness
a creature void of form
♪ Come in, she said I'll give
you shelter from the storm
Hey, I don't have
all the answers.
In life, to be honest, I've
failed as much as I've succeeded.
But I love my wife,
I love my life,
And I wish you my
kind of success.
♪ If I pass this way again
you can rest assured
♪ I'll always do my best for
he on that I give my word
♪ In a world of steel-eyed death
♪ And men who are
fighting to be warm
♪ Come in, she said I'll give ya
♪ Shelter from the storm
♪ Not a word was spoke between us
♪ There was no risk involved
♪ Nothing up to that point
had even been resolved
♪ Try imagining a place where
it's always safe and warm
♪ Come in, she said I'll give ya
♪ Shelter from the storm
♪ I was burned out from exhaustion
♪ Buried in the hail
♪ Poisoned in the bushes and
blown out on the trail
♪ Hunted like a crocodile
♪ Ravaged in the corn
♪ Come in, she said I'll give ya
♪ Shelter from the storm
♪ Suddenly I turned around
♪ And she was standing there
♪ With silver bracelets on her
wrists and flowers in her hair
♪ She walked up to me so gracefully
♪ And took my crown of thorns
♪ Come in, she said I'll give ya
♪ Shelter from the storm ♪♪
♪ I know the language of your laugh
♪ Tripping over circumstance
♪ I know the story of your walk
♪ I taste the sugar and the salt
♪ A taste to savor your little ways
♪ The colors that you choose
♪ To paint your day ♪♪