[whistle being blown in distance]
-[horns honking and chatter]
-[man] Yo, Tommy!
[man whistles] Hey, taxi!
-[upbeat band music playing]
-Cigars. Cigarettes.
[chatter and laughter]
[man] Hey, great idea.
Hello, New York.
I'm Bobby Rydell and I'm glad to be here!
[Bobby] Thank you all
for coming to see us tonight.
It's Saturday night at the Copa!
We think you're gonna have
a great time tonight.
We're gonna do our best
to make sure of that.
As always, a very special thanks
to Mr Jules Podell for having us out.
Let's get started.
♪ That old black magic has me
In its spell ♪
♪ That old black magic
That you, uh, weave so well ♪
♪ Those icy fingers
Up and down my spine ♪
♪ The same old witchcraft
When your eyes meet mine ♪
♪ I love them so well ♪
-♪ That same old tingle... ♪
-[woman] Cigars?
♪ That I feel inside ♪
♪ And then that elevator
Starts its ride ♪
♪ Darling... ♪
Hello, sweetheart.
Here's my coat. And you see this here hat?
I want you to guard it with your life.
It was a gift from my mother.
-Yes, Mr Loscudo.
-[Loscudo] Here, that's for you.
-Thank you, sir.
-[man] Gio!
-Hey, Carmine. How are you, pally?
-Good to see you.
-Oh, thank you. That's unnecessary.
-Come on, let's go. Andiamo.
I saw this kid, Bobby Rydell,
two and a half years ago in South Philly.
Nobody knew who he was.
[Carmine] They know him now.
Hey, give me Loscudo's hat.
-But he said to guard it.
-I know. I heard.
Give it to me, all right? Come on.
[Bobby] ♪ Yeah, I should stay away ♪
♪ But what can I do? ♪
♪ I hear your name... ♪
-Hey, be respectful, and watch your mouth.
-Shut up. She works here, tough guy.
-Yeah, what are you gonna do?
-[grunting]
-[woman screams]
-Tony Lip!
[thudding and clattering]
♪ Well, now you're the lover
I have waited for ♪
♪ You're the mate
That fate had me created for ♪
♪ And every time
your lips meet mine, yow... ♪
[grunting and groaning]
[bystanders muttering]
[man grunts]
You put your hands on me, you punk?
Do yourself a favor,
go home with your friends.
You don't tell me where to go.
You know who I am?
I'm going back in there.
-[grunting]
-[onlookers gasp]
♪ Under that old black magic
called love ♪
♪ Keep talking about
That black old magic ♪
♪ Yeah, baby, cos I love, oh, yeah
Love that thing ♪
♪ Old black magic ♪
♪ Yeah, love ♪
[cheering and applause]
You tell Juley Podell,
if I don't get my hat,
I'm gonna burn this joint down! Hear me?
Joe, it's gonna turn up.
I swear it'll turn up.
-Really? You tell that fat Jew bastard...
-It'll turn up.
I don't get my hat,
I'll burn the Copa down!
I'm gonna have to go back
to driving garbage trucks.
Jesus Christ. Loscudo's out of his mind.
-Mm-hm.
-We earned our money tonight.
Lip, I thought
you were gonna kill that guy.
-Yeah.
-Better him than me.
So what are you gonna do
while we're closed?
I don't know.
Maybe go work at my uncle's pizza joint.
-You?
-I'm gonna drink for two months.
-[door squeaking open]
-[Tony chuckles]
-Take me home, Lip.
-Hey, good luck.
-You, too.
-See you, Carmine.
-No, that should not happen. Well...
-No, I don't want to be a--
My hat!
Heard it was missing, so I looked into it.
I wanted to kill that broad.
-No, no. It wasn't her fault.
-Who had the balls to clip Gio's hat?
-Don't worry about it. I took care of it.
-Yeah, I hope you gave him some beating.
Here. Take this. Put it in your kick.
No, no, thanks.
It was a pleasure, Mr Loscudo, really.
Bullshit. Take it.
And from now on, you don't call me
Mr Loscudo. You hear me?
-I'm your pal Gio.
-[chuckles]
["One Mint Julep" by The Clovers]
♪ One early morning ♪
♪ As I was walking ♪
♪ I met a woman ♪
♪ We started talking ♪
♪ I took her home to get a few nips ♪
♪ But all I had was a mint julep ♪
♪ One mint julep ♪
♪ Was the cause of it all ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I don't remember just how it started ♪
-[sighs, sniffs]
-♪ But all I know is ♪
-[sighs]
-♪ We should have parted ♪
♪ I stole a kiss and then another ♪
-♪ I didn't mean to take it further ♪
-[sighs]
♪ One mint julep
Was the cause of it all ♪
♪ The lights were burning low
There in the parlor ♪
♪ When through the kitchen door
Up popped her father ♪
♪ He said I saw you when
You kissed my daughter ♪
♪ Gotta wed her right now
Or face a slaughter ♪
-♪ One mint julep ♪
-[grunts]
♪ Was the cause of it all ♪
-Morning.
-Good night. [sighs]
[TV] One down,
and the batter will be Roger Maris.
-[man] We need to get back in this.
-The pitch-curveball...
[man] Come on, Roger. Come on.
Come on, Roger, hit one out! Let's do it!
-Johnny, quiet. You're gonna jinx it.
-Come on, Roger.
Hey, Johnny. Think you could yell louder?
-Maris is up.
-Yeah, so am I now.
-What the hell all you guys doing here?
-We came over to keep Dolores company.
[commentary in background]
-Come on.
-Tony!
[in Italian]
Thank you, ma'am.
[commentary in background]
-Come on, Roger, please.
-Let's do it, baby.
-I'll walk you out.
-Sure.
-We need to get back in this ball game.
-Come on.
-Thank you so much.
-Any problems, give us a call.
-[clapping]
-Come on, Roger.
-The one-two pitch.
-Come on!
-It's hit deep into right field...
-[excited chatter]
[all cheering]
-Yes!
-We did it! We got it!
-Yeah! Whoo!
-There it is!
-All right.
-Three-one, baby.
-Coming back.
-Roger, baby, way to go!
-Three-one.
-Way to go!
[Johnny] Do it again.
Let's do it again. Come on, baby.
No, Tony. Go get dressed. We're gonna eat.
-All right.
-No game seven, no game seven.
[clinking]
[Dolores] ...from thy bounty,
through Christ, our Lord. Amen.
[others] Amen.
And if anyone hears of a job for Tony,
let us know.
-Dolor.
-What?
Please.
-What happened? You get fired?
-No.
No. The Copa's closing for repairs, so
he needs something for a couple of months.
[in Italian]
All the people he knows,
he'll find something in no time.
Well, he had a great job
at the Sanitation Department.
You shouldn't have
punched out the foreman.
-He shouldn't have woke me up.
-[laughter]
That's Tony.
I can't believe they lost.
-Don't worry.
-Relax.
[lively chatter]
That never happened before.
They're gonna win the World Series.
[chatter continues]
I'm telling you,
this is gonna be the easiest 50 bucks
-you ever gonna make.
-Yeah, we'll see.
Hey, there they are. Hi, Johnny.
-Tony, how are you?
-Hey, Paulie.
-How you doing?
-I'm good, I'm good.
So Johnny here tells me you ate 48
White Castle burgers all in one sitting.
-Cheeseburgers.
-You tell him, Frankie.
I don't believe it.
What do we care if you believe it?
Hey, Gorman.
-What's the record here for hot dogs?
-Eighteen. Fat Paulie.
-Why wasn't Lip in on that contest?
-What contest? I was hungry.
-[chuckling]
-[Gorman] The bet's simple.
Half a C-note.
Most hot dogs in an hour wins.
With toppings.
-What the hell you weigh?
-Two sixty.
Hey, two-- Your left ass weighs 260.
May my mother-in-law drop dead
on the spot if I'm lying.
[chuckling]
-All right. You're on.
-Good.
Pick it up, Lip!
The baby elephant just hit 19!
Let's go, Lip! Let's go!
Come on, let's go, Lip!
Let's get this going!
You're embarrassing!
You're embarrassing your son!
He is killing you!
[Tony groans]
Hey, Nicky, you doing your homework?
-Yep.
-Good.
-[Tony groans]
-Where you been?
-Gorman's.
-I'm making dinner.
[sighs]
Fat Paulie bet me 50 bucks
he could eat more hot dogs than me.
He knocked off 24. Guy's an animal.
Are you crazy? You lost $50?
Dolores, please.
I ate 26.
You are so lucky. You know that?
-[Tony chuckles]
-Rent is due on Monday.
-[chuckles]
-[phone ringing]
You gonna get that?
-[sighs] Yeah?
-[Jules] Hey, Lip.
Some guy called over here.
A doctor. He's looking for a driver.
-You interested?
-Yeah.
They're interviewing guys
tomorrow afternoon.
The address is, uh... 881,
7th Avenue, 2:15.
[chatter]
-Hey. Excuse me.
-We're not open right now.
But you're welcome to purchase tickets
to tonight's performance.
Nah, that's all right. I, uh...
I think I got the wrong address, but...
Is there a doctor's office in here?
-A doctor's office?
-Dr Shirley?
Oh. You have the correct address.
Dr Shirley lives upstairs, above the Hall.
[sighs] How you doing?
[clears throat]
I'm here for the driver job.
Tony Lip.
-No, I should be on there.
-Uh...
No. Um, I have
a Tony Val-- Vallelala--
Vallelonga. Yeah. That's me.
-Fill it out while you wait.
-What?
Fill it out while you wait.
-Oh. Yeah.
-[clicks fingers]
[Tony grunts]
Have a seat.
[bells chiming nearby]
-[distant door opens and closes]
-[footsteps approaching]
Mr Vallelonga.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Oh.
-[grunts]
-I'm Dr Donald Shirley.
-Tony.
-Yes. Please sit down.
[chains rattling]
Some place you got here. [chuckles]
-Are them horns real?
-Elephant tusks, yes.
What about that? Is that a molar?
-A what?
-A molar, like a, like a shark tooth.
-Or a tiger's, maybe.
-It was a gift.
I thought, uh...
I thought I was going to an office.
They said a doctor needed a driver.
That's all they told you?
-Yeah.
-[chuckles]
Actually,
it's a bit more complicated than that.
Have you ever driven
professionally before?
Yeah. Sanitation. Garbage trucks.
Plus, I drive my boss home at night.
But I can drive anything.
Limos. Tow trucks.
-Snowplows. Whatever.
-I see.
-What other experience do you have?
-I worked a lot of joints.
Wagon Wheel, Peppermint Lounge, Copa.
-In what capacity?
-What do you mean?
-What did you do there?
-Uh...
Public relations.
Well, first of all, Tony,
I'm not a medical doctor, I'm a musician.
-You mean, like, songs?
-Yes.
And I'm about to embark on a concert tour,
the majority of which will be down south.
Atlantic City.
No. The Deep South.
First, we're starting in the Midwest
and then we're taking a hard left.
Kentucky, North Carolina, Tennessee,
and on down through the Delta.
Do you foresee any issues
in working for a black man?
No.
No, no, no. It was just the other day,
me and the wife had a couple
of colored guys over at the house.
For, for drinks.
Hmm. I see. You're married.
Yeah. Two kids.
I'm not sure this is the proper job
for a married man.
Why? Are we bringing broads?
My point is
we'll be gone for eight straight weeks.
No breaks, right up until Christmas.
You're quite sure
you can leave your family for that long?
-Depends what you're paying.
-A hundred dollars a week.
-Plus room and board.
-Hmm.
But let me be crystal clear.
I'm not just hiring a chauffeur.
I need someone
who can handle my itinerary.
Be a personal assistant. I need a valet.
I need someone who can launder my clothes
and shine my shoes.
Good luck, Doc.
Tony.
I had my record label ask around town
to find me the right man.
Your name came up more than once.
You've impressed several people
with your...
innate ability to handle trouble.
And that is why I called
and enquired about your availability.
Okay, here's the deal. I got no problem
being on the road with you.
But I ain't no butler.
I ain't ironing no shirts
and I'm not polishing nobody's shoes.
You need somebody to get you
from point A to point B
and to make sure there's
no problems along the way?
And believe me, you, in the Deep South...
there's gonna be problems.
So if you want me,
it's a buck and a quarter a week.
Or go hire that little Chink just pranced
out of here, see how far you get.
Well, Mr Vallelonga...
thank you for stopping by.
["Throw It Out Of Your Mind"
by Timmy Shaw]
[chatter]
Hey, Bobby.
Give me a Rheingold. Ice cold.
-[song continues]
-[chatter]
Mr Tony.
Augie asking about you.
[slaps bar] Come on!
I'm dying of thirst over here.
Shut up! I'm talking.
-When?
-Now. He in his box.
[knocks]
Tony Lip.
What the hell happened at the Copa?
I hear you almost split a guy's face open.
That guy you hit, Mikey Cerrone,
part of Charlie the Hand's crew.
Guess he should've known better.
[sighs] Hand asked me to look into it.
I spoke to Podell. Whole thing was,
uh... over a piece of ass, right?
Yeah.
Beef like that should never happen
inside the club.
They were out of line.
So we squashed it.
You, uh, looking to earn
a little extra scharole?
I can keep you busy
while the Copa is down.
What I gotta do?
Things.
Appreciate it, but, uh...
I want to spend some time with the family.
Don't be stupid.
You make yourself a few extra bucks,
you buy something nice
for that pretty little wife of yours.
Hmm.
Nah, I'm good. I'm flush right now.
[The Blue Jays]
♪ So long, Lover's Island ♪
♪ Dee ♪
♪ Dee-ooh ♪
♪ Ee, ah, ooh, ay... ♪
[song continues quietly]
Here's 50. Here.
Pay me 60 by New Year's, you get it back.
Hey, Lip.
Everything okay?
What, you got beak trouble, Charlie?
Mind your business.
-♪ So long, Lover's Island ♪
-[door opens]
So come on. I'm dying to hear.
What happened with the doctor interview?
He ain't a real doctor.
He's a piano player.
Well, I don't understand.
Why did they say that he was a doctor?
I don't know. I think he's, like, a doctor
of, uh, piano playing or something.
-You can be that?
-I guess.
He lives on top of Carnegie Hall.
You should've seen this place, Dee.
It was filled with statues
and all kinds of fancy crap.
And he was sitting
on top of a friggin' throne
all dressed up
like the king of the jungle bunnies.
He's colored?
[scoffs softly]
Well, you wouldn't last a week with him.
For the right money, I would.
-[Tony snoring]
-[phone ringing]
[groans]
[sighs] Yeah.
Oh.
Look... [clears throat]
Really? Uh, okay.
-Everything okay?
-Okay, hang on a sec.
It's, uh, Dr Shirley, the piano guy.
He wants to talk to you.
-Me?
-Yeah.
-What? No.
-Come on.
-Take it.
-No. Tony...
Just, just talk.
Hello?
[chuckles] Uh, good morning,
Doctor, It's nice to talk to you.
Well, uh, yes, that is a long time.
It is.
Yes. I'm sure.
[faintly over phone] Thank you.
Thank you for calling.
Bye, now.
What'd he say?
He wanted to know if I'd be okay
with him taking my husband away
from his family for two months.
He said he'd pay you what you asked for.
[Tony grunts]
-Hey.
-Hmm?
It's good money. We need it.
Can't be eating 26 hot dogs every day.
I know. [sniffles]
I told him it was okay for you to go.
All right, hey, look,
so here's the first half of your pay.
-You'll get the rest when the tour's over.
-No, I gotta get paid every week.
Sorry, that's not
how the record company does it.
We gotta have some guarantee
you'll finish the job.
Why wouldn't I finish the job?
I took it, didn't I?
Well, then we got nothing to worry about.
Here's the deal, Mr Vallelonga.
Okay, it's your job to get Don
to all his tour dates on time.
If he misses any shows,
you're not getting your back end.
-He's not gonna miss any show.
-Good.
Oh, you're gonna need this.
This is the book I was telling you about.
Sometimes you guys are staying
in the same hotel, sometimes you're not.
-[Tony] Oh, yeah, the...
-[man] Yeah, yeah.
All right, don't let me down. Let's go.
[music in background]
-Madonna, is this the new one?
-Yeah, the record company rented it.
-Nice, huh?
-Beautiful.
So what'd my sister have to say
about you being gone for three weeks?
-Eight weeks.
-[scoffs]
Ten to one, you slap this moolie out,
you come home in under a month.
[swears in Italian]
-[Dolores] Come here.
-[Tony] Boys, huddle up.
-Say good-bye to your father.
-Frankie, Nicky. Come here.
-All right. You gonna be good boys?
-Uh-huh.
-You'll listen to your mother?
Yeah? All right, give me a kiss.
I'm counting on youse.
-Don't go too far.
-We won't.
-Did you go to the AAA for the maps?
-Yes. No. I mean,
the record companies gave me the maps
and the itinerary. And this thing.
"The Negro Motorist's Green Book."
Yeah, it lists all the places
coloreds can stay down south.
Like a, you know,
"traveling while black."
"Traveling while black"?
Yeah, if you're black
and you gotta travel for some reason.
-Got a special book for that?
-I guess.
-Did you pack the iron?
-I ain't lugging no iron, Dee.
-How are you gonna press your pants?
-I'll put 'em under the mattress.
I want you to write me a letter.
Every chance you get.
-I can't write letters.
-Yes, you can.
-I can't write!
-Take you five minutes. Promise.
It's embarrassing.
It ain't gonna be no good.
It's a lot cheaper
than calling long-distance, Tony.
-Promise me you're gonna write.
-I promise.
Dee, put this in the bank today.
It's half my pay.
Oh, here. There's a couple of sandwiches
for you and Dr Shirley.
Thanks.
-Be careful.
-I will.
-I love you.
-I love you, too, baby.
["A Letter From My Baby" by Timmy Shaw]
You better be home for Christmas,
or don't come home at all.
[in Italian]
I got it, Pop. I got it.
♪ I got a letter from my baby ♪
♪ Mailman brought it today ♪
♪ She said she's so sorry ♪
♪ Uh, that she went away ♪
♪ She said, Daddy, don't worry ♪
♪ Because it won't be long ♪
♪ Hey, before I'll be back home ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Hey. I'm Tony.
His driver. Bum a smoke?
Thanks.
So you're the band?
[in Russian accent] Oleg. Cello.
George. Bass.
And we're not a band. We're a trio.
Oh. Trio. Right.
-[Dr Shirley] Good morning. Excuse me.
-Morning.
[groans]
[Dr Shirley] Thank you, Amit.
Have a wonderful trip, sir.
["Goodbye, My Lover, Goodbye"
by Robert Mosely]
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ Goodbye, my love ♪
♪ Though I love you truly... ♪
Tony, the first thing I'd like you to do
when we arrive in the city...
-Hmm.
-...is check the piano where I'm playing.
Make sure it's a Steinway
as per my contract.
[song continues over radio]
And can you see to it that there's
a bottle of Cutty Sark in my room?
-Every night.
-Every night?
[Tony chuckles]
Well, if you ever need
any help with that...
I won't.
Ten and two on the wheel, please.
Hey, Doc.
I noticed on the itinerary thing,
the last show's on the 23rd of December.
-Right?
-Birmingham, yes. It's a Christmas show.
So any way we could, uh,
maybe hit the road early next morning
so we'd be home in time for Christmas Eve?
-We'll see.
-Appreciate it.
[clears throat]
Could you put out the cigarette, please?
Why?
I can't breathe back here.
What are you talking about?
Smoke's going in my lungs.
-I'm doing all the work here.
-Thank you.
[Tony chuckles]
♪ And I know ♪
♪ I'm the one ♪
♪ You really love... ♪
[new song begins]
♪ Your ruby lips ♪
♪ Your lovely eyes ♪
♪ Made my life romantic ♪
♪ When you took advantage of me... ♪
[in Russian]
What are you looking at?
You speak German, huh?
That was Russian.
Yeah, I was stationed in Germany
in the Army.
I could pick up a little bit
of what you were saying there.
Watch out for them Krauts.
They're all sneaks.
Kennedy should've bombed them
when he had the chance.
Plus, now them Cuban bastards.
Ain't they supposed to be following us?
They have the itinerary.
As long as they get to the show on time,
I'm not worried about it
and neither should you.
I ain't worried about nothing.
In fact, when you see me worried,
you'll know.
-Tony, how about some quiet time?
-You'll know if I'm worried.
-Hmm?
-Sure.
♪ Your ruby lips... ♪
[chuckles] It's amazing you said that.
"How about some quiet time?"
Dolores, my wife,
used to say that all the time.
Well, not all the time, but you know.
She says it when I come home
from work sometimes.
She's been with the kids all day,
and she'll say:
"Tony, how about some quiet time?"
Exactly like how you said it.
I mean, it's amazing.
[chatter]
How is that?
Salty.
Have you ever considered
becoming a food critic?
No. Not really. Why? Is there money in it?
I'm just saying you have a marvelous way
with words when describing food.
"Salty."
So vivid one can almost taste it.
Hey, I'm just saying it's salty.
And salt's cheating.
Any cook can make things salty.
To make it taste good without the salt,
with just the other flavors,
that's the trick.
-You take the basic ingredients--
-We should really get going soon
if we expect
to get to Pittsburgh by dinner.
Hmm. Hey, when I was in the Army,
I knew a guy from Pittsburgh.
Except he called it "Titsburgh".
Cos he said all the women there
had huge tits.
That's absurd. Why would women
in Pittsburgh have larger breasts
than, say, women in New York?
Guess we'll find out, huh? [chuckles]
Hey, you know, when you first hired me,
my wife went out
and bought one of your records.
The one about the orphans.
-Orphans?
-Yeah.
Cover had a bunch of kids
sitting around a campfire.
Orpheus.
Yeah.
Orpheus In The Underworld.
It's based on a French opera.
And those weren't children on the cover.
Those were demons in the bowels of hell.
No shit. Must have been naughty kids.
["What'Cha Gonna Do" by Bill Massey]
[Tony sighs]
-What are-- What are you doing?
-Gotta take a leak, Doc.
Here? Now?
You want me to piss my pants?
[song continues]
♪ What'cha gonna do? ♪
[song fades out]
[chatter and laughter outside]
-[horn honks in distance]
-[woman laughing]
[chatter continues]
[laughing]
[soft ambient music]
[soft ambient music fades out]
-Oh, hey, Doc.
-Good afternoon.
[Tony clears throat]
Take this for any incidentals we may need.
If you wanna buy something,
you don't have to ask.
Just keep the receipts, please.
When it runs low, let me know.
-Oh. Thanks.
-One more thing.
We'll be attending...
many events before and after the concerts,
interacting with some of the wealthiest
and most highly-educated people
in the country.
It is my feeling that your diction,
however charming it may be
in the tristate area,
could use some... finessing.
You mean diction... like in what way?
Like in the only way
the word is ever used.
Okay.
Your intonation, inflection,
your choice of words.
Hey, I got my own problems.
Now I gotta worry about
what people think about the way I talk?
There are simple techniques
I can teach you that are effective.
-I can help you.
-I don't need no goddamn help.
People don't like the way I talk,
they can go take a shit.
The profanity is another issue.
[swears in Italian]
Why are you breaking my balls?
Because you can do better, Mr Vallelonga.
Which brings me to one more point.
As the guest of honor, I'll be introduced
when entering these intimate events.
You will be introduced as well.
In my humble opinion...
"Vallelonga" may be difficult
to pronounce.
So I was thinking...
"Valle" would be more appropriate.
-[chuckles]
-Tony Valle. Short and sweet.
Eh... Nah.
They got a problem with Vallelonga,
they can call me Tony Lip.
These are genteel people.
"Tony the Lip" may be a little...
-worldly for them.
-Well, then it's Tony Vallelonga.
All these high-class people,
so much smarter than me,
with their intelligence
and speaking abilities,
you tell me they can't pronounce my name?
They don't like it, they can shove it
up their ass, I'll just wait outside.
A sound compromise.
[piano playing mid-tempo jazz intro]
[jazz band joins in]
[chatter and laughter]
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight we are privileged
to present a great American artist.
At age 18, at Arthur Fiedler's invitation,
our guest made his concert debut
with the Boston Pops.
He holds Doctorates in Psychology,
in Music, and in the Liturgical Arts.
And he has performed at the White House
twice in the past 14 months.
He is a true virtuoso.
...unique artist.
So, ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome the Don Shirley Trio.
[applause]
[dramatic intro in a minor key]
[jazzy, syncopated, fugue-like melody]
[cello joins in]
[chuckles]
-[lively chatter]
-A new pair of shoes!
[excited shouts]
-Hard ten! Lady's friend.
-He keeps on winning!
It's your dice.
I'm just having a lucky night.
-You cheating, brother!
-[Dr Shirley] Tony.
-Get him again. Get him again.
-Boss man's calling.
He ain't my boss.
I work for the record company.
-Yeah, I work for the record company, too!
-Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, come on, man. Give us a chance
to win back our loot, huh?
-I'm sorry, fellas, duty calls.
-Come on, man.
"Duty calls"? My man,
my duty is to get my money back.
I've been looking for you.
Yeah, sorry.
The guys were having a little game.
Next time you need extra money,
you just ask me.
It's more fun winning it.
And what if you lost?
Grab some cards. I don't lose, Doc.
I don't lose.
Stooping down in the gravel, pitching dice
for pocket change makes you a winner?
What are you giving me shit for?
Everybody was doing it.
They didn't have a choice
whether to be inside or out.
You did.
Now, wipe off your knees.
You have dirt on them.
[soft ambient music]
[birdsong]
[music intensifies]
[Tony] Dear Dolores, how are you?
I am fine.
"I'm eating real good. Hamburgers, mostly.
So don't worry about me not eating good.
I saw Dr Shirley play the piano tonight.
He don't play like a colored guy.
He plays like Liberace, but better.
He's like a genius, I think.
When I look at him
in the rear-view mirror,
I can tell he's always thinking
about stuff in his head.
I guess that's what geniuses do.
But it don't look fun to be that smart.
I miss you very, very much."
["Lucille" by Little Richard]
[music continues on radio]
-Who is this?
-Who?
On the radio.
-Little Richard.
-Really? That's Little Richard?
Yeah. Think you could play
something like that, Doc?
♪ Lucille... ♪
I don't know. Sounds fairly complicated.
Got that right.
So where did
this "Tony the Lip" moniker come from?
[chuckles] It's not Tony the Lip.
It's Tony Lip. One word.
I got it when I was a kid,
cos my friend said
I was the best bullshit artist
in the Bronx. [chuckles]
-Why are you smiling?
-What do you mean?
It doesn't bother you that your friends,
the people closest to you
consider you a liar?
Who said "liar"? I said "bullshit artist".
-And what's the difference?
-Cos I don't lie. Ever.
I'm just good at talking people into...
you know, doing things
they don't wanna do.
By bullshitting them.
-And you're proud of that?
-Well, it got me this job.
♪ Lucille, please don't... ♪
[Chubby Checker]
♪ Baby, baby, baby, take it easy... ♪
Wait a minute. You're full of shit.
You never heard of Chubby Checker?
Of course I've heard of him.
I just never heard his music.
-I mean...
-But I like this. This is nice.
-He's got a silky voice, very smooth.
-Yeah, he's terrific.
-This is what everybody's dancing to now.
-Eyes on the road, Tony.
[Aretha Franklin] ♪ Baby, here I am... ♪
You know this song.
-I don't think so, no.
-How could you not know this music?
Aretha Franklin!
Chubby Checker, Little Richard, Sam Cooke.
I mean, come on, Doc.
These are your people.
♪ And it won't be long
No, it won't be long... ♪
[insects buzzing]
Do you want anything?
-I'm getting a pack of smokes.
-No, thank you.
[stones crunching underfoot]
[sighs]
-[bells jingling]
-[sighs]
[Oleg speaking softly] ...grabbed the rock
and put it in his pocket.
Thank you, Oleg.
Nice turtleneck. Way to mix it up.
Got you an apple, Doc.
-[engine starts]
-[Tony grunts]
Before we pull out, Tony,
we need to have a talk.
-Yeah?
-Oleg told me what you did.
-What'd I do?
-You stole a jade stone from the store.
-No, I didn't.
-He watched you do it.
I didn't steal no stone!
You picked it up
and put it in your pocket.
I picked up a rock off of the ground.
I didn't steal from a box.
Why would you pick up
a rock off the ground?
I don't know.
Cos it ain't stealing.
It's just a regular rock.
And why would you want a regular rock?
-To have. For luck, maybe.
-A lucky rock.
-Yeah.
-Let me see it.
[Tony sighs]
Mm-mm.
Take it back and pay for it.
[swears in Italian]
I told you that Kraut was a snake.
Rats me out
for something I didn't even do!
-Pay for the stone, you'll feel better.
-I feel fine.
And I ain't paying
for no regular rock I found in the dirt.
Do not drive, Mr Vallelonga.
[Tony sighs]
Put it back.
[piano playing softly]
[starts engine]
-Feel better?
-No.
If you'd like, Tony,
I'd happily buy you the stone.
Don't bother.
You took all the fun out of it.
[piano playing fades out]
[cello playing classical music]
Excuse me. Sir.
-I'm with the band.
-You're all set up.
This isn't the piano, right?
-That's it.
-It ain't a Steinway.
So what?
Dr Shirley only plays
on Steinway grand pianos.
It's in his written contract.
Who's Dr Shirley?
Dr Shirley. The Don Shirley Trio.
They're playing tonight.
-Does it really matter?
-Yeah, it does. It's in his contract.
Come on, man. Man, these coons can play
on anything you put in front of them.
But it's a piece of shit.
-And there's garbage in there.
-So take it out.
What'd you say?
You heard me.
Hey. You got two, three hours.
Just get a clean Steinway in here.
-Oh, there ain't a Steinway on campus.
-Not my problem.
[scoffs] I bet there's not two Steinways
in the whole state of Indiana.
I guess you'd better move your ass, then.
Who you think you're talking to,
greaseball? [grunts]
[whimpers]
[plays "Happy Talk" by Richard Rodgers
and Oscar Hammerstein II]
[Tony] Dear Dolores, this morning
I had steak and eggs. For breakfast.
The band has been playing
at very ritzy joints.
Dr Shirley and I
are getting along pretty good.
But sometimes I think he gets sad
and that's why he drinks too much.
I never knew
how very beautiful this country was.
Now that I'm seeing it, I know.
You won't believe
how beautiful nature is.
It is as beautiful as they say.
And the traffic out here in the country
is nothing, which is fine by me.
Right now I'm eating
spaghetti and meatballs, in a diner,
that tastes like
ketchup on Chinese noodles.
We are heading down south now.
I will write you another letter
when we get down south.
I love you. Your husband, Tony.
PS. Kiss the kids for me.
-[music ends]
-[applause]
["Ba-da" by Roy 'Boogie Boy' Perkins]
-Got any family, Doc?
-Not really.
Not really? Either you do or you don't.
-It's a long story, Tony.
-What, we're in a hurry now?
-[turns down music]
-Let's hear it.
I have a brother somewhere.
We used to get together once in a while,
but it got more and more difficult
to stay in touch.
Curse of being a musician, I guess.
Always on the road.
Like a carnival worker.
-Hmm.
-Or a criminal.
Took quite the toll
on my marriage as well.
-You're married?
-Was.
June.
Good person.
Terrible grammar, but a kind soul.
You'd quite like her.
June. Like, uh, like Lassie's mom.
Unfortunately, I couldn't do a husband act
and a concert pianist act.
Couldn't seem to manage both worlds.
[Tony] "Kentucky Fried Chicken."
In Kentucky!
When's that ever gonna happen?
["Cookin'" by Al Casey Combo]
[chuckles] All right!
-Hey, you want some?
-I'm fine. Thank you, Tony.
All right.
Mmm.
I think this is the best
Kentucky Fried Chicken I ever had.
Probably cos it's fresher
down here, right?
I don't think I've ever met anyone
with your appetite.
No. I got the bucket,
so you could have some.
-I've never had fried chicken in my life.
-Who you bullshitting?
You people love the fried chicken,
the grits and the collard greens.
I love it, too.
Negro cooks used to make it all the time
when I was in the Army.
You have
a very narrow assessment of me, Tony.
Yeah, right? I'm good.
No. No, you're not good.
You're bad. I'm saying,
just because other Negroes enjoy certain
types of music, it doesn't mean I have to.
-Nor do we all eat the same kind of food.
-Whoa! Wait a minute.
If you said all guineas like pizza,
and spaghetti and meatballs,
-I'm not gonna get insulted.
-You're missing the point.
-For you to assume that every Negro--
-Hey, you want some or not?
-No.
-Here. Come on.
-Tell me that don't smell good.
-It...
-Huh?
-It smells okay.
I prefer not to get grease on my blanket.
"Ooh, I'm gonna get grease on my blankey!"
Have a piece. It ain't gonna kill you.
Come on, take it, eat it.
-No.
-Take it. I'm throwing it in the back.
-You-- Don't you dare.
-Then you better take it.
How? Do you have plates or utensils?
Eat it with your hands,
that's how you're supposed to.
-I can't do that.
-Eat it. Come on. Take it.
I gotta drive. Ten and two on the wheel.
-Tony... [groans]
-Come on! Take it! Come on.
There you go. Huh?
I... I can't do this, Tony.
Eat the goddamn thing!
Jesus.
[rock and roll on radio]
-What, no good?
-Mm.
["Go To the Mardi Gras"
by Professor Longhair]
It just seems...
so un-- unsanitary.
Who gives a shit?
Just relax and enjoy it.
You know, my father used to say...
"Whatever you do, do it 100%.
When you work, work.
When you laugh, laugh.
When you eat,
eat like it's your last meal."
You want another piece? Here.
Have a breast. Delicious.
-Take it. Here you go.
-What do we do about the bones?
We do this.
This is what we do.
♪ If you go to New Orleans
You ought to go see the Mardi Gras... ♪
-There you go.
-[both laugh]
♪ You ought to go see the Mardi Gras ♪
♪ When you see the Mardi Gras... ♪
What's the big deal, Doc?
The squirrels would've eaten it anyway.
-Pick it up, Tony.
-Nature takes care of the Earth.
-Pick it up.
-Aw, geez.
♪ If you wanna go to New Orleans... ♪
[chatter]
[Tony grunts]
-[lively chatter]
-[door slams]
[train horn blares in distance]
[cat meows]
This can't be right.
It says right here:
"Cozy as your own home."
-Place looks like my ass.
-This is the place.
[Tony sighs heavily]
The square one, please.
-Just this one?
-Thank you.
Hey, uh...
if you need anything, I'll be
right up the street at the Easton Inn.
Thank you, Tony.
[chatter, music playing over radio]
[dog barking]
-Hey, Floyd, we ready.
-I told you.
-I can't play, my shoulder.
-You and that damn shoulder.
Hey! Hey, fancy-pants!
-You wanna play?
-I beg your pardon?
Come on, brother, we short a man.
Oh, I... I'd rather not.
What, you too high and mighty?
[other man]
No, no, let him alone, let him alone.
He just afraid of getting
that butler uniform dusty.
Mm. I'm just, um...
I'm on my way to meet a friend.
Yeah, well, thanks for nothing.
-[men laughing]
-Floyd, come on, man!
Shut your ass up, man, and leave me alone!
[soft ambient music]
[groans]
[sighs, sniffs]
Mm.
Yeah.
"For vacation without aggravation."
Hmm.
"Delightful dinners
for particular people."
[urgent knocking on door]
-Yeah?
-Get up! It's George!
[George panting] Get up.
Tony, come on. Hurry up.
Dr Shirley's in trouble.
I went out for a drink,
I walk into this bar,
and Dr Shirley's in there
getting bounced around.
I didn't wanna leave him,
but I didn't know what to do.
Who let him out of his cage?
And they put that little tie on him, too.
Why you all dressed up?
-[grunting and laughter]
-[door opens]
Get your hands off him.
What in the good goddamn
we got here, fellas?
Hand him over,
we walk out, won't be a problem.
I just wanted a drink, Tony.
Hey, I told you we'll leave.
-Not a big deal. Come on.
-He ain't going nowhere.
We need a Brillo Pad
to wash these dishes with.
[Tony] Listen, assholes.
Do yourselves a favor and let him go.
Now!
Say it nice.
I just said it nice.
This boy is gonna get
what he's got coming to him.
[click]
And you... you ain't got no say.
Maybe. But whatever happens here,
I'm gonna put a bullet
right in the middle of your thick skull.
He ain't got no gun, Ray.
He's full of shit!
What if he ain't?
Well, I sure ain't.
And I ain't about to let this
come to pass in my place.
Let the spook go. Let him go.
Come on.
Get him out of here.
[bartender] I want these Yankees
off of my property. Go on.
Go on, George. Go. Go.
[George] I got you, Doc.
[bartender] Go on.
-You out of your mind?
-I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to put you in that position.
Wait, wait, wait.
-Are you gonna throw up again?
-[groans]
I'm okay.
Honest to God, Doc,
I don't understand you.
You could have drunk here.
You got a whole bottle.
-I just needed some air.
-Air?
Do you know where you are?
Does geography really matter?
What?
If I was in a bar
in your neighborhood, would...
the conversation be any different?
[soft ambient music]
From now on, you don't go
nowhere without me. Nowhere!
-Got it?
-I understand.
-Where's your room?
-Tony...
What?
Do you really have a gun?
Course not.
Doc, where's your goddamn room?
-Come on. Over there?
-There it is.
You gotta get to bed, Doc, you got
a big show tomorrow night. Come on.
[up-tempo jazz]
-[music ends]
-[cheering and applause]
[Dr Shirley] Thank you.
Louisville,
thank you for your warm hospitality.
-[applause]
-[man] Bravo!
[applause continues]
Thank you. Thank you.
["Why Oh Why" by Little Alice]
♪ Why, oh, why has my baby... ♪
-Don't be lazy, Tony. Enunciate.
-I am!
[Dr Shirley] Betty bought a bit of better
butter to make the bitter butter better.
[Tony] B-- Betty bought butta-er.
Butta-- Who says that? Butta-er.
You have to start somewhere, Tony.
A singer does vocal exercises.
An athlete warms up before they rehearse.
[Tony]
Athletes practice. They don't rehearse.
[clanking, steam hissing]
Ah, shit.
-[steam hissing]
-[grunts]
[soft ambient music]
[car boot slams shut]
[Tony grunts]
[music intensifies]
[man] Ladies and gentlemen,
a very special guest from the far north,
-Don Shirley.
-[applause]
Accompanying Mr Shirley,
the members of his trio,
Oleg Malacovich, George Dyer,
and his associate Tony Valle--
Valle-- Vallelong-longia.
[applause]
Oh, this is my lovely wife, Margaret.
If you gentlemen don't mind,
we're gonna steal Donnie away
for some introductions.
I'd like you all to meet Don Shirley.
-[George] Yeah. I'll take one.
-[Tony] Hmm. What's that?
-A pimento and cheese sandwich, sir.
-Yeah, I'll try one of them.
Oof. [groans]
Sorry. Not for me.
-[clinking]
-[chatter quietens]
Here we go.
Earlier this week, we asked our help
what Mr Shirley might like for supper.
So the boys in the kitchen
whipped up a special menu
in honor of our guest. Gentlemen.
Home-cooked fried chicken!
[applause and murmuring]
There we go. Bring it in. Serve it up hot.
[mid-tempo jazz]
[music ends]
[applause]
Thank you. Thank you.
We'll return after a brief intermission.
-[quiet chatter]
-[woman laughing]
-Excuse me, Don. Lovely work in there.
-Why, thank you.
Uh, are you looking for the commode?
-Yes. I...
-Yeah, here. Let me help you.
It's right out there before that pine.
I'd prefer not to use that.
Well, don't be silly, Don.
It looks a lot worse from the outside.
And I suppose you'd know from experience.
Well, I've never had any complaints.
Well, I could return to my motel
and use the facilities there...
but that would take
at least a half an hour.
We don't mind waiting.
Why don't I just pull over?
You can piss in the woods.
Animals go in the woods.
It's gonna be at least 20 minutes
all the way back to your motel.
So let's just get there,
so I can go back and finish the show.
[sighs] See? That's the difference
between you and me.
-I'd have zero problem going in the woods.
-I'm well aware.
What are you sore at me for?
I don't make the rules down here.
No?
Then who does?
Oh. You're saying
just cos I'm white and they're white?
You know, that's a very prejudiced thing
you just said there.
A very prejudiced thing.
I got more in common
with the Hymies at 2nd Avenue deli
-than with these hillbilly pricks here.
-Eyes on the road.
You always say that
when you don't like what I'm saying.
Eyes on the road!
-[chatter and laughter]
-[Tony] I don't get it.
How does he smile
and shake their hands like that?
They try to pull that outhouse shit on me,
I'd piss right on the living room floor.
Don't, don't do that.
We have many concert dates left.
Yeah. So?
You realize we're contractually obliged
to perform them?
Course I do.
You don't play, we don't get paid.
What's your point?
Ugly circumstances
are going to happen again.
So control yourself.
Don't lecture me, you rat.
Dr Shirley could have stayed up north,
getting rear-end kissed
at Park Avenue parties
for three times money.
But he ask for this.
[chatter continues]
Why?
What on God's green Earth are you doing?
-A letter.
-Looks more like a piecemeal ransom note.
May I?
"Deer Dolores."
D-E-A-R. This is an animal.
"I'm meeting all the highly leading
citizens of the town.
People that use big words, all of them.
But you know me, I get by.
I'm a good bullshiter."
Two T's in "bullshitter".
"As I'm writing this letter,
I'm eating potato chips
and I'm starting to get thirsty.
I washed my socks
and dried them on the TV.
I should have brung the iron."
You know this is pathetic, right?
-Tell me what you're trying to say.
-I don't know.
You know, I miss her and shit.
Then say that. But do it in a manner
that no-one else has ever done it before.
And without the profanity.
Something like, uh...
Put this down.
-Dear Dolores...
-Hold on. I'll start a new one.
D-E-A-R Dolores...
When I think of you...
I'm reminded
of the beautiful plains of Iowa.
What planes?
The plains. P-L-A-I-N-S.
Those big fields we saw.
Oh. Yeah, those were nice. Plains.
"Which is what they call
big fields around here."
Tony, no expounding.
-No what?
-Just write what I say.
No good.
The distance between us...
is breaking my spirit.
"Between us."
My time and experiences without you
are meaningless to me.
[birds chirping]
Falling in love with you
was the easiest thing I've ever done.
"Falling in love with you..."
[Tony] ...was the easiest thing
I have ever done.
Nothing matters to me but you.
And every day I'm alive,
I'm aware of this.
I loved you the day I met you
I love you today,
and I will love you the rest of my life.
[piano playing mid-tempo]
So can I put, uh... "PS. Kiss the kids"?
-A PS?
-Yeah, like, at the end.
That's like clanging a cowbell
at the end of Shostakovich's "Seventh".
Right. So that's good.
It's perfect, Tony.
[Tony] Everybody talks
about Willie Mays, 1954.
It wasn't even the greatest catch
in the Polo Grounds.
That was Joe DiMaggio, 1936,
second game of the World Series.
Final out, 500 feet...
-You like that, Doc?
-That's a handsome suit.
-Sharp.
-Mm-hm.
[Tony] Guy looks just like you.
He does?
Well, size-wise. Yeah.
[Dr Shirley chuckles] He's about a 42.
-Why don't you try it on?
-Hmm...
What, you gotta wear
a tuxedo onstage every night?
You could mix it up a little, Doc.
Come on, let's see how it looks on you.
We got plenty of time.
[bell jingles]
-[music playing over radio]
-I'll be right back.
-How you doing?
-May I help you, sir?
Yeah, we want to try on that, uh,
beautiful gray suit in the window.
-You got it in a 42?
-Of course.
-That's the one.
-Dressing room is in the back, sir.
Thank you. I'll be just a moment.
Take your time, Doc.
I'll check out some ties for you.
Uh, excuse me.
You're not allowed to try that on.
I beg your pardon?
Uh, if you'd like to purchase it first,
we'd be happy to tailor it to your needs.
I see.
[bell jingles]
[up-tempo music]
[music ends]
[cheering and applause]
[grunts]
[phone ringing]
Yeah.
That's me.
[soft, dramatic music fades in]
Hey, Officer.
I got a call about Dr Shirley.
Come on.
His friend's here.
-[Dr Shirley] Thank you.
-[Tony sighs]
-Get a guy a towel, for Christ's sake!
-You a lawyer?
-No.
-Well, you should call one.
-We're taking your auntie in.
-For what?
Manager caught him and the other guy.
Well, can we get the cuffs off him,
let him put his pants on,
-we talk about this?
-Sure, we could.
But we ain't.
Okay, look.
We're out of here tomorrow morning.
You'll never see us again.
There's gotta be something
we can do to work this out.
What if you let him go and
I give you something to thank you?
[laughs] You bribing us?
No! Hell, no.
A gift. A thank you.
-[officer] What kind of thank you?
-[Tony] Like a...
You know, donation
to the police force, youse guys.
Whatever you want.
You like suits?
I was walking
through your nice town today,
and I seen a store that was selling suits.
Primo suits.
What if, as a thank you, a donation...
I buy youse each a suit?
You get all dressed up,
you take the wife out for dinner.
I mean, guys like you,
you work hard, you deserve it.
They were wrong for the way
they treated me and you rewarded them.
I was hired to get you
from one show to the next.
How I do it shouldn't matter to you.
-I just wish you hadn't paid 'em off.
-I did what I had to do.
You know, if this got out,
it would kill your career.
Okay, Tony.
I need you to stop it
with the phony altruism
-and concern for my career.
-What the hell does that mean?
You were only thinking
about yourself back there,
because you know if I miss a show,
it'll come out of your pocketbook.
Of course I don't want you to miss a show,
you ungrateful bastard!
You think I'm doing this for my health?
Tonight, I saved your ass.
So show a little appreciation, maybe.
Besides, I told you
never to go nowhere without me!
I assumed you'd want this
to be the exception.
[soft ambient music fades in]
[car door opens]
[door closes]
[soft ambient music continues]
[engine off]
Want me to get some... makeup
or something for the show tomorrow?
No, I'm fine.
-You sure? Bruise kind of shows.
-I said I'm fine.
Okay.
[car door closes]
-[man 1] He didn't ask me to do that.
-[man 2] Dom, that's what he told me.
He didn't ask me. Oh...
-Tony Lip. What the hell?
-Dominic, Mags.
-What are you guys doing around here?
-Brooklyn sent us down.
-Take care of a few things.
-Yeah.
[in Italian]
[laughter]
I'm working here.
Sorry, Doc.
They're some friends from New York.
-Hey, can you get Dr Shirley's luggage?
-All right.
[soft, dramatic music fades in]
[music intensifies]
[chatter]
Called his room. Be down in a minute.
-[sighs]
-[lock clicks]
[door rattles]
-Hey, Doc.
-Where are you off to?
I'm just going downstairs.
To have a drink.
[in Italian]
Tony... I think you're doing
a wonderful job.
So...
I'd like to formally offer you
the position of my road manager.
With the title also comes
more responsibility, but...
that also means a raise in pay.
No. No.
No, thanks.
We agreed on 125 a week.
Plus expenses. That's our deal.
Right?
[chuckles] I ain't going nowhere, Doc.
I, I was just going down to tell them.
[chuckles, sighs]
Tony.
[soft ambient music]
I'm sorry about last night.
Don't worry about it.
I've been working nightclubs
in New York City my whole life.
I know it's a...
complicated world.
[music intensifies]
So where'd you learn
how to play like that?
-My mother.
-Your mother?
-Really?
-Mm-hm.
She taught me how to play
on an old spinet.
Soon as I could walk, we'd...
travel around the Florida Panhandle,
put on my little shows
in parishes and halls.
Fortunately, a man who had seen me play
arranged for me to study
at the Leningrad Conservatory of Music.
I was the first Negro ever accepted there.
That's where they taught you
all them songs you play?
Actually, I was trained
to play classical music.
Brahms, Franz Liszt, Beethoven, Chopin.
It's all I ever wanted to play.
But I was persuaded by my record company
to pursue a career
in popular music instead.
They insisted
that audiences would never accept
a Negro pianist on a classical stage.
Wanted to turn me into
just another colored entertainer.
You know, the guy
who's smoking while he's playing
and sets a glass of whisky on his piano,
and then complains because
he's not respected like Arthur Rubinstein.
[chuckling]
You don't see Arthur Rubinstein
putting a glass of whisky on his piano.
I don't know. Personally, I think
if you'd stuck to the classic stuff,
-it would've been a big mistake.
-A mistake?
Performing the music
I trained my entire life to play?
Trained? What are you, a seal?
People love what you do.
Anyone could sound like Beethoven or...
"Joe Pan" or them other guys you said.
But your music... what you do...
Only you can do that.
Thank you, Tony.
But not everyone can play Chopin.
Not like I can.
[Bobby Page &amp; The Riff Raffs]
♪ I love my baby... ♪
[Dr Shirley]
The trees have shed their leafy clothing,
and their colors have faded
to grays and browns.
"I saw millions of trees
all dusted with snow,
just like out of a fairy tale."
He's so expressive!
Got to admit,
Lip's letters... they're not bad.
Oh, well, it's in the family.
They say our great-great-great-grandfather
helped Da Vinci with the Sixteen Chapel.
-You mean Michelangelo.
-Right.
What does Michelangelo have to do
with writing letters?
I'm just saying, we're an arty family.
"I will count the hours,
minutes and seconds
until you are in my arms.
Love you, Tony.
PS. Kiss the kids."
-John!
-Yeah?
-I want a letter.
-Yeah.
-Soon as you make a meal.
-[chuckling]
[lively piano music]
[laughs]
-That was a bullshit artist!
-Eyes forward, Tony.
[piano music continues]
[Dr Shirley] Tony!
All right, everybody,
let's give our finest Louisiana welcome
to Don Shirley and the Don Shirley Trio.
[applause]
-[music ends]
-[applause]
[grunts] Your mother's ass.
Can't see shit.
[Tony grunts]
What the hell's this guy doing?
[siren wailing]
Son of a bitch.
License and papers.
[Tony] Am I glad to see you!
We had to turn off the main road,
and, uh... now we're lost.
-Step out of the car.
-What'd I do?
Out of the car!
-[sighs]
-[door closes]
-Why are you on this road?
-I told you.
We had to make a detour and we got lost.
And why are you driving him?
He's my boss.
He can't be out here at night.
This is a sundown town.
What's that?
Get him out of the car and check his ID.
Oh, come on, it's pouring rain.
Sir, I can just get it right here
through the window--
-Get him out of the car.
-Come on, get out, now.
Get out, now. Get out!
Got ID?
How you say this last name?
Vallelonga.
Yeah, what kind of name is that?
It's Italian.
Oh. Oh, I see.
That's why you're driving him around.
You're half a nigger yourself. [grunts]
Hands in the air! Now! Now!
[Dr Shirley] Excuse me.
[Dr Shirley clears throat]
Excuse me, sirs.
I, I understand
why my associate is being held,
but what exactly am I being charged with?
You seem like reasonable men.
Perhaps you could let me out, so that
we could discuss the situation further.
Just put the apple butter away, boy.
You ain't going nowhere no time soon.
You cannot hold me without cause.
Oh, I got cause.
Cos you let the sun set on your black ass.
I want to speak to my lawyer.
I want my call.
This is a flagrant violation of my rights.
You know...
he does have, uh... rights.
Give the Negro his goddamn phone call.
You happy?
[lifts receiver]
You know a lawyer? Call him.
[officer] I walk up to the car and I say:
"Sir, you know how fast you were going?"
He says: "I'm sorry, Officer.
I didn't mean to speed, but..."
[Dr Shirley] As my mother always said:
"What kind of brand-new fool are you?"
Look at them over there.
Take a good look at the officer you hit.
Look at him.
He's over there having a grand old time,
chatting up with his pals,
enjoying a nice cup of coffee.
And where are you?
In here, with me, who did nothing.
Yet I'm the one who pays the price.
I'm the one who's gonna miss
the Birmingham show.
Hey, I'm gonna lose a lot of money, too,
if you don't play Birmingham.
So that little temper tantrum,
was it worth it?
Hmm?
You never win with violence, Tony.
You only win
when you maintain your dignity.
Dignity always prevails.
And tonight, because of you, we did not.
[phone rings]
I wouldn't touch that mattress, Doc.
-[phone rings]
-[officer] Maryville Police.
No, sir.
No, no, I, I'm not, sir.
Yes, sir. He's right here, sir. Yes, sir.
-Yes, sir.
-Give me.
Chief Pratt. Who's this?
Baloney.
[muffled shouting over the phone]
Yes, sir. I can hear it now, Governor.
[officer] Uh...
No, sir, I'm sorry. I...
No, of course
I can recognize your voice, it's...
[soft music fades in]
Sir?
You're saying the boy
we got locked up called whom?
Oh, and he called you.
No. Now, sir, an officer was assaulted
in the line of duty.
[soft music intensifies]
No, sir. No.
I don't want no National Guard
coming down here, neither, sir.
I'll get to it immediately, Governor.
Good night to you and the missus.
-Get 'em out.
-What?
-Cut 'em goddamn loose.
-That dago wop hit me!
You want to keep your goddamn job?
Then you do what I goddamn tell you to do
when I goddamn tell you to do it!
And I'm telling you
to get 'em the goddamn out!
Who the hell did you call?
Bobby Kennedy just saved our asses.
Madonna. How great is that?
It's not great. It's not great at all.
-It's humiliating.
-The hell you talking about?
We were screwed. Now we ain't.
And I just put the Attorney General
of the United States
-in an incredibly awkward position.
-So what?
That's what the guy gets paid for.
What else he got to do?
That man and his brother
are trying to change this country.
That's what else "he got to do"!
Now he thinks I'm some kind of...
Calling from some... backwoods swamp jail,
asking to attenuate assault charges?
Who does that?
Garbage. That's who.
You shouldn't have hit him.
I didn't like the way he was treating you.
Making you stand out in the rain.
Please, you hit him
because of what he called you.
I've had to endure
that kind of talk my entire life.
You could take it for at least one night.
What, I can't get mad
at what he was saying cos I ain't black?
-Christ, I'm blacker than you are.
-Excuse me?
You don't know shit about your own people.
What they eat,
how they talk, how they live.
You don't even know who Little Richard is.
So knowing who Little Richard is
makes you blacker than me?
Oh, Tony, I wish
you could hear yourself sometimes.
You wouldn't talk so damn much.
Bullshit. I know exactly who I am.
I'm the guy who lived in the same
neighborhood in the Bronx my entire life
with my mother, my father, my brother,
and now my wife and kids.
That's it. That's who I am.
I'm the asshole
who has to hustle every goddamn day
to put food on the table.
You, Mr Big Shot,
you live on top of a castle,
traveling around the world
doing concerts for rich people.
I live on the streets.
You sit on a throne.
So, yeah, my world is
way more blacker than yours.
-Pull over.
-What?
Pull over.
-I ain't pulling over.
-Stop the car, Tony!
-What?
-[door opens]
What are you doing?
Doc?
Doc, what the hell are you doing? Doc.
-Get back in the car.
-Yes, I live in a castle, Tony! Alone.
And rich white people pay me
to play piano for them,
because it makes them feel cultured.
But as soon as I step off that stage,
I go right back to being
just another nigger to them.
Because that is their true culture.
And I suffer that slight alone,
because I'm not accepted by my own people,
cos I'm not like them, either.
So if I'm not black enough,
and if I'm not white enough,
and if I'm not man enough,
then tell me, Tony, what am I?
[soft ambient music]
[car door closes]
[music continues]
I need some sleep.
All right.
I'll stop at the next place we see
and sneak you into my room.
No. No.
I refuse to stay in an establishment
where I'm not welcome.
Yeah? Okay.
[soft ambient music fades out]
Tony, do you have to smoke everywhere?
I didn't know it bothered you.
You should've told me.
All you gotta do is say the word, Doc.
[sighs]
-[ear pops]
-[grunts]
You do realize you'll be home
before that letter arrives.
Yeah, I know.
Just thought I'd bring it with me.
Save on stamps.
All right.
Tony, give it here. I'll fix it.
No offense, Doc,
but I think I got the hang of it now.
"Dear Dolores,
sometimes you remind me of a house.
A house with beautiful lights on it...
where everyone is happy inside."
[soft ambient music fades in]
[chuckles softly]
Yes, Tony. You got it.
Yeah? [chuckles]
Thanks.
Hey, Doc, thanks
for helping me with, uh, the letters.
You're really good at writing 'em.
My pleasure, Tony.
You know, um, when you get home,
maybe you should write...
write one to your brother.
[music continues]
He knows where I am
if he ever wants to reconnect.
Eh. I wouldn't wait.
You know... world's full of lonely people
afraid to make the first move.
Yeah, I'll finish this tomorrow.
[coughs]
You know, Doc, something's been
eating at me this whole trip.
Hmm?
[soft ambient music fades out]
That Titsburgh was a major disappointment.
I didn't notice any difference at all.
Did you?
Good night, Tony.
["O Come All Ye Faithful Jazz Trio"
playing]
-[man 1] Good evening.
-[man 2] Welcome, welcome. Come on in.
-[Dr Shirley] All righty.
-[Tony sighs]
Welcome, Mr Shirley.
Graham Kindell, I'm the general manager.
-It is a pleasure to meet you.
-Thank you, Mr Kindell.
-This is Mr Tony Vallelonga.
-Nice to meeting you, Tony.
-How you doing?
-Let's keep the car right here in our...
"guest of honor" spot.
Right this way, gentlemen.
-[Tony] Hmm. Nice.
-How was your drive up?
-[Dr Shirley] Oh, it was wonderful.
-Good to hear.
As you can imagine, our Christmas show
is our biggest show of the year,
and we are so happy
to have you here, Mr Shirley.
So if you need anything,
anything at all, you let me know.
-Mm-hm. Thank you.
-Now, here we are.
We got about an hour before showtime.
Any questions?
Where's the restaurant?
Well, you continue down the hall here,
Tony, to the right and across the lobby.
-Good luck. Break a leg.
-Thank you.
Well, he said we got an hour.
You must be starving, Doc.
Go ahead. I'll meet you there.
["O Christmas Tree" playing on piano]
May we join you?
Mm. Go ahead.
Cocktail, gentlemen?
-I'm good.
-Three shots vodka.
Oh.
Last show. Cold War over, time for truce.
-Is Dr Shirley in his dressing room?
-Yeah. More like half a broom closet.
Tell you, I don't know
how he puts up with that shit.
Six years ago, in 1956,
Nat King Cole was invited to perform
at the Municipal Auditorium
here in Birmingham.
Mr Cole was the first Negro asked to play
at a white establishment in this city.
As soon as he started playing,
a group of men attack him
for playing white people's music.
They pull him off stage...
and beat him badly.
Jesus Christ.
You asked me once:
"Why Dr Shirley does this?"
I tell you. Because genius is not enough.
It takes courage
to change people's hearts.
Thanks.
[George] Thank you.
No? Nazdarovye!
Danke schön.
-[Dr Shirley] Good evening.
-Can I help you?
Oh, um...
Um, there. Some friends of mine.
Uh, y-you... you can't come in here.
[Tony groans]
-I understand, but...
-Hey. What's going on?
This... gentleman says
that I'm not permitted to dine here.
No, you don't understand.
He's playing tonight.
-He's the main event. Come on.
-I'm sorry, but...
-It is the policy of the restaurant.
-Everything all right?
Uh, no, it's not all right. This guy's
saying Dr Shirley can't eat here.
Oh, well, I apologize, but... [sighs]
...these are long-standing traditions,
club rules. I'm sure you understand.
No, I do not understand.
In 45 minutes, I will be up there
on that stage entertaining your guests.
Yet I can't eat here?
[sighs] I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me the bozos in his band
and all these people who came here
to see him play, they can eat here?
But the star of the show,
the parking spot of honor, he can't?
I'm afraid not.
Well, he's gotta eat.
I mean, he's gotta have dinner.
[stammers] Okay, I'll tell you what.
Why don't we bring something
to his dressing room?
-John, show him a menu.
-[Dr Shirley] No.
I'm not eating in that storage room.
Okay, uh, well, if you prefer,
there's a very popular establishment
right down the road, the Orange Bird,
they'd be happy to feed you.
-[scoffs]
-Doc, come here.
-[laughs quietly]
-Just one second.
Maybe that other place is better anyway.
The dinner rolls here are like rocks.
You just go over and...
you go over and come back.
It's the last show.
It's the bottom of the ninth.
Let's just get it over with and we can
go home and get away from these pricks.
Huh?
Ah, there you go.
The fish is wonderful tonight.
Either I eat in this room...
or I'm not performing tonight.
May I have a word with you?
[sighs] No.
[sighs] Mr Villanueva,
you have to talk sense to Mr Shirley.
Please make him understand,
we're not insulting him personally.
This is just the way
things are done down here.
Yeah, well, he's not from down here.
Yeah, just, just ask him to be reasonable.
I got 400 guests in there
expecting to be entertained tonight.
And Dr Shirley expects to eat tonight.
Why can't you just make an exception
this one time?
Let me tell you a story. [clears throat]
You ever hear of
the Boston Celtics basketball club?
-Yeah.
-Well, those boys came through here
couple years ago on a barnstorming tour,
and seeing as they was
the world champions of the league and all,
we were tickled to have them here,
and we rolled out the welcome wagon.
So do you know what table
their big coon ate at that night?
-No.
-I don't either.
But it wasn't one of ours.
Now, let's cut the bullshit.
Tell me what it's gonna take, huh?
Say, uh, $100, you get your boy to play?
You think you can buy me?
[chuckles] With all due respect, sir,
you wouldn't be in a job like this
if you couldn't be bought.
-[Mr Kindell grunts]
-[Dr Shirley] Stop. Tony.
It's all right.
I'll play...
if you want me to.
[soft music fades in]
All right. Let's get the fuck out of here.
What do you mean "let's get out of here"?
Where the hell do you think you're going?
Don, don't do this.
Now, you signed a contract
and I know you're the kind of man
who honors a contract.
Connie, Bill, everything's gonna be fine.
You got a show to do, mister!
You turn yourself around
right now, goddamn it! Right now!
This is why you people
don't work down here.
Cos you're unreliable, you hear me?
I shipped that goddamn Steinway
in from Atlanta for you!
Tony?
Are you hungry?
Does Betty like butta-er?
[laughs]
-[man] One, two...
-[drumsticks clicking]
[upbeat live music and chatter]
-You a cop?
-Do I look Irish?
What you want, baby?
-Two Cutty Sarks, neat.
-Coming up.
Mm. Whatever your specialty is,
we'll take it.
Two Orange Birds!
[band music ends]
I like what you did back there, Doc.
You stood up for yourself.
It's like what your friend,
the President, said: "Ask not...
your country what you can do for it.
Ask what you do for yourself."
You know?
So, darling...
what you do all dressed up like that?
-Nothing particularly important.
-[scoffs]
-Shouldn't judge a man by his clothes.
-[Tony chuckles]
He's only the greatest
piano player in the world.
That right? You good?
-[chuckles]
-Don't be shy, Doc. Tell her who you are.
Don't tell me nothing. Show me.
[bartender chuckles]
Come on.
[Tony chuckles]
[chatter]
[laughs]
[plays "Winter Wind" by Chopin]
[music intensifies]
[stops playing]
[cheering and applause]
Whoo!
[Tony] Yeah! Yeah!
[lively blues music]
[music fades out]
That's how you break a key.
[both laughing]
Oh, that was a good time.
I'd do that once a month for free.
-You were unbelievable.
-Hey, Tony.
-I bet if we leave now, we can make it.
-Make what?
[Dr Shirley]
Christmas Eve, in New York City.
[two gunshots]
[man] Oh, shit!
[grunts]
[dog barking]
Don't ever flash
your wad of cash in a bar.
I knew you had a gun.
["Your Replacement is Here" by Edd Henry]
♪ No more heartaches ♪
♪ And no more sorrow ♪
♪ Everything's looking brighter ♪
♪ For tomorrow ♪
♪ So I guess I might as well ♪
♪ Jump in right now, dear ♪
♪ Baby, your replacement is here... ♪
This could get bad, Doc.
Yes.
It's a shame we don't have something
to protect us on our journey.
[clicks tongue] Oh, I know.
Why don't you put
your lucky rock up on the dash, Tony?
Come on, Tony.
We need all the help we can get.
Thank you.
I feel safer already.
You're a real prick, you know that?
[chuckles]
[soft ambient music]
[Tony sighs]
-[siren wailing]
-Ah, shit!
[Dr Shirley groans]
Goddamn cops.
[music intensifies]
What are you doing out here?
We're trying to get to New York.
-Is there a problem, Officer?
-Yeah.
I noticed your car was tilting left.
Looks like your back tire is flat.
[Tony grunts]
Ah... [swears in Italian]
[Tony sighs]
[Tony grunts]
Keep it moving. Keep it moving.
[soft ambient music]
[Tony sighs]
[Tony grunts]
Okay, be careful, gentlemen.
Merry Christmas.
-Merry Christmas.
-Thanks, Officer.
[engine starts]
[both chuckle]
[music fades out]
[radio] Weather advisory warning
this Christmas Eve
as a major snowstorm
is hitting the Eastern Seaboard
with the severest weather
in eastern Pennsylvania,
northern New Jersey
and the five boroughs.
Travelers are advised to stay
off the New Jersey Turnpike.
[Tony] All right, that's it. We're done.
I'm pulling us into the next motel.
Keep going as long as you can, Tony.
I can't keep my eyes open.
I'm getting hypnotized here.
Think my brain's gonna explode.
Hey, we gave it a shot, Doc.
What are you gonna do?
[Frank Sinatra] ♪ Have yourself ♪
♪ A merry little Christmas... ♪
All right, the table is set, ladies and
gentlemen. Don't run in the house!
[lively chatter]
-Mom, Frankie won't let me use it.
-Frankie, let Nicky use it!
♪ Out of sight... ♪
[lively chatter]
♪ Have yourself... ♪
Kids! Wash your hands.
♪ Make the Yuletide gay... ♪
-Dee! Do you need help with the calzone?
-No, I'm fine. No.
All right! It's time to eat!
♪ Our troubles will be miles away ♪
♪ And have yourself ♪
♪ A merry little Christmas ♪
♪ Now ♪
Tony. Tony, wake up.
[gasps]
-You all right?
-You're home.
Get inside.
[Tony grunts]
[closes door]
-Good night.
-Wait, wait.
Come... Come up and meet my family.
Merry Christmas, Tony.
[Tony] Yeah...
Merry Christmas.
[soft ambient music]
[music fades out]
[music and lively chatter]
[woman]
Hey! You're gonna choke on the bone.
-I'm just getting started over here.
-[lively chatter]
-You got it? You got it.
-I got it.
-Dolores, do you need any help?
-No, no, honey.
-Not while I'm eating!
-Go ahead.
-You're not gonna smoke...
-[Tony singing in Italian]
-[cheering]
-Look who it is! Shakespeare's home! Hey!
Dad!
[Tony continues singing]
-[Tony] Hey. [kisses] How are you?
-[excited chatter]
-You made it back!
-Hey, Pop. Mwah! Hey!
-Merry Christmas.
-Buon Natale.
-Tony, God bless.
-Hey.
-Glad you made it back.
[chatter continues]
[man] Wonderful, wonderful!
[man whoops]
-Yay!
-Ah.
You hungry?
-I'm starving.
-All right. Sit down.
Anything left? [chuckles] Let's go!
[wind whistling softly]
-Welcome home, Dr Shirley.
-Thank you, Amit.
I turned down your bed, sir.
Uh, shall I unpack your luggage now?
No, no. Please, go home to your family.
Thank you, sir.
-Merry Christmas, sir.
-Merry Christmas.
[clock ticking]
[silence]
[soft ambient music]
[sighs]
[music fades out]
♪ Santa Claus is coming... ♪
[lively chatter]
-Always with the kissing.
-[both laugh]
What? You never kiss me
like that at the table.
[woman]
Why don't you ever kiss me like that?
All right, all right, all right,
relax, relax.
♪ Santa Claus is coming... ♪
So, Tony, you all right?
You seem a little quiet.
Yeah. Nah, I'm just tired, you know?
Mm, long trip.
You take care of that thing?
Oh.
-Thanks.
-Yeah, you owe me 75 bucks.
Seventy-five? Charlie said 60.
Oh. I'm doing this for free?
-[chuckles]
-Hey, Tony. Tony, tell us about the trip.
-You've been gone two months.
-Yeah, how was he, the tootsoon?
-He get on your nerves?
-Don't call him that.
♪ Santa Claus is coming ♪
♪ To town... ♪
All right.
Tony, you should have seen
the day last week.
Little Frankie climbed up onto the TV.
I took a picture of him, it was so cute.
-He was so funny up there.
-What, are you nuts, Dee?
With all the tubes back there?
He could've got electrocuted.
-Did he break it?
-You're thinking of toasters.
You can't get electrocuted
from the TV set!
She's not thinking about a toaster.
She's thinking about a TV!
-Is she taking it into the bathtub?
-[loud chatter]
-[arguing continues]
-[knocking]
-[man] You're not gonna get electrocuted.
-[arguing continues]
-Charlie!
-Hey, Lip. Johnny invited me.
-Oh. Well, come on in.
-[laughs] All right.
Oh. You remember Marie?
-Hey, Marie.
-Charlie, you actually came?
-I was kidding!
-[laughs]
-With the wife, too? Geez.
-Merry Christmas.
-Get in here.
-Merry Christmas, hello.
What a surprise. Nice to see you.
[Johnny] Everybody, Charlie
from the pawnshop. Didn't bring nothing.
Christmas. Can you believe it?
Come here. Sit down.
[man] Sit down, sit down.
[soft music fades in]
Doc. [laughs]
Ah. Welcome.
[Tony] Oh.
-[chatter]
-[Tony] Hey, everybody!
-[man] Stop it, stop it.
-This is Dr Donald Shirley.
Merry Christmas.
♪ Yuletide carols
Being sung by a choir... ♪
Well, come on. Make some room.
Get this man a plate!
[lively chatter resumes]
[quietly] Oh.
♪ Turkey and some mistletoe... ♪
-Hello.
-You must be Dolores.
Welcome.
-Buon Natale.
-[Dolores laughs]
Thank you for sharing
your husband with me.
[quietly] Thank you
for helping him with the letters.
[laughs]
["The Lonesome Road" by Don Shirley]
["Go To The Mardi Gras"
by Professor Longhair]
[whistled melody]
♪ While you stroll in New Orleans ♪
♪ You ought to go see the Mardi Gras ♪
♪ If you go to New Orleans ♪
♪ When you see the Mardi Gras ♪
♪ Somebody'll tell you
What's Carnival for ♪
♪ Get your ticket in your hand ♪
♪ If you wanna go to New Orleans ♪
♪ You know when you get to New Orleans ♪
♪ Somebody will show you the Zulu King ♪
♪ You will see the Zulu King ♪
♪ Down on St Claude and Dumaine ♪
♪ You know, you'll see the Zulu King ♪
♪ And if you stay right there ♪
♪ I'm sure you'll see the Zulu Queen ♪
[whistled melody]
[song fading]
["Rich Woman"
by Li'l Millet and His Creoles]
♪ I got a woman with plenty of money ♪
♪ She got the money and I got the honey ♪
♪ Called my baby late last night ♪
♪ She told me,
Daddy, everything was all right ♪
♪ I don't have to worry
Cos she's real fine ♪
♪ I know my baby and she's all mine ♪
♪ She give me a Cadillac,
a diamond ring ♪
♪ She told me,
Daddy, don't you worry 'bout a thing ♪
♪ She's all mine and I'm so glad ♪
♪ She's the best woman I ever had ♪
[song fading]
Subtitling by Pixelogic Media