I'm gonna die here.
Shit.
Man, looks like we both had a rough landing.
Life Hutch, activated.
Warning, damage detected.
Communication network, functional.
Maintenance robotics...
Error.
Piece of shit.
Maintenance robotics, error.
Maintenance robotics, malfunction.
Wait!
Stop! Hold on! Halt program!
Halt program!
Unable to comply.
Prometheus CVW2.
ECMs are online. You are clear to engage.
Nova 6, en route.
Nova 9, en route.
Nova 4, en route.
Acknowledged, you are go for weapons hot.
Copy that. Going hot.
Payload is Divine Flash 12 Judgment two.
Armed and ready to hunt.
Nova Squadron line up,
echelon formation. Hit them fast and hard.
731, 731, hostile fire incoming!
We lost Rocket one!
Firing!
Come on, come on. Come on.
Mayday message received.
Life Hutch 817-RD9G. Rescue inbound.
Warning: maintenance robot malfunction.
No shit.