- [Beth] Yay!
- [all laughing]
Wait, what's that?
Do I hear something
coming down the chimney?
Rick Santa-chez here with gifts
from across the multiverse.
- Oh, my God.
- Yes!
For Jerry, an extra dimensional version
of Miracle on 34th Street.
Two hours longer!
They fixed my only problem with it!
For Beth, a framed photo of the two of us from
a universe where she wasn't murdered as a child.
Oh, my God. Dad.
And for Space Beth, the same thing because
we don't know which of you is real.
I am also touched.
Summer, check your Venmo.
- [gasps] Money? How did you know?!
- You're 17.
And last but not least,
for my number one number two.
Morty you asked for this
a long time ago
and I finally went far, far away enough
to get it
since shipping would have killed me.
- You didn't! No fucking way.
- [all] No fucking way.
- Does it make the noises?
- Of course, that's like half the fun.
- Awesome!
- Whoa, do not turn that on!
Don't worry. Morty's only going to use
this very honorable weapon
in designated Jedi zones,
like the garage right now.
Holy crap. I hate to say it, but I wish
there was something to attack.
It's too bad nobody bought
a cart of fruit!
- You beautiful son of a bitch.
- Grapefruit!
Mango! Papaya! Watermelon!
A second papaya!
Another watermelon! Strike me down.
- What?
- Strike me down!
- I'm not striking you down.
- Strike me down.
I'll become a pile of clothes
like that old guy.
But you'll die, you're drunk.
- Here, I'll do it myself--
- No!
Wow, you did it! Just like Obi Wan.
Rick?
You can come out now. I'm serious.
Did you, like, become your clothes?
Are you T-shirt Rick now?
[Rick] Psst. Over here, butt fart.
- Oh, that was awesome!
- Right?
Rick, you know you've been
so great the last couple months.
The family's so happy,
I'm really grateful.
Aw, thanks, kid,
but less talk more melon slaying.
Heads up!
Whoops!
- Shit, open it, Rick!
- Let me do it!
- Get up-- Fucking move!
- Hurry!
Oh, whoa! Whoa, whoa!
You dropped it perfectly vertical,
Morty. Perfectly fucking vertical!
- I got it, I got it, aw!
- Oh, shit.
- Shit.
- Elevator. Elevator.
We gotta get ahead of it.
Level ten?
No, no, no, 15.
[elevator beeping]
Wait, we live over
a cool sushi spot?
- [speaking Japanese]
- Domo. Domo. Not now, though.
Okay, we overshot it.
Good problem to have.
- Still doing the eel roll?
- We should've gone to ten.
No, Morty, not ten.
- Morty, wait, wait.
- Cut it out.
What the fuck?
- Rick?
- You dumb fucking robot.
- You had one job.
- That job was to be a good grandpa.
- I go where the kid goes.
- Don't touch me.
How long have I--
You said you weren't a robot.
It killed me to lie to you.
But it would have literally
killed me not to lie to you.
Betrayal. Betrayal on all sides.
Don't overreact.
I replaced myself towards the beginning
of that whole Knights of the Sun thing.
I'm no good to anybody till
I resolve this arch-nemesis crap.
You're hunting the guy
who killed your wife?
You don't have to rub it in,
that's why I removed myself.
I've become the thing I hate.
It's like a Netflix drama down here,
and I don't mean an accidentally good one,
I mean a regular-ass Netflix drama.
I did you a favor.
You gave him a fucking lightsaber
for Christmas?
It's almost like someone designed me
to be 22% more thoughtful than you.
I'm shutting you down.
Don't you dare. You've done enough.
The whole family.
Everybody loves this thing.
Oh, good.
Your lightsaber's probably
run out of sub-basement
- by now, so, congrats.
- Unbelievable.
I can't believe you tricked us
into loving you.
Not because I like it,
because it's my job.
- Thank God I don't have to do it anymore.
- The fuck you don't. It's Christmas!
Get up there and trick everyone
into loving you more.
Let's get our miracle on.
- Speaking of miracles...
- What, bored of your toy already?
Just, uh, excited to spend time
with my family.
You know me and Morty,
we're all about those streets.
Would you look at this?
New York City.
Wow, who would've thought
it had so many streets?
And avenues too. Oh, gosh.
Hey, sir.
Sir, have you seen any miracles?
- My little girl, she's sick and she needs a miracle.
- [helicopter whirring]
The Presidential Blackhawk
is landing on the lawn.
[Morty] I'll get rid of him.
You got something to tell me, Morty?
Merry Christmas?
Who dropped a lightsaber
perfectly fucking vertical?
Oh, shit.
Guess what.
It's a mile deep and still going.
- You know what's in the hilt of that?
- Kyber crystals.
Okay, nerd. Whatever it is,
when it hits the core,
it's gonna cause a chain reaction
that destroys the Earth.
It is?
Why are you still playing
with laser swords? You're 14.
You know all that Star Wars
shit is silly, right?
Lucas promised a new trilogy for decades,
then, when he delivered, fans turned on him
and started giving any knucklehead
with nerd cred a shot
and churned out
these irredeemable cash grabs.
Half pretend to be satisfied,
half shit on it
and in the end no one's happy.
Do you know why, Morty?
Because when you start with a turd,
you end with a turd.
[Morty sobbing]
Why you crying? Where's Rick?
He's busy. And I hate him.
And I lost my lightsaber
and now it might destroy Earth
and you're unloading all this Gen X
hatred on me for wanting one
- and it's the worst Christmas ever.
- Okay, Morty, Morty, Morty.
I shouldn't have talked to you
like you're a UN official.
Let's get your embarrassing lightsaber back
so you can swing it around instead of kissing girls.
Whoa. You found me. Found me. Found me.
- [computer] Security breach.
- What the hell?
- Unauthorized presence.
- What the fuck, Morty?
This morning, a real life version
of George Lucas's trademarked lightsaber
was dropped point down and is whomp-Whomping
its way to the core of the Earth
where it will blow us all up.
Touch my shit and die.
That's not a threat from me,
that's how advanced my shit is.
Impressive lair, Sanchez.
Got about 600,000 permits?
If I wanted the government
in my house, I'd buy an Alexa.
- I invited him in, Rick.
- Yeah, well, they can leave.
I'll destroy it.
- We're gonna retrieve it.
- That's stupid.
What kind of grandfather are you?
It's Christmas, for God's sake,
and you look like Phil Spector
wiped his ass with Randy Quaid.
If you're gonna help, help,
otherwise step aside.
Merry Christmas to me.
- Merry Christmas to me!
- [Rick] To me.
Anyhoo, I'm no expert
but it seems we've got a...
A certain amount of time
to build a big drill ship.
A big drill ship?
That's some loud
stepping aside you're doing.
- Let me destroy the thing.
- You've destroyed enough.
[crowd] Ooh.
[screams]
Oh, I see someone found
my Told-ya-so Dispenser.
Oh, my God,
look at all these streets.
We got 34th Street. 35th Street.
Oh, 36th Street coming too.
Oh, it's a miracle.
We got miracles on 37th Street.
38th, and don't even get me
started on the avenues.
I can't believe they cut this.
Mm-hm.
Dad. You've been so great lately.
I'm almost afraid it's not real.
You're not a robot, are you?
Ha. Put it this way, honey.
If I am, I'm a robot programmed
to love you very, very much.
[all] Aw.
Will this drill down fast enough
to get under the lightsaber?
Yep. It will be under the lightsaber
in one hour--
Wait, it's lower now.
Oh, right, it's moving.
You fucking idiot. Get out of here.
Good luck finding
a good scientist on Christmas.
I'm president of the United Assholes.
[Rick whistling]
All right, genius, I give you permission
to make our drill ship faster.
I'm not touching that thing.
I'll get neurotypical cooties.
I have son-in-laws more imaginative.
All right, just destroy the lightsaber.
Thought you'd never ask.
Not true, I knew you'd ask.
- What is that?
- A second lightsaber
with an Al-controlled
gyroscopic rocket in the hilt.
- You had a lightsaber?
- Oh, did you want one?
What a terrible gift
that would have made.
Vertisaber, state your prime directive.
- To stay vertical.
- Then show 'em how it's done.
Affirmative.
- Yeah!
- America!
Maintain verticality, Vertisaber.
[Vertisaber] Affirmative.
All right, looking good.
Stay on target.
Uh-huh.
Progress report.
- Vertisaber? Do you copy?
- Do I have to respond every time?
Excuse me?
I'm designed
to stay perfectly vertical,
not to give constant affirmation.
You do your job I'll do mine.
I control you.
Okay, I'll just turn off my brain
and you can do that, bye.
Fucking kidding me? Shit.
- Trajectory's drifting, sir.
- Where is it coming out?
Looks like Italy, sir.
[all gasp]
That could've been worse.
Well, uh, that is definitely not a more.
- Way to show us how it's done, Rick.
- Whatever.
- Italian prime minister on line one.
- Put him on hold.
We can pin this on the Saudis.
This is something they'd do.
They may as well have done it.
They did do it.
[Fred] Oh, there's another miracle
at the end of the intersection
of 401st Boulevard
and 7,000 Street.
That's a miracle per block so far,
Okay, even I'm nearing my limit.
Let's play a Christmas game.
Oh, um, have you guys ever played
"Are You a Robot?"
Each person here has to decide
whether or not they're a robot.
- [Jerry] Never played that.
- [Summer] Yes!
Don't say it out loud.
'Cause if you're a robot,
you're not allowed to say you are,
that's the rule.
That's the horrible,
painful thing about being a robot.
But you do have to answer
everyone's questions.
And it's their jobs to decide
whether you are or aren't a robot
because if you are a robot,
you can't say.
You're not allowed to say at all.
I'll go first. Uh, question?
Ooh! Uh, are you a robot?
Can I just ask that?
You can. But don't forget that if I am,
I have to lie even though I don't want to.
- More questions?
- Can you feel things?
Oh, fuck yes. Yes.
That's the problem.
If I'm a robot, which I'm not,
don't forget I have to say that,
but yes, yes, I feel so much,
I'm filled with love for certain people,
but also filled with shame
if I'm programmed to deceive them,
but that's a big if.
- What's your skeleton made of?
- Titanium.
- You're a robot.
- Yes.
No.
But that's what a robot would say.
So you get the idea.
- Whoo!
- Suck it, bitches!
This is fun. I've always been afraid
to let my guard down
and have stupid family fun like this
but Grandpa Rick is making me
learn to be vulnerable.
- Me too.
- Right on.
[alarm blaring]
Your derivative drill ship
is now faster than a lightsaber.
- You want front or back?
- Who says the two of us are going?
- You didn't want to--
- For fuck's sake, bye, good luck.
- Don't blow up my planet.
- You act like you're the one
- that got stabbed in the back.
- I am the one.
You wanna know why I replaced myself
in the beginning of that Knights of the Sun thing?
I said don't take the fucking sword
and you were like, "Whatever,"
like I'm our neighbor Gene
or David Arquette or something.
You called me boring.
I've become dog shit to you.
That's what happens when you let people in
and they stop respecting you.
They touch your shit,
they kill your fucking family.
Trust him. You're going to learn
the same fucking thing.
I am not going to kill your family, Morty.
That means a lot.
In case this goes south,
any last words, Morty?
I've never been old enough to vote,
- but when I am, I'll vote for you.
- Thanks, Morty.
Every vote counts.
I can have them
legally change your age.
Uh, no, I'm not in any hurry
to get into that shit show.
[man] Approaching the lightsaber in
T-minus-- Shit, now, T-minus-now.
I missed countdown day at the academy.
Now or never, Morty.
- There it is!
- Reverse the jets.
I got this.
No. I do!
Morty,
you magnificent little bastard.
Let's get this thing topside.
[all cheering]
May the Force be with me.
I think you mean with me.
What? You hate Star Wars.
I was your age
when this shit was in theaters.
This franchise raised me,
trained me,
taught me good from evil,
made having a bad father empowering.
And when that third movie
got all muppety...
something in me began to rot,
but make no mistake, child.
I own Star Wars. Not you.
Not that bubble throat,
pompadour fuck,
not some Mickey Mouse shit machine.
They didn't pay the price with their souls.
I did. I earned this. Not you.
America. Transform and roll out.
Bastard!
Rick. I would be honored if you
would carve the ham this year.
- Whoa. Dad. That's--
- Unheard of?
You're quite right, Summer.
It's my way of saying I see your mom's father
as my father too.
Oh, Jerry, why don't you cut it?
What the hell are you doing?
He's like adopting you into
his biological family, Grandpa.
Morty, I am sure glad to see you.
You ready to tag
your old grandpa back in?
You're not my grandpa,
you're a fucking robot.
Ugh. Finally.
♪ The first Noel ♪
♪ The angels did say ♪
♪ Was to certain poor shepherds ♪
♪ In fields as they lay ♪
Okay, okay, okay.
[groans]
- Summer, do you have any drugs?
- Are you serious?
I guess not.
I'm just glad I'm not
the one that ruined Christmas.
- People of Earth.
- Hmm, that's never good.
I'm not here to play the blame game,
but Morty Smith got a lightsaber for Christmas,
dropped it, and it's now heading for
the Earth's core again-- For the first time.
Son of a bitch. He played with it!
If it does reach the core,
it will blow all of you up.
I mean, all of us up.
But don't abandon hope.
We're doing everything we can to stop it
and only if that fails,
will we launch the White House into space.
Welp, I'm busted.
Clearly in space already.
- You did ruin Christmas.
- Nuh-uh.
He stole my lightsaber and must've dropped it.
A second time.
Does that mean you stopped it a first time?
- How?
- A drill ship.
A drill ship? Awesome.
It was, but the government
took it with them.
Then we lean on the only asshole
smart enough to make another one.
But Rick's gone.
And I'm not sure
he's ever coming back.
Then let's settle
for the next best thing.
Oh, fuck, just let me die. Turn me off.
Not that I can be turned off,
because I'm obviously not a robot.
[beeping]
Fuck yeah. I got you.
Okay, I can work with that.
[shouting]
What do you mean the White House chef
was grocery shopping?
Well, do you know how to make an egg?
You do?
Everyone does?
Good news, sir. The lightsaber
was intercepted before it hit the core.
All right, here we go.
I don't suppose
you could send it up here.
Uh, who intercepted it anyway?
[man] That's the bad news.
That is bad news.
Hey, Mr. P. Drop something?
Morty!
I see you and, uh, Rick patched
things up, that's nice.
The real Rick and I have never
been worse thanks to that wedge
you drove between us
to get that lightsaber.
Yeah, well, looks like you got it back.
Your journey is complete. As a nerd.
You're the nerd. You can't say
all that crazy shit about Star Wars
and then act like you're cool.
Oh, really? Would a person
who wasn't cool have one of these?
I think so?
Slowly closing door, slide.
Oh, no, I'm not gonna make it.
What a shame to be put out
of my misery again.
Aw, man.
[Morty] What the hell?
Was this always part of the White House?
Carter built it with his own two hands.
Reagan tried to destroy it.
George W added kegs to the cantina.
But only I saw its true value.
Mr. President. You need to come home
and tell the people the truth.
The fuck I do!
Droids, get that saber.
Give it a minute.
Usually comes out on the fourth try.
All right, here we go.
Look at 'em: lightsaber hands!
Tell me that's not cool.
It's not. I always wanted to fight
with a lightsaber, but not like this.
- You ruined it.
- Disney ruined it!
You think I want 30 low-rent
TV series with bad CGI?
They film everything on
that one big green screen.
- Like you've got better ideas.
- I've got a million.
Here's one:
a robot with lightsabers for eyes.
Goddamn it, he can't see.
It was a good idea otherwise.
Uh, admit it, you were intimidated.
Now, Morty...
Come on, put down
the lightsaber gatling gun.
We had our fun, right?
Star Wars rules
say you have to forgive me.
I'm done with that
and I'm done with you!
- Morty. No!
- Rick bot!
He sacrificed his life for me.
Yeah, don't be too touched.
He's actively trying to die.
Ugh. It's okay, it doesn't hurt.
Oh, God, they're sliding, Morty.
They're sliding! They're sliding!
♪ The first Noel, the angels... ♪
Perfectly fucking vertical.
[alarm blaring]
Save yourself, Morty.
Rick can build another me!
- If I was a robot, which I'm not.
- I don't want another you.
No!
- Rick? You came to help.
- Better tend to your lil toaster.
[coughing and gurgling]
I'm coughing up oil, Morty.
Oh, Rick bot,
I never should've pushed you away.
- You were so great.
- Of course I'm great, I'm Rick.
Rick literally built me
to make you happy, Morty.
Anything I do is technically
something Rick did.
But maybe he can do
a little more himself.
- God, how long do you take to die?
- Goodbye, Morty.
[powering down]
Ugh. Jesus.
Rick, uh...
I guess this is a bad time
to ask for a new White House?
Morty, would you mind
calling me an Uber?
Right, well, uh...
Merry Christmas. [chuckles]
I guess I'll go watch a guy scream
about streets with the family.
Also, you need to shower.
Hey. Maybe the robot's right.
I should have included you in my shit.
You can help me if you want.
Wow, are those all
the places Rick Prime could be?
I wish, Morty. It's all the places he is.
- Oh, jeez.
- Welcome to my darkness.
I spent my life hunting this guy, Morty.
This is the closest I've ever been
to catching Rick Prime. It's impossible.
He's an incredibly crafty piece of shit.
Hunting him destroyed me, Morty.
But now we're gonna do it together.
You and me. It's gonna
take over your life, Morty.
Rick and Morty, Season 7,
hunting my nemesis.
Maybe trying to stay
healthy while doing it.
Juggling plates.
Not every episode, Morty.
It could be all happening in the background.
Who knows? You know, no one will. Except us.
It's the most painful shit
I've ever had to deal with
and I'm bringing you into it.
Because you asked for it, Morty.
You and me, Morty.
[theme music playing]
Ooh-wee. What a season, huh?
Rick Prime. Therapy.
And that thing we did with Roy,
remember that?
Sorry I wasn't around,
been busy getting
my little poopy butt in shape.
Been toning and boning.
You might think I'm over-compensating
for the emptiness
after Amy left with Poopy Jr,
but my trainer Carl says
the best way to get over a girl
is to get under a 300-pound squat.
Damn right.
Ah. Ooh-wee, that's the good stuff.
Oh, sugar, oh, sugar, oh, sugar!
Is it bad?
Oh! It seems really bad, isn't it?
[groaning]
Someone call Amy, tell her I need her.
Tell her I love her.
Not my phone,
she blocked me, use yours.
Ooh-wee.
I am broken.