Hey, you kids! Don't be bad outside my store!
- I keep a nice store!
- Give it up, old man.
We're just cool, bad kids doing young stuff.
- Wanna do more skateboard moves?
- Which ones?
- The rad ones, that's which.
- How are you kids?
- Grandpa's trying to get your attention.
- Yeah, screw off.
- Grandson, what's that mean?
- He's one of those cult people.
They worship Roy
that says he's everybody's grandpa.
So, what do you wanna do today?
Eat some snacks
and maybe let me kiss you finally?
- With my mouth.
- [Marta] This is going on right now.
- Let's go check it out.
- Oh, jeez.
Come on, just for fun, you know?
No, that's not what--
You think I'm a religious leader.
This isn't a religion. This is actual truth.
I'm a scientist in real-life.
But this is a video game.
You at least understand that, right?
This is a video game?
But you said I'm your grandson.
I'm saying everyone is.
Everyone here. Everyone but me.
You're all my grandson, your name is Morty,
you're stuck in a video game,
- and I'm here to get you out.
- What about me? Am I your grandson?
I just said everyone is!
- Wow. incredible.
- But don't react like that.
It's not a religion. This is what is happening.
You, me and your sister are at
an arcade called Blips and Chitz.
It's been taken over by terrorists.
The power went out, the game restarted,
and your identity has been splintered
into all the non-player characters.
I jacked in as Roy,
that's the player character, to get you, Morty,
out of the game before it's over and you die.
- Okay, question over here.
- Am I your grandson?
Jesus. Yes! Every single one of you
is one five-billionth of Morty.
All of you, collectively, are Morty.
I don't wanna seem impatient
but there's a lot more that we have to get done.
So if this is how hard it's gonna be,
we are in a lot of trouble.
Summer, what?
I can't do this if you keep bugging me!
Do you understand time dilation?
I'm losing a month a second out here.
There's an alien army shooting people.
What am I doing?
It's a small group of alien terrorists.
- Just do a Die Hard.
- What does that mean?
Sneak around, use air vents.
You've never seen Die Hard?
I'm 17. No, I've never seen fucking Die Hard.
Well, neither did the guy in Die Hard,
so you're nailing it. Good luck!
[theme music playing]
- [Joanna] Larry...
- [Larry] No, I'm at the end of my rope,
I swear to God.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Your hair.
This is not a daughter's haircut.
I'm not a daughter, I'm a grandson.
Your family had a fine religion.
You were raised Jewish.
Dad, tell me anything about being Jewish.
A million things.
You go to the temple with the special hat.
- The falafafluten.
- Oh, the falafafluten?
Our Jewish words are gibberish
because we're a 14-year-old boy
who was raised nondenominational Christian
and we're in a video game.
I don't need to hear this schmoitenheiven.
Let me ask you this, little miss grandson,
little miss video game character.
If you're not my daughter,
why stand in my house spouting this?
- Why even live here?
- Good question.
There she goes. My daughter.
One five-billionth of a kid
trapped in a video game.
Yeah, that and a college degree
will pay the rent.
What do you people want?
We have many interests, but right now
my primary one is the location of your safe.
We exchange tokens for digital currency.
- We don't have a safe.
- Correction, what you don't have is a head.
Is this a weapon or a medical tool?
Why would you give me a gun
with a laser that thin?
Did you hear me tell him
he wouldn't have a head?
- He's dead, isn't he?
- People die in surgery.
[console] Hey, who touched me?
I don't like being touched!
Check the hostages.
Make sure nobody else here
is doing a Die Hard.
♪ Hello, hello, hello
My name is Morty ♪
♪ I'm a 14-year-old boy
In a video game ♪
- All right! Yeah!
- Gee.
I feel like every time I explain this,
I lose followers, but this isn't a religion.
And while I do have a message
from a world beyond this one,
and I do need the entire world
to hear my message,
what I do not need is any more songs about it.
Not in this genre.
I'm an old-school hip-hop man.
And no, that's not an invitation for you to try it
because I'm just gonna say it,
we're missing the mark on diversity.
Get down! You're all under arrest
for being religious the wrong way!
It's not a religion. Just shoot me.
- Your God makes you bulletproof?
- There isn't even a God in the real world.
- There's extra no God in here.
- You know what?
- Talking like that is why you're getting shot.
- If you kill him, the game ends and we all die.
- Get down, lady.
- Not a lady. And you're not a soldier.
We're one person, split into little pieces.
You feel me? Dawg?
You're not gonna hurt me. You're me.
My name is Kevin. I'm a Marine. I'm 30.
I'm a little racist but my best friend is an immigrant
that translated for me in a generic, overseas war.
That's not true. We're 14,
we like pizza and masturbation.
We wear a yellow shirt, and we have hair
that looks like a brown helmet.
And we miss our family
and we're in way over our heads again.
- Why's this always happen, man?
- I know, right? Oh, jeez.
- Oh, jeez.
- Come here.
[all] Oh, jeez. Oh, jeez.
Oh, jeez. Oh, jeez.
- Who is that?
- Her video-game name is Marta.
Okay. See, this I can work with.
"Sneak around.
Crawl in some vents. Do a Die Hard."
[screams]
[beeping]
[gasps]
[both shouting]
Oh, my God, it's disgusting.
Actually, it tastes really good.
It's disgusting that it tastes good.
[Jons] Frank, have you found him? Report.
Walkie-talkie. That's Die Hard.
Don't have to see it to know that.
This is Jons. I repeat, have you found him?
[Summer] Breaker, breaker. Walkie-talkie.
I got your walkie-talkie. Bitch.
Are you doing a Die Hard?
Maybe. Are you? Also?
More or less. And my associate, Frank?
Your associate Frank
is definitely not doing a Die Hard.
You might even say he's doing a "Die Easy."
Because I killed him and it wasn't difficult.
- [blabbering]
- Calm yourself, Winslow.
Winslow! Ugh.
It's not every day one meets a fellow
Die Hard enthusiast, miss...
- Call me Die Hard.
- Okay, Die Hard.
Tell me. What do you know about Die Hard?
What do you care?
You writing a book about Die Hard?
I've written several.
Every sentient civilization
across the galaxy develops the same myth.
In Centauri, it's Tower Man.
The Orionese have their Thornberg Cycle.
In Andromeda, it's Foolish to Have
Imagined You'd Be Able to Kill.
All of them what you'd call Die Hard.
The difference being that cultures like mine
are aware of its importance
whereas I'm starting to doubt
you could even recall a line.
Walkie-talkie Die Hard, motherfucker.
[screaming]
[news anchor] Not so long ago, Grandsonism
was being dismissed as a cult.
But since a majority decided,
"Hey, you know what, we like jerking off
and playing video games and our sister is
fighting terrorists, " major strides have been made.
The world is united, because the world
is one 14-year-old boy, Morty.
But where's it all coming from?
Some say Grandsonism's leader, Roy,
has a secret base in these mountains.
I couldn't find it so I'm standing
in the general area with a microphone.
For Good Enough News, I'm Tony.
There she is, my right-hand Morty.
- [Marta] Got enough spaceships?
- Not yet.
I figure five more years of game time
before I can take the whole fake population
into fake outer space.
- What do we do?
- Nothing. It's fake. We keep going.
The game's map has edges, but the game's
engine will let us go past them.
That will force the game to reset,
but first it will kick us out,
which Morty should survive.
Whatever amount of Morty we have.
So if you don't have
handkerchiefs soaked in chloroform,
I hope you can keep flipping idiots to our cause.
They're not idiots, Grandpa. They're me.
Ha. You'll know how funny that is when
we get back. I had your father picked up.
- He's over there.
- What? Why?
I thought you'd be grateful
and less distracted than if I let him die.
- He's been in real bad shape since he lost his wife.
- My mom?
Your not-at-all-real mom in a video game,
occupied by a tiny fraction of yourself.
A fraction of yourself which is now dead forever,
and fractions add up,
so I had your dad brought here.
You're welcome, you heartless monster.
Marta. It's me, Dad.
I converted for you.
My name is Morty. So is yours.
There's no conversion. We're Morty. It's a fact.
Sure. Anything you say.
I don't wanna fight. I'm proud of you.
Are you mad at me because
before you became the most powerful woman,
I shamed you for your haircut
and called you a slutty jobless hobo?
If I were you, I'd be mad about that.
You are me. And why would I be mad at myself?
Good point. ls there anything to eat?
- There's a kitchenette.
- Oh, a kitchenette.
- Such red carpet treatment.
- Excuse me?
Thank you, I love it. We're all part of Morty.
Some of us more important parts than others...
The part of me that's my father is a twat.
That's also gonna be funny when we get back.
Next time you try to do a Die Hard,
don't hide under a long table
like the guy from Die Hard.
- [screams]
- Okay, I won't.
You said she doesn't know Die Hard.
- She doesn't.
- She's killing us off one by one.
What do you expect her to do,
buy us each an ice cream, two by two?
She's improvising,
which is how she's going to fall into our trap.
I'm going to wander the arcade unarmed,
and when she comes across me,
I'll pretend to be a hostage.
And because she hasn't seen Die Hard,
instead of handing me an unloaded gun,
she'll hand me a--
Die Hard! Die Hard! Die Hard!
- What the hell was that?
- [Summer] Die Hard! Die Hard!
You can't keep yelling "Die Hard"
into a walkie-talkie and--
She threw her walkie-talkie away.
She hates Die Hard.
Which makes her the ultimate McClane.
Forget everything you know about Die Hard
and just go shoot that bitch.
[president]
Thank you for meeting with me, Mr. Roy.
Half the country hangs on your word.
Heck, most of them.
You're like a pope, I reckon.
I'm not. It's not a religion.
We're in a video game.
I've heard the message.
You're not on the clock here.
You want every single person on a spaceship,
but you got a bunch of holdouts.
Maybe people that prefer
their leaders a little more elected.
Right. Your voters. People that like
being told what to do but don't like admitting it.
- Not sure I'd put it that way.
- You'd put it a stupid way.
This was a waste of time.
I've got 92% of you ready to vamoose.
We're not gonna get the rest
by making deals with parasites.
Mr. President, Roy is Rick. He's not us.
You and I, we're Morty.
Is that so hard to believe?
I've known it and believed it longer.
We became video-game characters
at the same moment,
but I knew the truth before you dropped
your skateboard and went to your first cult meeting.
How do you think a guy
becomes a president, honey?
By not paying attention?
Sorry to call you honey,
I know we're parts of a 14-year-old boy,
but my part's old-fashioned
and vaguely Southern.
I'm confused. if you know Rick is real, why--?
Why hold out?
Because he's a rude, entitled cock.
He's here to save us. He could've let us die.
He spent 50 years--
Fifty years, it's what, a couple hours to him?
He refuses to leave without his grandson,
but what's "grandson" mean to him?
Sounds like it means butler.
Someone to "Help Summer
with her Die Hard," whatever that means.
I'll tell you what it doesn't mean.
Fly fishing. A hug.
A little appreciation for what
is clearly a pretty decent kid.
At least the 8% of him
that makes up the decent half
of the greatest goddamn nation on the planet.
We're not a person to him yet.
We're not Morty yet. We're divided.
We're divided
because some of us don't trust the guy.
What happens when we're all back together?
One Morty? indivisible?
Under a cranky old bag of dicks?
A man you can lock in a box with five billion pieces
of his own goddamn flesh and blood
for 50 goddamn simulated years
and never hear him say "I love you"?
Sorry, pumpkin tits, that dog don't hunt.
Want some heroin?
It's a video game, might as well.
Just about ready for launch.
I can get out of these clothes.
I don't have nearly enough pockets.
It'll be nice to have my own dick back.
- You're fine leaving 8% of me to die?
- It's not your finest 8%\, Morty.
And 8%\ of anything is expendable.
Eight percent of pizza is crust.
Eight percent of the Snyder Cut
was Batman dreaming.
I don't know that reference.
We're in a video game.
- Not for long, baby.
- I'm not leaving without all of me.
What? Let me crunch these numbers.
Eight percent of five billion plus one person--
- If you stay, it changes nothing.
- If she's not going,
- I don't think my country wants to go.
- Who invited you to chime in, monitor face?
Why give me a monitor
if my opinion doesn't matter?
Your opinion isn't allowed to matter.
We're all Morty.
How many of us are we supposed to give up?
Look, I don't know about you,
but I was already taking a big leap of faith.
We're basically giving up our lives
to become a tiny part of a stranger.
- These lives aren't real.
- Yeah, but they're longer.
- [all shouting]
- What is this, suicide by summit meeting?
Everyone stop!
Rick, I'll get every single part
of me to get on every ship.
- Good.
- But you have to tell us you love us.
At this point even if he said it--
What's with the pause?
Screw you, wait for it.
- Holy war!
- Holier war!
Holiest war ever!
[Tony] Loyalist Evacucratic Grandsonistas
claimed seven new cities today
while the Stayputlican
Contrasurgent Confederation
of Dedication to Video Game Reality
invaded the territories of Mortopia,
New South Saint Morty, and Wemortyall.
In the end, what does it matter, everyone's Morty,
nobody wants to die,
and that's a hell of a reason
to kill yourself, but what can we do?
Oh, jeez.
You know you're my grandson
and none of this is real.
What are you trying to achieve?
You're only hurting yourself.
The only reason any of us matter
is we're pieces of Morty.
You taught us that, Rick.
But you also taught us
you don't care about Morty.
Here's how much I care.
If you don't stop blowing up my flying saucers,
I will exterminate every last one of you.
Anything it takes.
What do I have to say?
I love and respect you, okay?
Too late for talk, Rick.
A robot. Of course.
I'm not gonna risk dying because
if I die in the game, you go brain dead.
- You're welcome.
- Better to die in Roy than to serve in hell.
And what about Summer? Do you not care?
We gotta get back, we gotta help her.
Wherever she is,
I'm sure she's doing fine without your help.
Woof. Jinx, anyone?
Should we finish the job, blow the place?
No, this can't end, not like this.
Do you think I jinxed her?
- Why aren't you shooting higher?
- I don't wanna shoot the glass, because...
You don't have to not do things
that were done in Die Hard.
You can shoot the glass. Shoot the glass!
Throw grenades. Do everything.
Just kill her!
Why are you here, Ms. Die Hard?
I want to know why you don't just leave.
[Summer] Die Hard!
Wait. Shh.
[Marta] ...and then what?
[Roy] And then we help
your sister do her Die Hard.
["Ode To Joy" playing over stereo]
Too much. It's too much.
- [music stops]
- Ooh. Sorry.
I've got a special guest with me, Ms. Die Hard.
Or should I call you...
this guy's sister?
- Mom.
- Hello, dear.
- I'm joining the other side.
- What? Why?
I wanna live in the real world with Roy.
I wanna help Summer with her Die Hard.
His name is Rick. And we have no way
of knowing if your generation is part of Morty.
Do you know how offensive that is?
Parenting like this pushed me
into religious radicalism.
- Bye.
- It's not...
Not a religion. But okay.
Ma'am, it's really not safe out here.
Also, it's time.
Are we going on the spaceship now?
- Pretty soon, Dad. Yeah.
- Are you lying?
You said it with that tone
that we use for dying people.
I won't lie to you.
You're dying, Dad. And we're...
not leaving.
- We're gonna live our lives out here.
- What? Why the fuck?
- Why?
- It's more real here.
The hell it is. My liver hurts.
I'm old here. I wanna be a teenage boy.
I wanna jump around
and do homework and jerk off.
But we would've been one tiny part of that.
In here, we get to be who we are.
Yeah. Great. Dead. I get to be a dead father.
Who do I make the--? [grunts]
- [EKG beeping]
- Who do I--?
- Who--?
- Don't talk.
- Gotta finish my zinger
- You don't.
Who do--? Who do--?
Who do I make the check out to?
"Best Daughter Ever...
incorporated"?
[EKG flatlining]
Thought you would've left by now.
I was hoping to get at least half of you home.
I can't hold out much longer.
I'm pretty much beating my heart voluntarily.
This is awkward, but the time dilation
has given me a chance to reflect.
- And I gotta say--
- There's no need for that.
I've come to tell you, I'm giving the go-ahead.
All of Morty will leave with you,
to the real world.
To be your grandson,
may we help Summer do her Die Hard.
I gotta say, I was not expecting that.
Why the change of heart?
My people are staying only out of loyalty.
I'm a relic. I don't represent them anymore.
You really are a good grandson, you know that?
- I'm proud of you, Morty.
- Please, call me Marta.
That's my video-game name.
Speaking of which, I do have one condition.
I must say I admire you, Ms. Die Hard.
You were a genuine McClane.
A most worthy Yankee doodle ruffian.
But now it's all come to an end.
And the quarterback, as they say, is toast.
I don't suppose you have a gun
taped to your back.
- What the hell does that mean?
- It's how Die Hard ends. Doesn't matter now.
Die Hard tapes a gun to his back?
That's the end of your perfect movie that
you've patterned your whole criminal life after?
It seems to have worked out pretty well
for me since you're about to die.
What was it you said? Ah, yes.
"Walkie-talkie Die Hard, motherfucker."
- Why are you laughing?
- Well, it's funny.
- The way you said "motherfucker." Just laughing.
- Okay. It's just that.
Oh, does that happen?
Does John McClane laugh,
and then Hans Gruber is confused
but then they start laughing together?
That actually does happen, yes.
- Wait. You knew their names?
- Not this whole time, no.
You left your book in the bathroom.
I read it while I took a shit.
I mean, mostly the ending.
[dramatic music playing]
[slow-mo shouting]
"...dip pee-doo," baby!
Nice timing, Grandpa Rick.
Tochter aus Elysium.
- Uh...
- Hi, remember me?
You shot me on that table, and the near-death
experience got me reflecting.
I didn't used to be like this. I ate a kid.
It was dark, and I thought he was a grown-up.
Ever since then, I haven't eaten anybody.
I was channeling all that pent-up
eating energy into this job.
But now...
thank you for freeing me.
Classic Tower Man.
Almost too on the nose. Right, Morty?
Sure. Whatever you say, Rick.
You know best. I trust you implicitly.
- Is he all right?
- Oh, yeah, he's fine.
Got him all out, every last piece.
What's with the jacked-up Roy machine?
Shouldn't you be taking that to repairs?
Nah, special order.
Some rich douche
wants his last game to keep running.
Hooked it up to an external battery.
We're supposed to store it.
- Weird.
- And get this.
- Game's still going, but Roy's dead.
- What?
He's just a corpse floating
at the edge of outer space.
But the game won't restart 'cause it's centered
on some old lady living a full life.
Sounds bad.
Well, put it in there.
Is anybody that wants this
later gonna be able to--?
Huh? Oh, yeah, everything's
cataloged and tracked.
People got the wrong idea from the size,
but it's all supported digitally.
- So I can put it anywhere. Here's fine?
- That's as fine as anywhere else.
[theme music playing]
- Why isn't anyone attacking him?
- It's fucking freezing out?
No, I think it's the sign.
Well, the sign from Die Hard 3
was clearly racist.
Obviously. But I think we went too broad.
"Everybody"? Who's that offending?
Everybody?
Ah, at this point, why even do it?
I wish my brother was still alive.