SENATOR: John F Walker,
you are hereby stripped of your title
and authority as Captain America,
effective immediately.
Everybody, grab what you can.
DOVICH: Power Broker will
catch up with us eventually.
- BUCKY: I've been making amends.
- No, you were avenging.
You want to climb out
of that hell you're in, do the work.
ISAIAH: She died while I was in jail.
They will never let a Black man
be Captain America.
SARAH: You gonna let Isaiah Bradley
get in your head?
If I was in his shoes,
I'd probably feel the exact same way.
But what would be the point
of all the pain and sacrifice
if I wasn't willing to stand up
and keep fightin'?
We will ensure the GRC vote never happens.
- I'm only here to kill the Falcon.
- You'll get your chance.
Tonight, we go to battle.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
KARLI: The movement is ready.
They're not going to stop.
Not unless we make them.
It's time.
REPORTER: (OVER TV) We have breaking news.
There's a complete lockdown
at the GRC meeting in Lower Manhattan
where authorities are saying
they're tracking multiple threats
from groups seeking to stop
the GRC's vote on global resettlement.
- There is a no-fly zone in effect...
- (SIREN WAILING)
...and the NYPD has the area secured
for the moment.
Everyone is urged to stay clear.
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
SAM: (OVER RADIO) I’m almost there.
What's the plan?
SAM: Karli's gotta be close.
- Keep your eyes open.
- Well, it could be anybody.
OFFICER: Sergeant Barnes.
SAM: And by the way,
I called in some backup.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you supposed to be here?
It's me.
- Sharon, what the hell are you doing here?
- Relax. No one's looking for me here.
- SAM: Is that Sharon?
- Unfortunately.
Hey, Sam.
I thought I'd get the band back together.
SAM: Thank you.
You're risking a lot coming here.
I hear pardons
aren't all they're cracked up to be.
Depends on the therapist.
SAM: They'll move
on the building soon. Be ready.
(WHOOSHING)
He's here. Do it now.
(HISSING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
MAN: Keep your head down.
Move toward the door, sir.
(COUGHING)
(ALL COUGHING AND SCREAMING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(WINGS WHOOSHING)
(MAN GROANS)
Sharon, Bucky,
what's going on on your end?
Nothing. All quiet.
I'm sorry, wait. Who are you?
- I'm Captain America.
- I thought he was on the Moon.
No one's moving toward the building.
Karli's not coming in.
She's trying to force everybody out.
- East evac teams...
- CAPTAIN AMERICA: It's a misdirect.
We gotta keep everybody inside.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You cost me a lot of money.
I wonder how much I can get
for your new bird costume.
A baguette and a few French fries.
(IN FRENCH)
The robes don't make the monk.
(CAPTAIN AMERICA GRUNTS)
You guys are gonna have to do something.
(OVER RADIO)
Don't let 'em out of the building.
- (ALARM BEEPS)
- Oops.
Here's one of them.
I'll get the evac.
Lennox, they're heading down
the east stairwell.
ANNOUNCER: (OVER SPEAKER)
This is an emergency evacuation.
Please proceed to your transports.
Groups one and two will leave
from secure vehicles in the basement.
Group three will leave
via air support on the roof
( INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Mr. Barnes, it's Karli.
(OVER CELL PHONE) Karli?
KARLI: Aren't you tired
of fighting for the wrong side?
(SCOFFS) I've done this before, kid.
I know how it ends.
It doesn't matter if I don't survive this.
I'm fighting for something
bigger than myself.
With all the bodies you've collected,
have you been able to say the same?
You don't think I ever fought
for something bigger than myself?
That's all I ever tried to do.
And I failed twice.
(SIREN WAILING)
( INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BEEPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CAPTAIN AMERICA GROANS)
You think your cause
justifies all this death,
but in the end,
the nightmares won't go away.
You're gonna remember
all the ones you killed.
Trust me.
Don't do this.
Don't go down this path.
If that's how you feel,
you should sit this one out.
Come on, you know I ain't gonna do that.
Well, thank you.
I'm glad you took my call.
You've been a big help.
Damn it!
LENNOX: Hostages en route.
ETA, six minutes.
Seriously, Bucky, you had one job.
- You worry about your guy.
- (ENGINE WHIRRING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Oh, my... I'm so sorry.
I didn't see you, I'm sorry.
SOLDIER: Hey!
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
- (MUFFLED EXPLOSION)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
(HISSING)
- Well, that's one down.
- How'd you manage that?
(GRUNTS)
Mercury vapor, amongst other things.
Boarding now.
- You better speed things up.
- (HELICOPTER HOVERING)
The chopper's about to take off.
- (GRUNTS)
- Bucky!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- I don't fly, man. That's your thing.
- (ENGINE REVS)
(GRUNTS)
(CLANKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (CLANKING)
- (GRUNTS)
(GEORGES GRUNTS)
(IN FRENCH) Au revoir!
(GLASS SHATTERS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (WINGS WHOOSHING)
Moving to the rendezvous,
about eight to ten minutes out.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(WINGS WHOOSHING)
(CAPTAIN AMERICA GRUNTS)
Redwing, see if anyone in there
has flight training.
(BEEPING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
DOVICH: Boss, Lennox ain't responding.
DEEDEE: We can still
get out of here before...
No. Diego's in the air.
The trucks are almost here.
Worst case scenario... we kill the hostages.
- We're supposed to use them to negotiate.
- To stop that vote.
Either way,
our message gets out to the world.
It doesn't even matter if we die.
The movement is strong enough
to continue without us.
Hope for the best. Prepare for the worst.
Hold tight. Move fast.
One world.
One people.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
(BLASTS)
(BEEPING)
(PILOT 1 SCREAMS)
(PILOT 2 SCREAMS)
(PILOT 2 GRUNTS)
- (HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
- (CLANKS)
(THUDS)
MAN: Yeah, man!
(CROWD CHEERING)
MAN: Whoo!
( INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIO)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(DRIVER GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS AND GROANS)
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(KARLI GRUNTS)
KARLI: We need a diversion.
Give him someone to rescue.
- GIGI: What do you mean?
- KARLI: Light it up.
- MAN: Help! Help us! Help!
- WOMAN: Get over here!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Hold on!
DOVICH: Let's go, get moving!
WALKER: Morgenthau!
Let's finish this.
I didn't mean to kill your friend.
I don't wanna hurt people
that don't matter.
You don't think Lemar's life mattered?
KARLI: Not to my fight.
I just want the people on that truck.
(SCREAMS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (CLANKS)
(GRUNTS)
We gotta get out of here.
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
MAN: Be careful. I've got you.
BUCKY: Go. Go!
MAN: Thank you for saving us.
You're welcome.
(DOVICH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(KARLI GRUNTING)
- (KARLI GRUNTS)
- (DOVICH SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS AND SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
- (GUN FIRING)
- (ALL SCREAMING)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
CAPTAIN AMERICA: A little birdie told me
you know how to fly a helicopter.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! (SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Whoa!
Boy, you just earned this ass-whoopin'.
Okay. What we're gonna do
requires perfect timing.
We're gonna count down from five.
When we get to one,
you're gonna grab the control.
Okay?
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Nice work, Ayla.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (CLANKS)
- (WOMAN GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
- WOMAN: Help! Help!
- MAN: Somebody help!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (CLANKS)
- (GRUNTS)
(KARLI GROANS)
(KARLI GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(GRUNTS)
(KARLI GRUNTS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(CREAKING)
(CREAKING AND CLANKING)
(PANTING)
(THUDS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CREAKING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GROANING)
(CREAKING)
- WOMAN: No!
- (ALL SCREAMING)
(CREAKING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
- (ALL CHEERING)
- Hell, yeah!
That's the Black Falcon there. I tell you.
Nah, that's Captain America.
(KARLI GRUNTS)
(CLANKING)
You of all people
bought into that bullshit?
I'm trying something different.
Maybe you should do the same.
(EXPLOSION)
(GUN FIRING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
This way.
BUCKY: Hey, Sharon. We're underground.
We entered the tunnel on William.
Heading south.
Looks like they split up. Here.
I got it.
(WHISTLING)
Dovich?
Dovich, is that you?
Drop your weapon, Karli.
I said drop it.
I'm disappointed in you.
That's what I was gonna say.
You know, when you came to Madripoor,
you reminded me of a young me.
I took you in, gave you an opportunity,
and you betrayed me.
Because you wanted
to control a world that hurt you.
But I wanted to change it.
I'm not interested in power or an empire.
- I have bigger dreams.
- SHARON: What, like this?
Come back and work for me again.
All of you.
We can make a difference together.
You just want me
because you need your muscle back.
Without us Super Soldiers, how much power
does the Power Broker really have?
More than you.
So, you're the Power Broker.
You hired Batroc to spy on me.
Karli, you know I'm always prepared.
Get outta my way.
I'm done with these games.
(IN FRENCH)
Now Power Broker...
you will pay me...
four times what you said you would.
(IN ENGLISH) Four times. Or...
(IN FRENCH)
I'll tell the whole world who you are.
(IN ENGLISH) Okay?
I don't do blackmail.
(GASPING)
Sam, stay back.
So, what's next, huh?
You kill ten this time,
then, what, a hundred?
Where does it end?
Please, let me help you.
Don't try and manipulate me.
Karli, don't!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I'm not gonna fight you!
Karli...
Stay down!
No.
The app says it's this way.
Let's go.
"Mercy bears
richer fruit than strict justice."
It's a great app.
( INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Thank you.
BUCKY: Lincoln, really?
Great man. Great quote.
Not when you say it.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Fight back!
Stop it!
Fight me! Fight back!
(GUN FIRING)
(EXHALES)
KARLI: (WHISPERING) I'm sorry.
(SOBBING)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
( INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIO)
REPORTER 1: What happened
to the Flag Smashers?
When did the government
make you Captain America?
- REPORTER 1: Is it still Falcon?
- REPORTER 2: Or is it Captain Falcon?
AYLA: Sam, thank you so much,
from all of us.
SENATOR: Sincerely.
You did your part in dealing
with those terrorists, now we'll do ours.
Are you still going forward
with resetting the borders?
Our peacekeeping troops
will begin relocating people soon.
The terrorists only set us back a bit.
Stop calling them terrorists.
What else would we call them?
Your peacekeeping troops carrying weapons
are forcing millions of people
into settlements around the world, right?
What do you think
those people are gonna call you?
These labels,
"terrorists," "refugee," "thug,"
they're often used
to get around the question, why?
LACONT: Those settlements
that happened five years ago,
do you think it is fair for governments
to have to support them?
Yes.
SENATOR: And the people who reappeared
only to find someone else
living in their family home,
they just end up homeless?
Look, I get it.
But you have no idea
how complicated this situation is.
You know what? You're right.
And that's a good thing.
We finally have a common struggle now.
Think about that.
For once,
all the people who've been begging,
and I mean, literally begging for you
to feel how hard any given day is...
Now you know.
How did it feel to be helpless?
Now if you could remember
what it was like to be helpless
and face a force so powerful
it could erase half the planet,
you would know that you're about
to have the exact same impact.
This isn't about easy decisions, Senator.
You don't understand.
(SCOFFS) I'm a Black man
carrying the stars and stripes.
What don't I understand?
Every time I pick this thing up,
I know there are millions of people
who are gonna hate me for it.
Even now, here...
I feel it.
The stares, the judgment.
And there's nothin' I can do to change it.
Yet, l'm still here.
No super serum,
no blond hair, or blue eyes.
The only power I have
is that I believe we can do better.
We can't demand that people step up
if we don't meet them halfway.
Look, you control the banks.
Shit, you can move borders!
You can knock down a forest with an email,
you can feed a million people
with a phone call.
But the question is,
who's in the room
when you make those decisions?
Hmm?
Is it the people you're gonna impact?
Or is it just more people like you?
I mean, this girl died trying to stop you,
and no one has stopped
for one second to ask why.
You've gotta do better, Senator.
You've gotta step up.
Because if you don't, the next Karli will.
And you don't wanna see 2.0.
People believed in her cause so much
that they helped her defy
the strongest governments in the world.
Why do you think that is?
Look, you people have just as much power
as an insane god
or a misguided teenager.
The question you have to ask yourself is,
"How are you going to use it?"
Sorry, I was, uh, I was texting and so,
all I heard was, um,
"a Black guy in stars and stripes."
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Nice job, Cap.
Thanks.
SAM: Sharon?
Blocking my light.
SAM: We gotta get you to a hospital.
She's not gonna listen.
(PANTING) It's not the worst thing
that's happened to me all week.
Told you.
MAN: Uh, Cap?
(BREATHING HEAVILY) I think
he's talking to you.
Look, I'm sorry
for how things ended down there.
For what it's worth,
suit looks good on you.
(CHUCKLES) Thanks.
All right, look,
can we get out of here, please?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I didn't forget my promise.
What's up?
So, we got eyes on the last
Flag Smasher that fell into the Hudson.
He's hurt but not down. Can you help?
Always.
(THRILLING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
( INDISTINCT CHATTER)
OFFICER: Confirming that prisoners
have cleared final processing.
We are transporting them to the Raft.
One world. One people.
- ( INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
- (SIRENS APPROACHING)
REPORTER: Four members
of the radical group, the Flag Smashers,
were killed today in a car bomb attack
as they were being transferred
to a high-security prison.
There are no suspects in the bombing.
The group had opposed
the global relocation efforts of the GRC,
who, just this week, had announced changes
in their overall policies
of repatriation and resettlement.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
VALENTINA: Oh!
Ooh. Hey, Walker, check your phone.
Looks like our friend, Zemo,
kinda got the last laugh, right?
Wow.
Couldn't have worked better
if I planned it myself.
Oh. Well, maybe I did.
No, I'm kidding, I didn't.
Or did I?
Anyway, it's gonna save people
a lot of paperwork
and a lot of redacting
and a lot of shredding.
(EXHALES, CLEARS THROAT)
What is he doing in there?
It's probably the helmet.
Walker! My God! Let's go!
(DOOR OPENS)
VALENTINA: Now, this is more like it.
It's the same, but black.
- Yeah, well...
- Yeah.
VALENTINA: Things are about to get weird.
So, when they do,
we're not gonna need a Captain America.
We're gonna need a U.S. Agent.
- WALKER: That's great.
- Keep your phone on.
- Will do, Val.
- Don't call me that.
Copy.
Thank you.
MRS. WALKER: U.S. Agent. (LAUGHS)
- I'm back! I'm back! I'm back! I'm back!
- (CHUCKLING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, what are you doing here?
It's late,
come in before someone call the cops.
What are you doing here?
It's not Wednesday.
I, uh, I have to tell you something.
About your son.
He was murdered.
What?
By the Winter Soldier.
(VOICE SHAKING) And that was me.
Why?
( INHALES)
I didn't have a choice.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
What you want, Black Falcon?
Hey, you need to learn some manners.
ISAIAH: He ain't a Falcon anymore,
but he's still Black.
I saw what you did out there.
And it seems, so did everyone else.
I heard the GRC was standing down
on those plans of theirs,
so you must have done somethin' right.
I ain't gonna lie.
You're special.
Thank you.
I mean, you ain't no Malcolm,
Martin, Mandela, but...
No argument there.
But I know what I've gotta do.
So, a Black Captain America, huh?
Damn right.
(CHUCKLES)
The fight you taking on
ain't gonna be easy, Sam.
SAM: Yeah, I might fail.
Shit, I might die.
But...
We built this country.
Bled for it.
I'm not gonna let
anybody tell me I can't fight for it.
Not after what everybody
before me went through.
Including you.
(VOICE SHAKING) Shit.
I almost bought that.
Man, do you ever lighten up?
Nope.
- Mm-mmm.
- (CHUCKLES)
Hey, why don't you clean up? There's, um...
Somethin' I wanna show you.
So, uh, where we going?
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Now, they'll never forget
what you did for this country.
Never.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh! There he is!
Where is everybody?
SENATOR: On behalf of
the United States Intelligence Community,
I'd like to offer you
and your family our sincerest apologies.
The Carter name has always been
synonymous with service and trust.
Today, we begin to set things right.
We begin to repay
some of the debt that is owed to you.
Thank you, Senator.
I've been waiting
to hear those words for a long time.
And we'd like to offer you a full pardon.
There may be
an opening in your old division.
Is that something you'd be interested in?
It would be my honor.
Welcome home, Agent Carter.
(CLAPPING)
( INDISTINCT MURMURING)
(LINE RINGING)
Start lining up our buyers.
Super Soldiers might be off the menu,
but we're about to have full access
to government secrets, prototype weapons,
you name it.
Should be something for everyone.
(MUSIC PLAYING)