Oh, my God, I cannot fucking believe this.
Here we fucking go!
Oh, jeez.
Pardon the interruption.
We are once again in the federal clear.
Rick, what the hell?
Are you a Turkey Dracula now?
Morty, is that a Pooplickian GamePod?
Actually it's the GamePod XL.
They say it's the most realistic
video-game console ever.
- I never got you that.
- Space Mom did.
She's in for the holiday weekend. Remember?
- In that case, let's go, let's get out--
- [Beth] I heard you smack the glass,
- if you bail, I'll disown you!
- [Space Beth] I'd say don't hop through a portal.
Wait, you can't.
Look at it this way, Morty.
Life is a subscription
and Thanksgiving is your family's yearly charge.
Wow, Dad, good job.
Rick, put some pants on.
Today has so few rules.
Yes, Patriarch.
Ding, ding, ding!
I'd like to make a toast.
Today is a day for thanks.
And for family.
And for remembering
all of those that have less.
- Okay, pick a scope.
- Pick a scope?
Can we please have a normal Thanksgiving?
- Seems like all the ones I remember.
- Good point.
- Baby, you, it's a toast--
- [both] Sorry!
Anyway, I'm thankful for my wife.
Beth. The Beth that chose me.
I'm so grateful to you
and I literally could not live without you.
- Aw.
- I really mean that.
If something were to happen to you
or if you were to leave me
or be unfaithful, I would die.
- Literally. Probably by my own hand.
- Okay.
I know how I'd do it.
Our first blender has an extra-long cord
and it was manufactured
before safety fuses,
so I'd draw a warm bath...
And blend some stuff. Good toast, honey.
To thankfulness.
To America?
To ending the toast?
[all] To ending the toast!
Just to be clear, I was saying I'd kill myself.
- God, we know.
- God.
[theme music playing]
Sorry, Jerry got all husband-y.
Yeah, do not miss that.
I was thinking we could set you up
in Jerry's man cave?
I'll sleep in my car.
It's got a Tardis thing going on,
bigger on the inside.
Dad calls it hack,
but my soaking tub begs to differ.
Maybe I'll trade you.
[grunting]
- My lower back.
- Oh, I got this.
- [back cracks]
- Jesus, that was great.
Well, you're me.
I find this is usually the biggest help.
Mm. Oh, I just love the Venusian stuff.
It's cool, I get insecure trying
to pronounce this crap too
but I got just the thing for that.
Here.
[in Venusian]
Okay, shoot that asteroid.
Now shoot that one.
Now shoot me in the face. This game's trash.
I didn't want to say anything,
but this does seem lame.
I thought it was maybe because
we've shot so many real asteroids.
- Let's look at the menu.
- There's the realism setting.
Oh. Cool. Also stupid.
The factory setting is four?
- What do we want, 10?
- No, do nine, I'm kidding.
- Shut up, Summer.
- Shut up, Summer. Put 10.
This is the same.
It's worse. It's-- Oh, I get it.
Okay. It's more real.
- The vast majority of space is empty.
- [Morty] What? Who cares?
Then what am I doing?
[Rick] Looks like you can record a video
for your kid in case you die.
Not a bad idea,
you're gonna be in space for a while.
May as well.
Um, hey. Son.
Uh, if you're seeing this, I starved to death
while looking for an asteroid.
Ugh. This is stupid.
You guys are trying
to convince yourselves it's cool
because you feel lame about it.
You know nothing about gamer culture.
- Bro, tell your son you love the shit out of him.
- Oh, I'm gonna!
Of course, we both can't sleep
at the same time.
Yeah, we do share a shitty back.
Turn around.
- At least let me--
- Yes, please.
- [back cracks]
- Oh, my God.
Okay I know we're not massage people,
but you need this.
You act
like this badass space cowboy,
but I know you're just
a scared little overachiever
- that keeps all her OCD right--
- Oh, my God.
Yeah. By the way,
you better be taking notes. I'm next.
- It's my back, you dumb bitch.
- Nice.
What?
[clanging noise]
- Well, I better get back to bed.
- Yup. Same.
Oh, so now you're
into highly realistic video games?
Maybe I decided real life
was too much right now
or maybe I'm not afraid
to change my mind about stuff.
Maybe mental flexibility
is stronger than stubbornness.
Nice manip', Sum-Sum!
Okay, I'm in the alley behind the library.
- Uptown or downtown?
- Shit, there's one uptown too?
I think I'm near the red line.
Is this Street Fighter?
[Summer] Street Fighterwhere you start
at the beginning of each fighter's day
and have to find each other to fight.
It's realistic. Not guaranteed a fight will happen.
That meter filling up
is us forgetting what made us so mad.
If anyone's interested
in a higher level of realism,
I'm booting up the O.G.
That's Original Game,
called a jigsaw puzzle, in the den.
Hey, gang!
Me and my space self are gonna
make a run to the Gloppy Drop System
for ice cream. Any flavor requests?
[both] Vanilla!
Why do you guys have to go all the way
to deep space just for ice cream?
Gloppy Dropulites
have less taste buds than humans.
Their ice cream is like a hospital bed.
It's designed for you to do less
so it does more.
Okay see you in a bit.
I'll get started sorting
all the obvious sky pieces.
Secret technique.
- I'm gonna eat your ass!
- It's on!
You will die in the street like a dog!
[sighs]
Stunning.
Thank you.
This is incredible.
[Space Beth]
Just glad I had something in your size.
[both laughing]
How far is Gloppy Drop?
And why do I always think I'm wearing a watch?
I actually have a pint of Gloppy Drop
on a little apartment orbiting Earth.
So we have time.
You have your own space station?
We have our own space station.
We're the same person.
There's differences.
- Like, one of us has no idea who she really is.
- Wrong.
But let's make a deal.
Let's trust ourselves enough to stop wondering
who we are when we're together.
We get to say anything to each other.
Things we'd never say to anyone else,
even ourselves.
What don't we say to ourselves?
How about,
"Wow, my ass looks good in that space suit."
I mean it. I'm a good looking woman.
That's nice of you to say.
I also find myself quite attractive.
We forgot the ice cream.
I want you back in my guts
like I'm one of your sick little fillies.
[both moaning]
Oh, goddammit, Morty!
You can't just take my controller.
Yes I can! It's mine.
Okay, Sum-Sum, gimme.
Make your own controller,
some of us need all the control we can get.
Fuck you!
So why are you so suddenly
into realistic video games?
I already was.
Yeah, but now you're into them the way I am.
You mean like staring at them in a numb trance.
Not judging, just noticing.
Yeah, you tend to notice stuff
a little before I do.
Eventually, you do notice.
And now we can both
not notice together, yes.
[Jerry] Oh, my God. Beth?
I thought you said you got ice cream?
[Beth] Yeah I-- it must be in the...
[Space Beth] Oh, the car!
We left it in the car.
[Jerry] Okay, good!
'Cause that would have been weird!
I worry things might become
more and more noticeable.
If he kills himself,
we're gonna have to get a new dad.
Jesus Christ, Summer!
Hey, Dad.
Um, what's this?
Making a controller.
This species of bionic space whale has
carbon wiring, great for smooth Gameplay.
I'm not killing it.
I'm replacing its esophagus
with a better one.
For free. It should thank me.
And it will, with its mind.
These things are telepathic,
they talk to you in dreams.
Does your replicator thing make ice cream
from the Gloppy Drop system?
Why would you want replicated
Gloppy Drop ice cream?
Crazy thing, I went with Space Beth
to get some
and we had such a great time
we forgot the ice cream!
Crazy, right?
That's a real question?
Maybe?
Come here, hold the pup down.
You're talking about an infinite father.
I've met myself out there infinite times.
infinite shit happens.
Including, as you put it,
forgetting the ice cream.
- You've forgotten the ice cream?
- Drill me for details when I'm drunker.
In the meantime,
don't worry about what's crazy.
You know, as the kids say, you do you.
Oh, thanks. Thank you so much, Dad.
One thing to keep in mind.
It's not your own ice cream
you're forgetting. It's your family's.
If you forget it too much,
you start having to keep secrets.
- And you're against secrets.
- Against? Hell no. Secrets are great.
I've had a pint of vanilla Gloppy Drop
in my fridge this whole time.
Take it. I'm just saying, lies pile up.
Like credit card debt.
You retain an advantage by staying liquid.
Gotcha. Well, I'd call this
a simple cash transaction.
Fun.
And done.
[both moaning]
Favorite Culkin.
[both] Kieran!
- Favorite song by Britney.
- [both] "Work Bitch."
Favorite hangover cure.
[both] Hair of the dog
with a guilty pleasure
- like Us Weekly.
- ...Humans Weekly
I told Dad.
I didn't have to. He knew.
I guess that's one reason
you didn't have to tell him.
[groans]
What'd he say?
We kind of talked in code.
I think he said it's fine until
it makes us feel indebted to our lessers.
That sounds like Dad.
Do we owe the family an explanation?
Do we have to spend our time together
figuring out how to please others?
I'm married.
We both are, but I'm in our marriage.
It's the defining difference between us.
There's no rule book that says you have to be.
What's gonna happen?
What is this?
Are we in love?
With ourself?
Does that make us the most or the least
healthy woman in the universe?
Anybody ever tell you
you're overly analytical?
Which I do love,
if that's what you need to call it.
I don't need to call it anything.
I would like to know
its shelf life.
I might know a way to gather that data.
- The Holodeck!
- Motel room! I like yours better.
[Jerry] Hmm. Uh...
[gasps]
[Jerry off screen] Beth! My Beth!
Well, not "my" Beth but, I finished!
It's done!
Kids do you know where your moms are?
Oh, you're busy with your GamePod.
Don't worry about it.
I'll find those two somewhere.
No! No, Dad, come play video games with us.
Okay, Dad, here's the infinite menu screen.
Oh, I don't know.
Here, here, I'll have
the console choose a game!
- Maybe let's skip this one?
- Really? Why? Looks fun!
Oh, okay, so we are a woman
married to a man
but having a sexual affair
with another woman.
Very spicy.
Very spicy, Jer.
Good job.
Looks pretty single player, kids?
Seriously, you two?
What the hell did you do in my holodeck?
Holy shit, you did a full
"San Junipero" in here?
Oh, my God, Beth, there's masturbating
and then there's masturbating.
- Dad, stop, I'm sorry!
- You'd know, old man.
Ugh! Look, this isn't my business and by all means
enjoy being sapphic horse girls together.
But you suck at doing it secretly.
We all know.
Including Jerry?
Dad's so in the dark
that he's enjoying a video game
about being in an affair.
- If you guys are doing this, you gotta tell him.
- Back off.
Take it easy. They're right.
Right that we have
to be twice as considerate
and twice as repressed because
some dick split us in two?
This is the shit I left.
This isn't. This is me.
This is the me
that doesn't tell you all to fuck off.
So allow me. Fuck off.
She'll tell her husband
what she wants when she feels like it.
And you can deal with it
or you can deal with me.
But you should know I have
all the Predatorweapons.
- Works for me.
- That's cool.
I guess it's time for ice cream.
Come on, kids, you're inhaling this stuff.
Your moms went to space.
Did you even thank them for doing it?
Thanks for doing it, Moms.
Very selfless of you.
Eat your ice cream however you want.
Nothing good lasts forever.
[in Venusian]
Okay, come on, it's Thanksgiving.
The least we can do is speak English.
Jerry, I had sex with your wife.
Or I'm your wife and had sex
with the clone you sleep with.
Your pick. We had sex. We loved it.
Beth Sanchez sure is something, huh?
I think I'll ask her to prom.
Jerry, for your own sake,
stay away from Beth Sanchez.
Worst case, she says no.
No, Jerry. Worst case she says yes.
She's too much woman for you.
Yeah, maybe she'd find
your simple naïveté endearing,
but she's intense.
Sooner or later, she'd tear you apart.
Ah. I'd be lucky
to be torn apart by Beth Sanchez.
- What the fuck?
- Dad's a bug! Dad rolled into a bug!
Oh, yeah, forgot I installed that.
Why does Jerry have a Pill Bug Protocol?
It's an emotional defense system.
I got drunk with Jerry one night
and he said it's what he wanted.
Don't blame me, I wanted tattoos.
He's in perfect health
and can unroll when he chooses to,
but can also stay in metabolic
hibernation pretty much indefinitely.
It's a cool power to have,
like if you have to fly coach
or if Summer asks you what you
thought of Wonder Woman 1984.
How do we undo it?
Only he can. That's the point.
It's total safety.
Even I can't reverse it.
If you try to pry him out and hit a nerve,
he'll literally turn into a Shrek.
In his own sad way, he's taken control.
This is classic Jerry. He'd rather be
a bug than have a conversation.
Have you heard
the way you start conversations?
You ladies discuss responsibility
while I get stoned
and play video games with your kids.
- [Rick] Fuck. More forest!
- [Morty] Look around!
[Summer] Try heading north.
- [Morty] Shit.
- [Rick] What the fuck?
[Summer] Maybe keep heading north?
- Ew. What the hell?
- [Morty] What happens in the shadows?
Jerry, sweetie?
If you can hear me, please, unroll.
He doesn't want to.
It's a little late to worry
about what he wants.
Jesus, Beth, don't fall for this.
This isn't love, it's a tantrum.
Yeah, but his tantrum is self-destructive.
Yours is destructive.
Maybe that's why I'm the one that loves him.
He worries. He wants to do right.
He's ashamed when he fails.
Aren't those things you love about me?
You want me to be like him?
You want me to propose?
Threaten to kill myself?
No. I love you the way you are
and I did it forever in a video game.
But in life, things go wrong.
Things stop working.
I like to fix those things and when I can't,
I'm pretty useless. Like my husband.
I don't get it. You're the house wife
and I'm the space lady,
but you're the one
that chewed me up and spit me out?
I don't want to just forget about you.
Me neither. It's a problem.
But we know someone that owes us a solution.
Oh, shit, we're out of the forest.
We found a clearing.
Go check it out! Go check out the clearing!
[Morty] Vampires? Come on!
That's not realistic!
It's obviously set in a world
where vampires hunt in clearings.
- How did you--?
- I'm working with the same information you are!
No more screen time
until your homework's done, Dad.
- What did that mean?
- We refuse to care.
You really came of age this Thanksgiving.
How old are we?
We've had a million Thanksgivings.
Can I explain how irrational this is?
Asked the guy that cloned his daughter.
Will I ever live that down?
- [both] No.
- You guys are having me
Eternal Sunshine all the Multiplicity porn scenes
from your minds.
- Sounds right.
- Basically.
Meanwhile, everyone around you,
your father, your cuckold husband,
your jaded children will just
happily and silently bear the burden
because it's more practical
for them than the truth
and you don't care
because it won't be your problem.
Solid repipe.
It's like he has a lifetime
of experience as a selfish ass.
[in Venusian]
When this fails and you fall in love again
and attack me for taking part in this,
I'm gonna say I tried to talk you
out of it for hours. In truth, I don't care.
- Three, two--
- [Jerry] For God's sake,
all of you, grow up.
- You un-rolled!
- What the hell!
Plot twist, Deus Ex Husbanda.
Oh, don't lobotomize yourselves for my comfort.
I may be a man but I'm also a baby,
and babies don't take responsibility
for other people's suffering.
I should never have said
I'd kill myself if you left me.
It's not true. All I'd do
is pack my shit and cry
while I look for a job on Starbucks' Wi-Fi.
And that's what I'm gonna do.
So the two of you can get
clone lesbian married by a robot
and finger yourselves on the moon
while laughing in Martian French
about my weird little dick!
Jerry, wait.
Jerry, don't leave angry.
Should I float out on a lotus leaf?
I have to be twice as confident
because my wife cheated on me
with herself?
It's not even cheating.
Oh, you here to help? You suck.
You don't know which one
is your real wife.
If it's me,
have you been cheating with a clone?
I'm not the clone but she has a point.
What a provocative conversation
it would've been great to have
before the two of you,
and I am counting two,
gave each other unfairly expert orgasms
while mocking my weird little dick!
You're the only one
who keeps saying "weird" and "little."
You've both seen it! You've both seen each other
and now you want to tell me all about it
but it's a little late.
Oh, my God. You're not mad that it was about you.
You're mad that it wasn't.
He wanted to permit our love.
Okay, it's not Handmaid's Tale
to loop in your husband.
I agree, we made a mistake.
Oh, because we should've noticed ourselves
losing control and gone to Sexmaster Jerry
and said, "Oh, pretty please, Jerry,
can I make out with myself?"
Yes, you may.
Yeah, see. Not so hot when it's above board,
homewreckers.
Oh, so we won't enjoy this?
Well, hold on, this is weird.
Weird and permitted.
- Wait, you like this?
- Who cares what he likes?
- I do.
- I might. And if she likes it, I permit it.
- You little pervert.
- You like a little pervert.
- I like humiliating a little pervert.
- I approve. Carry on.
I'm freaked out by how hot this is.
- [Space Beth] Am I permitted to do this?
- [Jerry] Until further notice.
- [Beth] I love it.
- [Jerry] Then it's permitted.
[Space Beth] Because you like whatever she likes.
Because you're a worm.
[Jerry] I will allow that assessment.
Pass the salt?
Damn it.
- [Beth] I allow this.
- [Space Beth] Then it's required.
- [Jerry] I approve.
- [Space Beth] Get over there.
- [Jerry] Good idea.
- [Beth] Wow, oh, okay. Honey?
[Jerry] I'm fine if you are.
- [Space Beth] You're never fine, shut up.
- [Jerry] Okay but--
- Okay. Wow.
- [Beth] This is not how I pictured this but--
- [Jerry] I have zero complaints.
- [Space Beth] I know what you want.
- [Jerry] I do not disagree with that.
- [Beth] What if we...?
- [Space Beth] Are you serious?
- [Jerry] Is this making fun of me?
- [Space Beth] Well, is that bad?
- [Jerry] I'll allow it. [shouting]
Jesus Christ. Fix the portal gun, Rick.
Morty, you asking me
makes me wanna do it less.
Okay, Thanksgiving!
Let's talk about Thanksgiving!
Who's thankful for what?
Go, Summer, you first.
Um, I guess I'm thankful, for, like, water?
Perfect! Wonderful!
Morty, what about you?
Fucking--
Are you fucking kidding me? Why? Why?
Discovery Channel!
- Discovery Channel, why?
- [both sobbing]
Okay. Just eat your food.
Everyone eat the food.
[Jerry] I'm sorry, is this?
Well, bye, kids!
I'll keep an eye out for my grandkid in space.
Your what? Oh. Right. Naruto.
Thanks for visiting, Space Beth.
Well, seems like we all learned
a little lesson this weekend.
At least, I know I did.
Me too, Jerry. Me too.
[garbage disposal whirring]
[theme music playing]
Hello there, Jerry. How can I help you today?
Howdy. Yeah, just here to hang.
Oh, I'm sorry, sweetie.
You can't come here by yourself.
Why not? It's just me in there.
Well, not that this is something you'd do,
but sometimes we have Jerrys come here
and try to touch other Jerrys.
Oh, no, that's not good.
Uh, well, see you later.
- Okay.
- Thank you.