- Captain Daly.
- Report.
A non-Federation vessel,
jumped straight out of white space.
Right in front of us.
Valdack.
- That can't be...
My data scan indicates a heavily-armoured
Gorgan Dreadnought.
Vessel ID number 9864321.
- Thank you, Dudani.
Valdack must've hijacked it
from the Fermi hub and tracked our position.
Tulaska, shield status?
- Shield's 100%.
Helmsman Packer?
- Captain?
Prime rear thrusters.
- Rear thrusters primed.
If that's Valdack,
he'll rip us to shreds.
Captain, we have to surrender,
there's no other way.
Let's not lose our heads, Lieutenant Walton.
Shield at 68%.
Heavy damage reported,
decks six through ten.
Fires in med centre and major rupture
to cargo bay Alpha.
We've got no choice, captain!
Do you want me to open comms
with Valdack's craft, captain?
Negative.
Shields are 54%.
There's no way out.
- Captain, please.
- Not now, Walton.
Helmsman Packer, take us
into that asteroid gas cluster.
Into the cluster?
That's suicide, sir.
It is our only chance.
That gas cluster is charged
with ionised pyron particles.
If our shields hold, we can use them
to increase our photon intensity.
Packer, increase thrusters.
Shield's at 43%.
It'll tear the ship apart, captain!
Walton, you are a Space Fleet officer,
act accordingly.
Shield's at 32%.
Valdack's not following.
- Packer, turn us around.
Tulaska, charge photon bolts.
All charged, captain.
Fire.
His hull's breached, shield's gone.
He's defenceless.
Lieutenant Lowry, open comms.
- He's already hailing us, captain.
- On screen.
Captain Daly, may you drown
in the venom of 900 Tragorian snakes!
You are defeated, Valdack.
Return the plasmorthian crystal
and we'll cause you no more damage.
You must think me a fool, captain.
I know the crystal's capabilities
and I will die before I give it up.
I gave you a chance, Valdack,
showed you mercy.
Reflect on that while you can.
Arrgh!
- Close comms.
Tulaska, destroy his ship.
- Yes, captain.
That was incredible, captain!
You saved our lives.
- I'm so sorry I lost it back there, captain.
Not for the first time, Walton.
I should know by now never to doubt you.
Please, forgive me.
At ease, Walton.
- Captain!
Sensors indicate an escape pod ejected
from Valdack's ship before detonation.
He's escaping with the crystal.
- Want me to plot a pursuit course, captain?
No.
We'll let him go...
for now.
It's great decision-making, captain.
Three cheers for Captain Daly.
Hip hip...
- Hooray!
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow,
for he 's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ F or he's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ And so say all of us. ♪
God bless you, Captain!
God bless you!
Thirteenth floor, welcome to Callister.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Hey.
Uh, Elena, my pass doesn't work.
You must renew on first of each month.
Yeah, I know that, but the first
was on the weekend, so...
OK.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Prepare to enter
the most immersive gaming experience
in years: Infinity, from Callister Inc.
Morning, Mr Daly.
Helmsman Packer.
- Huh?
Uh, I mean, Mr Packer.
Nate.
OK.
Hey, are you making coffees?
- Yeah.
Do you think maybe you could
make me one too?
Sure, sure. What do you want?
Just vanilla latte.
Skimmed milk.
Yeah, good call.
Those are some very, very big numbers
and we might just have to hold you to that.
Well no, yes, of course.
Oh, are you OK, man?
I guess you didn't see my gym bag.
Come on, get up.
I'm sorry, bud.
- OK.
You left it...
You're gonna do it for me,
you're gonna make it good.
You're a God to me, at least.
Oh, no, the ladies' bathroom is that way,
the sign's kind of confusing.
You're Robert Daly, right?
Right.
Yeah, hi.
I'm Nanette, Nanette Cole.
Um, I started here today coding on the
update and I...
I just wanted to, uh, pass on my admiration
to the person
who actually designed Infinity.
The procedural algorithm is, is amazing.
It's just some beautiful code.
Thank you.
That's actually the reason
that I wanted to work here.
You must be busy, I'm so sorry.
- No, no, it's fine.
Sorry.
- No.
Uh, well, just fangirling, sorry, um...
Ooh, vintage!
Yeah, it's Space Fleet.
Wow!
- It's a TV show.
Before your time and before my time,
actually.
But it was visionary.
Is this on, like, tape?
Yeah, I've got the VHS, DVD, Blu-ray...
The whole thing, seasons one to six.
Netflix has it these days.
"Aboard the spaceship USS Callister," OK.
Yeah. So, OK, so, Callister is like the...
The...
- Yeah, when we set up the company...
I suggested that we call it Callister
as kind of a little tribute.
Walton didn't really get the reference
but he let me have that one.
Mini-skirted damsels.
A little cold for that in space.
That is just what a Bargradian sand warrior
would say.
Bob, Christmas is closing in
like a Goddamn meteor.
We've got customers all over our balls,
waiting for the Infinity update.
Tell me it's gonna be up and running
before the weekend.
I, I'll ask Kabir...
You're CTO, don't ask anybody anything.
You should be telling people things
like I'm fucking telling you right now.
- Alright, I'll talk to him.
Good.
- I'm sorry.
OK.
- Hello?
- Hello.
Sorry, I couldn't find a good moment to...
So...
Oh, you must be new.
I'm James Walton, I run the company.
- Hi.
- Well, we run the company, kind of.
Bob here is the hardware
and I am the shiny front end.
I'm Nanette Cole.
- Which department?
Engine Architecture.
- And this your first day?
Uh, yeah.
Have you had the tour?
No, I...
Please, allow me.
OK.
It was so nice to meet you.
Just a little bit
cos it's a big department.
Uh, I sit up here.
You know, people call it a care-free
environment, I call it care-full.
- Interesting, OK.
- Not scary...
- Yeah.
- I'm excited to see what happens.
Dudani?
Kabir?
- Oh!
Mm! Mr Daly.
Do you have the latest ETA
on the update patch?
It's just there's still some runtime errors.
The thing is, Mr Daly, we could have it
ready by end of play today
but if we had time, we could alter the
trading mechanics
and tweak the critical hit system,
but of course that'd add another week.
Maybe ten days or so.
Mr Daly?
Yeah. Yeah, do all of that.
Thank you
- All...? OK, we're on it.
Welcome back, Captain.
Have you located Valdack's position?
Not yet but our sensors are scanning
every star system between here and Valatros.
So, your answer is no?
Uh...
I'm afraid so, sir.
You...
are pathetic, Walton.
What are you?
What's that?
Pathetic.
So, Valdack's out there...
somewhere, and you village idiots
are asleep at the wheel.
You're not just disgraceful,
you're disgusting - all of you.
So, can you do one thing?
Can you find Valdack?
I'm not asking, I'm telling you.
Understand? Hmm?
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes, captain.
- Yes.
Aye, captain.
Huh?
Well, alright.
Tulaska, check security protocols.
If they've expired, you're in trouble.
Yes, captain.
Dudani, have you checked those probe results?
No room for errors.
Of course, captain.
Helmsman Packer?
- Captain?
Vanilla latte.
Skim milk.
At once.
Walton?
Exit game.
Hi, Nanette.
Feel like you have everything you need here?
- Mm-hmm.
That's a nice sweater.
- Oh, thank you.
Cashmere?
Mr Daly.
Got that new ETA on the update patch.
New ETA?
Yeah, it's all good but now we're looking
at December 24th for rollout.
We don't patch until Christmas Eve?
Well, yeah, I mean, with the alterations
you approved.
OK, OK.
Thank you.
- OK.
Hey, Robert.
- Hi.
Um, I was just gonna fix a coffee,
do you want one?
Sure.
- OK.
Uh, vanilla latte, with skim milk.
Okey-dokes.
- OK.
Absolutely.
Mm-hmm, well, yes, they are great numbers.
OK. Mm-hmm.
Ta-ta.
Total fucking shitwit.
Do you want coffee?
Um, Brushed Suede, thank you.
So how you settling in? Are you settling in?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Everyone here is really friendly.
And, um, it is not like my last job,
thank God.
Yeah?
It was a toxic workplace, you know?
My boss was a major-league bully
and it's not like here.
Like with, uh, Mr...
- Walton.
Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, he's a really good guy.
He's a bit of a player.
Chuck a ham sandwich across the room,
he'll fuck it before it hits the ground.
But he's basically an alright bloke.
OK, well...
There's, uh, two bosses here anyway,
so, I guess...
Two how?
Robert Daly.
Oh!
I mean, well, yeah, technically.
Mr Daly is actually the whole reason
that I'm here.
Really? Interesting.
I mean, who wouldn't want to work
under an incredible mind like that?
You know, his coding is... It's sublime.
Do you have a thing for him?
Daly? No, no.
No. It's not like that.
It's purely professional.
I like his code.
Oh, fucking hell, I was gonna say,
you know...
Don't be too nice to him,
cos he gets a bit stare-y.
Wide berth, that's my advice.
Wide berth.
OK.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
There you go.
- Thank you.
- Bye!
- No bye! I'm coming.
No, suck a dick, Karl.
Welcome to Callister.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Goddamnit, Robert!
Christmas Eve, really?
Not OK.
Hello?
Oh, boy, it looks like
there's a new girl in the office.
What's your name, hun?
Come in. Let me fix you a drink.
We have everything
from Bengarian phlegm shots to, uh...
Ooh, distilled root blood
from the Cangor quadrant.
What's your poison?
Some of this actually is poison,
so don't be shy.
Am I dreaming?
Yeah. No, no, 'fraid not.
I remember dreaming.
- Me too.
But where, where am I?
This is USS Callister, Space Fleet's finest.
Exploring the furthest reaches
of the known universe and beyond.
We are its loyal space crew and now,
apparently, so are you - cheers.
Your name? Babe, what's your name?
- Nanette.
But we've met.
Maybe, in the real world.
I wouldn't have no way of knowing.
What do you mean?
You, you, you'd better sit down.
No, I don't, I don't wanna sit down.
I wanna know what's going on.
You're onboard Robert Daly's ship.
Robert Daly the CTO?
Here, he's Captain Daly, our fearless leader.
Yeah, you're seriously gonna need
to sit the fuck down.
Welcome.
You are, um, hey, hey, you're the intern
from work right, Nate?
Packer, Nate Packer.
Wait, so I'm still just the intern out there?
Jesus...
You're, um... You're...?
Dudani, diagnostics.
Welcome.
Right...
You're the receptionist, right?
- Elena.
Your skin is blue...
- Weird blue alien skin, I know.
It's fucked up, almost sort of racist.
Uh...
- OK, Walt!
Fix her something.
Something she'll recognise. Vodka.
So what's it like out there now?
- What?
- Like, what year is it?
- Wait, don't do her head in.
What year? I... I saw you today.
Ooh, did you see me? Did I look thin? Hmm?
Like wheatgrass, yoga thin?
Can we not pop her fucking mind?
Someone needs to be straight with me
right now.
OK.
OK, listen.
This is Infinity.
That's what we're all inside,
that's where all of this exists.
Infinity, the game?
Daly's got his own modded version of Infinity
reskinned to look like his favourite TV show.
Space Thing? Space Thing...
Space Fleet, hence the groovy decor.
And this tasteful get-up.
Infinity. That, that's an online game,
like a multiplayer deal... This...
This is his development build,
sealed off so he can control it.
He keeps it offline so the custom code
he's written can't be detected and deleted.
Mm, yes. It's a bubble universe
ruled by an asshole god.
He...
put us in, in here?
Mm-hmm. Drink your vodka.
How do we get out?
- No, really, drink it.
Drink it.
You can't leave.
- What!
None of us can.
Because you're not actually you.
What?
- I know it's mental...
but you're a copy of you.
A digital clone.
- No.
No I am... I'm me.
- I am me. I'm me.
- No, not the real you.
Daly's created an identical
digital version of you -
of all of us - from your DNA,
he'll have harvested it somehow.
Oh, he told me he got mine
from the rim of a smoothie cup.
He retrieved Packer's juices
from the bathroom...
Man, you have got to let that go,
she does not need details.
Yeah, basically he's got a gizmo.
I theorise an advanced biometric
DNA virtual clone...
Yes, he's got a fucking gizmo,
that's what I said.
He fed your DNA in,
he put you inside his computer
and bam, you pop up here like a Pop Tart.
Yeah, we've all been through it.
He brings us in for different reasons,
just shit we did in the office.
I called him out for staring.
I reset admin permissions
on a test build for 14 minutes.
Insufficient smiling.
I brought him the wrong sandwich.
OK, never mind the reasons, the point
is that we're stuck in Daly's playground
and that's all you need to know.
This is a dream.
Yeah, it has to be.
It's more like an eternal waking nightmare
from which there is no escape.
No, no. No, no, no!
For fuck's sake,
I'm trying to break her in gently!
The quicker she gets it, the easier it'll be.
Daddy's home.
He'll be here any moment.
No... I'm gonna get out of here!
Whoa, you gotta stay on the bridge.
He controls everything,
he does shit to make us...
Get off!
- cooperate. You have no idea.
I'm trying to help you.
- Leave it.
He's gonna fuck us all up
if she doesn't play ball!
She's gonna have to work it out for
herself, like we all did.
There's gotta be a way out... Come on!
Lieutenant Cole, welcome aboard.
Crew, we have a new member of the team.
Science Officer, Nanette Cole.
Please take your post.
I believe we've finally managed
to track Valdack to an unchartered planet.
No.
Take your post, that is an order.
I'm not doing this.
The whole thing's much better
if you let yourself get into it.
If you think that I'm playing along
with your Space Force bullshit...
Space Fleet.
- Whatever!
You can think again.
- This is my ship.
I am your captain, an order is an order.
- Then go fuck yourself...
sir.
OK.
So, we're doing it this way.
What, are you gonna throw a fireball?
Oh, dear!
You can't see, you can't breathe.
Unpleasant, isn't it?
Do you submit?
You won't die, you know.
No-one dies in here unless I want them to.
I can keep you like this forever
if I feel like it.
Forever gasping for breath
with a mouth that isn't there.
Do you submit?
Good girl.
Lieutenant Cole, Valdack's hideout -
triangulate the signal, please.
It's any button, they're all the same.
Well?
I'm getting a signal from a classified
planet, Rannotch...
Rannoch.
Planet Rannoch.
Excellent.
Dudani, prepare the transmat system.
Of course, Captain.
- Walton, Packer, Lowry with me.
We'll transport down to the planet,
reclaim the crystal
and bring Valdack to justice.
Actually, Cole...
you come, too.
Perfect opportunity for you to prove you're
more than a recommendation
from Space Fleet. What do you say?
Mr Dudani, transport.
- Aye aye, captain.
Breathable atmosphere.
Scanning for plasmorthium traces.
Crystal's this way, let's go.
- Nate... Hey, Nate...
- Helmsman Packer, OK?
You gotta call me Helmsman Packer.
He hates it when we don't use
our proper titles.
OK. You got a gun, so...
Not gonna happen.
- Take him out!
Then give it to me!
- OK, one, our guns don't even work.
Only his does - and two, the motherfucker
is invincible, OK? Come on, let's go.
At least you've got a gun.
Captain...
- Shh.
We meet again, Captain Daly!
We're trapped!
Not advisable.
My plasma grenade will turn you
into screaming soup.
He's not going to kill us, captain.
He had the element of surprise,
he'd have done it when he had the chance.
Haven't worked out how to use the crystal,
have you, Valdack?
It's true, I require
your Space Fleet knowledge.
But it's also true
that you're gonna give it to me.
Don't be so sure.
Jesus, I...
- Shh!
Let's see how your resolve holds up
once you're devoured one by one
by my Arachnajax!
Holy shit! Oh, my God!
We're all gonna die!
Killing us won't make us tell you
how the crystal works, Valdack.
We will never...
Hold on, I think my pizza's here.
Pause game.
What's happening?
You heard him, he paused the game
cos he's got a pizza delivery, out there.
Hold on!
Watch out, he'll be back soon.
That's good. This launcher's heavy as shit!
How you holding up?
You know, we're existing.
How you doing, Gillian?
Well, yeah.
- You look great...
- Her name's Gillian.
She was in marketing.
- Yeah, Daly turned her into... THAT
cos she wouldn't play along
when he cloned her into here.
This universe is littered with things
like her -
poor fuckers who stepped out of line.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
Here comes Captain Dick.
Hey.
Hey, hey!
"Get you!
I'm gonna get you..."
Hey, hey!
If we die, the secret of the crystal
dies with us, Valdack.
Oh, my God! We all are gonna die!
Valdack?
What is it, captain? Final words?
Over there!
A naked lady!
Where? Really?
Great plan, captain.
Unparalleled tactics, captain!
We've fought many battles,
haven't we, captain?
We have.
- And I've been a good adversary for you...
have I not?
Then please...
...end it.
Please...
Killing in cold blood
is against Space Fleet code.
Wish I could help.
Pl...
Sorry, bud.
Take him to the brig.
No...
- Dudani.
- Captain?
Transport us aboard.
- Yes, Captain.
- No more...
- It's OK.
- Hip hip...
- Hooray!
Hip hip...
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow,
for he's a jolly fellow ♪
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ And so say... ♪
- Oh, my fuck!
That wasn't very nice.
Today, I will show you mercy.
Great mercy-showing, captain.
- Shh!
Tomorrow, you should reconsider
your amenability.
I may not be feeling so benevolent.
Exit game.
Oh, fucking hell.
This was tense.
I don't like tense.
Drink?
- Mm-hmm.
- So how was the mission?
- Wasn't too bad.
Usual standoff storyline.
Ooh, saw Gillian from marketing.
- Oh, that's nice.
There is no way that I am kissing
that asshole.
Then he's just gonna get more
and more pissed.
How about you kiss him, then?
- You get used to it.
It's quite... There's no tongues.
If that's any consolation,
there's never any tongues.
Doing tongues is not Space Fleet way.
Mm. It's not like it can get beyond kissing,
anyway.
What do you mean?
Oh, you haven't noticed?
What are you doing?
Please... Please don't do that, don't...
Oh, my God! Oh, oh!
- Yes.
Oh.
- There's no genitals in Space Fleet.
This is a wholesome universe.
He must've modified our code that way.
Mm, we're all the same.
If you don't believe me, take a look
down there.
We have tried grinding our mounds
together out of sheer boredom.
No sensation at all.
Can't even shit.
Can't even have the basic fucking pleasure
of pushing out a shit.
I miss taking shit.
OK.
Stealing my pussy is a red fucking line.
We are gonna get this bastard.
- No.
Yeah.
- We've tried a million times.
No way out.
Walton. Come on, Walton.
Like I said, he's an asshole god!
Mm-mm.
Daly's smart but he's not a god.
He's a coder.
He is fallible.
Kabir.
What was that thing
he was holding in his hand?
That scanner thing?
His Omni coder,
primary communications device.
You said he kept his version
of the game offline.
But the Omni coder made contact
with the outside world
when the pizza came, so it's gotta be
connected to his, uh...
his home system, at least.
The Omni coder's gone.
- It loads
when he loads and it goes
when he goes and that's the only one.
No.
There has got to be a way to connect.
You won't hack in, I've tried.
I haven't.
Bingo.
Oh, that's good.
- Yeah.
This is part of Infinity's front end.
You can invite a friend
with a custom message.
A message to outside?
Just one. 140 characters maximum.
So who you gonna contact?
Thirteenth floor.
Welcome to Callister.
Hey, Elena.
Hi.
You need me to buzz you in?
- What? Uh, no, no, I...
I got that for you.
- Oh, thank you.
After you.
Um, Mr Daly, hi.
Hi.
Um, can I talk to you for a second?
Did you just send me an Infinity invite?
Wha...? No.
It was really weird,
it had a message attached.
Something about people trapped in a game.
Probably just a spam bot.
Firewall doesn't always get them all.
Yeah.
- I wouldn't, I wouldn't worry about it.
Didn't open a link, did you?
Oh, God, no.
Maybe just upgrade your security software.
- Alright.
Have a good one.
Oh... Yeah...
Could you please, please cut that shit out?
Trying to make it like a hobby.
Oh... Yeah, yeah...
Oh... That's good.
Guys!
Way too early, he's only been
at work a few hours.
She got the message!
I did it. I...
That's me!
That's me or the cops or something!
Oh, we are getting out of here.
What is Space Fleet?
I'll tell you what it is.
It is a belief system...
founded on the very best of human nature.
It is a goal for us to strive towards...
For the betterment of the universe.
For the betterment of life itself.
And you assholes are fucking it up!
- I did it. I did it. I did it!
I sent the message. It was me.
No-one else was involved.
I swear.
I tried the carrot, now meet the stick.
- No, no.
This is gonna make you happy, Daly,
cos you're sick.
And you need help.
No, don't, don't!
Captain, captain, please.
OK, look, she's new. She'll behave.
We'll all behave.
Just let her off... Let her off this once,
pl... Please.
OK.
No! Don't kill her, no!
No, no! No!
You know what makes me happy?
The look on your face right now.
Dudani, Walton, Tulaska,
take this thing to the brig with Valdack.
Packer, find a barren planet
we can dump her on.
And you, you can just stay here
and think about your attitude.
Exit game.
Update patch.
The update patch!
It's there, there.
So what? It's a wormhole.
Uh-uh, that is the Christmas update patch
pre-installing itself.
The wormhole - it's just how the game's
expressing the uplink.
So?
So Daly's custom build
is still connected to the Internet.
In some way.
If this is another one of your plans,
just stop
before somebody else gets monsterfied.
No, no, this, this can work.
We can't get online access from the ship,
he'll have crippled permission.
Yes, but what if we fly into the wormhole?
Like, on purpose?
We'd hit the system firewall.
- Exactly.
And have our rogue coding deleted.
- Yeah.
Deleted, as in...?
- As in die.
Whether it's dying would depend largely
on your philosophical position
regarding sentient code but...
- We would cease to exist, that's true.
But we'd be free.
We'd be free.
But this is academic since we have no
means of getting to the wormhole.
There's no way to pilot the damn thing
without Daly here.
He'd stop us like that.
What about if he's logged in
but on pause?
Like when his pizza came,
he was just frozen there.
Flying would be possible but that wormhole's
a whole parsec away,
we'd never reach it before he got back.
Unless we stalled him for longer.
And that we do how?
If we can get Daly's Omni coder,
we can make a phone call, right?
Theoretically, yes, but...
If we can get real me on the phone again,
I, um...
I may have some leverage.
- Leverage?
Mm-hm.
- On yourself?
Like what?
My, uh, photocloud account.
I know the password, obviously,
there's some pretty...
interesting images on there that I should
have deleted a while ago but I didn't.
So, we can blackmail me.
I'm pretty sure that I'd do anything to keep
those photos from getting out.
Must be pretty pictures.
- Look.
If this is going to work,
we all have to be in on it.
OK?
Flying into certain death in a wormhole beats
another 10,000 years with Captain Ass.
I'm in.
- OK.
Me too.
Also me.
Well, I am out.
Daly won. Daly's always won.
We just have to get on with it
cos we don't have a chance.
Yes, we do.
We fly into the wormhole
and we are extinct.
We are gone. We are rid of his shit.
Sounds peachy.
What is with you?
Don't you wanna fight back?
Why won't you fight back?
Tommy.
Who is Tommy?
- He's my son.
He's six years old.
At least he was when I woke up in here.
See, in the early days of this ship,
it was just me and Daly.
I was his pet project.
He tried everything to break me
and I withstood it all
cos just thought there was still a chance
I could get out and see my boy again.
In a way I was right,
I did get to see him again.
Just not the real him.
Daly told me what happened.
Back on the outside, the real me, uh...
brought Tommy to work one day,
show him around.
He would've loved seeing
all those computers.
He's really into that stuff.
Anyway, evidently Tommy
had a lollipop that day.
That's all Daly needed.
He copied him in here.
It was Tommy alright.
As alike in every way.
Dad!
You know what he did to him?
Tommy!
He took Tommy
and he threw him out of the airlock...
Tommy!
- Daddy!
...right out into space.
Daddy!
He made me watch.
Tommy!
Have you ever seen an unsuited body
compress in space?
They freeze...
and crack like a porcelain doll.
I take my hat off to Daly,
the detail in this place is exceptional.
And he said he'd do it again, and again
cos Daly's still got Tommy's DNA.
He's got all of our DNA.
He keeps it in his bedroom
in a fucking mini-fridge by his desk.
And so I have to stay in line
because even if we die in here,
he can bring us back.
He can bring Tommy back
whenever he wants...
and God knows how he'd take it out on him.
God knows what he'd do.
So you see, what choice do I have?
Walton.
We are going to get that fucking lollipop.
But you gotta believe me.
Can you do that?
Can you?
Good to see you at your position, Cole.
Captain, you've come at just the right time!
I have?
I'm picking up a distress signal
from the surface of Skillane IV.
Looks like a crashed shuttle.
What should we do?
Space Fleet never turn its back
on those who need our help.
Dudani, set a course for Skillane IV.
- Aye aye, sir.
We'll send a search party.
Packer, Tulaska?
- Actually, Captain...
I was thinking maybe you could take me along.
As science officer, I need to learn the ropes
and I could use your close attention.
Good.
Yes, good idea.
Atmosphere's good.
Over there.
From here, the shuttle appears
to be deserted.
We'll scout the area,
check for any lifeforms.
Daly out.
Cole, we should head out this way.
Cole...
It's kind of hot here, don't you think?
Oh, my God...
What are you doing, Cole?
The water looks so inviting,
doesn't it?
What are you talking about...?
Come on, Robert!
Ooh!
Oh, the water is great!
Swimming is a leisure activity.
We're on Space Fleet duty.
You know what?
We could always say that
I started drowning...
and you had to come in and rescue me.
Yeah...?
Oh, what about that? Ohhh!
Come on!
Come on in.
I... Cole.
Come on!
Cole...
Come on.
Come on in, my big Captain.
OK.
Come on.
You gonna take all day?
OK!
OK, I'm coming in.
OK. Gotta patch it in.
It worked. I'm connected.
I can access her PhotoCloud account.
- You actually remember that password?
Uppercase Y998, lowercase gb7,
uppercase TY, ampersand four.
Secure choice.
There are thousands of images,
this could take a while.
Boring life.
God damn...
That is gymnastic physique?
It's nice... Nice bedding.
Oh, OK, should, should I keep scrolling?
Any of the last nine would do.
Ow!
Thank you.
- Pleasure.
Um, are you heading out for the night?
- Yes.
Cos it's Christmas Eve and we've got ten days
off work to recover from it.
Go home.
- I will.
I just have to finish...
- Whatever, Merry Christmas, loser.
Yeah.
OK, Merry Christmas.
Oh, my God!
Elliott, you fucking asshole.
Nanette Cole,
we 've hacked your PhotoCloud account
and have control of the entire contents
of your photo gallery.
Who is this? Um, what, uh,
what do you want?
What we want is for you to do exactly
as instructed
or your entire gallery will be shared
with your friends and your family.
And PornHub.
OK.
Yeah, I'll do what you want... Anything.
I'll do anything.
Then listen very carefully.
We don't have much time.
Stand up, get your coat
and follow our instructions.
OK.
Where are we going?
We're just swimming.
It's nice, right?
Yes.
- Yeah.
We should probably head back.
- Help!
Oh!
- Something grabbed me, I think!
No, it didn't, I don't think anything did.
I'm sorry, I... I think I, I imagined it.
So stupid.
That's fine...
That's funny.
- Yeah, yeah it's funny. It's funny.
Easy, Cole.
I... I'm in position.
- OK, we're gonna hang up now.
Make the phone call. Be sure to complete
the rest of your mission.
I will.
- You better.
OK, I'll send it back down.
Oh, hi!
This is fucking crazy...
Hi, yes, I'd like...
I'd like to order a pizza.
Oh, I guess you'd better get that.
See who it... Hold on.
Yeah.
It's the door.
Oh, OK.
Pause game.
- Dudani, pick me up.
- You got it. Stand by.
Coming!
Hello?
- Uh, pizza.
I didn't order a pizza.
OK, look, someone did, OK,
so do you want it or not?
Because I can't take it back.
What the hell am I doing?
That's the signal.
She's got the DNA!
All of it. Tommy, too.
Packer, we ready to fly?
- Uh-huh.
Well?
- You're supposed to say something
like, "Engage" or "Increase thrust."
- Just fucking go.
There you go.
So, I got it here in under ten.
There's supposed to be
30 in it for me, yeah?
What's happening? The door's closing.
Hello?
Shit.
- Come on, man.
Hello?
Come on, man, you promised.
Nice. Nice. Merry Christmas, asshole!
Resume game.
Can we go any faster? That dud disk
isn't gonna fool him forever.
The update is gonna complete before long
and that means "bye-bye, wormhole."
The only quicker route is
through that asteroid belt there.
Let's go that way.
No, it's way too dense.
- If the ship broke up, we wouldn't die.
We'd just be left spinning in space.
- Till Daly works out what's happening
and he'll find us
and then he'll fuck us over.
Resume game.
Lieutenant Cole, we should head for...
Cole?
Daly to bridge, what's going on?
Shit, he has a backup disk.
- Come in, bridge.
Don't. Answer.
Dudani?
Goddamnit!
The wormhole, it's decreasing in size.
Upload must be in the last few percent.
Dammit, Packer, we are gonna have to go
through the belt.
Do you think that you can do that?
I think I can try.
Ship 's computer on.
Computer, where's the USS Callister?
USS Callister is on course.
On course for where?
- The wormhole.
What wormhole?
- The update vortex.
Sons of bitches!
Prepare for take-off.
I've got a heat signature.
Looks like a shuttle
just took off from Skillane IV.
- Oh, God, it's Daly.
Shield's at 86%.
We're taking a beating here.
Incoming transmission.
Hello, loyal, trusty crew. Come in.
I know you can hear me.
Whatever is you think you're going to do
won't work, but it is going to cost you!
Let's go faster!
- Already at maximum.
Daly can't touch us
unless he makes it onboard
and that's shuttle's a jalopy,
he won't catch us in time.
I hope you're right.
Shield's 58%.
If you thought what happened to you
in the past was bad, that was nothing!
What I'm going to do to you is going to be
Goddamn fucking biblical.
I'm literally going to turn
your insides out.
But I'll keep you alive.
In tiny little jars and there you'll stay
until I'm bored of you.
Why are we listening to this?
- Yes, fuck him!
We're at the edge of the belt,
I think we're gonna make it.
- What was that?
- Primary drive.
I've lost all thrust.
Engine's not responding.
We're drifting here.
USS Callister has lost engine power.
I'm coming to get you! Hello!
Is there any way that we can fix the engines?
That's only feasible manually,
by climbing inside the jet fader.
So...?
So we'd burn to a crisp when the jet came on.
We'd burn without dying.
- So one of us needs to go.
OK.
One of us already has.
Walton?
I'm pretty sure I can fix this.
Um, ah, Walton!
Are you sure about this?
I'm sure.
Tulaska, can you patch me through
to Daly?
Patching through.
Hey, hey, Daly, can you hear me?
Walton?
- Robert?
Hey.
- You're going to pay for this.
Robert, listen.
- I'm going to bring Tommy back in.
Hey, Robert?
- God so help me...
you are going to regret all of this
so hard.
Bob, I wanna talk to you, here.
I was thinking I should say...
sorry.
Go on.
You created Infinity.
You're a fucking genius.
I exploited that...
and treated you like a golden goose
and I got fat on the profits.
Figuratively speaking.
And I was thinking I should've appreciated
you more, you know.
I should've treated you better.
I was thinking I should say all that...
but you threw my son
out of an airlock, so...
fuck you to death.
Walton? Walton!
We've got power back.
Faster!
Speed already at maximum.
Well, I don't care, whatever,
just catch them!
Wormhole almost closed.
Daly's gaining on us.
Keep her steady.
Steady.
- I'm trying.
Come on! Come on!
I hope we are going to die.
Goddamnit!
What happened?
The mod's gone.
Daly's Space Fleet mod has been stripped
away by the firewall.
OK, so this is good.
We're still alive.
Yeah, it only erased the Space Fleet mod.
We're not on Daly's computer
anymore.
We're in the cloud.
Where is Daly?
The firewall deleted his rogue game code
and his controls are disabled.
You mean...
He's stuck there.
Update complete. Wormhole closed.
Controls are disabled.
- No.
No... No, no, no!
Assholes!
The brig unlocked itself.
- My Valdack outfit turned into this!
More to the point,
I'm not a fucking beetle thing anymore.
I've got my body back.
- Got my whole body back.
I'm guessing we all have.
So what do we do now?
We've got an infinite, procedurally
generated universe at our disposal.
We can go anywhere.
Holy mackerel...
Rogue universe detected.
Deletion in progress.
No, undelete!
- Deletion in progress.
Undelete.
- Rogue universe detected.
Deletion in progress.
- Exit game!
Rogue universe detected...
Exit game!
Exit fucking game!
Incoming transmission.
It says Gamer 691.
That's a player tag.
Another ship, another player.
We're online.
Um, OK, patch them through.
- Um, hello.
- Hey there.
This is the crew of the USS Callister.
Oh, man, are we glad to hear from...
Yeah. Merry Christmas.
So are we gonna blow each other
or are we gonna trade?
Uh...
Hello, do you have anything to trade at
all?
No, uh...
- So why did you respond?
OK, just get the hell out of my quadrant
or I'll blast you to shit.
You've got 10 seconds.
Oh, do try! We'll photon-bolt you
right up the perineum, you stupid little boy.
Ooh, scary. Nine...
- OK.
Come on, then.
- Yes. Thank you, Shania!
Um, Nate.
- Yes, Captain?
Stick us in hyper warp
and let's fuck off somewhere.
Aye, captain.
- Really, Nanette is fine.
Four...
- Aye aye, Nanette.
Three...
Two...
One! Ah, you better run!
King of space right here!
King of space...