[Donovan] There is no corpse.
There's no corpse.
I heard you.
Remind Felix Manning
that I do not tolerate loose ends.
Yes, Mr. Fisk.
But the body was probably just swept
away in the current.
Even if Murdock
somehow escaped from the cab,
how does a blind man swim to shore?
This look like a blind man to you?
We investigated him thoroughly.
His associates.
Medical and school records all check out.
All confirm that Matt Murdock
lost his sight at age nine.
[Fisk softly] Yes.
Nevertheless...
a man capable of that could have survived.
And he threatened
to come between Vanessa and I.
[Donovan] It's time for the government
to honor our deal.
Thanks to my client,
the Albanian Syndicate
has been completely wiped out.
Their counterfeiting ring,
their Dark Web child pornography.
And the Jalisco connection
Mr. Fisk divulged last week
gave the DEA an early
and very white Christmas.
And in exchange
for his ongoing cooperation,
the DOJ will not be filing charges
against Vanessa Marianna.
Mr. Fisk is also entitled to the return
of certain personal belongings,
supervised movement within the hotel.
He'll get everything he was offered.
In time.
[Donovan] That time is now,
Special Agent Nadeem.
Unless you'd like my client
to stop talking.
FBI has sacrificed a great deal for me.
And I will continue to cooperate
and trust you'll honor your word.
There's a criminal I've employed.
A facilitator.
On my behalf,
he's laundered and hid money,
bribed law enforcement
and court officials,
orchestrated perjured testimony,
manufactured evidence.
[Ray] Who is he?
A lawyer. Matthew Murdock.
[theme music playing]
Alpha Team on approach.
[door opens]
FBI. Get back in your apartment
and close the door.
Stack up.
Breach.
[agent shouting] FBI!
[Agent Fremont] Clear!
Murdock's been home.
Recently.
[woman] It was so nice to see you again.
Take care.
[Karen] Felix Manning?
You haven't returned my calls.
Karen Page, from the Bulletin.
Before I go to print,
I'm obligated to offer you
a chance to comment
on your involvement
in laundering money for Wilson Fisk.
Look, if you talk to me off the record,
help me connect some dots,
I promise I will keep your name out of it.
But that is only if you talk to me.
You're a fixer, Mr. Manning.
You're a freelancer.
Other clients, a lot to lose.
Once this story breaks,
Fisk is gonna hang you out to dry.
If I were you,
I would start looking out for myself.
Karen Page.
Daughter of Paxton and Penelope.
239 Kings Road, Fagan Corners, Vermont.
You had the back room. My guess,
Dad wanted his little girl to be safe.
Sadly, he should've been more worried
about his little boy.
Drug addicts really do destroy families,
don't they?
Off the record,
you're incorrect.
About what I do for a living.
I don't fix problems.
[scribbling]
I make them disappear.
[tires screech]
[Karen breathes heavily]
Karen Page?
-Who are you?
-Don't move.
FBI.
Uh... I have a weapon in my purse.
And a concealed carry permit.
Keep your hands exactly where they are
and follow my instructions.
Now turn around.
[Karen whispering] Okay. Okay.
[breathes heavily]
[Karen] Okay. Okay.
[Karen breathes heavily]
What do you want from me?
What happened?
Why'd you bring me here?
I asked him to.
Is Matt okay?
You wanna tell me what's going on?
Ms. Page, I get that you
ask questions for a living,
but, for now, I'll be the one asking.
[indistinct chatter]
[Ray] When's the last time
you heard from Matt Murdock?
Um...
Months.
You haven't seen
or spoken to him in months?
Uh, no.
He give you any indication
when he'd be back?
[clears throat] Uh, no.
[Ray] Or whether he'd be back at all?
[sighs] No. Then why have you been paying his bills?
He's a friend. Someone had to do it
while he was away.
So your friend, a blind man
who you haven't spoken to in months,
just ups and disappears, and you
don't file a missing persons report?
I figured he'd come back
when he was ready.
Can you think of any reason
why Matt Murdock would go on the run?
No.
You were a secretary
for Nelson and Murdock.
Mmm-mmm. Office manager.
And when did the firm
first start working for Wilson Fisk?
Um...
We never worked for Wilson Fisk.
Is that your signature?
Do you remember depositing this
retainer check for a company called CGI?
Yes, I do. Um... Look, Matt and Foggy
took on one case for them. That's all.
According to my source,
CGI was a front for Fisk.
Well, we didn't know that at the time.
But you do now.
So you see how your last answer
wasn't technically accurate?
Okay, we never knowingly worked for Fisk.
They hired us through someone else.
Who?
Some executive.
Hang on.
Was it this guy?
James Wesley. You remember him?
Uh, yeah. I think that was him. Why?
Just trying to put the pieces together.
Okay. Uh... Well, here are some
other pieces for you to put together.
Um...
Felix Manning. Red Lion National Bank.
Vancorp. Any of that ring any bells?
I don't follow.
[Karen] Well, instead of letting Fisk
use you and the FBI
to retaliate against innocent lawyers
who put him in prison,
why don't you ask him if he hired
a fixer named Felix Manning
to launder money through Red Lion?
Ask him if he's the true owner
of a shell company called Vancorp.
Why would I do that?
Because it just bought
the Presidential Hotel.
Where are you getting this from?
I ask questions for a living.
I just ask better ones than you do.
Like, has your so-called prisoner just
bought the prison you're keeping him in?
[chuckles]
Has he bought?
-So this is what? Just a theory?
-[Karen scoffs]
You have any proof?
Fisk is using you, Agent Nadeem.
That's what he does.
Is that a no?
Am I under arrest?
Not at this time.
Then I'm done
answering the wrong questions.
[breathing shakily]
Is this everything?
Everything Felix's investigators
were able to dig up on short notice.
Uh...
This will take some time.
I brought an audiobook.
[Fisk sighs]
[rhythmic tapping]
[man] Dex, ready to go?
Game starts in 20. Traffic's a nightmare.
We gotta hustle.
What's the deal?
You don't even got your uniform on.
You all right, buddy?
Trouble in paradise?
Does the headmaster know you're drilling
a hole in his pile of bricks?
He doesn't like it.
He gives you a hard time,
you send him my way.
It's damn fine practice.
Hey, I got you a little something.
I was gonna wait until after the game...
100% leather.
That's steerhide in the pocket
and cowhide in the palm,
so it's nice and soft.
Try it on.
An all-star pitcher
deserves some all-star gear.
Come on, let's go break it in.
Wait.
Real quick, can I show you my new wind-up?
[chuckles softly]
All right, showboat.
Let's see it.
[indistinct chatter and cheering]
You're in the zone, Dex.
Keep throwing those heaters.
[umpire] Strike!
Strike!
Strike! Strike!
All right, kiddo. Pack it in.
Let's give that arm of yours a rest.
You're pulling me?
-I'm gonna let Kanon finish it out.
-But... but no one's gotten a hit off me.
I know. You're killin' it out here.
No question.
But I gotta give other kids
some field time.
You can't do this. It's not fair!
You gotta let me keep going.
Keep it together, okay?
Take a few deep breaths.
Big gulps of air.
[stammers] I need...
I need to keep going.
[sobs] If I pitch a perfect game,
then they might...
[sobbing]
[clicks tongue]
Dex...
you could pitch a billion perfect games.
It won't bring your parents back.
Okay.
Hit the pine.
Grab a Popsicle.
We'll talk later.
[Mercer] Well, this has been nice so far,
hasn't it?
Talking like this.
Now that we've gotten to know
each other a little bit,
I wonder if we could talk
about Coach Bradley?
What happened at the field?
How did it make you feel?
Sad?
Maybe a little scared? I wasn't sad.
Why not, do you think?
He was a jerk.
How so?
How was Coach Bradley a jerk?
He never let me do what I wanted.
Didn't know shit about pitching.
He was your coach for a long time.
Was he always such a jerk to you?
What about last year
when he named you MVP?
Was he a jerk then?
No. He used to be awesome.
[Mercer] Dex, tell me...
And be honest.
We like honesty around here.
When you hit Coach Bradley...
was that an accident?
Whatever you say stays between us.
That's the law.
No.
It wasn't an accident.
Am I in trouble?
No.
It wasn't your fault.
But I just told you, I did it on purpose.
That doesn't mean it was your fault.
It's confusing, isn't it?
Here, let me put it like this.
This is you, right?
Yeah.
This is fantastic.
But you see how alone you are?
It's just you,
surrounded by all this emptiness.
It's been that way
for most of your life, hasn't it?
Yeah.
I mean, most kids, they have moms or dads
to teach them right from wrong,
to show them how to behave.
My parents mostly got mad at me.
Yes.
Then they died.
And there were things
that you never learned.
You see?
Not your fault.
Good news is, you've got me now.
Now, we've got a lot of work to do,
but I think that it is going to be fun.
We are going to establish some routines,
learn to stay calm.
And first things first,
we're gonna practice empathy.
What's that?
That means being kind to someone
when they're in pain.
So let's say, for example, that my cat
got sick this morning and I was upset.
What would you say to me?
How about something like,
"I'm sorry. That sounds hard."
I'm sorry. That sounds really hard.
Look at you!
You even put a "really" in there.
I like a fast learner.
I think we are gonna make a terrific team,
you and me.
-[bottle pops open]
-[Mercer] Oh. [laughs]
Nothing marks an occasion
like a little bubbly, huh?
It's a... a Cava, actually.
Spanish champagne.
It was a little farewell gift
from the chiropractor down the hall.
Tomorrow is my last day in the building.
Here. Go on.
I'm not 21.
Good for you.
[Mercer coughing] [sniffs]
It's been quite a challenging day.
Quite a few goodbyes.
Lots of...
longtime clients.
That... That's hard.
That's really hard.
And then there's this,
our last session together,
which I've been dreading
since my prognosis.
Then don't leave.
We can keep meeting.
I can keep getting better.
Dex...
[crying] You can't leave.
[Mercer] You are gonna be fine, Dex.
We prepared for this.
You are gonna get a job
with a nice, rigid structure.
You're gonna stick to your meds.
And if you get off track, you can...
listen to these.
This is every session we've had.
Cycle through them again.
When we remind ourselves
of how far we've come,
we're less inclined to slip back.
And one last thing.
This is a, uh... a colleague of mine.
He's a fine therapist, with a lot
of expertise in your particular--
I don't want another therapist!
Are you trying to scare me?
No.
Not scare you.
Then what is your intention?
And be honest.
I want...
I want to kill you.
[Mercer] Say more.
Why do you want to kill me?
To put me out of my misery?
To punish you.
I'm not quite sure what I've done wrong.
I want to kill you for dying.
For leaving me.
Death always wins, Dex.
Eventually.
But when it comes quietly and naturally,
it can be a beautiful event.
Which is why
we never hasten it with violence.
[breathes shakily]
I can't do this alone.
[coughs, inhales]
You remember what I did?
Last time I was alone?
Then find someone.
I don't want another therapist!
Any good person
with a decent heart will do.
Someone to look up to.
Your internal compass isn't broken, Dex.
It just works better when you have
the North Star to guide you.
[telephone ringing]
Suicide Prevention, this is Dex.
Who am I speaking with?
Hi, Craig. How can I help you today?
I'm sorry. That's hard.
That's really hard.
Why don't you tell me a little bit more
about how you're feeling?
That's a lot to deal with.
I'm glad you called.
[whispering] You're doing amazing.
[Dex] Tell me, Craig,
are you thinking
about taking your own life right now?
Okay.
Do you have a plan?
What kind of gun do you have, Craig?
I'm familiar with the M11.
Did a couple years in the army.
Got real cozy with the M11.
It's reliable.
Let me ask you a question, Craig.
If this asshole stepdad of yours
is giving you so much grief,
why take your own life?
Why not...
[inhales sharply]
Take a deep breath, Craig.
We're gonna work through this together.
I'm not going anywhere.
If I may ask, Mr. Fisk,
without getting into specifics,
what's this all about?
Right now, I am New York's scapegoat.
Downstairs, there are protesters
chanting prayers
to drive me out into the wilderness.
The attention that it brings
is an impediment for my plan.
Fortunately,
the public is easily distracted. Which makes the solution
for my problem quite simple.
The city needs a new villain.
And I think I might've found him.
[Julie] Can I start you off
with something to drink?
Looks like you need a little more time.
I'll grab you a water.
This is gonna sound random,
but did you used to work
at the Brooklyn Suicide Hotline?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
That... was a tough job. [chuckles]
It was. [chuckles]
You probably don't remember me. I'm Julie.
Dex.
Yeah, of course I remember you.
Small world, huh?
I haven't seen you in here before.
It's... it's my first day, actually.
I got offered double the pay
to leave my last job
if I could start here immediately.
Not that I'm complaining.
What about you?
Are you staying at the hotel?
[stammers] No. I live here.
In New York, not in the hotel.
[both laughing]
The FBI has an office upstairs.
We're guarding Wilson Fisk.
A G-man.
-[Dex chuckles softly]
-[woman] Excuse me, miss! Hello?
I need to go help that table
so they don't fire me on my first day.
What time do you get off?
In about an hour.
Do you wanna hang out after?
Catch up?
Uh...
Yeah. [chuckles]
That... That'd be great.
Hmm.
I got your coppa, your prosciutto,
your mocetta, your sweet soppressata.
All you can eat. Free!
For anybody who promises
to vote for Foggy Nelson,
my less handsome brother.
You can't do that, Theo.
It violates election law.
It's an illegal inducement to vote.
I don't see Mrs. Wobschall
calling the cops.
[laughs]
May I borrow a pen?
Is that an actual ballot, Mrs. Callahan?
I just voted for you.
Absentee.
When Wilson Fisk set off
those explosives in Hell's Kitchen,
I lost my husband.
Everything that matters, gone.
Except my vote.
I'm counting on you, Foggy.
You get that son of a bitch.
I will. I promise.
Thank you, everyone.
And I'll be here till close
to answer any questions.
Yeah, I got a few.
Like, what's the secret ingredient
in your world-famous Nelson's sub?
A soft robiola.
[inhales and exhales]
Perfect. Uh, team at work
is gonna love that.
Uh...
Give me six.
Uh, Theo can help you at the counter.
Is there anything else?
Yeah.
When's the last time you saw Matt Murdock?
Who are you?
[Foggy] Crashing my campaign event,
trying to intimidate me,
dropping the names of my friends...
I'm not backing off my criticism
of the feds' love affair with Fisk!
You seem like a decent guy, Mr. Nelson.
You care about people.
About doing the right thing.
I'm guessing that's why
you ditched Matt Murdock
as your law partner in the first place.
Am I correct?
You really think I'm gonna answer
a question that leading?
To be clear:
did you dissolve your partnership
because Mr. Murdock
took on Wilson Fisk as a client?
If you're referring to a single case
where we represented a client
who allegedly worked for Fisk
even though we didn't know
that at the time...
the answer's no.
It had nothing to do with it.
Nelson and Murdock
represented a lot of clients,
for whom all work
was completely ethical and legal
and protected
by attorney-client privilege.
When's the last time you saw Matt Murdock?
Two nights ago.
Where?
A bar in Hell's Kitchen.
And what did you discuss?
That we hadn't seen each other in a while.
-Did he tell you where he was going?
-No.
-Where you could find him?
Did he tell you anything?
That he was sorry.
About what?
That our friendship
isn't what it used to be.
So you didn't knowingly
give him your bar ID?
What?
[sighs]
Of course not. Why would I?
So he could enter a prison,
falsely using your identity,
and make contact with an Albanian gang
linked to the murder
of nine federal agents.
I...
I didn't give him my ID.
Nor was I aware of anything
that he was planning.
But with all due respect,
-I think you have Matt Murdock all wrong.
-[scoffs]
Yeah, well, uh...
I don't think I do.
I think Matt Murdock
is hiding a double life.
Lawyer by day and criminal by night.
And you and Ms. Page
both know all about it.
It makes you uncomfortable.
And complicit.
And that's why you're no longer
law partners or friends.
Because once he's finally caught,
you know you're on the hook
as an accessory to his crimes.
Or, if you're lucky,
simply aiding and abetting.
Remind me, Special Agent Nadeem,
what's Matt being charged with?
Nothing so far.
Great.
Then the only thing
I'm aiding and abetting is your exit.
Don't forget to vote.
[Julie] Every day?
[chuckles]
FDR Drive's my favorite route, too.
There's nothing in the world
like a winter run on the East River.
Between your workout habits
and new gig, it's...
it's almost like you're stalking me.
[laughs]
Damn. The secret's out.
So...
why aren't you in social work anymore?
Uh...
Tried to pursue my dream as a dancer.
It actually was going pretty well
until I tore my ACL, again.
I'm sorry. That must've been really hard.
But you were brave to go for it
in the first place.
I, um...
I didn't have a backup plan.
My parents made the mistake of telling me
I could be anything I wanted.
Must've been nice to hear,
even if it didn't work out.
My parents
were never really that involved.
Sounds like you didn't need
the message anyhow.
You did great all on your own.
[chuckles]
So, what's it like
working for Wilson Fisk?
I don't work for him.
I work for the federal government.
Must be scary to be up close and personal
with someone so dangerous.
It is what it is.
Do you think a killer like that
deserves a second chance?
You worked at the hotline for three years.
I think you of all people would believe
everyone deserves a second chance.
How did you know
I worked there for three years?
You were only there for one.
You mentioned it earlier.
You quit to do ballet.
Did I also mention ballet earlier?
Specifically?
I guess I... I just assumed.
[chuckles softly] Anyway, um...
It's late. I should get home.
You're ditching me?
No, not at all. I...
I just have to go feed my dog.
You don't have a dog.
How do you know that?
Julie, you're misreading this.
Let me pay for dinner.
We'll go for a walk in the park.
I'll explain.
Dinner's on me.
Julie.
You're very special to me.
Let go of me, Dex.
Please.
I said let go!
[Dex breathing heavily]
Just being at Matt's apartment,
and his bloody clothes...
And I just-- It threw me.
Nadeem's smart. I probably gave him
everything he needs to figure it out.
Wait. You told the FBI
that Matt is Daredevil?
No, no. Of course not.
[sighs] They know he's hiding something.
It's not what they think, but this is bad.
This is really bad. Infinitely bad.
-We could all go to jail.
-Foggy--
I should've never let Matt
tell you his secret.
This is my fault.
I'm not gonna let you pay
for our shitty mistakes.
If it comes to it,
I'll plead in exchange for your immunity.
Foggy...
You always see the good in people.
But you put us on such high pedestals,
you can't see who we really are.
I didn't tell the FBI Matt is Daredevil.
I did something worse.
Karen, breathe.
I'm in trouble.
Tell me what happened.
I'm gonna need attorney-client privilege
before I can.
Okay, um, give me five bucks.
[breathing heavily]
Good enough. I'm officially your lawyer.
Do you remember the... the Healy trial?
And there was that...
that guy from... from CGI
who offered us a stupid amount of money
to take his case?
Yeah, how could I forget that creep?
His name's James Wesley.
He worked for Fisk.
He disappeared shortly after that,
and they think
Matt had something to do with it.
That's crazy.
Matt had nothing to do with that.
I know. But if they keep investigating,
they're gonna find out that I did.
What?
I killed him.
[yells]
[breathing heavily]
Shit. Shit.
[groans] [yelling]
-[yells]
-[cutlery clattering]
[yells]
[breathing heavily]
[Mercer] It's good to see you, Dex.
How was your week?
[young Dex] I'm scared, Dr. Mercer.
[Mercer] Scared? What's making you scared?
[groans]
[Ray] Alpha Team on approach.
[Ray] FBI. Get back in your apartment
and close the door.
[door closes] [Ray] Stack up.
Breach.
[FBI agent] FBI!
Clear!
Murdock's been home.
Recently.
Command post, we're clear.
Suspect's not here.
[woman over police radio]
NYPD has been advised. Citywide BOLO.
Suspect Matthew Murdock
to be considered armed and dangerous.