-No!
-Yes!
-No, no fucking way!
-What? Why not?
-I mean, what, like, what--
-What are you even gonna do with it?
-I'm gonna look at it.
And make an assessment.
No. How's Venice?
Kendall, this is not a request;
it's a demand.
I am not sending you a picture
of my dick. Okay? No.
-No... Why?
-I need it for my records.
I can't say this clearly
enough. Dick pic!
-I hear you.
-Dick pic!
Dick pic! Dick pic! Dick pic!
Okay, fine. Fine, fine,
fuck you, fine. Jesus. Fuck.
I mean, how do you even do this?
-So, like, what was wrong?
-Nothing. Nothing.
It was great. It was great.
Why didn't you send it to me before?
Just because
after Dinosaur-gate, I just...
I wanted to get out a clear statement
and show them I'm not a sourpuss.
And y'know, I just, I got into it.
And I wanted to show 'em
I have a positive plan, and...
-Fuck.
-No, Shiv. Like, raw--raw is good.
It's memorable. Y'know, it's...
Find an audience with an income
and a pulse.
I'm not saying no to the center because
I'm saying follow the ad revenue.
No, yeah. No, sure. I think the cynicism
was pretty clear.
-What up, sis?
-Hey.
-Mega-dump and a line!
-This is all--It's just--It's bullshit.
Because what it is, really, it's just--
it's displacement activity.
I just need to find him and ask him,
"Is it still happening? Is it still me?"
-Just, y'know, thrash it out.
-You don't wanna thrash. You wanna--
-Hey there! How are you?
-Hey, Peter. It's been a long time.
Look, the shareholders want
a CEO successor named
before the shareholder meeting.
They have made that clear.
So, if you're serious about us
as a dream ticket,
it'd be smart to be able
to preempt any bad stuff
that could come out if you
came under the spotlight.
Okay, okay.
You want me to just tell you
all the terrible things that I,
Roman Roy, have ever done?
How would you feel if I had
some oppo research done?
See what a tenacious bottom-feeder
could grub up on you?
I'd say that sounds like fun.
-We went Blanch.
-Thank you, Gerri.
-Blanch!
-For the internal investigation?
-Blanch and Partners.
Beautiful, soft-soaping fucks!
That interview is going to be like
slipping into a bubble bath.
I'll just light a scented candle
in there, put some Eagles on
and start playing with myself.
They came. Look at them.
All the little piggies at the trough.
All the cruise noise,
a fucking nothing burger.
Reassured now
that they still love you?
Love. Fear. Whatever.
-Could I have a word?
-Yeah. Fine.
-Hey, Dad.
-In a minute, Shiv.
I'm sorry but I should just--Y'know?
In a minute.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
-Hey, brother. I'll get one.
-Sure thing! That'll be 18,000 dollars.
Ever feel like you're
being fed a bad investment?
Logan Roy and his family are taking a
once-great media brand down a dead end.
Corporate Governance. Fail!
Acquisition strategy. Fail!
Succession planning. Fail!
The Roys are failing Waystar.
As a shareholder, you can replace Logan
Roy's rubber-stamp board right now.
Vote and let this year's
shareholder meeting
launch a fresh start for Waystar,
the company you own.
Cool.
So Sandy and Stewy have sent out
thousands of them.
-All major shareholders.
-What does DF King say?
They say it might be time
to start getting worried.
Yeah, we've had some disappointing
feedback on a couple of key investors.
The Pierce pursuit has played
badly in some quarters.
-Jack, the Ulsterman is wavering.
-He's four percent, isn't he?
-We should have a conversation.
-With that fat fuck? Fuck that guy.
You should jam your dick in
his one good artery.
There's also one other person
who has a significant chunk of stock
who we hear is no longer solid.
-Your mother, Caroline.
-Really? Mom?
What is she, three percent voting stock?
We'd been kinda counting on them.
I mean, we're at 36 percent.
Without their seven to add,
that is scary.
I'll talk to her.
Let her know this isn't funny,
and that she can kill you with
the wrong move.
Well, I imagine that's quite
a large part of the attraction.
We think that it'd be really
helpful to get you to the UK
-for a personal appeal to Jack.
-Like, tomorrow.
Roman, Kendall, Shiv
could hit their mom.
Okay. London. I'll take care
of the Ulsterman,
you're on your mom, but keep it simple.
No Shiv.
I'm sorry--Wait. You mean
London, all of us, you mean?
Are you sure we need to?
That's like--
What are we? A fucking octopus?
Giving, like, reach-arounds to--
to every fish on the reef now or...?
-All right, relax, branzino-porno-man.
-It's fine. It's fine.
Colin will come.
Kerry, we can fix it, right?
You can reshuffle the Dundee stuff?
About the journalism wing?
Yeah, I'm sure they'll come to you.
Then straight to Singapore,
Christchurch, do it that way.
I need to make some calls.
Kerry, we're hunkering.
Frank, Gerri, let's get down to it.
It's going to be an all-nighter.
Hey, Rome. What's happening? Where's
Dad? We're supposed to be talking.
Yeah, yeah, something came in.
He's hunkering.
He wanted me to tell you, "Sorry, rain
check. Maybe in the a.m. Maybe."
Are your nips hard? They must be,
because you are so out in the cold.
-Tom Wambsgans.
-Yeah. Hi.
-Thanks for making the time.
-No, not at all. Big priority.
No, I managed to push all my gropes
to this afternoon. I'm just kidding.
-This is my colleague, Stefan Strauss.
-Hey, hey, hi.
-How do you do?
-My name's Kenneth Chan...
-...and we're with Blanch and Partners.
-Yes.
We are helping to investigate
historic sexual abuse
and associated wrongdoings
at Brightstar Cruises.
-Sure.
-So, as head of the division
-we were hoping you could--
-Well, briefly, I, I--
I followed Bill's long reign.
Um, I was but a minnow
trailing in the wake of Bill,
the big sperm whale, the legend.
Sure, but in terms of your time
at Parks, were you aware
of any historical allegations
that had been dealt with
other than in a way outlined
in the corporate guidelines?
In my brief spell, um...
I don't, at this time, recall anything
that at that time would have caused me
any real concern.
Okay. Well, we can take a dig
into that in a moment, but for now,
in terms of records
and document-keeping...
We need to locate
all written information
relevant to this investigation
and safeguard it from destruction,
negligence, malfeasance.
Do you know any document destruction
which might hinder our inquiries?
I think, um...
You know what? I've just realized
we're gonna be here for a while,
and I wanna give you my best attention,
but I really need to pee.
-We'd rather you stayed here.
-I've got a pathetically weak bladder.
I'm like an old woman who's had a baby
somehow. So, I'm gonna--
But I'm--I'm so sorry.
I'll be right back. Okay.
Who's the pilot today?
Not Serge, right?
-No, sir. Serge is off rotation.
-Good.
I like a boring bastard flying me.
Serge always looks as if
his dick's still wet,
and he's gonna give me the name
of a good fucking pinot.
-Are you all right, son?
-Yeah, I'm good. Thanks for the ride.
It's good to see you.
Good to see you, too, Dad.
I hope we can swing it with Mom.
Yeah, I--I was gonna say,
you know, that thing up at Argestes...
No, yeah. It's not--
I didn't even know you were there.
I mean, if I did, I would--Y'know?
I know. Yeah, I know. Sure.
Did I even make contact?
I don't... think s--
Yeah, I'm not quite sure what we're
talking about, to be honest.
Because... that's not something I'd do.
Y'know?
Yeah, I know. I know that.
I know. I know.
Fucking... cars, buildings, everywhere.
-He didn't tell you I was coming?
-No. No, he did not.
For a media guy, he's not
the greatest communicator.
Thank you. I was going anyway to check
out some theater, and he asked
would I talk through a couple things
with him. Bounce some stuff.
-You feelin' bouncy?
-Honestly? A little deflated.
After all the retreats I've done,
you know, still got a bit of an ego.
-Hey! Hi!
-Hey!
-Hey, Rhea. Dad, Rhea's here.
-Yeah, well... Not a big deal.
Course it's not a big deal.
Why would it be?
-It's convenient.
-Okay, well, here we go.
Roy boys on tour, and we got 'em
in all sizes. Alpha, beta, cuck.
He's fucking leaving the country?
Rather than speak to me.
-How long have you known this?
-Plans change, so...
-He wanted to apologize.
-Bullshit.
-Hey.
-You--
-Hey, Shiv. Hey. Hey.
-Do you know he's gone?
-Can I ask you about something?
-Can you believe you this? He's gone.
And his fucking flunkies didn't even
tell me, running interference for him.
I won't have it.
I'm not gonna chase him around the party
like a schoolgirl with a crush.
No, absolutely.
Hey, um, I just wanted to check it
definitely is bullshit this
internal investigation?
-He hasn't even responded to the memo.
-Cause it didn't feel that bullshitty.
It wasn't all softballs?
You ever been hit in the face with a
softball? Just how inside this are you?
'Cause there isn't a world in which I
get hung out to dry,
in which I have to play the fuckbag?
Is there? He supports me, right? Logan?
I mean, never mind the jokes and the "ha
ha," he's not gonna fry me, is he?
No, Tom. No. You know what?
I think I have to go out there.
I have to... go and fix this, okay?
-You okay?
-Sure.
Sure. "Sure." Don't poke the bear.
He can take anything. Load him up.
I don't fucking know.
All this energy. I'm gonna have to fight
now for every fucking shareholder vote.
My ex-wife, my old friends turning.
I kill Sandy. Sandy kills me.
So fucking what?
The next Zucker-fucker comes along
and swallows you whole.
-Shits you out as an app.
-Yeah...
We've had some private polling
on potential next CEOs, who'd play well.
-I'd value your thoughts.
-On the kids?
Who's got it?
I could do with a clear eye.
As execs, okay. Well...
Shiv thinks she's smarter than she is.
Roman could actually be good,
but, um... but nowhere near right now.
Kendall's... I don't know.
It's like you put him a big diaper and
he can shit himself whenever he likes.
He has all the shots but he doesn't know
when to play them. I don't know.
Yikes. Look at them.
Fucking coochie-fucking-coo.
Yeah, I haven't seen him
like this for a while.
Yeah, not since Sally Anne
and the summer of the horses.
-Remember that shit?
-Right.
-Well...
-Do you think, um...
-like, do you think they're fucking?
-My God, could you imagine?
Like a rhino fucking a hummingbird.
She'd have to go cowgirl, right?
Otherwise, he'd just like
snap her like a candy cane.
Dude, are you... like...
talking yourself hard right now?
Boys! Come on through.
Come through, I guess.
All right. Come through what?
So... Shiv's memo.
Okay, we're what?
We're putting the concept of Siobhan
on the table for general discussion?
You're tearing apart my sister's pious
bullshit for your entertainment?
-I had a dream like this once.
-It's just good to air some views.
Okay.
Yeah, I mean, I think the twin quotes
from Thomas Aquinas
and Amelia Earhart really...
...kick us off with a bang.
Wow, so many pictures.
All the smiling children,
all the various hues, that melted
the heart of even this hardened racist.
-I like the spacing. Um... Luxurious.
-It is. But the protein.
Well, there's no shortage
of concepts, for sure.
It's a rich gumbo of ideas
and buzz words.
Look, we should be gentle.
It's easy to be overly critical
of the workings of a major corporation
when you have no experience running one.
You can't blame her
for a lack of experience.
Well, sure you can. Just watch,
you'll get the hang of it soon enough.
No, thanks. But those are really good,
are organic. I'll grab him and see--
-Hey, Tom.
-Hey, Greg! How ya doin'?
Good, good. Yeah. Good, yeah. Just busy.
Just--Why are you, um--
-Sure, what's going on?
-I'm have a few pals over for dinner.
Ooh, look at you, Fancy Dan. The Greg
Man. What are you talking about?
-Hey.
-Welcome to the next wave.
-Just a talking shop for renewal.
-"Just a talking shop for renewal."
No, no, no. It's good. It's good.
We're good. Listen, I wanted to, um,
I wanted to ask you. I was in the area,
actually, that's why I came round.
I wanted to ask you, how was today
with the guys? The interview?
Yeah. Um...
Yeah. Okay, I--
A little bit jittery.
A bit of a stress comedown.
You know, I, got a haircut.
Even though I didn't really need
a haircut.
I think I just wanted someone to touch
my head, you know. Soothing.
-And I found it a little stressful--
-Great. Great.
So, here's my thing. Greg, you know
the papers? The copies? I want them.
Yeah. I did my part of the deal.
You got the office,
a pretty little Gustav Klimt poster
up there,
and now it's time for me
to habeas the corpus.
No, right. I mean, I just guess...
I just guess that they're,
like, my insurance policy.
Yeah, but you don't need
an insurance policy.
-In case things were to turn nasty.
-They're not gonna turn nasty.
Okay? No one's gonna
break your legs, y'know?
Okay, well that feels a bit nasty.
But it's the insurance
which is causing the nastiness.
If you were uninsured,
you'd be a lot safer. Ironically.
Okay, well, they're not actually here,
so I don't really know what to tell you.
Okay. Greg. Look. Okay, you played
your hand very well. I like it.
I do. But we need to end this now.
Or I tell Logan that you took
copies of sensitive documents.
Okay, that...
Well, I don't--
Okay, well, I--I keep them at--
-I keep them at the office.
-You keep them at the office?
Yeah. 'Cause they're work.
I'll go in early, and I'll give them
to you first thing tomorrow.
Right. But--But--But...
Except I can't trust you.
Okay, it's not personal.
I just can't trust you. So, in a
friendly way, I'm staying here tonight.
And I'm gonna go with you tomorrow
to wherever you have the papers,
and then later, together we're gonna
dispose of them off-premises.
And if you squeal or you try to take
copies, I'll break your legs.
Sorry, I hope you didn't mind
eating in. But it's just...
paps in this town, fucking animals.
Sure. If only someone
had some influence over them.
You okay?
Siobhan's coming over.
Apparently, she's all fired up.
I imagine you've seen a few temper
tantrums from your children.
I don't know.
She wants answers.
-Okay.
-What if you're right?
-What if she doesn't have it in her?
-That's not exactly what I said.
I worry for her.
Y'know, maybe I jumped too fast.
Nothing's been said publicly
though, right?
With Kendall,
it wasn't the best situation.
Maybe I should just say "Fuck it"
and let her do it. I don't fucking know.
-When does she get in?
-Tomorrow.
You know,
if you wanted me to...
I think I might be able
to help you make this go away.
-It's delicate.
-Would you like me to try?
Let me see what I can do.
You wanna stay over or what?
Okay. Um...
I wasn't expecting that.
Okay, so look.
From the oppo research on you,
I'm gonna ask you some yes-nos.
Did you get jerked off by your personal
trainer at the end of sessions?
Nope. No. No, I did not. Libel.
There's rumors
of a face tattoo situation.
No memory of that. No.
Hey, dude. Have you seen this?
From UK Comms?
What? Hey, Gerri, have you seen this?
I'll call you back.
-Where's Dad? Is he awake?
-Shit. I don't know.
Is he, like, on his own?
Did Rhea go home?
They were having Scotches
when I came in.
I was at Edward's hell hole
in Mayfair. When did you get in?
Did you bring a piece of ass back
with you?
-'Cause I think I heard.
-He needs to see this.
-You think--Should I wake him?
-I think so, yeah.
Fuck it, he needs to see this.
I'm gonna get him up.
Wake him up. Definitely.
You're gonna see him boning.
-Dad.
-Just go in.
-He needs to see the story. Go in.
-Dude, fuck you.
Okay, I'm coming in, Dad.
Dad.
Where the fuck am I?
The family's line
is emotional distress.
Yes, they're saying you punched him,
which caused him, in effect,
to drive his car into the river.
I did not punch anyone.
Yeah, this is, um-- this is incorrect.
-I never touched that kid.
-Well, I mean...
-Shouted a little, jostled a glass--
-Stop mumbling!
-At--At most, you shouted.
-Did--I shouted him into the river?
No, that's what I mean. I'm--
I'm saying that it's not right. This...
I should never have come.
I walked into a trap.
I've been badly advised.
You hear that, Gerri? Karolina?
-Yeah.
-Yes, we heard.
Is Hugo there?
I don't think we have any huge concerns
in terms of legal liabilities, right?
Fuck no. No, they're saying
you owed a duty of care
and threatening legal action,
but that won't fly.
The issue is we hear
that they may come to the US,
and appear on the Morning Juice
with this, which would not be--
From what I hear, what they really want
is actually just the apology.
-A personal apology.
-No.
Sure. I guess the only thing is,
in terms of the proxy battle...
It's Sandy's tabloid that's stirring
this up. They interviewed them.
-Of course.
-It's a transparent effort
to rattle our shareholders.
How about we offer
a visit to the family?
We may be able to get a statement
out of them absolving you of guilt.
Just say sorry,
and for all the distress.
But we make it clear
that Sandy and Stewy
are beating their drum
with the bones of a dead kid.
So it rebounds.
-You think that gets me out?
-Definitely.
Yeah.
Well, I suppose everybody has
to apologize for everything nowadays.
Okay. Okay. Set it up.
-Great.
-Will do.
Bye, guys.
You have a fun night, Dad?
-What the fuck does that mean?
-Nothin'.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Okay. All right.
-Dad. You remember Naomi Pierce.
She was in Venice at the Biennale,
so, it was easy for her to pop over--
Italian take out. Nice.
Thanks for having me.
-How's your cousin?
-She actually is taking the month off
-to visit British Columbia.
-I bet she is.
I think the whole sale experience
was quite draining for her.
Ooh, I can only imagine.
Naomi, send her my love and the whole
fucking gang, won't you?
Boys, I need five on strategy
in private.
-Later.
-I'll see you over there.
Bye.
Nice.
So... on your mom.
Probably just bullshit.
She's always been a piece of work.
See if you can sweet talk her.
And if necessary, make her an offer
that brings her back into line.
-I need her three percent.
-Well, what do we have to play with?
Well, cash is difficult, because
it looks like a bribe, but--
So, reopen the divorce settlement,
maybe?
Yeah.
Offer her ten million.
See if she pipes down.
I'll go as high as 50,
but I won't be happy.
Exciting. Grinding Mom down.
-So... looking forward to dinner?
-Yeah, last time I ate there,
it was three muddy trout for six
and fill up on mustard.
Poor bastards.
Slim pickings?
Whatever happens, we need her vote.
Whatever it takes.
-Whatever it takes. Right.
-All right, Dad. Got it.
But I don't like being fucked.
So, screw her out a bit.
Anything you save under the 50,
we can split.
Well, that oughta cover
the... subsequent therapy.
-Yeah. No, no. I'm kiddin'.
-Yep. Me, too.
-We need her.
-Got it.
What, did Rhea stay late or...
Did you guys...
-Why?
-Nothing.
No. No, no, no.
I mean, just, um...
I just wanted to say...
and don't take this the wrong way,
like... are you sure this thing
with Rhea is a good idea?
It--It feels like...
Yeah, it feels like she could be
playing you?
-I can take care of myself.
-Sure.
I know you can take care of yourself,
and your business is your business.
-I'm just...
-You're the one who's cunt-struck.
Whoa. Okay...
No, I'm--I'm just--
It's just maybe not a good look.
The old f--
Not the old fool, but, y'know--
That's not what I'm saying. I'm saying
that's how she could make you seem.
-Just--Just being honest.
-I appreciate it.
Okay, well...
I think Naomi wants me to take her
to The Regent's Park Zoo.
Apparently, we're in a fucking
Simon and Garfunkel song.
-So, um, I'll travel to Mom's--
-I think we should do a brainstorming.
Yeah.
Will you come with me?
-As in...
-Down to the boy's family.
Right. I mean...
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Okay.
We should stick together on this.
Don't you agree?
-Is Dad here?
-Would you like a drink of some kind?
No, I'm fine. Thanks.
-Hey, what's poppin', Malala Roy?
-Where's Dad?
Were you chasing the dragon?
He is ghost. Again.
-Isn't that cool?
-For fuck's sake. Where is he?
-He's seeing the Ulsterman, no?
-Paying homage to a dead kid's parents.
He's seeing the Ulsterman at the races.
Very much enjoyed your little me-mo.
What the fuck?
Yeah, it was... very compelling.
It was like eye crack.
-Well, has Dad read it?
-Has he not got back to you?
'Cause he read it yesterday,
so he has had a ton of time.
For fuck's sake.
Yeah, we all read it.
It was a little round table thing;
-me, Ken, Dad, Rhea.
-Rhea? Rhea's in town?
Do you know nothing of the company
you're supposed to be taking over?
Y'know, Waystar?
Waystar Royco?
-We do hate speech and roller coasters.
-Fuck you.
-Okay.
Um, before I hand these over,
could I actually make one final request?
Leo, my neighbor here,
he sneezes like a cartoon character,
so, I was thinking
maybe a corner office--
Don't overplay your hand, Gregory.
Come on.
-Okay, w--
-Come on.
"Secret," Greg?
-Yeah?
-But not "Top Secret." Interesting.
Just "Secret," that's smart.
Just so people know, you know,
that these are secret.
They're secret. Yeah. I don't know,
'cause sometimes, the janitors,
they come and throw stuff out and--
But look, the actual envelope
says "Receipts."
Ooh! But they're not, in fact,
receipts.
Greg!
You're a criminal mastermind.
What polyglot genius could ever hope
to crack your impenetrable code?
-Shut up.
-God.
-Easy.
-Sorry.
Thanks for making time.
Yeah, well, you know, an unexpected gap
in the schedule.
And you what,
you just happen to be here?
-Seeing some theater.
-Lovely.
-"See some theater."
-And your dad offered me the ride.
And look, it's--it's good to chat.
Because he's...
he's a very...
Your dad's a tough guy. I...
I took it pretty hard getting fired.
Yeah, sure. Sure, and...
you know, we appreciate
what you tried to do for us.
But he's been kind.
He's been kind to me.
-People don't talk about his kindness.
-Yeah, no they don't. Not a great deal.
Look, I'm being very frank.
I hope that's okay.
-Is it too much or bad?
-Yeah... No...
Thank you.
I feel we have a connection
and I like you.
And I know what it's like to fight your
way through in our industry, you know?
Yeah. No, sure, I-- appreciate it.
-Because you must be fond of Marcia.
-So...
Yeah, we have a, um, relationship.
Yeah, you know, a very...
functioning relationship.
Well, look, yeah, I don't know what
to say. I just like you and I...
Your father's a very appealing man
and I hope--
No, it's fine. It's--No, it's good to
check before you fuck someone's dad.
I mean, yeah. Do your due diligence,
your paperwork.
Do I need to sign like
a release form or...?
I feel like a total idiot,
so, congratulations.
-No, you shouldn't. It's--
-No?
'Cause you play your cards
pretty close.
Who says I have cards?
But you're okay?
Honestly, no. I feel like
a flame-roasted, wood-fired dipshit.
Yeah, I did the thing that
I said I was never gonna do, and...
Now, I don't know.
I don't--I don't know.
Well, the problem is
it just so happens
you're very smart
and talented, Siobhan.
Thank you.
But... what does my dad think?
Right?
I've managed to get myself
into this situation
where "What does my dad think?"
is my entire fucking universe.
Well, I mean... maybe...
Maybe isn't now the time
to just let him know, you know?
You have options.
-Okay, yeah, but I can't bluff him.
-Sure, but...
I happen to know there's a media
operation in need of a dynamic new CEO.
And I happen to know Nan Pierce
has a certain regard for you.
And I happen to know she wouldn't mind
putting a fucking sharp, burnt stick
in your dad's cyclops eye.
Me at Pierce?
-That's never gonna happen, is it?
-I don't know.
But I can get it floated with clean
hands, and they'll consider it for sure.
Then it's all upside.
Keep it in your back pocket,
lay it out to your dad,
or even take the job.
Well...
let me think about it.
Thank you.
And...
So, what are--
Whatcha doin' tonight, Dad?
Tonight? Cheltenham.
-The Ulsterman.
-Yeah.
Watch him eat a fucking horse.
Then, I don't know. I... You know,
I might have dinner with Rhea.
Yeah. Great.
-Yeah, she's never been to Cheltenham.
-Yeah, well...
It could be nice to see Cheltenham.
Excuse me?
You got a problem?
No.
Look at this place.
-How you doin'?
-Hi. I'm Colin.
-Max. Pleasure.
-He's with you?
So, what do we got? Mom? Dad?
And the boy's uncle is here also.
He's Phillip Cleave. He'll take photos.
I'll put together some press comments.
Actually, Ken.
Why don't you come in with me?
-You want me--
-Well, it looks a little weird.
I bring you all this way, and you sit
in the car like a Labrador. Come in.
-Paul, Andrew's uncle.
-Paul, pleased to meet you. Logan Roy.
-And this is my son, Kendall.
-Hi. Hello.
Steven and Theresa are in the lounge,
if you'd like to come in.
Please.
Theresa. Steven.
Hi. Hello.
-Steven.
-Logan Roy.
-Would like a tea or a coffee?
-Well, yeah, that's kind.
I'm good. Thank you.
Thank you so much for seeing me.
You know, this has been
a terrible tragedy.
Of course.
-I'm doing teas.
-Um, no, not for me. Thank you. Thanks.
Water?
Yes. Actually, thank you.
Yes, please.
-You staying at your mother's?
-Um, yep. Yes, I am.
-Okay, let's go.
-Hey, Dad.
Do you think I should maybe
say something to them?
No.
Poor bastards.
They've been through the ringer,
you know?
Fuck knows how they cope.
They're embarrassed, really.
They knew he was a druggie.
Yeah, that is life.
Don't forget it. Right?
You know, there's nothing
to be ashamed of. Our stuff.
We give them a bit of a laugh,
some decent TV to watch,
news that doesn't talk down to them.
Good fucking people. Nice fucking folk.
-You know, Dad won't be pleased.
-Well, she demanded my attendance, so...
More scared of Mom
than Dad? Interesting.
What is this?
A museum of wartime food?
This is for display, right?
None of this edible.
-What did we buy last time we came?
-Um...
It was a Scotch egg that I thought was
a huge arancini, and some lard.
I'm just gonna get a banana.
-Can't get food poisoning from bananas.
-You'd be surprised.
Hello?
Hey, hi--hi--hi, I'm involved
in a criminal conspiracy.
"Really?"
Yes, yes, I am.
I destroyed some papers
that I shouldn't have.
"Did you?"
Yes, I did. Is that bad?
"Yeah, that's bad. Yeah, that could
be bad. You could go to jail.
Yeah, would you like that? Would you
like that, pretty boy like you?
Would you like it?
You might even like that."
Male rape.
Rape of the male.
That was lower jacket pocket.
Lower jacket pocket.
This is inside pocket.
All aboard inside pocket.
Here I am, I'm moving.
I'm moving. I'm moving.
Brisk movement. Brisk movement.
This is faster.
Okay, wind is blowing.
And I'm talking louder.
"No, I don't remember, Greg.
No, I don't remember." Okay.
...criminal conspiracy.
"Really?"
Thank you, sir.
-Mom?
-Hello!
-Hey!
-Siobhan.
-Hi. Hello.
-Ro-Ro!
-Hey, Mommy!
-Thank you for coming down.
-Yeah, well, just following orders.
-Like a Nazi.
-Exactly. Right?
Well, you're in the country,
so what were you going to do?
Go out whoring in Soho?
Yeah, that would have been
the first choice.
Well, look, Kendall's
gone to the pub apparently,
so, I've just had a little bit
of pigeon done.
Didn't think anyone would be
feeling terribly hungry. I know I'm not.
-No, right.
-Don't want a great bolus of gubbins.
-Take a plate.
-Thank you.
-Catch.
-So, how are you?
Well, I might just as well ask you
if you're going to go into all that.
It was-- Wasn't intended
as an aggressive question, Mom. It's...
No, I'm fine.
Rory's wonderful.
-So, should I be mother?
-Yeah, why don't you give it a go?
Yes, well, I'm sorry it's
not a 48-ounce T-bone steak
with truffle fries, but there we go.
Some of us don't want
coronary heart attacks.
It's nice, Mom. It's nice.
There's quite a lot of shot
in the pigeon,
so mind how you go
or you'll crack a tooth.
And the shot can take a bit
of feather in, too.
Shot and feather.
Shall we begin with
the negotiation straight away?
The first time I've had you
in for the night in a decade.
It's just a shame it's so you can put
the squeeze on me for your father.
Ma, it's not like that.
-No?
-No.
Tell me, what does it feel like being
sent here to wheedle out your mother.
Don't look at me. I'm not getting
involved. She's right.
Thank you.
Thank you, a bit of solidarity.
Twenty years too late,
but never mind.
Someone's taking Mommy's side.
If you want to get into it,
you're just posturing, right?
And if you go with Sandy and Stewy,
you're burning down the Coliseum
with your children inside it.
I've thought about it.
I've discussed with Rory.
Yeah, well, great to get
his brain on it.
Potatoes.
He's actually rather clever.
Yeah, before he rolls one of his tobacco
and hash monstrosities.
-My God.
-Sorry, what was that?
Nothing, Mum.
There's a number.
Here we go. The chiseling
begins. This'll be good.
How much can we screw out
of our dear old mother?
Well, Dad,
unrelated to the vote of course,
is willing to reopen
the divorce settlement.
-So, what's the number?
-Well, what do you want?
-I want to piss off your father.
-Well, I think that's working.
Come on, help yourselves.
All right then, come on.
What's his top number?
Well, he told me
to tell you ten, but it's 40.
-So, it's 50.
-No, it's 40.
Roman, you're not very good at this.
No, what's the real top?
He doesn't have the real top.
Dad would never tell him.
I know what I'd like.
Tell him the summer palace.
-The Hamptons House.
-You hate it out there.
Yeah, but he loves it, doesn't he?
He loves the parties, the clam bakes
with people who despise him. Such fun.
But that's like--What is that?
That's like 150 million.
It doesn't matter, Roman.
It's just numbers.
I'll have a word with Jack the
Ulsterman, too. Can throw that in.
-Okay. But--
-Or...
How about 20 million and you kids
give me Christmas every year.
Come on. Mom, don't make it like--
I would like to come for Christmas.
Sure.
No--You never invite us.
Well, that's because you've made it
quite clear you wouldn't come.
-That was one time.
-That was several times.
-I was 18.
-Look.
I would like to see you
for Christmas...
instead of you always being
with your father.
Why don't you ask him
what he'd rather?
He can keep the summer palace
if I get the family every Christmas.
You have to have good lines
of communication after a divorce.
It's absolutely key. So, I think
we have to hear which he'd prefer.
Let's make him choose.
Y'know, it's a shame
you didn't make it to supper.
It ended up
being rather a nice evening.
I'm sorry I missed it.
Turned out your father was prepared
to sell you all off like chattels
to keep a piece of real estate,
but that doesn't surprise me.
You're gonna be okay to come
for Christmas, I take it?
Great.
Hey, Mom. Mom.
I--I...
have some...
some things I'd like to, um...
to talk about.
To--To tell you.
No more long lists
of my emotional deficiencies.
No, Mom.
No, it's...
It's something I've done...
that I don't feel great about.
Right.
Dear.
-Do you think maybe we can talk?
-Sure. Absolutely.
Go ahead, but, um...
Yeah, but are they quite
difficult things? Because...
you know... a bit tired
for home truths.
Right.
Well, yeah, it's a bit difficult.
Okay..
Well... go on.
-It's fine.
-No, no. I want to. Come on.
-It's okay.
-No.
If you want,
we can absolutely do it now, but...
you know, it might be better
to do it over an egg?
Sure. Let's--Let's do it over an egg.
Yeah. We'll feel better
in the morning,
and we can do it tomorrow.
Okay.
Sleep tight, sweet boy.
Fuck.
Yeah, how did it come to this?
-How did it come to this?
-You're right.
-What's th--
No one will ever know.
No one will ever know
you sent me to shred the records
of off-book hush-money
and illegal intimidation.
Yeah. Put on the disappearing sauce.
-Sauce it. Sauce it.
-Okay. A little purifying flame.
-Okay, stand back.
-Yeah.
-Okay, just a minute.
-The evidence doesn't want
to be destroyed.
"Lord of Malfeasance,
give us your divine blessing."
-Hey, hold my beer?
-Hey! Yep.
-Yeah.
-Good!
-Hi, there.
-Hi... I'm here to see Logan Roy.
Sure, this gentleman
will show you to him.
-Hey, Dad.
-Siobhan. They told me you were here.
This is unexpected.
Yeah, we were due a check-in
with the memo.
And then you fled the country,
then you fled London.
My schedule goes through Kerry.
We've had some emergencies.
-Yeah, you're kind of elusive, Dad.
-Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Well, because, honestly, I was afraid
that you would run away again.
I have never run away
from anything in my life.
Can we just--just talk
about the memo?
I owe you a response.
You've not--you've not read it?
Siobhan, I have an in-tray
the size of Argentina.
Okay.
You know--Actually,
you know what? Also, I...
I need to ask. Is it still me?
-What?
-Come on! Dad.
Has anything changed? Because,
you know, it feels like it has.
And, you know, when you said it...
it felt really real.
And I know--I know you
haven't always liked my words.
You haven't always been happy with my
words, but come on. We can discuss.
You know that I want this,
and that I can do it.
Then why are you fucking me about?
-As in...
-Putting your name for the Pierce job?
Talking to those backstabbers.
What's that all about?
If you're gonna come in here, talking
a whole load of crap to your father?
-Who t--who told you?
-Who told me?
It's all over town. Nan Pierce is
shouting it like a trophy in the city.
Okay, well, you know what?
I had to keep my options open, Dad.
Yeah. I see.
I see. 'Cause we--
'Cause we have a little fallout
or something?
We're a family. We can have our bumps.
I don't expect that.
-Well, it's not that I was--
-Family, Siobhan!
If you don't understand that...
then fuck off.
Eggy pegs?
She doin' eggy pegs?
She's, um...
She's sorry if she misses
our departure.
She's got quite a lot to do.
Sure. Can happen.
Yeah. Yeah, it can. Right.
There you go.
Hey, Dad. Um, Dad.
Just need to confirm something.
Decent deal. Right?
20 and Christmas.
-Good kid. Good kid.
-Yep, I screwed Mom for you.
That's, you know,
the fucking dream, right?
You should probably go
and poke your eyes out now.
Right. Yeah.
-How'd it go with Shiv?
-We had it out. Yeah.
With the ammunition, I think I got
the noose from around my neck.
-Good. Good.
-Thank you.
-I'm pleased to help.
-You know, I've been thinking...
maybe... maybe look farther
afield for the next me.
Maybe a shortlist of two or three?
I'd be pleased to help you look.
-Yeah.
-Hey, Ken. Listen, is she on the plane?
Okay, just...
I think we've got a problem.
Just be careful, okay?
I think I got fucked.