Now you will rule for eternity, my lord.
Sleep.
Let the transference begin.
Death to the false god.
Protect him!
Ten fights waged.
Ten fights won.
The Winged Warrior.
The Bird of Prey.
The Angel of Death.
ANGEL!
Let's hear it for the fat man!
Our next challenger...
comes straight...
from the Munich Circus.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the only one that could
take on an Angel...
is the Devil himself.
I give you...
the amazing...
the fantastic...
NIGHTCRAWLER!
Caution
High voltage!
Sorry mutants!
Did you get lost little mouse?
The fight is over there.
And it's about to get exciting.
Ah, you mean this?
They went that way!
Have a good night, Henryk.
You too, Milosz.
Hi Honey.
Hi.
Do you sell rugs?
You're not allowed in this area.
This rug is for sale?
I said, this --
Earthquake!
Are you alright?
She's fine.
Then let her go!
We will.
We just wanted to have a word
You're not wearing your badges.
No metal.
Some guys at the factory
said they saw something today.
Something that didn't add up.
Put your weapons away.
You've been a good citizen, Henryk...
A good neighbor... a good worker.
I want to believe that's who you are.
It is.
But nobody in this town really knows you.
Yes you do.
I am Henryk Gurzsky.
Jakob, I've had dinner in your home...
And you were lying the whole time.
I brought a killer into my house.
Is this you?
Are you the one they call Magneto?
Take me in.
Please...
Just let my daughter go.
Go with your mother.
Please...!
Don't leave me.
I'm not going to let them take you.
What's going on?
She's one of them?
Tell her to stop!
She can't control it!
She's scared of you!
I'm not going to let them take you!
Make her stop!
You know what we do to thieves.
Pick a hand.
Enough.
If you're with her,
I suggest you walk away.
While you still can.
Walk away
Who rules this world?
What language is that?
Clown-face. What's the deal?
Beat it!
I'm sorry.
You can't feel it, can you?
Now you feel it.
I've never seen another
mutant in this town.
You speak Egyptian?
Arabic?
Cleansed.
Henryk, please.
Don't do this.
...all of your towers and temples...
Will fall.
And the dawn of a new age will rise.